<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="192610-2018"
            EDITION="2018086">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-191964-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180710</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>86</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180504</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 086-192610</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192610-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79300000">Market and economic research; polling and statistics</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="BE100">Arr. de Bruxelles-Capitale / Arr. van Brussel-Hoofdstad</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="BE100">Arr. de Bruxelles-Capitale / Arr. van Brussel-Hoofdstad</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180427</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180710 16:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>AGC02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>AG</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Plan for sektorsamarbejde om færdigheder. Mod en fælles vision om adressering af SMEs behov for færdigheder inden for bilindustrien: styrkelse af udviklingen af opkvalificerings- og omskolingsstrategier</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Blaupause zur Branchenzusammenarbeit für Kompetenzen. Auf dem Weg zu einer gemeinsamen Vision für die Befriedigung des Bedarfs an Kompetenzen für KMU im Automobilsektor: Stärkung der Entwicklung von Strategien für Weiterbildung und Umschulung</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brussels</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Blueprint for sectoral cooperation on skills. Towards a common vision on addressing SMEs skills needs in the automotive sector: strengthening the development of upskilling and reskilling strategies</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruselas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Plan rector para la cooperación sectorial en materia de competencias. Hacia un enfoque común sobre la resolución de las necesidades en materia de competencias de las pymes en el sector de la automoción: fortalecimiento del desarrollo de estrategias de mejora y reciclaje de competencias</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Alakohtaista osaamisyhteistyötä koskeva suunnitelma. Tavoitteena on yhteisen näkemyksen luominen pienten ja keskisuurten yritysten tarpeista huolehtimiseksi autoalalla: vahvistetaan osaamisen kehittämistä ja uudistamista koskevien strategioiden kehittämistä. </P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Belgique</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Plan relatif à la coopération sectorielle en matière de compétences. Vers une vision commune portant sur les besoins en compétences des PME dans le secteur automobile : renforcer le développement des stratégies de compétences et de reconversion professionnelle</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Βέλγιο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Σχέδιο στρατηγικής για τομεακή συνεργασία στον τομέα των δεξιοτήτων. Προς ένα κοινό όραμα για την αντιμετώπιση των αναγκών σε δεξιότητες των ΜΜΕ στον τομέα της αυτοκινητοβιομηχανίας: ενίσχυση της ανάπτυξης στρατηγικών αναβάθμισης των δεξιοτήτων και επαγγελματικής επιμόρφωσης</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Belgio</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Piano per la cooperazione settoriale in materia di competenze. Verso una visione comune sull'affrontare le esigenze di competenze delle PMI nel settore automobilistico: rafforzare lo sviluppo delle strategie di perfezionamento e riqualificazione</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>België</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brussel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Blauwdruk voor sectorale samenwerking op het gebied van vaardigheden: ontwikkeling van een gemeenschappelijke visie om in te spelen op de behoeften op het gebied van vaardigheden van het mkb in de automobielsector: versterking van de ontwikkeling van strategieën voor bij- en omscholing.</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Plano para a cooperação setorial em matéria de competências. No intuito de uma visão comum de abordagem às necessidades de competências das PME no setor automóvel: reforçando o desenvolvimento de estratégias de requalificação e aumento de qualificações</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Strategi för sektoriellt samarbete kring kompetens. Mot en gemensam vision för att adressera kompetensbehoven hos små och medelstora företag inom fordonssektorn: främjande av utvecklingen av kompetensutvecklande och omskolande strategier</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Belgie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Plán odvětvové spolupráce v oblasti dovedností. Směrem ke společné vizi pro řešení potřeb malých a středních podniků týkajících se dovedností v oblasti automobilového průmyslu: posílení vypracovávání strategií rozšiřování dovedností a rekvalifikace</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Oskuste alase valdkondliku koostöö tegevuskava. Ühise nägemuse suunas autotööstussektoris VKEdele vajaminevate oskuste käsitlemisel: täiend- ja ümberõppe strateegiate arenduse tugevdamine </P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brüsszel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tervezet a készségekkel kapcsolatos ágazati együttműködésre. Közös jövőkép felé a kkv-k gépjárműipari képzettségi igényeinek kezelésére vonatkozóan: a készségfejlesztési és átképzési stratégiák fejlesztésének megerősítése</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Briuselis</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sektorių bendradarbiavimo įgūdžių srityje planas. Siekiant bendros vizijos, kaip tenkinti MVĮ įgūdžių poreikius automobilių pramonės sektoriuje: galimybių kelti kvalifikaciją arba persikvalifikavimo strategijų plėtros stiprinimas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Beļģija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brisele</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Plāns nozaru sadarbībai prasmju jomā. Ceļā uz kopīgu redzējumu par MVU autobūves nozares prasmju vajadzību risināšanu – kvalifikācijas celšanas un pārkvalifikācijas stratēģiju attīstības stiprināšana</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>il-Belġju</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brussell</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pjan għal Kooperazzjoni Settorjali fuq il-Ħiliet. Lejn viżjoni komuni biex jiġu indirizzati l-bżonnijiet fil-ħiliet għall-SMEs fis-settur tal-vetturi: it-tisħiħ tal-iżvilupp ta' strateġiji għal titjib fil-ħiliet u l-kisba ta' ħiliet oħra</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruksela</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Plan współpracy sektorowej na rzecz umiejętności. W kierunku wspólnej wizji zagospodarowania potrzeb MŚP w zakresie umiejętności w sektorze motoryzacyjnym: wzmocnienie rozwoju strategii podnoszenia umiejętności i przekwalifikowywania się</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Belgicko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Koncepcia pre sektorovú spoluprácu v oblasti zručností. Smerom k spoločnej vízii pri riešení potrieb MSP v oblasti automobilového priemyslu: posilnenie rozvoja stratégií zvyšovania kvalifikácie a rekvalifikácie</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruselj</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Načrt za sektorsko sodelovanje na področju spretnosti. Na poti k skupni viziji obravnavanja potreb po spretnostih MSP v avtomobilskem sektorju: krepitev razvoja strategij izpopolnjevanja in prekvalifikacije</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Bheilg, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Treoirphlean maidir le comhar earnála i dtaobh scileanna. I dtreo físe coitinne chun aghaidh a thabhairt ar éilimh scileanna na FBManna san earnáil gluaisteán: forbairt na straitéisí uas-scilithe agus athscilithea neartú</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Бeлгия</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Брюксел</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Схема за секторно сътрудничество по отношение на уменията. За обща визия за справяне с нуждите от умения на МСП в автомобилния сектор: подсилване на развитието на стратегии за повишаване на уменията и преквалификация</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Planul de cooperare sectorială în materie de competențe. Către o viziune comună privind abordarea nevoilor în materie de competențe ale IMM-urilor în domeniul automobilelor: consolidarea dezvoltării strategiilor de actualizare a competențelor și de recalificare</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Nacrt za sektorsku suradnju u području vještina. Prema zajedničkoj viziji o rješavanju potreba za vještinama malih i srednjih poduzeća u automobilskom sektoru: jačanje razvoja strategija za usavršavanje i prekvalificiranje</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="DA">Forvaltningsorganet for Små og Mellemstore Virksomheder (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="DE">Die Exekutivagentur für kleine und mittlere Unternehmen (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">The Executive Agency for Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="ES">Agencia Ejecutiva para las Pequeñas y Medianas Empresas (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="FI">Pienistä ja keskisuurista yrityksistä vastaava toimeenpanovirasto (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="FR">Agence exécutive pour les petites et moyennes entreprises (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="EL">Εκτελεστικός Οργανισμός για τις Μικρομεσαίες Επιχειρήσεις (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="IT">Agenzia esecutiva per le piccole e le medie imprese (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="NL">Uitvoerend Agentschap voor kleine en middelgrote ondernemingen (Easme)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="PT">Agência de Execução para as Pequenas e Médias Empresas (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="SV">Genomförandeorganet för små och medelstora företag (Easme)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="CS">Výkonná agentura pro malé a střední podniky (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="ET">Väikeste ja Keskmise Suurusega Ettevõtjate Rakendusamet (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="HU">A Kkv-ügyi Végrehajtó Ügynökség (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="LT">Mažųjų ir vidutinių įmonių reikalų vykdomoji įstaiga (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="LV">Mazo un vidējo uzņēmumu izpildaģentūra (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="MT">L-Aġenzija Eżekuttiva għall-Intrapriżi Żgħar u Medji (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="PL">Agencja Wykonawcza ds. Małych i Średnich Przedsiębiorstw (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="SK">Výkonná agentúra pre malé a stredné podniky (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="SL">Izvajalska agencija za mala in srednja podjetja (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="GA">An Ghníomhaireacht Feidhmiúcháin um Fhiontair Bheaga agus Mheánmhéide (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="BG">Изпълнителна агенция за малките и средните предприятия (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="RO">Agenția Executivă pentru Întreprinderi Mici și Mijlocii (EASME)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="HR">Izvršna agencija za mala i srednja poduzeća (EASME)</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="DA">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Forvaltningsorganet for Små og Mellemstore Virksomheder (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Plan for sektorsamarbejde om færdigheder. Mod en fælles vision om adressering af SMEs behov for færdigheder inden for bilindustrien: styrkelse af udviklingen af opkvalificerings- og omskolingsstrategier</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME ønsker at indgå en tjenesteydelseskontrakt vedrørende støtte til bilindustrien inden for bevaring og opnåelse af ny nøglefærdigheder med henblik på at vedligeholde og styrke den europæiske bilindustris konkurrenceevne på det globale marked, og dermed bidrage til den overordnede plan for sektorspecifik strategi. Målet er at forbedre bevidstheden om de eksisterende bedste praksisser inden for relevante politikker og initiativer til opkvalificering eller omskoling (især for SMV'er) i EU og i lande uden for EU hvor bilindustrien har en vigtig position.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Opgaverne skal udføres i lokaler udpeget af kontrahenten, undtagen møder, der skal afholdes i EASME's eller Europa-Kommissionens lokaler.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME ønsker at indgå en tjenesteydelseskontrakt vedrørende støtte til bilindustrien inden for bevaring og opnåelse af ny nøglefærdigheder med henblik på at vedligeholde og styrke den europæiske bilindustris konkurrenceevne på det globale marked, og dermed bidrage til den overordnede plan for sektorspecifik strategi.</P>
                  <P>Arbejderne opdeles i 2 hovedfaser:</P>
                  <P>1. fase (måned 1 – måned 9):</P>
                  <P>Opgaverne, der skal udføres under arbejdspakke 1: Den første fase dedikeres til den strukturerede indhentning og analyse af oplysninger og data, baseret på skrivebordsundersøgelser, online rundspørger, workshopper og interview af nøgleinteressenter:</P>
                  <P>2. fase (måned 10 – måned 18)</P>
                  <P>Opgaverne der skal udføres under arbejdspakke 2: landerapporter der skal leveres i form af bilag, bedste praksisser, benchmarking af politikker og industriens initiativer der skal leveres som en del af den endelige rapport, udvikling af et sæt af støttehandlinger og anbefalinger der skal leveres som en køreplan for gennemførelsen:</P>
                  <P>Opgaverne der skal udføres under arbejdspakke 3: færdiggørelse, validering og udbredelse af aktiviteter:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Program for små og mellemstore virksomheders konkurrenceevne C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Se internetadressen anført i punkt I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Se internetadressen anført i punkt I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Forvaltningsorganet for Små og Mellemstore Virksomheder (EASME), Covent Garden 2, Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgien.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Se internetadressen anført i punkt I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Retten</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Se internetadressen anført i afsnit I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="DE">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Die Exekutivagentur für kleine und mittlere Unternehmen (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Blaupause zur Branchenzusammenarbeit für Kompetenzen. Auf dem Weg zu einer gemeinsamen Vision für die Befriedigung des Bedarfs an Kompetenzen für KMU im Automobilsektor: Stärkung der Entwicklung von Strategien für Weiterbildung und Umschulung</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Die EASME möchte einen Dienstleistungsvertrag abschließen, um die Automobilindustrie dabei zu unterstützen, Schlüsselqualifikationen beizubehalten und neue zu erwerben, um die Wettbewerbsfähigkeit des europäischen Automobilsektors auf einem globalen Markt zu erhalten und zu stärken und somit einen Beitrag zu der sektorbezogenen Kompetenzstrategie der Blaupause leisten. Ziel ist es, die Sensibilisierung für die bestehenden bewährten Verfahren relevanter Politiken und Initiativen für die Weiterbildung und Umschulung (insbesondere für KMU) in der EU und in Ländern außerhalb der EU, in denen der Automobilsektor eine starke Position innehat, zu verbessern.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Die Aufgaben sind in den vom Auftragnehmer bestimmten Räumlichkeiten durchzuführen; davon ausgenommen sind Sitzungen, die in den Räumlichkeiten der EASME oder der Europäischen Kommission in Brüssel stattfinden.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Die EASME möchte einen Dienstleistungsvertrag abschließen, um die Automobilindustrie dabei zu unterstützen, Schlüsselqualifikationen beizubehalten und neue zu erwerben, um die Wettbewerbsfähigkeit des europäischen Automobilsektors auf einem globalen Markt zu erhalten und zu stärken und somit einen Beitrag zu der sektorbezogenen Kompetenzstrategie der Blaupause leisten.</P>
                  <P>Die Arbeit wird in 2 Hauptphasen aufgeteilt:</P>
                  <P>1. Phase (Monat 1 - Monat 9):</P>
                  <P>Die unter AP 1 auszuführenden Aufgaben umfassen: Die erste Phase wird der strukturierten Sammlung und Analyse von Informationen und Daten gewidmet sein, basierend auf Sekundärforschung, Online-Umfragen, Workshops und Gesprächen mit Hauptinteressenträgern:</P>
                  <P>2. Phase (Monat 10 - Monat 18)</P>
                  <P>Die unter AP 2 auszuführenden Aufgaben umfassen: Länderberichte als Anhang, bewährte Praktiken, Leistungsbewertung von Politiken und Brancheninitiativen, die als Teil des Abschlussberichts geliefert werden sollen, Ausarbeitung einer Reihe von unterstützenden Maßnahmen und Empfehlungen in Form eines Umsetzungsplans:</P>
                  <P>Die unter AP 3 auszuführenden Aufgaben umfassen: Fertigstellungs-, Validierungs- und Verbreitungsmaßnahmen:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Arbeitsprogramm für die Wettbewerbsfähigkeit von Unternehmen und für kleine und mittlere Unternehmen, C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Siehe die in Abschnitt I.3 angegebene Internetadresse.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Siehe die in Abschnitt I.3 angegebene Internetadresse.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Die Exekutivagentur für kleine und mittlere Unternehmen (EASME), Covent Garden 2, Place Rogier 16, 1210 Brussels, Belgien.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Siehe die in Abschnitt I.3 angegebene Internetadresse.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Gericht</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Siehe die in Abschnitt I.3 angegebene Internetadresse.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>The Executive Agency for Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Blueprint for sectoral cooperation on skills. Towards a common vision on addressing SMEs skills needs in the automotive sector: strengthening the development of upskilling and reskilling strategies</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME wishes to enter into a service contract to support the automotive industry in retaining key skills and acquiring new ones, in order to maintain and strengthen the competitive edge of the European automotive sector on a global market, and thus to contribute to the overall Blueprint sectoral skills strategy. The goal is to improve awareness of the existing best practices of relevant policies and initiatives on up/reskilling (in particular for SMEs) in the EU and in countries outside of the EU where the automotive sector holds a strong position.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>The tasks are to be performed at the premises designated by the contractor, save where meetings are to beheld at EASME's or the European Commission’s premise.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME wishes to enter into a service contract to support the automotive industry in retaining key skills and acquiring new ones, in order to maintain and strengthen the competitive edge of the European automotive sector on a global market, and thus to contribute to the overall Blueprint sectoral skills strategy.</P>
                  <P>The work will be split in 2 main phases:</P>
                  <P>1<FT TYPE="SUP">st</FT> phase (Month 1 – Month 9):</P>
                  <P>Tasks to be performed under WP 1: The first phase will be dedicated to the structured collection and analysis of information and data, based on desk research, online surveys, workshops and interviews of key stakeholders:</P>
                  <P>2<FT TYPE="SUP">nd</FT> phase (Month 10 – Month 18)</P>
                  <P>Tasks to be performed under WP2: country reports to be delivered as an annex, best practices, bench marking of polices and industry initiatives to be delivered as part of the final report, elaboration of a set of supportive actions and recommendations to be delivered in the form of implementation roadmap:</P>
                  <P>Tasks to be performed under WP3: finalisation, validation and dissemination activities:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Programme for Competitveness of Entreprises and small and medium-sized entreprises C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>See the Internet address provided in Section I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>See the Internet address provided in Section I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>The Executive Agency for Small and Medium-size Enterprises (EASME) Covent Garden 2 Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels Belgium.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>See internet address provided at section I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>General Court</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>See Internet address provided in Section I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="ES">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agencia Ejecutiva para las Pequeñas y Medianas Empresas (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Plan rector para la cooperación sectorial en materia de competencias. Hacia un enfoque común sobre la resolución de las necesidades en materia de competencias de las pymes en el sector de la automoción: fortalecimiento del desarrollo de estrategias de mejora y reciclaje de competencias</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>La EASME desea celebrar un contrato de servicios para dar apoyo a la industria automovilística en la retención de competencias clave y la adquisición de nuevas competencias, para mantener y reforzar la ventaja competitiva del sector automovilístico europeo en el mercado global y así contribuir a la estrategia global del plan rector sectorial en material de competencias. El objetivo es mejorar la concienciación respecto a las mejores prácticas existentes relacionadas con las políticas e iniciativas relevantes en materia de mejora y reciclaje de competencias (especialmente para pymes) en la UE y en países fuera de la UE donde el sector automovilístico mantiene una sólida posición.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Las tareas se desarrollarán en las instalaciones que indique el contratista, excepto en el caso de las reuniones, que se celebrarán en las instalaciones de la EASME o de la Comisión Europea.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>La EASME desea celebrar un contrato de servicios para dar apoyo a la industria automovilística en la retención de competencias clave y la adquisición de nuevas competencias, para mantener y reforzar la ventaja competitiva del sector automovilístico europeo en el mercado global y así contribuir a la estrategia global del plan rector sectorial en material de competencias.</P>
                  <P>El trabajo se dividirá en 2 fases principales:</P>
                  <P>Primera fase (mes 1 – mes 9):</P>
                  <P>Tareas a realizarse en el marco del programa de trabajo 1: La primera fase estará dedicada a la recopilación estructurada y el análisis de información y datos, basados en investigación documental, encuestas en línea, talleres y entrevistas a partes interesadas clave:</P>
                  <P>Segunda fase (mes 10 – mes 18):</P>
                  <P>Tareas a realizarse en el marco del programa de trabajo 2: informes del país a presentarse como anexo, mejores prácticas, evaluación comparativa de políticas e iniciativas industriales a presentarse como parte del informe final, elaboración de un conjunto de acciones de apoyo y recomendaciones a presentarse en forma de hoja de ruta de ejecución:</P>
                  <P>Tareas a realizarse en el marco del programa de trabajo 3: actividades de finalización, validación y divulgación:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Programa para la Competitividad de las empresas y las pymes, C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Véase la dirección de internet que figura en el apartado I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Véase la dirección de internet que figura en el apartado I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Agencia Ejecutiva para las Pequeñas y Medianas Empresas (EASME), Covent Garden 2, Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Bélgica.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Véase la dirección de internet que figura en el apartado I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal General</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Véase la dirección de internet que figura en el apartado I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="FI">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Pienistä ja keskisuurista yrityksistä vastaava toimeenpanovirasto (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Alakohtaista osaamisyhteistyötä koskeva suunnitelma. Tavoitteena on yhteisen näkemyksen luominen pienten ja keskisuurten yritysten tarpeista huolehtimiseksi autoalalla: vahvistetaan osaamisen kehittämistä ja uudistamista koskevien strategioiden kehittämistä. </P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME haluaa solmia palvelusopimuksen autonrakennusalan tukemiseksi keskeisen osaamisen säilyttämiseksi ja uusien taitojen omaksumiseksi, jotta se voisi säilyttää ja vahvistaa Euroopan autonrakennusalan kilpailukykyä maailmanlaajuisilla markkinoilla ja näin tuoda oman panoksensa alakohtaista osaamisyhteistyötä koskevan suunnitelman toteutumiseen. Tavoitteena on parantaa tietoisuutta olemassa olevista parhaista käytännöistä osaamisen parantamisen ja uusille aloille suuntautumisen kannalta tärkeiden toimintalinjauksien ja aloitteiden suhteen (eritoten pienten ja keskisuurten yritysten osalta) EU:ssa ja niissä EU:n ulkopuolisissa maissa, joissa autoalalla on vankka asema.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>tehtävät on suoritettava sopimusosapuolen osoittamissa toimitiloissa lukuun ottamatta kokouksia, jotka järjestetään pienistä ja keskisuurista yrityksistä vastaavan toimeenpanoviraston (EASME) tai Euroopan komission toimitiloissa.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME haluaa solmia palvelusopimuksen autonrakennusalan tukemiseksi keskeisen osaamisen säilyttämiseksi ja uusien taitojen omaksumiseksi, jotta se voisi säilyttää ja vahvistaa Euroopan autonrakennusalan kilpailukykyä maailmanlaajuisilla markkinoilla ja näin tuoda oman panoksensa alakohtaista osaamisyhteistyötä koskevan suunnitelman toteutumiseen.</P>
                  <P>Työ jakaantuu 2 päävaiheeseen:</P>
                  <P>1. vaihe (kuukaudet 1–9):</P>
                  <P>Ensimmäisen vaiheen aikana suoritettavat tehtävät: ensimmäinen vaihe keskittyy tiedon ja datan jäsentyneeseen keräämiseen ja analysointiin perustuen työpöytätutkimukseen, verkkokyselyihin, työpajoihin ja keskeisten sidosryhmien haastatteluihin,</P>
                  <P>2. vaihe (kuukaudet 10–18):</P>
                  <P>Toisen vaiheen aikana suoritettavat tehtävät: maaraportit, jotka toimitetaan liitteenä, parhaat käytännöt, toimintalinjauksien ja aloitteiden vertailuanalyysi, joka liitetään loppuraporttiin, etenemissuunnitelman muodossa toimitettavien tukitoimien ja suositusten laadinta.</P>
                  <P>Kolmannen vaiheen aikana suoritettavat tehtävät: viimeistely, tulosten validointi ja levitys.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Yritysten sekä pienten ja keskisuurten yritysten kilpailukykyä koskeva ohjelma, C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>katso kohdassa I.3 annettu internetosoite.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>katso kohdassa I.3 annettu internetosoite.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Pienistä ja keskisuurista yrityksistä vastaava toimeenpanovirasto (EASME), Covent Garden 2, Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgia.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Katso kohdassa I.3 annettu internetosoite.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Unionin yleinen tuomioistuin</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Katso kohdassa I.3 annettu internetosoite.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="FR">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agence exécutive pour les petites et moyennes entreprises (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Plan relatif à la coopération sectorielle en matière de compétences. Vers une vision commune portant sur les besoins en compétences des PME dans le secteur automobile : renforcer le développement des stratégies de compétences et de reconversion professionnelle</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME souhaite conclure un marché de services pour apporter un soutien à l’industrie automobile pour retenir les compétences clés et acquérir de nouvelles compétences, afin de maintenir et de renforcer l’avantage concurrentiel du secteur automobile européen dans le marché mondial et de contribuer donc au plan global de la stratégie des compétences du secteur. Le but étant d’améliorer la prise de conscience des meilleures pratiques existantes sur les politiques pertinentes et d’initiatives sur les compétences / la reconversion professionnelle (en particulier pour les PME) dans l’UE et dans les pays en dehors de l’UE où le secteur automobile occupe une forte position.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Les tâches à effectuer se dérouleront dans les locaux désignés par le contractant, sauf dans les cas où les réunions se tiendront dans un local de l'EASME ou celui de la Commission européenne.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME souhaite conclure un marché de services pour apporter un soutien à l’industrie automobile pour retenir les compétences clés et acquérir de nouvelles compétences, afin de maintenir et de renforcer l’avantage concurrentiel du secteur automobile européen dans le marché mondial et de contribuer donc au plan global de la stratégie des compétences du secteur.</P>
                  <P>Le travail sera divisé en 2 phase principales :</P>
                  <P>1<FT TYPE="SUP">ère</FT> phase (Mois 1 – Mois 9) :</P>
                  <P>Les tâches à réaliser dans le programme de travail 1 : La première phase sera destinée à la collecte structurée et à l’analyse des informations et des données, sur la base d’une recherche documentaire, des enquêtes en ligne, des ateliers et entretiens des principales parties prenantes :</P>
                  <P>2<FT TYPE="SUP">ème</FT> phase (Mois 10 – Mois 18) :</P>
                  <P>Les tâches à réaliser dans le programme de travail 2 : des rapports sur les pays à transmettre comme annexe, les meilleures pratiques, une analyse comparative des politiques et des initiatives de l’industrie à livrer comme partie du rapport final, l’élaboration d’un ensemble d’actions de soutien et de recommandations à livrer sous forme d’une feuille de route pour l’exécution :</P>
                  <P>Les tâches à réaliser dans le programme de travail 3 : finalisation, validation et activités de diffusion :</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Programme de travail pour la compétitivité des entreprises et des petites et moyennes entreprises, C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Voir adresse Internet mentionnée à la section I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Voir adresse Internet mentionnée à la section I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>L'agence exécutive pour les petites et moyennes entreprises (EASME), Covent Garden 2, Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgique.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Voir adresse Internet mentionnée à la section I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Voir l'adresse Internet mentionnée à la section I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="EL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Εκτελεστικός Οργανισμός για τις Μικρομεσαίες Επιχειρήσεις (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Σχέδιο στρατηγικής για τομεακή συνεργασία στον τομέα των δεξιοτήτων. Προς ένα κοινό όραμα για την αντιμετώπιση των αναγκών σε δεξιότητες των ΜΜΕ στον τομέα της αυτοκινητοβιομηχανίας: ενίσχυση της ανάπτυξης στρατηγικών αναβάθμισης των δεξιοτήτων και επαγγελματικής επιμόρφωσης</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Ο EASME επιθυμεί να συνάψει σύμβαση παροχής υπηρεσιών με σκοπό να υποστηρίξει την αυτοκινητοβιομηχανία όσον αφορά την διατήρηση βασικών δεξιοτήτων και την απόκτηση νέων προκειμένου να διατηρήσει και να ενισχύσει το ανταγωνιστικό πλεονέκτημα του ευρωπαϊκού τομέα της αυτοκινητοβιομηχανίας σε μια παγκόσμια αγορά και, ως εκ τούτου, να συμβάλει στο συνολικό σχέδιο στρατηγικής όσον αφορά τις τομεακές δεξιότητες. Στόχος είναι να βελτιωθεί η ενημέρωση σχετικά με τις υπάρχουσες βέλτιστες πρακτικές των σχετικών πολιτικών και πρωτοβουλιών για την αναβάθμιση / επανακατάρτιση (ιδίως όσον αφορά τις ΜΜΕ) στην ΕΕ και σε χώρες εκτός της ΕΕ όπου ο τομέας της αυτοκινητοβιομηχανίας κατέχει ισχυρή θέση.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Η εκτέλεση των καθηκόντων θα πραγματοποιηθεί στις εγκαταστάσεις που θα ορίσει ο ανάδοχος, εκτός από τις συναντήσεις οι οποίες θα πραγματοποιηθούν στις εγκαταστάσεις του EASME ή στις εγκαταστάσεις της Ευρωπαϊκής Επιτροπής.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Ο EASME επιθυμεί να συνάψει σύμβαση παροχής υπηρεσιών με σκοπό να υποστηρίξει την αυτοκινητοβιομηχανία όσον αφορά την διατήρηση βασικών δεξιοτήτων και την απόκτηση νέων προκειμένου να διατηρήσει και να ενισχύσει το ανταγωνιστικό πλεονέκτημα του ευρωπαϊκού τομέα της αυτοκινητοβιομηχανίας σε μια παγκόσμια αγορά και, ως εκ τούτου, να συμβάλει στο συνολικό σχέδιο στρατηγικής όσον αφορά τις τομεακές δεξιότητες.</P>
                  <P>Το έργο θα χωριστεί σε 2 κύριες φάσεις:</P>
                  <P>Πρώτο φάση (1ος Μήνας – 9ος Μήνας):</P>
                  <P>Εργασίες προς εκτέλεση στο πλαίσιο του πακέτου εργασίας 1: Η πρώτη φάση θα είναι αφιερωμένη στη δομημένη συλλογή και ανάλυση πληροφοριών και δεδομένων, βασισμένη σε δευτερογενή στατιστική ανάλυση, επιγραμμικές έρευνες, εργαστήρια και συνεντεύξεις βασικών ενδιαφερομένων φορέων:</P>
                  <P>Δεύτερο φάση (10ος Μήνας – 18ος Μήνας)</P>
                  <P>Εργασίες προς εκτέλεση στο πλαίσιο του πακέτου εργασίας 2: εκθέσεις ανά χώρα, που θα παραδοθούν ως παράρτημα, βέλτιστες πρακτικές, βαθμολόγηση των πολιτικών και των πρωτοβουλιών του κλάδου που θα εκδοθούν στο πλαίσιο της τελικής έκθεσης, εκπόνηση δέσμης υποστηρικτικών δράσεων και συστάσεων που θα παραδοθούν στην μορφή χάρτη πορείας σχετικά με την υλοποίηση:</P>
                  <P>Εργασίες προς εκτέλεση στο πλαίσιο του πακέτου εργασίας 3: δραστηριότητες οριστικοποίησης, επικύρωσης και διάδοσης:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Πρόγραμμα για την ανταγωνιστικότητα των επιχειρήσεων και τις μικρομεσαίες επιχειρήσεις C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Βλέπε διαδικτυακή διεύθυνση που παρέχεται στο τμήμα I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Βλέπε διαδικτυακή διεύθυνση που παρέχεται στο τμήμα I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Εκτελεστικός Οργανισμός για τις Μικρομεσαίες Επιχειρήσεις (EASME), Covent Garden 2 Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels,Βέλγιο.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Βλέπε διαδικτυακή διεύθυνση που παρέχεται στο τμήμα I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Γενικό Δικαστήριο</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Βλέπε διαδικτυακή διεύθυνση που παρέχεται στο τμήμα I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="IT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agenzia esecutiva per le piccole e le medie imprese (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Piano per la cooperazione settoriale in materia di competenze. Verso una visione comune sull'affrontare le esigenze di competenze delle PMI nel settore automobilistico: rafforzare lo sviluppo delle strategie di perfezionamento e riqualificazione</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME intende stipulare un contratto di servizi per sostenere l'industria automobilistica nel mantenimento delle competenze chiave e l’acquisizione di nuove, al fine di mantenere e rafforzare il vantaggio competitivo del settore automobilistico europeo in un mercato globale, e quindi contribuire alla strategia generale del programma di qualificazione settoriale. L'obiettivo consiste nel migliorare la consapevolezza delle migliori pratiche esistenti delle pertinenti politiche e iniziative di perfezionamento e riqualificazione (in particolare per le PMI) nell'UE e nei paesi al di fuori dell'UE in cui il settore automobilistico detiene una posizione di forza.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Gli incarichi dovranno essere eseguiti presso le strutture designate dal contraente, tranne quando le riunioni si terranno presso uffici dell'EASME o in quelli della Commissione europea.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME intende stipulare un contratto di servizi per sostenere l'industria automobilistica nel mantenimento delle competenze chiave e l’acquisizione di nuove, al fine di mantenere e rafforzare il vantaggio competitivo del settore automobilistico europeo in un mercato globale, e quindi contribuire alla strategia generale del programma di qualificazione settoriale.</P>
                  <P>Il lavoro sarà diviso in 2 fasi principali:</P>
                  <P>1a fase (da mese 1a mese 9):</P>
                  <P>Compiti da eseguire nell’ambito del pacchetto lavorativo 1: La prima fase sarà dedicata alla raccolta strutturata e all'analisi di informazioni e dati, sulla base di ricerche documentali, sondaggi online, seminari e interviste ai principali soggetti interessati:</P>
                  <P>2a fase (da mese 10 a mese 18)</P>
                  <P>Compiti da svolgere nell'ambito del pacchetto lavorativo 2: relazioni sui paesi da consegnare come allegati, migliori pratiche, analisi comparativa delle politiche e iniziative industriali da consegnare come parte della relazione finale, elaborazione di una serie di azioni di sostegno e raccomandazioni da fornire sotto forma di tabella di marcia per l'attuazione:</P>
                  <P>Compiti da eseguire nell’ambito del pacchetto lavorativo 3: attività di completamento, validazione e diffusione:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Programma per la competitività delle imprese e delle piccole e medie imprese, C(2017) 4563 finale</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Cfr. indirizzo Internet indicato alla sezione I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Cfr. indirizzo Internet indicato alla sezione I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Agenzia esecutiva per le piccole e medie imprese (EASME), Covent Garden 2, place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgio.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Cfr. indirizzo Internet indicato alla sezione I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunale</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Cfr. indirizzo Internet indicato alla Sezione I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="NL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Uitvoerend Agentschap voor kleine en middelgrote ondernemingen (Easme)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Blauwdruk voor sectorale samenwerking op het gebied van vaardigheden: ontwikkeling van een gemeenschappelijke visie om in te spelen op de behoeften op het gebied van vaardigheden van het mkb in de automobielsector: versterking van de ontwikkeling van strategieën voor bij- en omscholing.</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Het Easme wil een dienstenovereenkomst sluiten voor de ondersteuning van de automobielsector bij het behoud van belangrijke vaardigheden en de verwerving van nieuwe vaardigheden, om het concurrentievoordeel van de Europese automobielsector op de globale markt te behouden en te versterken, en zo bij te dragen tot de algemene blauwdruk voor de sectorale strategie op het gebied van vaardigheden. Het doel is de verbetering van het bewustzijn inzake de bestaande beste praktijken met betrekking tot relevante beleidslijnen en initiatieven inzake bij- en omscholing (in het bijzonder voor het mkb) in de EU en in landen buiten de EU waar de automobielsector een sterke positie heeft.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>de taken moeten worden uitgevoerd in de door de contractant aangeduide kantoren, behalve als er bijeenkomsten moeten worden gehouden in het kantoor van het Easme of de Europese Commissie.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Het Easme wil een dienstenovereenkomst sluiten voor de ondersteuning van de automobielsector bij het behoud van belangrijke vaardigheden en de verwerving van nieuwe vaardigheden, om het concurrentievoordeel van de Europese automobielsector op de globale markt te behouden en te versterken, en zo bij te dragen tot de algemene blauwdruk voor de sectorale strategie op het gebied van vaardigheden.</P>
                  <P>Het werk wordt opgesplitst in 2 hoofdfasen:</P>
                  <P>Eerste fase (maand 1 – maand 9):</P>
                  <P>De uit te voeren taken in het kader van werkfase 1 zijn: de eerste fase is gewijd aan de gestructureerde verzameling en analyse van informatie en gegevens op basis van literatuuronderzoek, online-enquêtes, workshops en interviews met de voornaamste belanghebbenden.</P>
                  <P>Tweede fase (maand 10 – maand 18):</P>
                  <P>De uit te voeren taken in het kader van werkfase 2 zijn: de levering van nationale verslagen als een bijlage, beste praktijken, de benchmarking van beleidslijnen en initiatieven van de industrie die als onderdeel van het eindverslag moet worden geleverd, de uitwerking van een reeks ondersteunende acties en aanbevelingen die in de vorm van een stappenplan voor de tenuitvoerlegging moeten worden geleverd.</P>
                  <P>De uit te voeren taken in het kader van werkfase 3 zijn: de afronding, validering en verspreidingsactiviteiten.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>programma voor het concurrentievermogen van ondernemingen en voor kleine en middelgrote ondernemingen, C(2017)4563 final.</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>zie het internetadres vermeld in I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Zie het internetadres vermeld in I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Uitvoerend Agentschap voor kleine en middelgrote ondernemingen (Easme), Covent Garden 2, place Rogier 16, 1210 Brussels, België.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>zie het internetadres vermeld in I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Gerecht</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>zie het internetadres vermeld in I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="PT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agência de Execução para as Pequenas e Médias Empresas (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Plano para a cooperação setorial em matéria de competências. No intuito de uma visão comum de abordagem às necessidades de competências das PME no setor automóvel: reforçando o desenvolvimento de estratégias de requalificação e aumento de qualificações</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>A EASME pretende celebrar um contrato de serviços para apoiar a indústria automóvel na retenção de competências chave e na aquisição de novas, de forma a manter e reforçar a vantagem competitiva do setor automóvel europeu num mercado global e, assim, contribuir para a estratégia do plano setorial de competências global. O objetivo é melhorar a consciencialização das melhores práticas existentes das políticas e iniciativas relevantes quanto a requalificação/aumento de qualificações (especialmente para as PME) na UE e em países fora da UE onde o setor automóvel detém uma forte posição.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>As tarefas serão executadas nas instalações designadas pelo contratante, exceto no caso de reuniões que devam ser realizadas nas instalações da Comissão Europeia ou da EASME.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>A EASME pretende celebrar um contrato de serviços para apoiar a indústria automóvel na retenção de competências chave e na aquisição de novas, de forma a manter e reforçar a vantagem competitiva do setor automóvel europeu num mercado global e, assim, contribuir para a estratégia do plano setorial de competências global.</P>
                  <P>O trabalho será dividido em 2 fases principais:</P>
                  <P>1.ª fase (Mês 1 – Mês 9):</P>
                  <P>As tarefas a serem realizadas no âmbito do pacote de trabalho 1: A primeira fase será dedicada à recolha estruturada e análise da informação e dados, com base em pesquisa de secretária, inquéritos em linha, workshops e entrevistas aos principais intervenientes:</P>
                  <P>2.ª fase (Mês 10 – Mês 18)</P>
                  <P>As tarefas a serem realizadas no âmbito do pacote de trabalho 2: relatórios de país a serem entregues como anexo, melhores práticas, avaliação comparativa de políticas e iniciativas da indústria a serem entregues como parte do relatório final, elaboração de um conjunto de ações de suporte e recomendações a serem entregues no formato de plano de implementação:</P>
                  <P>Tarefas a serem realizadas no âmbito do pacote de trabalho 3: finalização, validação e atividades de disseminação:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Programa de trabalho para a Competitividade das Empresas e das Pequenas e Médias Empresas C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Ver endereço Internet disponibilizado no ponto I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Ver endereço Internet disponibilizado no ponto I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Agência de Execução para as Pequenas e Médias Empresas (EASME) Covent Garden 2 Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels Bélgica.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Ver endereço Internet disponibilizado no ponto I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal Geral</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Ver endereço Internet disponibilizado no ponto I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="SV">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Genomförandeorganet för små och medelstora företag (Easme)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Strategi för sektoriellt samarbete kring kompetens. Mot en gemensam vision för att adressera kompetensbehoven hos små och medelstora företag inom fordonssektorn: främjande av utvecklingen av kompetensutvecklande och omskolande strategier</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Easme önskar ingå ett tjänstekontrakt för att stödja fordonsindustrin i att behålla nyckelfärdigheter och erhålla nya, för att upprätthålla och stärka konkurrenskraften hos den europeiska fordonssektorn på den globala marknaden, och därmed bidra till den övergripande sektoriella kompetensstrategin. Målet är att öka medvetenheten kring nuvarande bästa praxis avseende relevant politik och initiativ för kompetensutveckling/omskolning (i synnerhet för små och medelstora företag) inom EU och i länder utanför EU, där fordonssektorn har en stark ställning.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Arbetsuppgifterna ska utföras i de lokaler som uppdragstagaren utser, utom då möten ska hållas i Easmes eller Europeiska kommissionens lokaler.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Easme önskar ingå ett tjänstekontrakt för att stödja fordonsindustrin i att behålla nyckelfärdigheter och erhålla nya, för att upprätthålla och stärka konkurrenskraften hos den europeiska fordonssektorn på den globala marknaden, och därmed bidra till den övergripande sektoriella kompetensstrategin.</P>
                  <P>Arbetet kommer att delas upp i 2 huvudsakliga etapper:</P>
                  <P>Första etappen (månad 1 - månad 9):</P>
                  <P>Uppgifter som ska utföras inom ramen för arbetspaket (work package - WP) 1 är: Den första etappen kommer att inriktas på strukturerad insamling och analys av information och data, baserad på teoretisk forskning, undersökningar på nätet, workshoppar och intervjuer med huvudintressenter:</P>
                  <P>Andra etappen (månad 10 - månad 18)</P>
                  <P>Uppgifter som ska utföras inom ramen för arbetspaket 2 är: landrapporter som ska levereras i form av en bilaga, bästa praxis, riktmärkning avseende politik och branschinitiativ som ska levereras som en del av den slutliga rapporten, utarbetande av en uppsättning stödåtgärder och rekommendationer som ska levereras i form av en färdplan för genomförande:</P>
                  <P>Uppgifter som ska utföras inom ramen för arbetspaket 3: slutförande, validering och spridningsaktiviteter:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Program för ”Competitiveness of Enterprises and small and medium-sized enterprises” (företagens konkurrenskraft och små och medelstora företag), C (2017) 4563 final (ej översatt till svenska)</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Se internetadressen som anges i avsnitt I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Se internetadressen som anges i avsnitt I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Genomförandeorganet för små och medelstora företag (Easme), Covent Garden 2, place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgien.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Se internetadressen som anges i avsnitt I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunalen</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Se internetadressen som anges i avsnitt I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="CS">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Výkonná agentura pro malé a střední podniky (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Plán odvětvové spolupráce v oblasti dovedností. Směrem ke společné vizi pro řešení potřeb malých a středních podniků týkajících se dovedností v oblasti automobilového průmyslu: posílení vypracovávání strategií rozšiřování dovedností a rekvalifikace</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME zamýšlí uzavřít smlouvu o poskytování služeb na podporu automobilového průmyslu týkající se udržení klíčových dovedností a získání nových dovedností s cílem zachovat a posílit konkurenceschopnost evropského automobilového odvětví na globálním trhu a podpořit tak vypracování celkové strategie týkající se plánu odvětvových dovedností. Cílem je zvýšit povědomí o stávajících osvědčených postupech týkajících se příslušných politik a iniciativ v oblasti rozšiřování dovedností/rekvalifikace (zejména pro malé a střední podniky) v EU a v zemích mimo EU, kde má automobilové odvětví silné postavení.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Úkoly budou prováděny v prostorách, které určí poskytovatel služeb, s výjimkou případů, kdy se jednání budou konat v prostorách EASME nebo Evropské komise.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME zamýšlí uzavřít smlouvu o poskytování služeb na podporu automobilového průmyslu týkající se udržení klíčových dovedností a získání nových dovedností s cílem zachovat a posílit konkurenceschopnost evropského automobilového odvětví na globálním trhu a podpořit tak vypracování celkové strategie týkající se plánu odvětvových dovedností.</P>
                  <P>Práce budou rozděleny do dvou hlavních fází:</P>
                  <P>1. fáze (měsíc 1 - měsíc 9):</P>
                  <P>úkoly, které mají být provedeny v rámci pracovního balíčku č. 1: první fáze bude zaměřena na strukturovaný sběr a analýzu informací a dat založených na sekundárním výzkumu, internetových průzkumech, workshopech a rozhovorech mezi klíčovými zúčastněnými stranami:</P>
                  <P>2. fáze (měsíc 10 - měsíc 18):</P>
                  <P>úkoly, které mají být provedeny v rámci pracovního balíčku č. 2: zprávy týkající se jednotlivých zemí, které mají být předloženy jako příloha, osvědčené postupy, referenční srovnání politik a průmyslových iniciativ, která mají být předložena se závěrečnou zprávou, vypracování souboru podpůrných opatření a doporučení, které mají být předloženy ve formě realizačního plánu:</P>
                  <P>úkoly, které mají být provedeny v rámci pracovního balíčku č. 3: činnosti týkající se dokončení, ověření a šíření informací:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Program pro konkurenceschopnost podniků a malých a středních podniků, C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Viz internetová adresa uvedená v oddílu I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Viz internetová adresa uvedená v oddílu I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Výkonná agentura pro malé a střední podniky (EASME), Covent Garden 2, place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgie.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Viz internetová adresa uvedená v oddíle I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunál</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Viz internetová adresa uvedená v oddíle I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="ET">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Väikeste ja Keskmise Suurusega Ettevõtjate Rakendusamet (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Oskuste alase valdkondliku koostöö tegevuskava. Ühise nägemuse suunas autotööstussektoris VKEdele vajaminevate oskuste käsitlemisel: täiend- ja ümberõppe strateegiate arenduse tugevdamine </P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME soovib sõlmida teenuslepingu, et toetada autotööstust põhioskuste alalhoidmisel ja uute oskuste omandamisel eesmärgiga hoida alal ja tugevdada Euroopa autotööstussektori konkurentsieelist globaalsel turul ja panustada sellega valdkondlike oskuste strateegia üldisesse tegevuskavasse. Ülesandeks on parendada (eriti VKEde) teadlikkust täiend/ümberõppe alaste asjakohaste poliitikate ja algatuste olemasolevatest parimatest tavadest ELs ja riikides väljaspool ELi, kus autotööstussektoril on tugev seisund.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Ülesanded täidetakse töövõtja määratud ruumides, välja arvatud juhul, kui kohtumised toimuvad EASME või Euroopa Komisjoni ruumis.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME soovib sõlmida teenuslepingu, et toetada autotööstust põhioskuste alalhoidmisel ja uute oskuste omandamisel eesmärgiga hoida alal ja tugevdada Euroopa autotööstussektori konkurentsieelist globaalsel turul ja panustada sellega valdkondlike oskuste strateegia üldisesse tegevuskavasse.</P>
                  <P>Töö jaotatakse 2 põhietappi:</P>
                  <P>1. etapp (1. kuu – 9. kuu):</P>
                  <P>1. tööetapi raames tuleb täita järgmised ülesanded: esimene etapp pühendatakse teabe ja andmete struktureeritud{b&gt; &lt;b}kogumisele ja analüüsile, tuginedes teoreetilisele turuanalüüsile, võrguuuringutele, õpikodadele ja peamiste sidusrühmade küsitlusele: </P>
                  <P>2. etapp (10. kuu – 18. kuu)</P>
                  <P>2. tööetapi raames tuleb täita järgmised ülesanded: aruanded riigi kohta tuleb esitada lisana, parimate tavade, poliitikate ja tööstusalgatuste võrdlusuuring tuleb esitada lõpparuande osana, tugitegevuste kogumi väljatöötamine ja soovitused tuleb esitada elluviimise tegevuskava kujul:</P>
                  <P>3. tööetapi raames tuleb täita järgmised ülesanded: lõpliku vormistamise, õigsuse kontrolli ja levitamisega seonduv tegevus:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Ettevõtete konkurentsivõime ning väikeste ja keskmise suurusega ettevõtjate tööprogramm – C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Vt punktis I.3 nimetatud internetiaadressi.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Vt punktis I.3 nimetatud internetiaadressi.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Väikeste ja Keskmise Suurusega Ettevõtjate Rakendusamet (EASME), Covent Garden 2, Place Rogier 16, 1210 Brussels, Belgia.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Vt punktis I.3 nimetatud internetiaadressi.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Üldkohus</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Vt punktis I.3 nimetatud internetiaadressi.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="HU">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>A Kkv-ügyi Végrehajtó Ügynökség (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Tervezet a készségekkel kapcsolatos ágazati együttműködésre. Közös jövőkép felé a kkv-k gépjárműipari képzettségi igényeinek kezelésére vonatkozóan: a készségfejlesztési és átképzési stratégiák fejlesztésének megerősítése</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Az EASME szolgáltatási szerződést kíván kötni a gépjárműipar kulcskészségek megtartásában és elsajátításában történő támogatására vonatkozóan, az európai gépjárműipar globális piaci versenyképességének fenntartása és megerősítése, és így az átfogó, ágazati készségekre irányuló stratégia tervezetéhez történő hozzájárulás érdekében. A célkitűzés a releváns, készségfejlesztésre és átképzésre irányuló szakpolitikákkal és kezdeményezésekkel kapcsolatos meglévő ismeretek fejlesztése az EU-ban és az olyan EU-n kívüli országokban, ahol a gépjárműipar piaci helyzete erős.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>A feladatokat a nyertes ajánlattevő által kijelölt helyen kell teljesíteni, kivéve, ha a találkozókat az EASME vagy az Európai Bizottság székhelyén kell megtartani.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Az EASME szolgáltatási szerződést kíván kötni a gépjárműipar kulcskészségek megtartásában és elsajátításában történő támogatására vonatkozóan, az európai gépjárműipar globális piaci versenyképességének fenntartása és megerősítése, és így az átfogó, ágazati készségekre irányuló stratégia tervezetéhez történő hozzájárulás érdekében.</P>
                  <P>A munkákat 2 fő szakaszra osztják:</P>
                  <P>1. szakasz (az 1. hónaptól a 9. hónapig):</P>
                  <P>Az 1. munkacsomag keretében elvégzendő feladatok a következők: Az első szakaszt elméleti kutatásokon, online kérdőíveken, workshopokon és a kulcsfontosságú érdekelt felekkel felvett interjúkon alapuló strukturált információ- és adatgyűjtésnek, valamint -elemzésnek szentelik:</P>
                  <P>2. szakasz (a 10. hónaptól a 18. hónapig)</P>
                  <P>A 2. munkacsomag keretében elvégzendő feladatok a következők: mellékletként elkészítendő országjelentések, legjobb gyakorlatok, a végleges jelentés részeként elkészítendő szakpolitikák és iparági kezdeményezések teljesítményértékelése, végrehajtási ütemtervként teljesítendő támogató intézkedések és ajánlások kidolgozása:</P>
                  <P>A 3. munkacsomag keretében elvégzendő feladatok: véglegesítés, hitelesítés és terjesztési tevékenységek:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>A vállalkozások versenyképességét és a kis- és középvállalkozásokat segítő program, C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Lásd az I.3. szakaszban megadott internetcímet.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Lásd az I.3. szakaszban megadott internetcímet.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Kkv-ügyi Végrehajtó Ügynökség (EASME), Covent Garden 2 Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgium.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Lásd az I.3. szakaszban megadott internetcímet.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Törvényszék</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Lásd az I.3. szakaszban megadott internetcímet.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="LT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Mažųjų ir vidutinių įmonių reikalų vykdomoji įstaiga (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Sektorių bendradarbiavimo įgūdžių srityje planas. Siekiant bendros vizijos, kaip tenkinti MVĮ įgūdžių poreikius automobilių pramonės sektoriuje: galimybių kelti kvalifikaciją arba persikvalifikavimo strategijų plėtros stiprinimas</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME pageidauja sudaryti paslaugų pirkimo sutartį siekdama paremti automobilių pramonę išlaikant pagrindinius įgūdžius ir įgyjant naujų tam, kad palaikytų ir stiprintų Europos automobilių sektoriaus konkurencingumą pasaulinėje rinkoje ir taip prisidėtų prie bendro Sektorių bendradarbiavimo įgūdžių srityje plano. Tikslas – gerinti supratimą apie atitinkamos politikos bei iniciatyvų, susijusių su kvalifikacijos kėlimu ar persikvalifikavimu (ypač MVĮ), turima gerąja patirtimi ES ir ne ES šalyse, kuriose stipriai išvystyta automobilių pramonė.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Užduotys turės būti atliekamos rangovo paskirtose patalpose, išskyrus susitikimų vietas EASME ar Europos Komisijos patalpose.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME pageidauja sudaryti paslaugų pirkimo sutartį siekdama paremti automobilių pramonę išlaikant pagrindinius įgūdžius ir įgyjant naujų tam, kad palaikytų ir stiprintų Europos automobilių sektoriaus konkurencingumą pasaulinėje rinkoje ir taip prisidėtų prie bendro Sektorių bendradarbiavimo įgūdžių srityje plano.</P>
                  <P>Darbas bus padalytas į 2 pagrindinius etapus:</P>
                  <P>1-asis etapas (1–9 mėnesiai)</P>
                  <P>Pagal 1 darbų projektą bus atliktos tokios užduotys: Pirmasis etapas bus skirtas sistemiškai rinkti ir analizuoti informaciją bei duomenis pagal teorinį tyrimą, internetines apklausas, praktinius seminarus ir pokalbius su pagrindinėmis suinteresuotosiomis šalimis.</P>
                  <P>2-asis etapas (10–18 mėnesiai)</P>
                  <P>Pagal 2 darbų projektą bus atliktos tokios užduotys: šalies ataskaitos turės būti teikiamos kaip priedas, geroji praktika, politikos ir pramonės iniciatyvų lyginamoji analizė, kuri turės būti teikiama prie baigiamosios ataskaitos, smulkiai išdėstomi pagalbiniai veiksmai ir rekomendacijos, kurias reikės pateikti kaip įgyvendinimo veiksmų gaires.</P>
                  <P>Pagal 3 darbų projektą bus atliktos tokios užduotys: baigiamoji, patvirtinimo ir platinimo veikla.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Programa dėl įmonių konkurencingumo ir mažųjų bei vidutinių įmonių, C(2017)4563 galutinė</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Žr. interneto adresą, nurodytą I.3. dalyje.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Žr. interneto adresą, nurodytą I.3. dalyje.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Mažųjų ir vidutinių įmonių reikalų vykdomoji įstaiga (EASME), Covent Garden 2, place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgija.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Žr. interneto adresą, nurodytą I.3 dalyje.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Bendrasis Teismas</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Žr. interneto adresą, nurodytą I.3 dalyje.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="LV">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Mazo un vidējo uzņēmumu izpildaģentūra (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Plāns nozaru sadarbībai prasmju jomā. Ceļā uz kopīgu redzējumu par MVU autobūves nozares prasmju vajadzību risināšanu – kvalifikācijas celšanas un pārkvalifikācijas stratēģiju attīstības stiprināšana</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME vēlas noslēgt pakalpojumu līgumu, lai atbalstītu autobūves nozari pamatprasmju saglabāšanā un jaunu prasmju gūšanā, kas palīdzētu uzturēt un stiprināt Eiropas autobūves nozares konkurētspēju globālajā tirgū, un tādējādi sniegtu ieguldījumu kopējā nozaru prasmju stratēģijas plānā. Mērķis ir uzlabot informētību par attiecīgās kvalifikācijas celšanas un pārkvalifikācijas (it īpaši saistībā ar MVU) politikas un iniciatīvu esošajām paraugpraksēm ES un valstīs ārpus ES, kur autobūves nozarei ir spēcīga pozīcija.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>uzdevumi jāveic darbuzņēmēja norādītajās telpās, izņemot gadījumus, kad sanāksmes paredzēts rīkot EASME vai Eiropas Komisijas telpās.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME vēlas noslēgt pakalpojumu līgumu, lai atbalstītu autobūves nozari pamatprasmju saglabāšanā un jaunu prasmju gūšanā, kas palīdzētu uzturēt un stiprināt Eiropas autobūves nozares konkurētspēju globālajā tirgū, un tādējādi sniegtu ieguldījumu kopējā nozaru prasmju stratēģijas plānā.</P>
                  <P>Darbs būs iedalīts 2 galvenajos posmos.</P>
                  <P>1. posms (1.–9. mēnesis) —</P>
                  <P>1. darba programmas ietvaros veicami šādi uzdevumi: pirmais posms būs paredzēts informācijas un datu strukturētai ievākšanai un analīzei, pamatojoties uz dokumentu izpēti, tiešsaistes aptaujām, darbsemināriem un galveno ieinteresēto personu intervijām.</P>
                  <P>2. posms (10.–18. mēnesis) —</P>
                  <P>2. darba programmas ietvaros veicami šādi uzdevumi: pārskati par valstīm jāiesniedz pielikuma veidā, paraugprakse, politikas un nozaru iniciatīvu salīdzinošā vērtēšana jāiesniedz kā daļa no gala ziņojuma, izstrādātais atbalsta rīcību un ieteikumu kopums jāiesniedz kā īstenošanas ceļvedis;</P>
                  <P>3. darba programmas ietvaros veicami šādi uzdevumi: pabeigšanas, pārbaudes un izplatīšanas pasākumi.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Uzņēmumu un mazo un vidējo uzņēmumu konkurētspējas programma, C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>skatīt interneta adresi, kas minēta I.3. iedaļā.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Skatīt interneta adresi, kas minēta I.3. iedaļā.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Mazo un vidējo uzņēmumu izpildaģentūra (EASME), Covent Garden 2, Place Rogier 16, 1210 Brussels, Beļģija</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>skatīt interneta adresi, kas minēta I.3. iedaļā.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Vispārējā tiesa</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>skatīt interneta adresi, kas minēta I.3. iedaļā.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="MT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>L-Aġenzija Eżekuttiva għall-Intrapriżi Żgħar u Medji (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Pjan għal Kooperazzjoni Settorjali fuq il-Ħiliet. Lejn viżjoni komuni biex jiġu indirizzati l-bżonnijiet fil-ħiliet għall-SMEs fis-settur tal-vetturi: it-tisħiħ tal-iżvilupp ta' strateġiji għal titjib fil-ħiliet u l-kisba ta' ħiliet oħra</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>L-EASME tixtieq tibda kuntratt ta' servizz biex tappoġġja lill-industrija tal-vetturi fiż-żamma ta' ħiliet ewlenin u l-kisba ta' oħrajn ġodda, sabiex jinżamm u jissaħħaħ il-karattru kompetittiv tas-settur tal-vetturi Ewropew fis-suq globali, u għalhekk ikun ta' kontribut għall-Pjan globali għal strateġija settorjali fuq il-ħiliet. L-għan huwa li tittejjeb il-kuxjenza dwar l-aqwa prattiki eżistenti ta' politiki u inizjattivi rilevanti dwar it-titjib fil-ħiliet jew il-kisba ta' ħiliet oħra (b'mod partikolari SMEs) fl-UE u fil-pajjiżi barra mill-UE fejn is-settur tal-vetturi għandu pożizzjoni qawwija.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Ix-xogħlijiet għandhom jitwettqu fil-bini indikat mill-kuntrattur, ħlief meta l-laqgħat iridu jsiru fil-bini tal-EASME jew tal-Kummissjoni Ewropea.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>L-EASME tixtieq tibda kuntratt ta' servizz biex tappoġġja lill-industrija tal-vetturi fiż-żamma ta' ħiliet ewlenin u l-kisba ta' oħrajn ġodda, sabiex jinżamm u jissaħħaħ il-karattru kompetittiv tas-settur tal-vetturi Ewropew fis-suq globali, u għalhekk ikun ta' kontribut għall-Pjan globali għal strateġija settorjali fuq il-ħiliet.</P>
                  <P>Ix-xogħol se jinqasam f'2 fażijiet ewlenin:</P>
                  <P>L-1 fażi (l-1 xahar – id-9 xahar):</P>
                  <P>Ix-xogħlijiet li jridu jitwettqu taħt l-1 Programm ta' Ħidma: L-ewwel fażi ser tkun iddedikata għall-ġbir strutturat u l-analiżi ta' informazzjoni u dejta, abbażi ta' riċerka ta' dokumenti (desk research), onlajn servejs, gruppi ta' ħidma u intervisti ta' partijiet interessati ewlenin:</P>
                  <P>It-2 fażi (l-10 xahar – it-18-il xahar)</P>
                  <P>Xogħlijiet li għandhom jitwettqu taħt it-2 Programm ta' Ħidma: ir-rapporti tal-pajjiżi għandhom jintbagħtu bħala anness, l-aqwa prattiki, il-valutazzjoni komparattiva ta' politiki u inizjattivi tal-industrija li għandhom jiġu ppreżentati bħala parti mir-rapport finali, l-iżvilupp ta' sett ta' azzjonijiet ta' appoġġ u rakkomandazzjonijiet li għandhom jingħataw fil-forma ta' pjan direzzjonali ta' implimentazzjoni:</P>
                  <P>Xogħlijiet li għandhom jitwettqu taħt it-3 Programm ta' Ħidma: attivitajiet ta' finalizzazzjoni, validazzjoni u tixrid:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Programm għall-Kompetittività tal-Intrapriżi u l-intrapriżi żgħar u medji, C(2017)4563 finali</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Ara l-indirizz tal-Internet ipprovdut fit-Taqsima I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Ara l-indirizz tal-Internet ipprovdut fit-Taqsima I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>L-Aġenzija Eżekuttiva għall-Intrapriżi Żgħar u Medji (EASME) Covent Garden 2 Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels il-Belġju.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Ara l-indirizz tal-Internet ipprovdut fit-Taqsima I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Il-Qorti Ġenerali</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Ara l-indirizz tal-Internet ipprovdut fit-Taqsima I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="PL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agencja Wykonawcza ds. Małych i Średnich Przedsiębiorstw (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Plan współpracy sektorowej na rzecz umiejętności. W kierunku wspólnej wizji zagospodarowania potrzeb MŚP w zakresie umiejętności w sektorze motoryzacyjnym: wzmocnienie rozwoju strategii podnoszenia umiejętności i przekwalifikowywania się</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME pragnie zawrzeć umowę o usługi w celu wsparcia przemysłu motoryzacyjnego w utrzymaniu kluczowych umiejętności i nabywaniu nowych, aby utrzymać i wzmocnić przewagę konkurencyjną europejskiego sektora motoryzacyjnego na rynku światowym, a tym samym przyczynić się do realizacji ogólnej strategii na rzecz umiejętności sektorowych w ramach projektu. Celem jest zwiększenie świadomości na temat istniejących najlepszych praktyk w zakresie odpowiednich polityk i inicjatyw dotyczących podnoszenia/zmiany kwalifikacji (w szczególności w przypadku MŚP) w UE i w krajach poza UE, w których sektor motoryzacyjny ma silną pozycję.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Zadania będą wykonywane w miejscach wyznaczonych przez wykonawcę, z wyłączeniem przypadków, w których spotkania będą odbywać się w EASME lub siedzibie Komisji Europejskiej.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME pragnie zawrzeć umowę o usługi w celu wsparcia przemysłu motoryzacyjnego w utrzymaniu kluczowych umiejętności i nabywaniu nowych, aby utrzymać i wzmocnić przewagę konkurencyjną europejskiego sektora motoryzacyjnego na rynku światowym, a tym samym przyczynić się do realizacji ogólnej strategii na rzecz umiejętności sektorowych w ramach projektu.</P>
                  <P>Prace podzielone będą na 2 główne etapy:</P>
                  <P>1. etap (1. miesiąc - 9. miesiąc)</P>
                  <P>Zadania, które należy wykonać w ramach 1. etapu obejmują: Pierwszy etap dotyczy zorganizowanego gromadzenia i analizy informacji i danych w oparciu o analizę dokumentacji, ankiety internetowe, warsztaty i wywiady z kluczowymi zainteresowanymi stronami:</P>
                  <P>2. etap (10. miesiąc - 18. miesiąc)</P>
                  <P>Zadania, które należy wykonać w ramach 2. etapu obejmują: sporządzanie sprawozdań dla poszczególnych krajów w formie załącznika, najlepsze praktyki, ocenę porównawczą polityk i inicjatyw branżowych w ramach sprawozdania końcowego, opracowanie zestawu działań wspierających i zaleceń, które należy przedstawić w formie planu działania (mapy drogowej):</P>
                  <P>Zadania, które należy wykonać w ramach 3. etapu obejmują: finalizację, zatwierdzenie i rozpowszechnianie:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Program na rzecz konkurencyjności przedsiębiorstw oraz małych i średnich przedsiębiorstw, C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>zob. adres internetowy w pkt I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>zob. adres internetowy w pkt I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Agencja Wykonawcza ds. Małych i Średnich Przedsiębiorstw (EASME), Covent Garden 2, place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgia.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Zob. adres internetowy w pkt I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Sąd</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Zob. adres internetowy w pkt I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="SK">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Výkonná agentúra pre malé a stredné podniky (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Koncepcia pre sektorovú spoluprácu v oblasti zručností. Smerom k spoločnej vízii pri riešení potrieb MSP v oblasti automobilového priemyslu: posilnenie rozvoja stratégií zvyšovania kvalifikácie a rekvalifikácie</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME si želá uzavrieť zmluvu o poskytovaní služieb na podporu automobilového priemyslu v oblasti zachovania kľúčových zručností a získavaní nových zručností s cieľom udržať a posilniť konkurenčnú výhodu európskeho automobilového odvetvia na globálnom trhu a prispieť tak k celkovej koncepcii stratégie v oblasti sektorových zručností. Cieľom je zlepšiť informovanosť o existujúcich osvedčených postupoch príslušných politík a iniciatív týkajúcich sa zvyšovania kvalifikácie/rekvalifikácie (najmä pre MSP) v EÚ a v krajinách mimo EÚ, v ktorých automobilový sektor zaujíma silnú pozíciu.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Úlohy sa budú vykonávať v priestoroch určených dodávateľom, okrem stretnutí, ktoré sa majú uskutočniť v priestoroch EASME alebo Európskej komisie.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME si želá uzavrieť zmluvu o poskytovaní služieb na podporu automobilového priemyslu v oblasti zachovania kľúčových zručností a získavaní nových zručností s cieľom udržať a posilniť konkurenčnú výhodu európskeho automobilového odvetvia na globálnom trhu a prispieť tak k celkovej koncepcii stratégie v oblasti sektorových zručností.</P>
                  <P>Práca bude rozdelená do 2 hlavných fáz:</P>
                  <P>1. fáza (mesiac 1 – mesiac 9):</P>
                  <P>Úlohy, ktoré sa majú vykonať v rámci pracovného balíka 1: Prvá fáza sa bude venovať štruktúrovanému zhromažďovaniu a analýze informácií a údajov založeným na teoretickom výskumne, online prieskumoch, workshopoch a rozhovoroch s kľúčovými zainteresovanými stranami:</P>
                  <P>2. fáza (mesiac 10 – mesiac 18)</P>
                  <P>Úlohy, ktoré sa majú vykonať v rámci pracovného balíka 2: správy z krajín sa majú dodať vo forme prílohy, osvedčené postupy, referenčné porovnanie politík a priemyselné iniciatívy sa majú dodať ako súčasť záverečnej správy, vypracovaný súbor podporných činností a odporúčaní sa má dodať vo forme plánu implementácie:</P>
                  <P>Úlohy, ktoré sa majú vykonať v rámci pracovného balíka 3: činnosti týkajúce sa dokončenia, overenia a šírenia informácií:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Program pre konkurencieschopnosť podnikov a malých a stredných podnikov C(2017)4563, konečná verzia</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Pozri internetovú adresu uvedenú v oddiele I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Pozri internetovú adresu uvedenú v oddiele I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Výkonná agentúra pre malé a stredné podniky (EASME), Covent Garden 2, place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgicko.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Pozri internetovú adresu uvedenú v oddiele I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Všeobecný súd</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Pozri internetovú adresu uvedenú v oddiele I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="SL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Izvajalska agencija za mala in srednja podjetja (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Načrt za sektorsko sodelovanje na področju spretnosti. Na poti k skupni viziji obravnavanja potreb po spretnostih MSP v avtomobilskem sektorju: krepitev razvoja strategij izpopolnjevanja in prekvalifikacije</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME želi skleniti naročilo storitev za podporo avtomobilski industriji pri ohranjanju ključnih spretnosti in pridobivanju novih, da bi ohranila in okrepila konkurenčno prednost evropskega avtomobilskega sektorja na svetovnem trgu in s tem prispevala k skupnemu načrtu strategije na področju spretnosti v tem sektorju. Cilj je izboljšati osveščenost o obstoječih dobrih praksah relevantnih politik in pobudah za izpopolnjevanje/prekvalifikacijo (zlasti za MSP) v EU in državah zunaj EU, kjer ima avtomobilski sektor močan položaj.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Naloge se bodo izvajale v prostorih, ki jih določi izvajalec, razen v primeru, da sestanki potekajo v prostorih EASME ali prostorih Evropske komisije.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME želi skleniti naročilo storitev za podporo avtomobilski industriji pri ohranjanju ključnih spretnosti in pridobivanju novih, da bi ohranila in okrepila konkurenčno prednost evropskega avtomobilskega sektorja na svetovnem trgu in s tem prispevala k skupnemu načrtu strategije na področju spretnosti v tem sektorju.</P>
                  <P>Delo bo razdeljeno v 2 glavni fazi:</P>
                  <P>1. faza (mesec 1 – mesec 9):</P>
                  <P>naloge, ki jih je treba izvesti v delovni fazi 1, so: prva faza bo namenjena strukturiranemu zbiranju in analizi informacij in podatkov v obliki teoretičnih raziskav, spletnih anket, delavnic in razgovorov s ključnimi deležniki;</P>
                  <P>2. faza (mesec 10 – mesec 18):</P>
                  <P>naloge, ki jih je treba izvesti v delovni fazi 2, zajemajo: poročila o državah, ki jih je treba predložiti kot prilogo, dobre prakse, primerjalne analize politik in industrijskih pobud, ki jih je treba predložiti kot del končnega poročila, izdelavo sklopa podpornih ukrepov in priporočil, ki jih je treba predložiti v obliki časovnega načrta za izvedbo;</P>
                  <P>naloge, ki jih je treba izvesti v delovni fazi 3, so: zaključna dela, potrjevanje in razširjanje.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Program za konkurenčnost podjetij ter za mala in srednja podjetja, C(2017) 4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Glejte spletni naslov v oddelku I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Glejte spletni naslov v oddelku I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Izvajalska agencija za mala in srednja podjetja (EASME), Covent Garden 2, Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgija.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Glejte spletni naslov v oddelku I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Splošno sodišče</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Glejte spletni naslov v oddelku I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="GA">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>An Ghníomhaireacht Feidhmiúcháin um Fhiontair Bheaga agus Mheánmhéide (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Treoirphlean maidir le comhar earnála i dtaobh scileanna. I dtreo físe coitinne chun aghaidh a thabhairt ar éilimh scileanna na FBManna san earnáil gluaisteán: forbairt na straitéisí uas-scilithe agus athscilithea neartú</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Is mian le EASME conradh seirbhíse a dhéanamh chun tacú leis an tionscal gluaisteán chun eochairscileanna a choinneáil agus chun cinn nua a fháil, d’fhonn faobhar iomaíoch earnáil gluaisteán na hEorpa a chothabháil agus a neartú ar mhargadh domhanda, agus dá réir sin cur le straitéis scileanna earnála an treoirphlean ar an iomlán. Is é an sprioc feabhas a chur ar an bhfeasacht faoi na dea-chleachtais reatha agus faoi na beartais ábhartha um uas-sciliú/athsciliú (go háirithe do na FBManna) san AE agus sna tíortha lasmuigh den AE ina bhfuil an earnáil gluaisteán láidir.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Beidh na tascanna le feidhmiú ag áitreabh arna ainmniú ag an gconraitheoir, seachas nuair a bheidh cruinnithe le tionól ag áitreabh EASME nó áitreabh an Choimisiúin Eorpaigh.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Is mian le EASME conradh seirbhíse a dhéanamh chun tacú leis an tionscal gluaisteán chun eochairscileanna a choinneáil agus chun cinn nua a fháil, d’fhonn faobhar iomaíoch earnáil gluaisteán na hEorpa a chothabháil agus a neartú ar mhargadh domhanda, agus dá réir sin cur le straitéis scileanna earnála an treoirphlean ar an iomlán.</P>
                  <P>Roinnfear an obair ina 2 phríomhchéim:</P>
                  <P>1ú céim (Mí 1 – Mí 9):</P>
                  <P>Tascanna atá le feidhmiú faoi Phacáiste Oibre 1: Beidh an chéad chéim tiomanta do bhailiú agus anailísiú struchtúrtha na faisnéise agus na sonraí, bunaithe ar thaighde deisce, suirbhéanna ar líne, ceardlanna agus agallaimh le heochair-gheallsealbhóirí:</P>
                  <P>2ú céim (Mí 10 – Mí 18)</P>
                  <P>Tascanna atá le feidhmiú faoi Phacáiste Oibre 2: tuairiscí tíre le seachadadh mar iarscríbhinn, dea-chleachtais, tagarmharcáil beartas agus tionscnaimh thionscail le seachadadh mar chuid den tuarascáil deiridh, mionsaothrú de thacar gníomhartha tacúla agus moltaí le seachadadh i bhfoirm treochláir fhorfheidhmithe:</P>
                  <P>Tascanna atá le feidhmiú faoi Phacáiste Oibre 3: tabhairt chun críche, bailíochtú, agus gníomhaíochtaí scaipthe:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Clár Oibre maidir le hIomaíochas Fiontar agus fiontar beag agus meánmhéide, C(2017) 4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Féach an seoladh Idirlín atá curtha ar fáil in Alt I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Féach an seoladh Idirlín atá curtha ar fáil in Alt I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>An Ghníomhaireacht Feidhmiúcháin um Fhiontair Bheaga agus Mheánmhéide (EASME), Covent Garden 2, place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, an Bheilg.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Féach an seoladh Idirlín atá curtha ar fáil in Alt I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>An Chúirt Ghinearálta</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Féach an seoladh Idirlín atá curtha ar fáil in alt I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="BG">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Изпълнителна агенция за малките и средните предприятия (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Схема за секторно сътрудничество по отношение на уменията. За обща визия за справяне с нуждите от умения на МСП в автомобилния сектор: подсилване на развитието на стратегии за повишаване на уменията и преквалификация</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME желае да сключи поръчка за услуги в подкрепа на автомобилната индустрия за поддържане на ключови умения и придобиване на нови такива, за да задържи и подсили конкурентното предимство на европейския автомобилен сектор на глобалния пазар и така да допринесе към общата схема за секторни умения. Целта е да се подобри информираността за съществуващи най-добри практики по съответните политики и инициативи за повишаване на уменията/преквалификация (в частност за МСП) в ЕС и в държави извън ЕС, където автомобилният сектор има силна позиция.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Задачите ще бъдат извършени в помещенията, определени от изпълнителя, с изключение на случаите, когато заседанията ще се провеждат в помещенията на EASME или на Европейската комисия.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME желае да сключи поръчка за услуги в подкрепа на автомобилната индустрия за поддържане на ключови умения и придобиване на нови такива, за да задържи и подсили конкурентното предимство на европейския автомобилен сектор на глобалния пазар и така да допринесе към общата схема за секторни умения.</P>
                  <P>Работата ще бъде разделена на 2 основни фази:</P>
                  <P>Първо: фаза (месец 1 — месец 9):</P>
                  <P>Задачите, които трябва да се извършат по РП 1: Първата фаза ще бъде посветена на структурираното събиране и анализ на информация и данни, базирани на вторично проучване, онлайн анкети, семинари и интервюта с ключови заинтересовани лица:</P>
                  <P>Втори фаза (месец 10 — месец 18)</P>
                  <P>Задачите, които трябва да се извършат по РП 2: доклади от държавите, които да се предоставят като приложение, най-добри практики, сравнителен анализ на политики и инициативи в промишлеността, които да се предоставят като част от окончателния доклад, изработване на набор от подкрепящи действия и препоръки, които да се предоставят под формата на карта за изпълнение:</P>
                  <P>Задачите, които трябва да се извършат по РП 3: финализиране, проверка и дейности по разпространение:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Работна програма за конкурентоспособност на предприятията и на малките и средните предприятия, C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Вж. интернет адреса, посочен в раздел I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Вж. интернет адреса, посочен в раздел I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Изпълнителна агенция за малките и средните предприятия (EASME), Covent Garden 2, place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Белгия.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Вж. интернет адреса, посочен в раздел I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Общ съд</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Вж. интернет адреса, посочен в раздел I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="RO">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agenția Executivă pentru Întreprinderi Mici și Mijlocii (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Planul de cooperare sectorială în materie de competențe. Către o viziune comună privind abordarea nevoilor în materie de competențe ale IMM-urilor în domeniul automobilelor: consolidarea dezvoltării strategiilor de actualizare a competențelor și de recalificare</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME dorește să încheie un contract de servicii care să sprijine industria automobilelor în menținerea competențelor-cheie și dobândirea de noi competențe, pentru a menține și consolida avantajul competitiv al sectorului european de automobile pe o piață mondială și, astfel, să contribuie la planul de strategie globală sectorială în materie de competențe. Scopul este de a îmbunătăți gradul de conștientizare a celor mai bune practici existente privind politicile și inițiativele relevante în materie de actualizare a competențelor/ recalificare (în special pentru IMM-uri) în UE și în țările din afara UE, în care sectorul automobilelor deține o poziție puternică.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Sarcinile vor fi executate la sediul specificat de contractant, cu excepția cazului în care trebuie organizate reuniuni la sediul EASME sau al Comisiei Europene.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME dorește să încheie un contract de servicii care să sprijine industria automobilelor în menținerea competențelor-cheie și dobândirea de noi competențe, pentru a menține și consolida avantajul competitiv al sectorului european de automobile pe o piață mondială și, astfel, să contribuie la planul de strategie globală sectorială în materie de competențe.</P>
                  <P>Lucrarea va fi împărțită în 2 etape principale:</P>
                  <P>Prima etapă (luna 1 – luna 9):</P>
                  <P>Sarcinile care urmează să fie executate în cadrul primei etape de lucru: Prima etapă va fi dedicată colectării și analizei structurate a informațiilor și datelor, pe baza cercetărilor documentare, a studiilor online, a atelierelor și a interviurilor principalelor părți interesate:</P>
                  <P>A 2-a etapă (luna 10 – luna 18)</P>
                  <P>Sarcinile care trebuie îndeplinite în cadrul etapei de lucru 2: rapoartele de țară care urmează să fie furnizate ca anexă, cele mai bune practici, analiză comparativă a politicilor și inițiativelor industriale care trebuie furnizate ca parte a raportului final, elaborarea unui set de acțiuni de sprijin și recomandări care trebuie furnizate sub forma unui plan de implementare:</P>
                  <P>Sarcinile care urmează a fi realizate în cadrul etapei de lucru 3: activități de finalizare, validare și diseminare:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Programul pentru Competitivitatea Întreprinderilor și a întreprinderilor mici și mijlocii, C(2017)4563 final</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>A se vedea adresa de internet indicată în secțiunea I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>A se vedea adresa de internet indicată în secțiunea I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Agenția Executivă pentru Întreprinderi Mici și Mijlocii (EASME), Covent Garden 2, Place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgia.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>A se vedea adresa de internet indicată la secțiunea I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunalul</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>A se vedea adresa de internet indicată în secțiunea I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F02" LG="HR">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Izvršna agencija za mala i srednja poduzeća (EASME)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Covent Garden 2, Place Charles Rogier 16, Office 10/179</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1210</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>easme-procurement@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/EASME</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ec.europa.eu/easme/en</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://etendering.ted.europa.eu/cft/cft-display.html?cftId=3523</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Nacrt za sektorsku suradnju u području vještina. Prema zajedničkoj viziji o rješavanju potreba za vještinama malih i srednjih poduzeća u automobilskom sektoru: jačanje razvoja strategija za usavršavanje i prekvalificiranje</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>EASME/COSME/2018/006</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79300000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>EASME želi sklopiti ugovor o pružanju usluga kako bi podržao automobilsku industriju u zadržavanju ključnih vještina i stjecanju novih, kako bi održao i ojačao konkurentnost europskog automobilskog sektora na globalnom tržištu, čime bi doprinio ukupnom nacrtu strategije za sektorske vještine. Cilj je poboljšati svijest o postojećim najboljim praksama relevantnih politika i inicijativa za usavršavanje/prekvalificiranje (posebice za mala i srednja poduzeća) u EU-u i zemljama izvan EU-a u kojima automobilski sektor ima snažnu poziciju.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Zadaci će se provoditi u prostorima koje je odredio izvoditelj, osim sastanaka koji će se održavati u prostorima EASME-a ili prostorima Europske komisije.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EASME želi sklopiti ugovor o pružanju usluga kako bi podržao automobilsku industriju u zadržavanju ključnih vještina i stjecanju novih, kako bi održao i ojačao konkurentnost europskog automobilskog sektora na globalnom tržištu, čime bi doprinio ukupnom nacrtu strategije za sektorske vještine.</P>
                  <P>Rad će se podijeliti u 2 glavne faze:</P>
                  <P>Prva faza (1. mjesec - 9. mjesec):</P>
                  <P>Zadaci koji će se provoditi u okviru radnog paketa 1 su sljedeći: Prva faza bit će posvećena strukturiranom prikupljanju i analizi informacija i podataka, temeljenih na uredskom istraživanju, mrežnim anketama, radionicama i intervjuima ključnih dionika:</P>
                  <P>Druga faza (10. mjesec - 18. mjesec)</P>
                  <P>Zadaci koji će se provoditi u okviru radnog paketa 2: izvješća po zemljama koja se dostavljaju kao prilog, najbolje prakse, komparativna analiza politika i industrijskih inicijativa koja će biti isporučena u okviru završnog izvješća, izrada niza potpornih mjera i preporuka koje će se isporučiti u obliku plana provedbe:</P>
                  <P>Zadaci koji će se provoditi u okviru radnog paketa 3: aktivnosti dovršetka, provjere i širenja:</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">800000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">18</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <EU_PROGR_RELATED>Program za konkurentnost poduzeća te malih i srednjih poduzeća C(2017)4563 završna verzija</EU_PROGR_RELATED>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Vidjeti internetsku adresu navedenu u odjeljku I.3.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Vidjeti internetsku adresu navedenu u odjeljku I.3.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-07-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="BG"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="CS"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DE"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ES"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="ET"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FI"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="FR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="GA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HR"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="HU"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="IT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="LV"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="MT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="PT"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="RO"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SK"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SL"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="SV"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">9</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-07-11</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Izvršna agencija za mala i srednja poduzeća (EASME), Covent Garden 2, place Rogier 16 1210 Brussels, Belgija.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Vidjeti internetsku adresu navedenu u odjeljku I.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Opći sud</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Rue du Fort Niedergrünewald</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+35 243031</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+35 243032100</FAX>
               <URL>http://curia.europa.eu</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Vidjeti internetsku adresu navedenu u odjeljku I.3.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
