<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="134787-2018"
            EDITION="2018061">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-138334-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20190326</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>61</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180328</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 061-134787</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:134787-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.porthosp.nhs.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="48000000">Software package and information systems</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="48210000">Networking software package</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKJ31">Portsmouth</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKJ31">Portsmouth</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180326</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="6">Body governed by public law</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="H">Health</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C01</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Софтуерни пакети и информационни системи</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Balíky programů a informační systémy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Programpakker og informationssystemer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Softwarepaket und Informationssysteme</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Πακέτα λογισμικού και συστήματα πληροφορικής</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Software package and information systems</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Paquetes de software y sistemas de información</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tarkvarapaketid ja infosüsteemid</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ohjelmatuotteet ja tietojärjestelmät</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Logiciels et systèmes d'information</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Software package and information systems</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Programski paketi i informacijski sustavi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Szoftvercsomag és információs rendszerek</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pacchetti software e sistemi di informazione</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Programinės įrangos paketai ir informacinės sistemos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Programmatūras pakotne un informācijas sistēmas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pakketti tas-softwer u sistemi ta' informazzjoni</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Software en informatiesystemen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pakiety oprogramowania i systemy informatyczne</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pacotes de software e sistemas de informação</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pachete software şi sisteme informatice</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Softvérové balíky a informačné systémy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Programski paketi in informacijski sistemi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Portsmouth</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Programvara och informationssystem</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Portsmouth Hospitals NHs Trust</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F01_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F01" LG="EN">
         <NOTICE TYPE="PRI_ONLY"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Portsmouth Hospitals NHs Trust</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Queen Alexandra Hospital, Southwick Hill Road</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Portsmouth</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>PO6 3LY</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Rupert Hatch</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+44 1489779614</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>rupert.hatch@soeprocurement.nhs.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKJ31"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.porthosp.nhs.uk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="BODY_PUBLIC"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="HEALTH"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Talent Management App RFI</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>F11572</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="48000000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The Organisational Development team within Portsmouth Hospitals NHS Trust (PHT), through NHS South of England Procurement Services (SoEPS), is seeking information from companies able to provide an employee driven electronic talent management application.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="48000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="48210000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKJ31"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The Organisational Development team within Portsmouth Hospitals NHS Trust (PHT), through NHS South of England Procurement Services (SoEPS), is seeking information from companies able to provide an employee driven electronic talent management application. The solution purpose and functionality needs to primarily focus on transforming the way the Trust manages employee retention and development. With an ever increasing focus on the use of technology and social media, the Trust would like to implement an electronic talent management app. It is intended that this will be managed by the employee, in the same way as many current social media applications are, allowing them to develop and promote their own talent and skills on mobile and desktop devices. By using additional management driven functions, the Trust envisages the solution will support succession planning, difficult to recruit to positions and the introduction of new roles from within our existing skills capability. An example of the vision for the application would be to allow an individual to promote themselves, outlining their skills, experience and aspirations for future roles. It will give them the opportunity to flag that they are interested in specific projects and development opportunities and it will also capture personal skills, knowledge and experience, continuing professional development, certificates and personal desires for their future career development. The software would allow recruiting managers and Human Resources to proactively search for those staff with potential or a readiness to step up to the next position in their career pathway. The Trust is seeking your views for this requirement and asks a number of set questions below. Please try to respond to as many as you can as your views are valuable whether or not you have come across all of the aspects covered. This is a process designed to help the Trust to establish the type of talent management solutions available and secure a realistic budget provision. It is not the beginning of a Tender exercise — a further Tender advertisement will be issued at the appropriate time as required. Your feedback at this point will not have a bearing on any future Tender submissions you may wish to offer at a later date. You will not be disadvantaged if you choose not to respond to this RFI but it will be helpful to understand your views at this early stage, so you are encouraged to respond as fully as you can. By responding to this RFI the Trust will also be made aware of your interest in a future tender and can ensure that you are notified directly when this is issued.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>2018-03-15</DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The Organisational Development team within Portsmouth Hospitals NHS Trust (PHT), through NHS South of England Procurement Services (SoEPS), is seeking information from companies able to provide an employee driven electronic talent management application. The solution purpose and functionality needs to primarily focus on transforming the way the Trust manages employee retention and development. With an ever increasing focus on the use of technology and social media, the Trust would like to implement an electronic talent management app. It is intended that this will be managed by the employee, in the same way as many current social media applications are, allowing them to develop and promote their own talent and skills on mobile and desktop devices. By using additional management driven functions, the Trust envisages the solution will support succession planning, difficult to recruit to positions and the introduction of new roles from within our existing skills capability. An example of the vision for the application would be to allow an individual to promote themselves, outlining their skills, experience and aspirations for future roles. It will give them the opportunity to flag that they are interested in specific projects and development opportunities and it will also capture personal skills, knowledge and experience, continuing professional development, certificates and personal desires for their future career development. The software would allow recruiting managers and Human Resources to proactively search for those staff with potential or a readiness to step up to the next position in their career pathway. The Trust is seeking your views for this requirement and asks a number of set questions below. Please try to respond to as many as you can as your views are valuable whether or not you have come across all of the aspects covered. This is a process designed to help the Trust to establish the type of talent management solutions available and secure a realistic budget provision. It is not the beginning of a Tender exercise — a further Tender advertisement will be issued at the appropriate time as required. Your feedback at this point will not have a bearing on any future Tender submissions you may wish to offer at a later date. You will not be disadvantaged if you choose not to respond to this RFI but it will be helpful to understand your views at this early stage, so you are encouraged to respond as fully as you can. By responding to this RFI the Trust will also be made aware of your interest in a future tender and can ensure that you are notified directly when this is issued. To register your interest in this project and to obtain the request for information please visit the SoEPS In-Tend e-tendering portal at: https://in-tendhost.co.uk/soepsprovider.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-26</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F01_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
