<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="150094-2018" EDITION="2018068"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-138391-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20190326</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>68</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180407</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 068-150094</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150094-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="31710000">Electronic equipment</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="32412000">Communications network</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="32523000">Telecommunications facilities</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180326</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>AP301</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Teknisk bistand til konsekvensevaluering af EU civilsamfundsstøtte i de østlige partnerskabslande</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Technische Unterstützung für die Überwachung der Auswirkungen der Unterstützung der Zivilgesellschaft der EU in östlichen Partnerländern</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussels</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Technical Assistance on Impact Monitoring of EU Civil Society Support in Eastern Partnership Countries</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IEV - Asistencia técnica para llevar a cabo un seguimiento del impacto que el apoyo de la sociedad civil de la Unión Europea ha tenido en los países de la Asociación Oriental</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Tekninen tuki EU:n kansalaisyhteiskunnan tuen vaikutusten seurantaan itäisissä kumppanimaissa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Belgique</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IEV - Assistance technique portant sur la surveillance de l’impact sur la société civile de l’UE. Soutien aux pays de l’Est partenaires</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Βέλγιο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Τεχνική βοήθεια για την παρακολούθηση των επιπτώσεων της στήριξης της κοινωνίας των πολιτών της ΕΕ στις χώρες της ανατολικής εταιρικής σχέσης</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Belgio</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Assistenza tecnica sul monitoraggio dell’impatto del supporto della società civile UE nei paesi del partenariato orientale</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>België</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Technische bijstand inzake toezicht op het effect van de ondersteuning voor het maatschappelijk middenveld van de EU in landen van het Oostelijk partnerschap</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IEV - Assistência técnica para acompanhamento do impacto do apoio da UE à sociedade civil nos países da Parceria Oriental</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Europeiska grannskapsinstrumentet - Tekniskt stöd för konsekvensövervakning av EU-stöd till civilsamhällen i de östra partnerskapsländerna</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Belgie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Technická pomoc na hodnocení dopadu podpory občanské společnosti EU v partnerských zemí v rámci východního sousedství</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Tehniline abi ELi kodanikuühiskonna toetamise mõju seireks idapartnerluse riikides</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüsszel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Technikai segítségnyújtás az EU civil társadalomra vonatkozó támogatása hatásának nyomon követéséhez a keleti partnerség országaiban</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Briuselis</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Techninė pagalba ES pilietinės visuomenės paramos poveikio stebėsenai Rytų partnerystės šalyse</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Beļģija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brisele</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EKI - Tehniskā palīdzība par ES pilsoniskās sabiedrības atbalsta ietekmes pārraudzību Austrumu partnerības valstīs</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Belġju</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussell</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Għajnuna Teknika dwar il-Monitoraġġ tal-Impatt tal-Appoġġ tas-Soċjetà Ċivili tal-UE fil-Pajjiżi tas-Sħubija tal-Lvant</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruksela</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Pomoc techniczna w zakresie monitorowania wpływu wsparcia UE na rzecz rozwoju społeczeństwa obywatelskiego w krajach Partnerstwa Wschodniego</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Belgicko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Technická pomoc pri monitorovaní vplyvu podpory občianskej spoločnosti EÚ v krajinách Východného partnerstva</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselj</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Tehnična pomoč pri spremljanju vpliva podpore EU na področju civilne družbe v državah vzhodnega partnerstva</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Bheilg, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Cúnamh Teicniúil um Monatóireacht ar Thionchar na Tacaíochta ón AE don tSochaí Shibhialta sna Tíortha i gComhpháirtíocht an Oirthir</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бeлгия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Брюксел</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕИС - Техническа помощ за мониторинг на въздействието на подкрепата на ЕС за гражданското общество в държавите от Източното партньорство</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IEV - Asistență tehnică privind monitorizarea impactului sprijinului societății civile din UE în țările Parteneriatului Estic</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Tehnička pomoć za praćenje utjecaja potpore civilnog društva EU-a u zemljama Istočnog partnerstva</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den Europæiske Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">La Unión Europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan unioni</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Union européenne</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Η Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Unione europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europese Unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">União Europeia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska unionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Liit</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Az Európai Unió</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos Sąjunga</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Savienība</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">L-Unjoni Ewropea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Unia Europejska</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európska únia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska unija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An tAontas Eorpach</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейски съюз</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Uniunea Europeană</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska unija</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: ENI - Teknisk bistand til konsekvensevaluering af EU civilsamfundsstøtte i de østlige partnerskabslande</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sted: Østlige naboskabspartnere — Armenien, Aserbajdsjan, Georgien, Hviderusland, Moldova og Ukraine</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VEJLEDENDE FORHÅNDSMEDDELELSE OM TJENESTEYDELSER</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udbudsreference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Begrænset.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programtitel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Det europæiske naboskabsinstrument (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Civilsamfundsfacilitet for det østlige partnerskab 2017 — Regionale foranstaltninger (budgetpost — 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den Europæiske Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, repræsenteret ved Europa-Kommissionen, for og på vegne af partnerlandene, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontraktens art</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Honorarbaseret</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivelse af kontrakten</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Det overvågende tekniske bistandsprojekt er en del af det regionale civilsamfundsfacilitet for det østlige område 2017. Hovedformålet er at oprette et kvalitativt overvågnings- og konsekvensvurderingssystem for EU-finansierede civilsamfundsprojekter og at anvende dette system til at indsamle dokumentation for konsekvensen som EU's civilsamfundsstøtte inden for den østlige naboskabsregion har haft på fremme af nationale reformer og leveringen af konkrete fordele for borgerne i de østlige partnerskabslande. Denne information skal krydskontrolleres mod beretningsrapporter, der indsendes af civilsamfundsorganisationer, og give tilbagemelding til projektledere i Europa-kommissionen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vejledende budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Foreløbig dato for offentliggørelse af udbudsbekendtgørelsen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Maj 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Retsgrundlag (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 236/2014 af 11.3.2014 angående fælles regler og procedurer for gennemførelsen af instrumenterne til finansiering af Unionens optræden udadtil og Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 232/2014 af 11.3.2014 om oprettelse af et europæisk naboskabsinstrument.</P><P>Vær opmærksom på, at efter Det Forenede Kongeriges tilbagetrækning fra EU vil reglerne om adgang til EU's udbudsprocedurer for økonomiske aktører, der er etableret i tredjelande, gælde for ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige, alt afhængigt af resultatet af forhandlingerne. Hvis en sådan adgang ikke gives ved retlige bestemmelser, der er gældende på tidspunktet for kontrakttildelingen, vil ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige kunne blive udelukket fra udbudsproceduren.</P><P>(1) Angiv venligst enhver specificitet, der kan have indflydelse på reglerne for deltagelse (såsom geografiske eller tematiske eller lang-/kortsigtede).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Bemærkninger:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Der skal være en periode på mindst 30 kalenderdage mellem offentliggørelsen af denne forhåndsmeddelelse og offentliggørelsen af den tilsvarende udbudsbekendtgørelse.</P><P>Der kan ikke fremsendes ansøgninger eller anmodninger om oplysninger på nuværende tidspunkt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: ENI - Technische Unterstützung für die Überwachung der Auswirkungen der Unterstützung der Zivilgesellschaft der EU in östlichen Partnerländern</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Standort: Partnerländer der Östlichen Nachbarschaft — Armenien, Aserbaidschan, Belarus, Georgien, Moldau, Ukraine</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VORINFORMATION FÜR EINEN DIENSTLEISTUNGSAUFTRAG</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verfahren</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nichtoffen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmbezeichnung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europäisches Nachbarschaftsinstrument (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanzierung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fazilität für die Zivilgesellschaft der Östlichen Partnerschaft 2017 - Regionale Maßnahmen (Haushaltslinie - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Öffentlicher Auftraggeber</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertreten durch die Europäische Kommission, im Auftrag und für Rechnung der Partnerländer, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Art des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>auf Honorarbasis</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Das Projekt zur Überwachung der technischen Unterstützung ist Teil der 2017 regionalen Fazilität für die Zivilgesellschaft Ost. Das Hauptziel ist die Einrichtung eines hochwertigen Systems zur Bewertung der Überwachung und der Auswirkungen der von der EU finanzierten Projekte auf die Zivilgesellschaft und dessen Verwendung für die Sammlung von Nachweisen über die Auswirkungen, die diese Unterstützung der Zivilgesellschaft durch die EU in der östlichen Nachbarschaft auf die Förderung der nationalen Reformen und die Bereitstellung von konkreten Leistungen für Bürger in den östlichen Partnerländern hatte. Diese Informationen sollen mit erzählenden Berichten, die von Organisationen der Zivilgesellschaft eingereicht wurden, verglichen und an die Projektleiter in der Europäische Kommission weitergeleitet werden.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veranschlagtes Budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Geplanter Zeitpunkt für die Veröffentlichung der Auftragsbekanntmachung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mai 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsgrundlage (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verordnung (EU) Nr. 236/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Festlegung gemeinsamer Vorschriften und Verfahren für die Anwendung der Instrumente der Union für die Finanzierung des auswärtigen Handelns und Verordnung (EU) Nr. 232/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Schaffung eines Europäischen Nachbarschaftsinstruments</P><P>Es gilt zu beachten, dass für Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich nach dem Austritt des Vereinigten Königreichs aus der EU in Abhängigkeit des Ausgangs der Verhandlungen die Bestimmungen über den Zugang zu Beschaffungsverfahren der EU für in Drittländern ansässige Wirtschaftsteilnehmer gelten werden. Falls dieser Zugang gemäß den bei Auftragsvergabe geltenden Bestimmung nicht gewährt wird, können Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich vom Beschaffungsverfahren ausgeschlossen werden.</P><P>(1) Bitte geben Sie alle Besonderheiten an, die sich auf die Regeln für die Teilnahme auswirken könnten (z. B. geographisch oder thematisch oder kurz-/mittelfristig).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Hinweise:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Es muss ein Zeitraum von mindestens 30 Kalendertagen zwischen der Veröffentlichung der Vorinformation und der Veröffentlichung der entsprechenden Auftragsbekanntmachung liegen.</P><P>Derzeit ist von der Einreichung von Bewerbungen oder weiteren Anfragen abzusehen.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussels: ENI - Technical Assistance on Impact Monitoring of EU Civil Society Support in Eastern Partnership Countries</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Location: Eastern Neighbourhood Partners Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova and Ukraine</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SERVICE PRIOR INFORMATION NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publication reference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programme title</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financing</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eastern partnership civil society facility 2017 - Regional actions (budget line - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contracting Authority</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, represented by the European Commission on behalf of and for the account of partner countries, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussels</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature of contract</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fee-based</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contract description</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The monitoring technical assistance project is part of the 2017 Regional East Civil Society Facility. Its main objective is to set up a qualitative monitoring and impact assessment system of EU-funded civil society projects, and employ this system to collect evidence on the impact that EU civil society support in the Neighbourhood East has had on promoting national reforms and providing tangible benefits for citizens in Eastern Partnership countries. This information is meant to be crosschecked against narrative reports submitted by civil society organisations and feed back to relevant project managers in the European Commission.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicative budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intended timing of publication of the contract notice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>May 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal basis(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulation (EU) nº 236/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 laying down common rules and procedures for the implementation of the Union's instruments for financing external action and Regulation (EU) nº 232/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 establishing a European Neighbourhood Instrument.</P><P>Please be aware that after the United Kingdom's withdrawal from the EU, the rules of access to EU procurement procedures of economic operators established in third countries will apply to candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom depending on the outcome of negotiations. In case such access is not provided by legal provisions in force at the time of the contract award, candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom, could be rejected from the procurement procedure.</P><P>(1) Please state any specificity that might have an impact on rules on participation (such as geographic or thematic or long /short term).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarks:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>There must be a minimum period of 30 calendar days between the publication of this prior information notice and the publication of the corresponding contract notice.</P><P>No applications or requests for information should be sent at this stage.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselas: IEV - Asistencia técnica para llevar a cabo un seguimiento del impacto que el apoyo de la sociedad civil de la Unión Europea ha tenido en los países de la Asociación Oriental</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lugar: Países vecinos del Este — Armenia, Azerbaiyán, Bielorrusia, Georgia, Moldavia y Ucrania</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNCIO DE INFORMACIÓN PREVIA DE CONTRATO DE SERVICIOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referencia de publicación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedimiento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restringido</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Título del programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Instrumento Europeo de Vecindad (IEV)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fondo de la sociedad civil de la Asociación Oriental 2017 - Acciones regionales (línea presupuestaria 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de contratación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>La Unión Europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada por la Comisión Europea, en nombre y por cuenta de los países asociados, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naturaleza del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Honorarios</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El proyecto de asistencia técnica para el seguimiento forma parte del Fondo Regional Oriental de la Sociedad Civil de 2017. Su principal objetivo es establecer un sistema cualitativo de seguimiento y evaluación del impacto de los proyectos de la sociedad civil financiados por la UE, y utilizar este sistema para recabar pruebas sobre el impacto que ha tenido el apoyo de la sociedad civil de la UE en el Este, en materia de promoción de reformas nacionales y beneficios para los ciudadanos en los países de la Asociación Oriental. Esta información debe compararse con los informes narrativos presentados por las organizaciones de la sociedad civil y servir como retroalimentación en el trabajo realizado por los gerentes de proyectos pertinentes en la Comisión Europea.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Presupuesto indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha de publicación prevista del anuncio de licitación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mayo de 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fundamento jurídico (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Reglamento (UE) n.º 236/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establecen normas comunes y procedimientos de ejecución de los instrumentos de la Unión para la financiación de la acción exterior, y, Reglamento (UE) n.º 232/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establece un Instrumento Europeo de Vecindad.</P><P>Téngase en cuenta que tras la retirada del Reino Unido de la Unión Europea, las normas de acceso a los procedimientos de contratación pública de la Unión Europea de los operadores económicos establecidos en terceros países se aplicarán a candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido en función del resultado de las negociaciones. En caso de que las disposiciones jurídicas en vigor en el momento de la adjudicación del contrato no faciliten dicho acceso, los candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido podrían ser excluidos del procedimiento de contratación.</P><P>(1) Mencione cualquier aspecto específico que podría repercutir en las normas de participación (por ejemplo, aspectos geográficos, temáticos o de corto o largo plazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observaciones:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deben pasar al menos 30 días naturales desde la publicación de este anuncio de información previa hasta la publicación del correspondiente anuncio de licitación.</P><P>Por el momento, no deben enviarse solicitudes ni peticiones de información complementaria.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: ENI - Tekninen tuki EU:n kansalaisyhteiskunnan tuen vaikutusten seurantaan itäisissä kumppanimaissa</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sijainti: Itäisiin naapurimaihin kuuluvat kumppanuusmaat: Armenia, Azerbaidžan, Georgia, Moldova, Ukraina, Valko-Venäjä</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PALVELUJA KOSKEVA ENNAKKOTIETOILMOITUS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen viite</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menettely</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rajoitettu menettely.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ohjelman nimi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan naapuruusväline (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahoitus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Itäisten kumppanimaiden kansalaisyhteiskuntaa tukeva väline 2017 - alueelliset toimet (budjettikohta 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan unioni</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, jota edustaa Euroopan komissio kumppanimaiden puolesta ja tiliin, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuslaji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Palkkiopohjainen</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuksen kuvaus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Seurannan tekninen tukihanke on osa vuoden 2017 alueellista itäisen kansalaisyhteiskunnan välinettä. Sen päätavoitteena on perustaa laadukas seuranta- ja vaikutustenarviointijärjestelmä EU:n rahoittamille kansalaisyhteiskuntahankkeille ja käyttää tätä järjestelmää keräämään todisteita vaikutuksista, joita EU:n kansalaisyhteiskunnan tuella itäisissä naapurimaissa on ollut kansallisten uudistusten edistämisessä ja konkreettisten etujen tuomisessa itäisten naapurimaiden kansalaisille. Näitä tietoja on tarkoitus verrata kansalaisyhteiskunnan organisaatioiden toimittamiin kertomuksiin ja palauttaa ne Euroopan komission asiaankuuluville hankepäälliköille.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Alustava budjetti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintailmoituksen ennakoitu julkaisemisajankohta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Toukokuu 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oikeusperusta (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) n:o 236/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, unionin ulkoisen toiminnan rahoitusvälineiden täytäntöönpanoa koskevista yhteisistä säännöistä ja menettelyistä sekä Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) n:o 232/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, Euroopan naapuruusvälineen perustamisesta.</P><P>On syytä ottaa huomioon, että Yhdistyneen kuningaskunnan EU:sta irtautumisen jälkeen kolmansiin maihin sijoittautuneisiin talouden toimijoihin sovellettavia EU:n hankintamenettelyihin osallistumista koskevia sääntöjä sovelletaan Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin oleviin hakijoihin tai tarjoajiin neuvottelujen lopputuloksesta riippuen. Mikäli sopimuksenteon hetkellä voimassa olevassa lainsäädännössä ei anneta lupaa tällaiseen osallistumiseen, Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin olevat hakijat tai tarjoajat voidaan hylätä hankintamenettelystä.</P><P>(1) Mainitse seikat, joilla voisi olla vaikutusta osallistumissääntöihin (kuten esimerkiksi maantieteellinen tai aihepiirikohtainen tai pitkä/lyhyt kesto).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Huom.:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Tämän ennakkotietoilmoituksen ja vastaavan hankintailmoituksen julkaisemisen välillä on oltava vähintään 30 kalenteripäivää.</P><P>Hakemuksia tai lisätietopyyntöjä ei pidä lähettää tässä vaiheessa.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: IEV - Assistance technique portant sur la surveillance de l’impact sur la société civile de l’UE. Soutien aux pays de l’Est partenaires</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lieu d'exécution : Pays de l'Europe orientale bénéficiaires de la politique européenne de voisinage — Arménie, Azerbaïdjan, Biélorussie, Géorgie, Moldavie et Ukraine</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVIS DE PRÉ-INFORMATION RELATIF À UN MARCHÉ DE SERVICES</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Référence de la publication</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restreinte.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intitulé du programme</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Instrument européen de voisinage (IEV)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financement</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cadre 2017 pour la société civile des partenaires des pays de l’Est - Actions régionales (ligne budgétaire - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pouvoir adjudicateur</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Union européenne</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, représentée par la Commission européenne, agissant au nom et pour le compte des pays partenaires, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgique.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>À prix unitaires</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le projet d’assistance technique en matière de surveillance fait partie du Cadre régional 2017 sur la société civile des pays de l’Est. Son principal objectif consiste à mettre en place un système de surveillance qualitative et d’évaluation de l’impact des projets financés par l’UE concernant la société civile, et à employer ce système pour recueillir des éléments probants sur l’impact qu’à apporté l’aide de l’UE au bénéfice de la société civile dans les pays de l’Est voisins sur la promotion de réformes nationales, ainsi que sur le fait de fournir des avantages tangibles aux citoyens des pays partenaires d’ l’Est. Ces informations ont vocation à être vérifiées à la lecture des exposés narratifs soumis par les organisations de la société civile et des retours adressés aux gestionnaires de projets pertinents au sein de la Commission européenne.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Budget indicatif</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date prévue pour la publication de l'avis de marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mai 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base juridique (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Règlement (UE) no 236/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 fixant les règles communes et les procédures de mise en œuvre des instruments de l'Union pour le financement de l'action extérieure et règlement (UE) no 232/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 instituant un instrument européen de voisinage.</P><P>Il convient de noter qu'à la suite du retrait du Royaume-Uni de l'UE, les règles d'accès aux procédures de passations des marchés de l'UE pour les opérateurs économiques établis dans des pays tiers s'appliqueront aux candidats ou aux soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni, en fonction du résultat des négociations. Si les dispositions légales en vigueur au moment de l'attribution du contrat ne prévoient pas un tel accès, les candidats ou les soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni pourraient être exclus de la procédure d'appel d'offres.</P><P>(1) Veuillez indiquer toute spécificité susceptible d’avoir un impact sur les règles de participation (par exemple géographique ou thématique ou à cours/long terme).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarques :</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Un délai minimal de 30 jours calendaires doit être respecté entre la publication du présent avis de pré-information et celle de l'avis de marché correspondant.</P><P>Aucune candidature ni demande de renseignements complémentaires ne sera envoyée à ce stade de la procédure.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Βρυξέλλες: ENI - Τεχνική βοήθεια για την παρακολούθηση των επιπτώσεων της στήριξης της κοινωνίας των πολιτών της ΕΕ στις χώρες της ανατολικής εταιρικής σχέσης</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Τόπος: Εταίροι της ανατολικής γειτονίας — Αρμενία, Αζερμπαϊτζάν, Λευκορωσία, Γεωργία, Μολδαβία και Ουκρανία</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ΠΡΟΚΑΤΑΡΚΤΙΚΉ ΑΝΑΚΟΊΝΩΣΗ ΓΙΑ ΥΠΗΡΕΣΊΕΣ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αριθ. αναφοράς της δημοσίευσης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Διαδικασία</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κλειστή.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τίτλος προγράμματος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ευρωπαϊκός Μηχανισμός Γειτονίας (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Χρηματοδότηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Μηχανισμός της κοινωνίας των πολιτών της ανατολικής εταιρικής σχέσης 2017 - Περιφερειακές δράσεις (κονδύλιο προϋπολογισμού - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα αρχή</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Η Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, εκπροσωπούμενη από την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή, εκ μέρους και για λογαριασμό των χωρών εταίρων, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Βέλγιο.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τύπος σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Βάσει αμοιβής</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Περιγραφή της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Το έργο παρακολούθησης τεχνικής βοήθειας αποτελεί μέρος του μηχανισμού της περιφερειακής ανατολικής κοινωνίας των πολιτών για το 2017. Ο κύριος στόχος του είναι να δημιουργήσει ένα ποιοτικό σύστημα παρακολούθησης και αξιολόγησης των επιπτώσεων έργων της κοινωνίας των πολιτών που χρηματοδοτούνται από την ΕΕ και να χρησιμοποιήσει αυτό το σύστημα για τη συλλογή αποδεικτικών στοιχείων σχετικά με τον αντίκτυπο που είχε η υποστήριξη της κοινωνίας των πολιτών στις γειτονικές χώρες της Ανατολικής Ευρώπης στην προώθηση εθνικών μεταρρυθμίσεων και στην παροχή απτών οφελών για τους πολίτες στις χώρες της ανατολικής εταιρικής σχέσης. Οι πληροφορίες αυτές πρέπει να αποτελέσουν αντικείμενο διασταύρωσης με τις αφηγηματικές εκθέσεις που υποβάλλονται από οργανώσεις της κοινωνίας των πολιτών και να ανατροφοδοτούνται από τους σχετικούς διαχειριστές έργων στην Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ενδεικτικός προϋπολογισμός</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης της προκήρυξης σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Μάιος 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Νομική βάση (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 236/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τον καθορισμό κοινών κανόνων και διαδικασιών για την εφαρμογή των μηχανισμών χρηματοδότησης της εξωτερικής δράσης της Ένωσης και κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 232/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τη θέσπιση Ευρωπαϊκού Μηχανισμού Γειτονίας.</P><P>Πρέπει να ληφθεί υπόψη ότι μετά την αποχώρηση του Ηνωμένου Βασιλείου από την ΕΕ, οι κανόνες πρόσβασης σε διαδικασίες διαγωνισμού της ΕΕ για οικονομικούς φορείς που είναι εγκατεστημένοι σε τρίτες χώρες θα ισχύουν για τους υποψήφιους ή προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο ανάλογα με το αποτέλεσμα των διαπραγματεύσεων. Σε περίπτωση που η πρόσβαση αυτή δεν παρέχεται από νομικές διατάξεις που ίσχυαν κατά τον χρόνο ανάθεσης της σύμβασης, οι υποψήφιοι ή οι προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο θα μπορούσαν να απορριφθούν από τη διαδικασία διαγωνισμού.</P><P>(1) Παρακαλείσθε να αναφέρετε οποιαδήποτε ιδιαιτερότητα που ενδέχεται να έχει αντίκτυπο στους κανόνες συμμετοχής (όπως γεωγραφική ή θεματική ή σε μακροπρόθεσμο/βραχυπρόθεσμο επίπεδο).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Παρατηρήσεις:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Μεταξύ της δημοσίευσης της παρούσας προκαταρκτικής ανακοίνωσης και της δημοσίευσης της αντίστοιχης προκήρυξης σύμβασης θα πρέπει να παρεμβληθεί χρονικό διάστημα τουλάχιστον 30 ημερολογιακών ημερών.</P><P>Κατά το παρόν στάδιο δεν πρέπει να αποστέλλονται υποψηφιότητες ή αιτήματα για παροχή πληροφοριών.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: ENI - Assistenza tecnica sul monitoraggio dell’impatto del supporto della società civile UE nei paesi del partenariato orientale</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ubicazione: Partner del vicinato orientale, Armenia, Azerbaigian, Bielorussia, Georgia, Moldova e Ucraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVISO DI PREINFORMAZIONE RELATIVO A SERVIZI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Riferimento della pubblicazione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ristretta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titolo del programma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Strumento europeo di vicinato (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanziamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Strumento della società civile di partenariato orientale 2017 - Azioni regionali (linea di bilancio - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Amministrazione aggiudicatrice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unione europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, rappresentata dalla Commissione europea, in nome e per conto dei paesi partner, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgio.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contratto in base a tariffa</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il progetto di assistenza tecnica di monitoraggio da parte dello Strumento della società civile orientale regionale 2017. Il suo obiettivo principale consiste nel configurare un sistema di valutazione dell’impatto e monitoraggio dei progetti della società civile finanziati dall’UE e nell’impiego di tale sistema per raccogliere prove sull’impatto che il supporto della società civile UE nel vicinato orientale produce sulla promozione delle riforme nazionali e sulla fornitura di benefici tangibili per i cittadini nei paesi del partenariato orientale. Tali informazioni saranno destinate ad essere controllate rispetto a rapporti narrativi presentati dalle organizzazioni della società civile e restituite ai pertinenti responsabili della gestione dei progetti nella Commissione europea.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Importo indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data di pubblicazione prevista del bando di gara d’appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Maggio 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base giuridica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regolamento (UE) n. 236/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, recante norme e procedure comuni per l'attuazione degli strumenti per il finanziamento dell'azione esterna dell'Unione e regolamento (UE) n. 232/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che istituisce uno strumento europeo di vicinato.</P><P>Si prega di notare che, dopo il ritiro del Regno Unito dall'UE, ai candidati o agli offerenti provenienti dal Regno Unito verranno applicate le regole di accesso alle procedure di appalto dell'UE per gli operatori economici stabiliti in paesi terzi, in funzione dell'esito delle negoziazioni. Nel caso in cui tale accesso non sia previsto dalle disposizioni giuridiche vigenti al momento dell'aggiudicazione del contratto, i candidati o gli offerenti del Regno Unito potranno essere esclusi dalla procedura d’appalto.</P><P>(1) Indicare qualsiasi specificità che possa avere un impatto sulle regole di partecipazione (come ad esempio geografica o tematica o a lungo/breve termine).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Osservazioni:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Dovrà intercorrere un periodo minimo di 30 giorni di calendario tra la pubblicazione dell'avviso di preinformazione e quella del corrispondente bando di gara d’appalto.</P><P>Si prega di non inviare candidature o richieste di ulteriori informazioni durante questa fase della procedura.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussel: ENI - Technische bijstand inzake toezicht op het effect van de ondersteuning voor het maatschappelijk middenveld van de EU in landen van het Oostelijk partnerschap</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Locatie: Partners van de oostelijke nabuurschap — Armenië, Azerbeidzjan, Belarus, Georgië, Moldavië, Oekraïne</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VOORAANKONDIGING VOOR DIENSTEN</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referentie van de bekendmaking:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet-openbaar.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titel van het programma:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europees nabuurschapsinstrument (ENI).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiering:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Faciliteit voor het maatschappelijk middenveld in het Oostelijk partnerschap 2017 - Regionale acties (begrotingslijn - 22.040201).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europese Unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertegenwoordigd door de Europese Commissie, ten behoeve en voor rekening van de partnerlanden, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, België.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aard van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Opdracht op basis van vergoeding.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschrijving van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Het project voor technische bijstand inzake toezicht is onderdeel van de regionale oostelijke faciliteit voor het maatschappelijk middenveld 2017. De voornaamste doelstelling van deze opdracht is het opstellen van een kwalitatief toezichts- en effectbeoordelingssysteem van projecten voor het maatschappelijk middenveld die door de EU zijn gefinancierd en dit systeem in te zetten om bewijs te verzamelen over de impact die de ondersteuning van het maatschappelijk middenveld in het Oostelijk nabuurschap heeft gehad in het bevorderen van nationale hervormingen en het verstrekken van tastbare voordelen voor de burgers in landen van het Oostelijk partnerschap. Deze informatie moet worden vergeleken met verhalende verslagen die worden ingediend door organisaties van het maatschappelijke middenveld en moet worden teruggekoppeld naar relevante projectmanagers in de Europese Commissie.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicatieve begroting:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beoogde datum voor bekendmaking van de aankondiging van opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mei 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Juridische basis (1):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verordening (EU) nr. 236/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van gemeenschappelijke voorschriften en procedures voor de tenuitvoerlegging van de instrumenten van de Unie ter financiering van extern optreden en Verordening (EU) nr. 232/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot invoering van een Europees nabuurschapsinstrument.</P><P>Gelieve op te merken dat, na de uitstap van het Verenigd Koninkrijk uit de EU en afhankelijk van het resultaat van de onderhandelingen, de regels voor toegang tot EU-aanbestedingsprocedures voor ondernemers die gevestigd zijn in derde landen van toepassing zullen zijn op gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk. Indien dergelijke toegang niet is voorzien door de geldende wettelijke bepalingen op het tijdstip van de gunning van de opdracht, kunnen gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk worden geweigerd voor de aanbestedingsprocedure.</P><P>(1) Vermeld elke specificiteit die een effect kan hebben op de deelnameregels (zoals geografische of thematische specificiteiten op korte of lange termijn).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opmerkingen:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Er moet een minimumtermijn van 30 kalenderdagen liggen tussen de bekendmaking van deze vooraankondiging en de bekendmaking van de overeenstemmende aankondiging van een opdracht.</P><P>In dit stadium mogen er geen aanvragen of verzoeken om inlichtingen worden verzonden.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelas: IEV - Assistência técnica para acompanhamento do impacto do apoio da UE à sociedade civil nos países da Parceria Oriental</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Localização: parceiros da Vizinhança Oriental - Arménia, Azerbaijão, Bielorrússia, Geórgia, Moldávia, Ucrânia</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANÚNCIO DE PRÉ-INFORMAÇÃO DE SERVIÇOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referência da publicação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Limitado.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Título do programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Instrumento Europeu de Vizinhança (IEV)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Instalações da sociedade civil 2017 para a Parceria Oriental - ações regionais (rubrica orçamental - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>União Europeia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada pela Comissão Europeia, em nome e por conta dos países parceiros, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natureza do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Baseado em honorários</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O projeto de assistência técnica de acompanhamento enquadra-se no mecanismo regional de apoio à sociedade civil 2017 a favor da região leste. O seu principal objetivo consiste em implementar um sistema de acompanhamento qualitativo e avaliação do impacto dos projetos da sociedade civil financiados pela UE e aplicar este sistema para recolher provas relativas ao impacto que o apoio da UE à sociedade civil na Vizinhança Oriental teve na promoção de reformas nacionais e na estipulação de benefícios tangíveis a favor dos cidadãos dos países da Parceria Oriental. Estas informações devem ser comparadas contra os relatórios narrativos apresentados pelas organizações da sociedade civil e apresentadas aos gestores de projeto relevantes na Comissão Europeia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orçamento indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista para a publicação do anúncio de concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Maio de 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base jurídica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulamento (UE) n.º 236/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que estabelece regras e procedimentos comuns para a execução dos instrumentos da União de financiamento da ação externa e Regulamento (UE) n.º 232/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que cria um instrumento europeu de vizinhança.</P><P>Importa notar que após a saída do Reino Unido da UE, as regras de acesso aos procedimentos de adjudicação de contratos da UE de operadores económicos estabelecidos em países terceiros aplicar-se-ão aos candidatos ou proponentes provenientes do Reino Unido consoante o resultado das negociações. Caso tal acesso não esteja previsto pelas disposições legais em vigor, os candidatos ou proponentes do Reino Unido poderão ser excluídos do concurso.</P><P>(1) Indique qualquer especificidade que possa ter impacto sobre as regras de participação (tais como geográficas ou temáticas ou a longo/curto prazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observações:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deve ser respeitado um período mínimo de 30 dias de calendário entre a publicação do presente anúncio de informação prévia e a publicação do anúncio de concurso correspondente.</P><P>Não devem ser enviadas candidaturas ou efetuados pedidos de informação nesta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: Europeiska grannskapsinstrumentet - Tekniskt stöd för konsekvensövervakning av EU-stöd till civilsamhällen i de östra partnerskapsländerna</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Plats: Partnerländer inom det östra grannskapet – Armenien, Azerbajdzjan, Georgien, Moldavien och Ukraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÖRHANDSMEDDELANDE OM TJÄNSTER</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publikationsreferens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Förfarande</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Selektivt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programtitel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeiska grannskapsinstrumentet (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Facilitet för det civila samhället i de östra partnerskapsländerna 2017 – regionala åtgärder (budgetlinje – 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska unionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representerad av Europeiska kommissionen till förmån för och på uppdrag av partnerländerna, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Typ av kontrakt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Arvodesbaserat</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivning av kontraktet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Det övervakande tekniska stödprojektet utgör en del av 2017 års regionala facilitet för det civila samhället i de östra partnerskapsländerna. Dess huvudsyfte är att införa ett system för kvalitetsövervakning och konsekvensbedömning av EU-finansierade projekt för civila samhällen, och att använda detta system för att samla in bevis på effekterna som EU:s stöd för civilsamhällen i det östra grannskapet har haft i främjandet av nationella reformer och tillhandahållandet av konkreta fördelar för medborgare i de östra partnerskapsländerna. Denna information ska dubbelkontrolleras mot redogörande rapporter som tillhandahålls av civilsamhällesorganisationer och återkopplas till relevanta projektledare i Europeiska kommissionen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Preliminär budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerad tidsplan för publicering av meddelandet om upphandling</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Maj 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rättslig grund (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 236/2014 av den 11.3.2014 om fastställande av gemensamma bestämmelser och förfaranden för genomförandet av unionens instrument för finansiering av yttre åtgärder och Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 232/2014 av den 11.3.2014 om inrättande av ett europeiskt grannskapsinstrument.</P><P>Observera att efter Storbritanniens utträde ur EU kommer reglerna om tillgång till EU:s upphandlingsförfaranden för ekonomiska aktörer etablerade i tredjeländer att tillämpas på sökande eller anbudsgivare från Storbritannien beroende på resultatet av förhandlingarna. Om sådan tillgång inte tillhandahålls av rättsliga bestämmelser som gäller vid tidpunkten för kontraktstilldelningen kan sökande eller anbudsgivare från Storbritannien komma att uteslutas från upphandlingsförfarandet.</P><P>(1) Ange om det finns något som kan påverka reglerna för deltagande (såsom geografiskt läge, tema eller tid på lång/kort sikt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Anmärkningar:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>En period på minst 30 kalenderdagar ska förflyta mellan publiceringen av detta förhandsmeddelande och publiceringen av motsvarande meddelande om upphandling.</P><P>Inga ansökningar eller begäranden av information ska skickas i detta skede.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: ENI - Technická pomoc na hodnocení dopadu podpory občanské společnosti EU v partnerských zemí v rámci východního sousedství</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokalita: Partnerské země v rámci východního sousedství – Arménie, Ázerbájdžán, Bělorusko, Gruzie, Moldavsko a Ukrajina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>OZNÁMENÍ PŘEDBĚŽNÝCH INFORMACÍ O SLUŽBÁCH</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenční číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užší.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Název programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Evropský nástroj sousedství (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financování</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regionální opatření v rámci nástroje občanské společnosti na podporu partnerských zemí východního sousedství v roce 2017 – (rozpočtová linie – 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veřejný zadavatel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastoupená Evropskou komisí jménem a ve prospěch partnerských zemí, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgie.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Povaha zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Placená</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popis zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt na monitorování technické pomoci je součástí nástroje občanské společnosti na podporu partnerských zemí východního sousedství v roce 2017. Jeho hlavním cílem je vytvořit kvalitativní systém na hodnocení dopadu projektů občanské společnosti financovaných EU a zajistit, aby sytém shromažďoval důkazy o dopadech, které má podpora občanské společnosti EU ve východním sousedství na podporu národních reforem a poskytování hmatatelných přínosů pro občany ve státech východního sousedství. Tato informace se musí ověřit s popisnými zprávami podanými organizacemi občanské společnosti a zpětnou vazbou příslušných projektových manažerů Evropské komise.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Směrný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zamýšlené datum zveřejnění oznámení o zakázce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>květen 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právní základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 236/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se stanoví společná pravidla a postupy pro provádění nástrojů Unie pro financování vnější činnosti, a nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 232/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se zřizuje evropský nástroj sousedství.</P><P>Připomínáme, že po vystoupení Spojeného království z EU se na zájemce nebo uchazeče ze Spojeného království, v závislosti od výsledku jednání, budou uplatňovat pravidla přístupu k postupům výběrového řízení EU ze strany hospodářských subjektů se sídlem ve třetích zemích. V případě, že takový přístup není zabezpečen právními předpisy platnými v době zadání zakázky, mohli by být uchazeči nebo účastníci ze Spojeného království vyloučeni z výběrového řízení.</P><P>(1) Uveďte prosím jakoukoli specifičnost, která by mohla mít dopad na pravidla účasti (např. zeměpisnou, tematickou nebo dlouhodobou/krátkodobou).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Mezi zveřejněním těchto předběžných informací o zakázce a zveřejněním odpovídajícího oznámení o zakázce musí uplynout minimálně 30 kalendářních dnů.</P><P>V této fázi nesmí být zasílány žádné přihlášky ani žádosti o informace.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: ENI - Tehniline abi ELi kodanikuühiskonna toetamise mõju seireks idapartnerluse riikides</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Asukoht: naabruspoliitika idapoolsed partnerriigid – Armeenia, Aserbaidžaan, Valgevene, Gruusia, Moldova ja Ukraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>TEENUSTE EELTEADE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaldamise viide</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menetlus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Piiratud.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmi pealkiri</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopa naabruspoliitika rahastamisvahend (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahastamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Idapartnerluse kodanikuühiskonna rahastamisvahend 2017 – piirkondlikud meetmed (eelarverida –22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaliku sektori hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Liit</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, keda esindab Euroopa Komisjon, partnerriikide eest ja nimel, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu laad</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tasupõhine</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Seire tehnilise abi projekt on osa 2017. aasta idapiirkonna kodanikuühiskonna rahastamisvahendist. Selle peamine eesmärk on luua ELi rahastatud kodanikuühiskonna projektide kvalitatiivne seire- ja mõjuhindamise süsteem ning kasutada seda süsteemi mõju kohta tõendusmaterjali kogumiseks, mida ELi kodanikuühiskonna toetamine idapartnerluse riikides on avaldanud riiklike reformide edendamisele ja idapartnerluse riikide kodanikele käegakatsutava kasu andmisele. See teave tuleb üle kontrollida kodanikuühiskonna organisatsioonide poolt esitatud jutustavatest aruannetest lähtuvalt ning anda tagasisidet asjaomastele projektijuhtidele Euroopa Komisjonis.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Soovituslik eelarve</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hanketeate avaldamise esialgne aeg</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mai 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Õiguslik alus (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014. aasta määrus (EL) nr 236/2014, milles sätestatakse liidu välistegevuse rahastamisvahendite rakendamise ühiseeskirjad ja menetlused, ning Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014. aasta määrus (EL) nr 232/2014, millega luuakse Euroopa naabruspoliitika rahastamisvahend.</P><P>Võtke teadmiseks, et olenevalt läbirääkimiste tulemustest kohaldatakse pärast Ühendkuningriigi EList lahkumist Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaatidele või pakkujatele kolmandates riikides asutatud ettevõtjatele kehtivaid ELi hankemenetlustele juurepääsu käsitlevaid eeskirju. Juhul, kui selline juurdepääs ei ole tagatud lepingu sõlmimise ajal kehtivate õiguslike sätete kaudu, võidakse Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaadid või pakkujad hankemenetlusest kõrvale jätta.</P><P>(1) Märkige kõik erijooned, mis võivad mõjutada osalemise tingimusi (näiteks geograafilised erijooned, valdkond, lühike või pikk tähtaeg).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Märkused</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Eelteate ja vastava hanketeate avaldamise vahele peab jääma vähemalt 30 kalendripäeva.</P><P>Taotlusi ega teabenõudeid ei või selles etapis veel saata.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüsszel: ENI - Technikai segítségnyújtás az EU civil társadalomra vonatkozó támogatása hatásának nyomon követéséhez a keleti partnerség országaiban</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Helyszín: Keleti szomszédsági partnerek: Azerbajdzsán, Fehéroroszország, Grúzia, Moldova, Örményország, Ukrajna</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SZOLGÁLTATÁSRA IRÁNYULÓ ELŐZETES ÖSSZESÍTETT HIRDETMÉNY</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A közzététel hivatkozási száma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Eljárás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Meghívásos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A program címe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Európai Szomszédsági Támogatási Eszköz (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanszírozás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A keleti partnerségi civil társadalmi eszköz 2017, regionális intézkedések (költségvetési tétel - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Az Európai Unió</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, amelyet az Európai Bizottság képvisel, a partnerországok nevében és megbízásából, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüsszel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés típusa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Díjalapú</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés meghatározása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A nyomon követésre irányuló technikai segítségnyújtási projekt a 2017. évi regionális keleti civil társadalmi eszköz része. A projekt fő célkitűzése az EU által finanszírozott civil társadalmi projektek kvalitatív ellenőrzési és hatásvizsgálati rendszerének felállítása és a rendszer segítségével bizonyítékok gyűjtése arra vonatkozóan, hogy az EU civil társadalomra vonatkozó támogatása a keleti szomszédságban milyen hatással volt a nemzeti reformok elősegítésére, és milyen konkrét hasznot hozott a keleti partnerség országainak állampolgárai számára. Az így kapott információkat össze fogják vetni a civil társadalmi szervezetek által benyújtott szöveges jelentésekkel, és visszajelzésként el fogják juttatni az Európai Bizottság illetékes projektvezetőihez.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Várható költségvetés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlati felhívás közzétételének tervezett időpontja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018. május</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Jogalap (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A külső tevékenységek finanszírozására vonatkozó uniós eszközök végrehajtására vonatkozó közös szabályok és eljárások megállapításáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű 236/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet, valamint az Európai Szomszédsági és Partnerségi Támogatási Eszköz létrehozásáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű 232/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet.</P><P>Figyelembe kell venni, hogy az Egyesült Királyságnak az EU-ból való kilépése után az Egyesült Királyságból származó jelentkezőkre vagy ajánlattevőkre – a tárgyalások kimenetelétől függően – az EU közbeszerzési eljárásaihoz való hozzáférés tekintetében a harmadik országok gazdasági szereplői számára érvényes szabályok vonatkoznak. Amennyiben az ilyen eljárásokban való részvételről nem rendelkezik a szerződés odaítélésének időpontjában hatályban lévő jogszabály, az Egyesült Királyságban székhellyel rendelkező jelentkezőket, illetve ajánlattevőket kizárhatják a közbeszerzési eljárásból.</P><P>(1) Kérjük, jelezzen bármely olyan sajátosságot, amely hatással lehet a részvételi szabályokra (például földrajzi, tematikai vagy hosszú/rövid távú sajátosság).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Megjegyzések:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Legalább 30 naptári napnak kell eltelnie a jelen előzetes tájékoztató hirdetmény megjelenése és a vonatkozó ajánlati felhívás közzététele között.</P><P>Ezen időszak alatt jelentkezések benyújtásának, illetve információkérésnek nincs helye.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Briuselis: ENI - Techninė pagalba ES pilietinės visuomenės paramos poveikio stebėsenai Rytų partnerystės šalyse</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vieta: Rytų partnerystės šalys: Armėnija, Azerbaidžanas, Baltarusija, Gruzija, Moldova ir Ukraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IŠANKSTINIS INFORMACINIS SKELBIMAS APIE PASLAUGŲ PIRKIMĄ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nuoroda į publikaciją</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ribotas konkursas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programos pavadinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europos kaimynystės priemonė (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansavimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2017 m. Rytų partnerystės pilietinės visuomenės priemonė. Regioniniai veiksmai (biudžeto eilutė 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Perkančioji organizacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos Sąjunga</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, atstovaujama Europos Komisijos, šalių partnerių vardu ir jų naudai, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Briuselis</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties pobūdis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mokama</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties apibūdinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Techninės pagalbos stebėsenos projektas yra 2017 m. Regioninės Rytų pilietinės visuomenės priemonės dalis. Pagrindinis jo tikslas – parengti kokybišką ES finansuojamų pilietinės visuomenės projektų stebėsenos ir poveikio vertinimo sistemą, taip pat panaudoti šią sistemą įrodymams apie ES pilietinės visuomenės paramos Rytų kaimynystės šalims poveikį nacionalinių reformų skatinimui ir apčiuopiamos naudos Rytų partnerystės šalių piliečiams teikimui rinkti. Ši informacija turės būti palyginta su pilietinės visuomenės organizacijų pateiktomis aprašomosiomis ataskaitomis ir grįžtamuoju ryšiu atitinkamiems Europos Komisijos projekto vadovams.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatytas biudžetas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatoma skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo data</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018 m. gegužės mėn.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teisinis pagrindas (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 236/2014, kuriuo nustatomos bendros Sąjungos išorės veiksmų finansavimo priemonių įgyvendinimo taisyklės ir procedūros, ir 11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 232/2014, kuriuo sukuriama Europos kaimynystės priemonė.</P><P>Prašome atkreipti dėmesį, kad Jungtinei Karalystei pasitraukus iš ES, ekonominės veiklos vykdytojų, įsikūrusių trečiosiose šalyse, prieigos prie ES pirkimo procedūrų taisyklės bus taikomos kandidatams ar konkurso dalyviams iš Jungtinės Karalystės, priklausomai nuo derybų rezultato. Jeigu tokia prieiga nebus suteikta galiojančiomis teisinėmis nuostatomis, kandidatai arba konkurso dalyviai iš Jungtinės Karalystės gali būti pašalinti iš pirkimo procedūros.</P><P>(1) Nurodykite bet kokias aplinkybes, galinčias turėti įtakos dalyvavimo taisyklėms (pvz., geografines ar temines, ilgalaikes ar trumpalaikes).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Pastabos:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Nuo šio išankstinio informacinio skelbimo publikavimo iki atitinkamo skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo turi praeiti mažiausiai 30 kalendorinių dienų.</P><P>Šiame etape negalima siųsti paraiškų ar kreiptis dėl informacijos.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brisele: EKI - Tehniskā palīdzība par ES pilsoniskās sabiedrības atbalsta ietekmes pārraudzību Austrumu partnerības valstīs</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vieta: austrumu kaimiņreģiona partneri – Armēnija, Azerbaidžāna, Baltkrievija, Gruzija, Moldova un Ukraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IEPRIEKŠĒJS INFORMATĪVS PAZIŅOJUMS PAR PAKALPOJUMU LĪGUMU</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsauce uz publikāciju</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Slēgta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmas nosaukums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eiropas kaimiņattiecību instruments (EKI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansējums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Austrumu partnerības pilsoniskās sabiedrības instruments 2017. gadam – reģionālie pasākumi (budžeta pozīcija 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Savienība</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ko partnervalstu vārdā un interesēs pārstāv Eiropas Komisija, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brisele</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Beļģija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma veids</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Līgums, kura pamatā ir samaksa par pakalpojumiem</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pārraudzības tehniskās palīdzības projekts ir daļa no Austrumu partnerības pilsoniskās sabiedrības instrumenta 2017. gadam. Tā galvenais mērķis ir izveidot kvalitatīvu ES finansēto pilsoniskās sabiedrības projektu pārraudzības un ietekmes novērtēšanas sistēmu un izmantot šo sistēmu pierādījumu apkopošanai par ES pilsoniskās sabiedrības atbalsta austrumu kaimiņreģionā ietekmi uz valsts reformu sekmēšanu un jūtamu labumu sniegšanu Austrumu partnerības valstu iedzīvotājiem. Šī informācija ir jāsalīdzina ar pilsoniskās sabiedrības organizāciju iesniegtajiem skaidrojošajiem ziņojumiem un jānodod attiecīgajiem Eiropas Komisijas projektu vadītājiem.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Provizoriskais budžets</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paziņojuma par līgumu paredzamais publicēšanas datums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018. gada maijs</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tiesiskais pamats (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 236/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko paredz kopīgus noteikumus un procedūras, lai īstenotu Savienības instrumentus ārējās darbības finansēšanai, un Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 232/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko izveido Eiropas kaimiņattiecību instrumentu.</P><P>Lūdzam ņemt vērā, ka pēc Apvienotās Karalistes izstāšanās no ES uz kandidātiem un pretendentiem no Apvienotās Karalistes atkarībā no sarunu iznākuma attieksies noteikumi par trešo valstu uzņēmēju tiesībām piedalīties ES iepirkuma procedūrās. Ja līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas brīdī spēkā esošajās tiesību normās šāda piekļuve nebūs paredzēta, kandidāti vai pretendenti no Apvienotās Karalistes var tikt izslēgti no iepirkuma procedūras.</P><P>(1) Lūdzam norādīt visus specifiskos iemeslus (piemēram, ģeogrāfiskus, tematiskus, īstermiņa vai ilgtermiņa), kas var ietekmēt dalības noteikumus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Piezīmes</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Starp šā iepriekšējā informatīvā paziņojuma un attiecīgā paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datumiem jāpaiet vismaz 30 kalendārajām dienām.</P><P>Šajā posmā nekādus pieteikumus vai informācijas pieprasījumus nesūtīt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussell: ENI - Għajnuna Teknika dwar il-Monitoraġġ tal-Impatt tal-Appoġġ tas-Soċjetà Ċivili tal-UE fil-Pajjiżi tas-Sħubija tal-Lvant</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Il-post: L-Imsieħba tal-Viċinat tal-Lvant l-Armenja, l-Ażerbajġan, il-Belarussja, il-Georgia, il-Moldova u l-Ukrajna</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVIŻ TA' TAGĦRIF MINN QABEL DWAR SERVIZZ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-proċedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-titlu tal-programm</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Strument Ewropew tal-Viċinat (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-iffinanzjar</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-faċilità tas-soċjetà ċivili tas-sħubija tal-Lvant għall-2017 - Azzjonijiet reġjonali (linja tal-baġit - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>L-Unjoni Ewropea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, irrappreżentata mill-Kummissjoni Ewropea, għall-pajjiżi msieħba u f'isimhom, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussell</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Belġju.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-tip ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bil-ħlas ta' miżata</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-deskrizzjoni tal-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-proġett tal-għajnuna teknika ta' monitoraġġ huwa parti mill-Faċilità tas-Soċjetà Ċivili Reġjonali tal-Lvant għall-2017. L-għan prinċipali tiegħu huwa li jistabbilixxi monitoraġġ kwalitattiv u sistema ta' valutazzjoni tal-impatt ta' proġetti tas-soċjetà ċivili ffinanzjati mill-UE, u li juża din is-sistema biex jiġbor l-evidenza dwar l-impatt li l-appoġġ tas-soċjetà ċivili tal-UE fil-Viċinat tal-Lvant kellu fuq il-promozzjoni ta' riformi nazzjonali u biex jipprovdi benefiċċji tanġibbli għaċ-ċittadini fil-pajjiżi tas-Sħubija tal-Lvant. Din l-informazzjoni għandha tiġi vverifikata kontra rapporti narrattivi ppreżentati mill-organizzazzjonijiet tas-soċjetà ċivili u tingħata lura lill-maniġers tal-proġetti rilevanti fil-Kummissjoni Ewropea.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-baġit indikattiv</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Iż-żmien maħsub għall-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mejju tal-2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-bażi legali (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 236/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi regoli u proċeduri komuni għall-implimentazzjoni tal-istrumenti tal-Unjoni għall-finanzjament tal-azzjoni esterna u r-Regolament (UE) Nru 232/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi Strument Ewropew tal-Viċinat.</P><P>Jekk jogħġbok kun af li wara l-irtirar tar-Renju Unit mill-UE, ir-regoli tal-aċċess għall-proċeduri ta' ksib tal-UE ta' operaturi ekonomiċi mwaqqfa f'pajjiżi terzi se japplikaw għall-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit skont ir-riżultat tan-negozjati. F'każ li tali aċċess mhux ipprovdut minn dispożizzjonijiet legali fis-seħħ fil-ħin tal-għoti tal-kuntratt, il-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit jistgħu jiġu mwarrba mill-proċedura tal-ksib.</P><P>(1) Jekk jogħġbok niżżel kwalunkwe speċifiċità li jista' jkollha impatt fuq ir-regoli għas-sehem (bħal dik ġeografika jew tematika jew fuq żmien qasir jew fit-tul).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Kummenti:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Irid ikun hemm perijodu minimu ta' 30 jum kalendarju bejn il-pubblikazzjoni ta' dan l-avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel u l-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt li għandu x'jaqsam miegħu.</P><P>M'għandhomx jintbagħtu applikazzjonijiet jew talbiet għal tagħrif f'dan l-istadju.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruksela: ENI - Pomoc techniczna w zakresie monitorowania wpływu wsparcia UE na rzecz rozwoju społeczeństwa obywatelskiego w krajach Partnerstwa Wschodniego</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokalizacja: kraje partnerskie wschodniego sąsiedztwa – Armenia, Azerbejdżan, Białoruś, Gruzja, Mołdawia, Ukraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>WSTĘPNE OGŁOSZENIE INFORMACYJNE DOTYCZĄCE ZAMÓWIENIA NA USŁUGI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numer referencyjny publikacji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograniczona.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nazwa programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europejski Instrument Sąsiedztwa (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansowanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Instrument wspierania rozwoju społeczeństwa obywatelskiego w ramach Partnerstwa Wschodniego na 2017 r. - Działania regionalne (linia budżetowa - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Instytucja zamawiająca</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unia Europejska</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentowana przez Komisję Europejską, w imieniu i na rzecz krajów partnerskich, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruksela</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rodzaj zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Według stawek jednostkowych</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt pomocy technicznej w zakresie monitorowania jest częścią regionalnego instrumentu wspierania rozwoju społeczeństwa obywatelskiego na wschodzie w 2017 r. Jego głównym celem jest ustanowienie systemu jakościowego do celów monitorowania i oceny wpływu projektów społeczeństwa obywatelskiego finansowanych przez UE oraz wykorzystanie tego systemu do gromadzenia dowodów dotyczących wpływu, jaki wsparcie społeczeństwa obywatelskiego UE w krajach sąsiedztwa wschodniego miało na promowanie reform krajowych i zapewnianie wymiernych korzyści obywatelom krajów Partnerstwa Wschodniego. Informacje te mają być następnie porównywane ze sprawozdaniami opisowymi składanymi przez organizacje społeczeństwa obywatelskiego i informacjami przekazywanymi odpowiednim kierownikom projektów w Komisji Europejskiej.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orientacyjny budżet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planowana data publikacji ogłoszenia o zamówieniu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Maj 2018 r.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Podstawa prawna (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 236/2014 z dnia 11.3.2014 ustanawiające wspólne zasady i procedury wdrażania unijnych instrumentów na rzecz finansowania działań zewnętrznych i rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 232/2014 z dnia 11.3.2014 ustanawiające Europejski Instrument Sąsiedztwa.</P><P>Należy mieć świadomość, że po wystąpieniu Zjednoczonego Królestwa z UE brytyjscy kandydaci i oferenci będą podlegać zasadom dostępu do unijnych procedur udzielania zamówień podmiotom gospodarczym w państwach trzecich w zależności od wyniku negocjacji. W sytuacji gdy przepisy prawa obowiązujące w chwili udzielenia zamówienia nie będą przewidywać takiego dostępu, kandydaci lub oferenci ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa mogą zostać wykluczeni z postępowania o udzielenie zamówienia.</P><P>(1) Uprasza się o wskazanie wszelkich okoliczności, które mogą mieć wpływ na warunki udziału (takie jak uwarunkowania geograficzne, tematyczne lub kwestie długo lub krótkoterminowe).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Uwagi:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Między publikacją niniejszego wstępnego ogłoszenia informacyjnego a publikacją odpowiedniego ogłoszenia o zamówieniu musi upłynąć co najmniej 30 dni kalendarzowych.</P><P>Na tym etapie nie należy przesyłać wniosków ani zapytań o informacje.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: ENI - Technická pomoc pri monitorovaní vplyvu podpory občianskej spoločnosti EÚ v krajinách Východného partnerstva</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Miesto: partneri v rámci Východného partnerstva: Arménsko, Azerbajdžan, Bielorusko, Gruzínsko, Moldavsko a Ukrajina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDBEŽNÉ OZNÁMENIE O OBSTARÁVANÍ SLUŽIEB</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčné číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Konanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užšia súťaž.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Názov programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nástroj európskeho susedstva (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zdroj financovania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nástroj občianskej spoločnosti Východné partnerstvo 2017 – regionálne činnosti (rozpočtová položka – 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verejný obstarávateľ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európska únia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastúpená Európskou komisiou v mene a záujme partnerských krajín, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgicko.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Charakter verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Odplatné</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt technickej pomoci pri monitorovaní je súčasťou nástroja regionálnej východnej občianskej spoločnosti v roku 2017. Jeho hlavným cieľom je vytvoriť kvalitatívny systém monitorovania a hodnotenia vplyvu projektov občianskej spoločnosti financovaných EÚ a využiť tento systém na zhromažďovanie dôkazov o vplyve, ktorý mala podpora občianskej spoločnosti EÚ v rámci Východného susedstva na propagáciu národných reforiem, a poskytovanie konkrétnych prínosov pre občanov v krajinách Východného partnerstva. Tieto informácie sa majú porovnávať s výpovednými správami, ktoré predkladajú organizácie občianskej spoločnosti, a majú poskytovať spätnú väzbu príslušným projektovým manažérom v Európskej komisii.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predbežný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plánovaný dátum zverejnenia oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>máj 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právny základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 236/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovujú spoločné pravidlá a postupy pre vykonávanie nástrojov Únie na financovanie vonkajšej činnosti, a nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 232/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj európskeho susedstva.</P><P>Pripomíname, že po vystúpení Spojeného kráľovstva z EÚ sa na záujemcov alebo uchádzačov zo Spojeného kráľovstva, v závislosti od výsledku rokovaní, budú uplatňovať pravidlá prístupu k postupom obstarávania EÚ zo strany hospodárskych subjektov so sídlom v tretích krajinách. V prípade, že takýto prístup sa nezabezpečí ustanoveniami platnými v čase pridelenia zákazky, záujemcovia alebo uchádzači zo Spojeného kráľovstva by mohli byť vylúčení z obstarávacieho konania.</P><P>(1) Uveďte akékoľvek špecifiká, ktoré by mohli mať vplyv na pravidlá účasti (napríklad geografické alebo tematické, dlhodobé alebo krátkodobé).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Medzi uverejnením predbežného oznámenia a uverejnením príslušného oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania musí uplynúť minimálne 30 kalendárnych dní.</P><P>V tomto období sa nemajú zasielať žiadne prihlášky ani žiadosti o informácie.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselj: ENI - Tehnična pomoč pri spremljanju vpliva podpore EU na področju civilne družbe v državah vzhodnega partnerstva</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokacija: Partnerske države vzhodnega sosedstva – Armenija, Azerbajdžan, Belorusija, Gruzija, Moldavija in Ukrajina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDHODNO INFORMATIVNO OBVESTILO O NAROČILU STORITEV</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčna številka dokumenta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postopek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Omejeni.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Evropski instrument sosedstva (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sklad za civilno družbo v vzhodnem sosedstvu 2017 – regionalni ukrepi (proračunska postavka 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ki jo zastopa Evropska komisija, v imenu in za račun partnerskih držav, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselj</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vrsta naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Na podlagi plačila</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt tehnične pomoči na področju spremljanja je del regionalnih ukrepov v okviru sklada za civilno družbo v vzhodnem sosedstvu 2017. Njegov glavni cilj je vzpostaviti kakovosten sistem za spremljanje in oceno učinka projektov civilne družbe, ki jih financira EU, ter uporabiti ta sistem za zbiranje dokazov o vplivu, ki ga je imela podpora EU na področju civilne družbe v vzhodnem sosedstvu na spodbujanje nacionalnih reform in zagotavljanje oprijemljivih koristi za državljane v državah vzhodnega partnerstva. Te informacije naj bi bile navzkrižno preverjene z opisnimi poročili, ki jih predložijo organizacije civilne družbe, in v obliki povratnih informacij zagotovljene ustreznim vodjem projektov v Evropski komisiji.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Okvirni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predvideni datum objave obvestila o naročilu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Maj 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravna podlaga (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uredba (EU) št. 236/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o določitvi skupnih pravil in postopkov za izvajanje instrumentov Unije za financiranje zunanjega delovanja in Uredba (EU) št. 232/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3. 2014 o vzpostavitvi evropskega instrumenta sosedstva.</P><P>Upoštevajte, da se bodo po izstopu Združenega kraljestva iz EU pravila za dostop do razpisnih postopkov EU s strani gospodarskih subjektov, ustanovljenih v tretjih državah, za kandidate ali ponudnike iz Združenega kraljestva uporabljala v skladu z rezultati pogajanj. V primeru, da v času oddaje naročila veljavne pravne določbe ne zagotavljajo tovrstnega dostopa, se lahko kandidatom ali ponudnikom iz Združenega kraljestva sodelovanje v razpisnem postopku zavrne.</P><P>(1) Navedite kakršno koli posebnost, ki bi lahko vplivala na pravila o sodelovanju (na primer geografsko ali tematsko, dolgo-/kratkoročno).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opombe:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Med objavo tega predhodnega informativnega obvestila in objavo ustreznega obvestila o naročilu mora preteči vsaj 30 koledarskih dni.</P><P>V tej fazi ne pošiljajte prijav ali zahtevkov za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-An Bhruiséil: ENI - Cúnamh Teicniúil um Monatóireacht ar Thionchar na Tacaíochta ón AE don tSochaí Shibhialta sna Tíortha i gComhpháirtíocht an Oirthir</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Láthair: Comhpháirtithe Chomharsanacht an Oirthir an Airméin, an Asarbaiseáin, an Bhealarúis, an Mholdóiv, an tSeoirsia agus an Úcráin</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÓGRA RÉAMHAISNÉISE SEIRBHÍSE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nós imeachta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Teoranta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teideal an chláir</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>An Ionstraim Eorpach um Chomharsanacht (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Maoiniú</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Saoráid Chomharsanacht an Oirthir um an tsochaí shibhialta 2017 - Gníomhartha réigiúnacha (líne bhuiséid - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás Conarthach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An tAontas Eorpach</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, arna ionadú ag an gCoimisiún Eorpach, ar son agus chun cuntais na dtíortha is comhpháirtithe, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>an Bhruiséil</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Bheilg.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cineál an chonartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bunaithe ar tháille</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ar an gconradh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Is cuid é an tionscadal um monatóireacht an chúnaimh theicniúil de Shaoráid Réigiúnach an Oirthir 2017 don tSochaí Shibhialta. Is é an príomhchuspóir leis córas measúnaithe monatóireachta agus tionchair cháilíochtúil a bhunú de thionscadail sa tsochaí shibhialta arna gcistiú ag an AE, agus an córas sin a úsáid chun fianaise a bhailiú faoi thionchar na tacaíochta ag an AE don tsochaí shibhialta i gComharsanacht an Oirthir chun athchóirithe náisiúnta a chur chun cinn agus chun tairbhí inláimhsithe a sholáthar do shaoránaigh sna tíortha i gComhpháirtíocht an Oirthir. Caithfear an fhaisnéis a chroscheadú i gcoinne tuairiscí scéalaíocha ó eagrais na sochaí sibhialta agus aiseolas a thabhairt do bhainisteoirí tionscadail ábhartha sa Choimisiún Eorpach.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buiséad táscach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>An sprioc atá beartaithe d'fhoilsiú an fhógra conartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bealtaine 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bunús dlí (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 236/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 lena leagtar síos na rialacha agus na nósanna imeachta coiteanna le haghaidh ionstraimí an Aontais a chur chun feidhme chun an ghníomhaíocht sheachtrach a mhaoiniú; agus Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 232/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 lena mbunaítear Ionstraim Eorpach um Chomharsanacht.</P><P>Tabhair faoi deara go gcuirfear na rialacha um rochtain ar nósanna imeachta soláthair an AE ag oibreoirí eacnamaíocha atá bunaithe i dtríú tíortha i bhfeidhm ar iarrthóirí nó ar thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe tar éis di tarraingt siar ón AE, ag brath ar thorthaí na hidirbheartaíochta. Sa chás nach gcuirfear a leithéid de rochtain ar fáil trí fhorálacha dlíthiúla a bheidh i bhfeidhm nuair a dhámhfar an conradh, d'fhéadfaí diúltú do thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe ón nós imeachta soláthair.</P><P>(1) Luaigh aon sainiúlacht a d’fhéadfadh tionchar a fheidhmiú ar rialacha na rannpháirtíochta (amhail sainiúlacht thíreolaíoch nó théamach, nó sainiúlacht fhadtéarmach/ghearrthéarmach).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Nótaí:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Ní mór tréimhse 30 lá féilire ar a laghad a bheith idir foilsiú an fhógra réamhaisnéise seo agus foilsiú an fhógra conartha chomhfhreagraigh.</P><P>Níor cheart aon iarratais ná iarrataí ar fhaisnéis a sheoladh faoi láthair.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Брюксел: ЕИС - Техническа помощ за мониторинг на въздействието на подкрепата на ЕС за гражданското общество в държавите от Източното партньорство</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Местоположение: Партньори от източното съседство — Армения, Азербайджан, Беларус, Грузия, Молдова и Украйна</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ОБЯВЛЕНИЕ ЗА ПРЕДВАРИТЕЛНА ИНФОРМАЦИЯ ЗА УСЛУГИ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Референтен номер на публикация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Процедура</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ограничена.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Заглавие на програма</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Европейски инструмент за съседство (ЕИС)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Финансиране</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Механизъм за гражданското общество в Източното партньорство за 2017 г. — Регионални действия (бюджетна линия — 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейски съюз</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, представляван от Европейската комисия, от името и за сметка на държавите-партньори, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Брюксел</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Белгия.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Вид на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Комисионна поръчка</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Описание на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Проектът за техническа помощ за мониторинг е част от Механизма за регионално източно гражданско общество през 2017 г. Основната цел на проекта е да се създаде качествена система за мониторинг и оценка на въздействието на проектите на гражданското общество, финансирани от ЕС, и да се използва тази система за събиране на доказателства относно въздействието на подкрепата на ЕС за гражданското общество в Източното съседство върху насърчаването на националните реформи и предоставянето на осезаеми ползи за гражданите в страните от Източното партньорство. Тази информация трябва да бъде подложена на кръстосана проверка спрямо разяснителните доклади, представени от организациите на гражданското общество и обратна връзка със съответните ръководители на проекти в Европейската комисия.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Индикативен бюджет</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Очакван срок за публикуване на обявлението за поръчка</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>май 2018 г.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Правно основание (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Регламент (ЕС) № 236/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за определяне на общи правила и процедури за изпълнението на инструментите на Съюза за финансиране на външната дейност и Регламент (ЕС) № 232/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за създаване на Европейски инструмент за съседство.</P><P>Моля, имайте предвид, че след оттеглянето на Обединеното кралство от ЕС, правилата за достъп до процедури за обществени поръчки на ЕС за икономически оператори, установени в трети държави, ще се прилагат за кандидати или оференти от Обединеното кралство, в зависимост от резултата от преговорите. В случай че такъв достъп не е предвиден в действащите правни разпоредби, които са в сила по време на възлагането на поръчката, кандидатите или оферентите от Обединеното кралство могат да бъдат отхвърлени от процедурата за обществена поръчка.</P><P>(1) Моля, посочете всяка особеност, която може да окаже въздействие върху правилата за участие (напр. географска или тематична, или кратък/дълъг срок).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Забележки:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Трябва да има минимален период от 30 календарни дни между публикуването на това обявление за предварителна информация и публикуването на съответното обявление за поръчка.</P><P>На този етап не трябва да се изпращат никакви молби или искания за информация.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: IEV - Asistență tehnică privind monitorizarea impactului sprijinului societății civile din UE în țările Parteneriatului Estic</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Locație: partenerii din vecinătatea estică Armenia, Azerbaidjan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova și Ucraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNȚ DE INTENȚIE PRIVIND UN CONTRACT DE ACHIZIȚII PUBLICE DE SERVICII</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referința publicației</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedură</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restrânsă.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titlul programului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Instrumentul european de vecinătate (IEV)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanțare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Facilitatea din 2017 pentru societate civilă a Parteneriatului estic - Acțiuni regionale (linia bugetară - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea contractantă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Uniunea Europeană</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentată de Comisia Europeană, în numele și în favoarea țărilor partenere, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bazat pe onorarii</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proiectul de asistență tehnică de monitorizare face parte din Facilitatea Regiunii de Est pentru Societatea Civilă din 2017. Obiectivul său principal este de a institui un sistem calitativ de monitorizare și evaluare a impactului proiectelor societății civile finanțate de UE și de a folosi acest sistem pentru a colecta dovezi cu privire la impactul pe care sprijinul societății civile din UE în Vecinătatea Estică l-a avut asupra promovării reformelor naționale și furnizării de beneficii tangibile pentru cetățenii din țările Parteneriatului Estic. Aceste informații trebuie să fie verificate în raport cu rapoartele narative transmise de organizațiile societății civile și rezultatele să revină la responsabilii de proiect relevanți din cadrul Comisiei Europene.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buget indicativ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevăzută de publicare a anunțului de participare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mai 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Temeiul juridic (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulamentul (UE) nr. 236/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de stabilire a normelor și procedurilor comune pentru punerea în aplicare a instrumentelor Uniunii pentru finanțarea acțiunii externe și Regulamentul (UE) nr. 232/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de instituire a unui instrument european de vecinătate.</P><P>A se avea în vedere că, după retragerea Marii Britanii din UE, normele de acces al operatorilor economici stabiliți în țări terțe la procedurile de achiziții publice ale UE se vor aplica ofertanților sau candidaților din Marea Britanie în funcție de rezultatul negocierilor. În cazul în care accesul nu este prevăzut de dispozițiile juridice în vigoare la momentul atribuirii contractului, candidații sau ofertanții din Regatul Unit ar putea fi respinși de la procedura de achiziții publice.</P><P>(1) Vă rugăm să precizați orice specificitate care ar putea avea un impact asupra regulilor de participare (cum ar fi de ordin geografic sau tematic sau pe termen lung/scurt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observații:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Trebuie respectată o perioadă de minimum 30 de zile calendaristice între publicarea prezentului anunț de intenție și publicarea anunțului de participare corespunzător.</P><P>În această etapă nu se acceptă candidaturi sau cereri de informații.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: ENI - Tehnička pomoć za praćenje utjecaja potpore civilnog društva EU-a u zemljama Istočnog partnerstva</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokacija: Partneri Istočnog susjedstva Armenija, Azerbajdžan, Bjelarus, Gruzija, Moldova i Ukrajina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PRETHODNA INFORMACIJSKA OBAVIJEST O USLUGAMA</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uputa na objavu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139597/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postupak</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograničeni.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europski instrument za susjedstvo (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regionalne akcije instrumenta Istočnog partnerstva za civilno društvo u 2017. (proračunska linija - 22.040201)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, koju predstavlja Europska komisija, u ime i za račun partnerskih država, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Priroda ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Temeljen na naknadama</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt tehničke pomoći za praćenje dio je Regionalnog instrumenta istočnog civilnog društva za 2017. Njezin je glavni cilj uspostaviti kvalitetan sustav praćenja i procjene učinaka projekata civilnog društva financiranog od strane EU-a i provesti ovaj sustav kako bi prikupio dokaze o utjecaju koji civilno društvo EU-a pruža u Istočnom susjedstvu na promicanje nacionalnih reformi i pružanju opipljivih pogodnosti za građane zemalja Istočnog partnerstva. Ova informacijska obavijest treba biti preusmjerena na narativna izvješća koja su dostavile organizacije civilnog društva i povratno informirati relevantne voditelje projekata u Europskoj komisiji.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indikativni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 500 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predviđeni datum objave poziva na nadmetanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Svibanj 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravni temelj (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uredba (EU) br. 236/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o utvrđivanju zajedničkih pravila i postupaka za provedbu instrumenata Unije za financiranje vanjskog djelovanja i Uredba (EU) br. 232/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o uspostavi Europskog instrumenta za susjedstvo.</P><P>Napominjemo da će se nakon povlačenja Ujedinjene Kraljevine iz EU-a na natjecatelje ili ponuditelje iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine primjenjivati pravila pristupa postupcima nabave EU-a za gospodarske subjekte s poslovnim nastanom u trećim zemljama, ovisno o rezultatima pregovora. U slučaju da pristup nije omogućen putem pravnih odredbi koje su na snazi u vrijeme sklapanja ugovora, natjecatelji ili ponuditelji iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine mogu biti odbijeni iz postupka javne nabave.</P><P>(1) Molimo navedite bilo kakve pojedinosti koje bi mogle utjecati na pravila sudjelovanja (poput geografskih ili tematskih ili dugoročnih/kratkoročnih).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Napomene:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Između objave ove prethodne informacijske obavijesti i objave odgovarajućeg poziva na nadmetanje mora proći najmanje 30 kalendarskih dana.</P><P>U toj se fazi ne smiju slati prijave ili zahtjevi za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>