<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="150232-2018"
            EDITION="2018068">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-155868-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180511</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>68</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180407</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 068-150232</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150232-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>https://www.dansk-retursystem.dk/dk/</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=208802&amp;B=DRS</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="42000000">Industrial machinery</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="DK012">Københavns omegn</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="DK012">Københavns omegn</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="EUR">4750000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180406</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180511 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="8">Other</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="B">Competitive procedure with negotiation</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="E">Environment</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01A02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Дaния</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Машини за промишлена употреба</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Průmyslové stroje</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrimaskiner</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Dänemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrielle Maschinen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Δανία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Μηχανήματα βιομηχανικών εγκαταστάσεων</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Denmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrial machinery</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Maquinaria industrial</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Taani</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tööstusmasinad</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Tanska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Teollisuuskoneet</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Danemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Machines industrielles</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Danmhairg, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrial machinery</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrijski strojevi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Dánia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ipari gépek</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Danimarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Macchinari industriali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Danija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pramoninės mašinos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Dānija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ražošanas iekārtas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>id-Danimarka</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Makkinarju industriali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Denemarken</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Bedrijfsmachines</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Dania</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Maszyny przemysłowe</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Máquinas industriais</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Danemarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Echipamente industriale</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Priemyselné mechanizmy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrijski stroji</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrimaskiner</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Dansk Retursystem A/S</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>7528ece8-15de-467e-821e-c176afbd6df3</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Dansk Retursystem A/S</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>25 49 61 40</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>Baldersbuen 1</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Hedehusene</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2640</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Ann-Britt Sørensen</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+45 43323232</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>abs@dansk-retursystem.dk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK012"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://www.dansk-retursystem.dk/dk/</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://eu.eu-supply.com/ctm/Company/CompanyInformation/Index/290789</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=208802&amp;B=DRS</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=208802&amp;B=DRS</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE_OTHER>Privately owned non-profit environmental company</CA_TYPE_OTHER>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="ENVIRONMENT"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Counting Line</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="42000000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The Counting Line will secure automatic handling of Collection Containers. The primary function of the Counting Line is to receive and buffer Collection Containers and hereafter count PET, ALU and Glass Beverage Packaging. Dansk Retursystem A/S (DRS) has initiated this Tender Procedure concerning the design, engineering, manufacturing, procurement, installation, testing and commissioning of material handling systems to receive and buffer Collection Containers as well as an overall Control and Monitoring System (CMS) for the complete Counting Line including DRS Supply. The Contract is not divided into lots due to the complexity of the Counting Line. Furthermore, if the Contract was divided into lots, it is DRS's assessment that there would be no competition for the contracts divided into lots.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">4750000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="42000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK012"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>2630 Taastrup.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>DRS is a privately owned, non-profit company which is owned by a number of Danish breweries.</P>
                  <P>DRS has the exclusive right to collect and sort empty disposable Beverage Packaging, including e.g. plastic bottles and aluminum cans, which are then recycled.</P>
                  <P>In line with the principle of circular economy, Beverage Packaging collected and sorted by DRS mainly finds use as new food packaging such as bottles and cans. This closed material loop requires that collection, sorting and recycling take place in such a way that the high quality of the Beverage Packaging material is preserved. Bales are therefore sold under contractual terms directly to specialized and highly performing recyclers in Europe.</P>
                  <P>The primary function of the Counting Line is to receive and buffer Collection Containers and hereafter count PET, ALU and Glass Beverage Packaging.</P>
                  <P>The scope of this Tender Procedure is to award the Contract to the Tenderer which has submitted the Most Economically Advantageous Tender on the basis of the award criteria “best price-quality ratio”. The contract will be awarded on the basis of the Tenderer’s description of the material handling systems to receive and buffer Collection Containers as well as an overall Control and Monitoring System (CMS) for the complete Counting Line including DRS Supply which must be in accordance with the minimum requirements and requirements as set out in the Tender Documents.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">4750000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">41</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>4</NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>This selection will be based on the following:</P>
                  <P>Candidates’ submitted references. DRS will assess which Candidates that have the most optimal experience in relation to delivery of contracts within the field of Material Handling Equipment (MHE) including warehouse control systems and/or warehouse management systems e.g. warehouse and internal logistic systems or similar of equivalent scope and complexity to the Contract.</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>DRS has included the following options under this Tender:</P>
                  <P>— Strategic Spare Parts, and</P>
                  <P>— maintenance service.</P>
                  <P>1. Strategic Spare Parts:</P>
                  <P>DRS may in part or wholly purchase Strategic Spare Parts from the consignment stock at the prices listed in the schedule to Part III.c (Prices and Payment Conditions).</P>
                  <P>The Tenderer shall for the purpose of DRS’s evaluation of the Tenders estimate the total value of the Strategic Spare Parts included in the consignment stock of Strategic Spare Parts. The estimated total value is to be listed in Appendix T2 (Price List).</P>
                  <P>2. Maintenance service:</P>
                  <P>DRS may decide that the Tenderer must perform the necessary maintenance service according to the Tenderer’s operation and maintenance manual to uphold function and guarantees during the Guarantee Period for:</P>
                  <P>— AGV’s,</P>
                  <P>— Case Conveyors.</P>
                  <P>The Tenderer shall list the prices for the abovementioned maintenance services to be performed according to the operation and maintenance manual in the Price List in Appendix T2.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>DRS will pay a remuneration of 15 000 EUR (excluding VAT) to the prequalified Tenderers (with exception of the Tenderer who has been awarded the Contract) for their participation in the Tender Procedure conditioned upon the Tenderers’ submission of Tender(s) as further described in the Tender Conditions Section 20.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>DRS has the following minimum requirements concerning the Candidates’ economical and financial standing:</P>
               <P>— the Candidate must have equity of at least 2 000 000 EUR at the end of the past financial year,</P>
               <P>— the Candidate must have a turnover of at least 10 000 000 EUR on average for the past 3 financial years,</P>
               <P>— the Candidate must have ordinary and sufficient liquidity in normal operations, including access to the necessary credits from a bank in the European Union.</P>
               <P>It is stated in the Tender Conditions how the Candidates / Tenderers must document fulfilment of the abovementioned minimum requirements for suitability.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>DRS has the following minimum requirements concerning the Candidates’ technical and professional ability:</P>
               <P>— the Candidate must provide a minimum of 3 and a maximum of 5 references meeting the following minimum requirements:</P>
               <P>—— the references must concern ongoing or completed projects within the past 3 years;</P>
               <P>—— the references must concern delivery contracts within the field of Material Handling Equipment (MHE) including warehouse control systems and/or warehouse management systems e.g. warehouse and internal logistic systems or similar of equivalent scope and complexity to the Contract;</P>
               <P>— for at least 1 of the references, the Candidate must according to the contract have performed deliveries of a value of at least 5 000 000 EUR,</P>
               <P>— for at least 1 of the references, the Candidate must according to the contract as primary delivery have performed deliveries of a value of at least 2 500 000 EUR:</P>
               <P>—— the references must contain a description of the contract, including:</P>
               <P>i) the location of performance;</P>
               <P>ii) the time of performance (date of commencement and completion date if the project has been completed);</P>
               <P>iii) the scope;</P>
               <P>iv) name and title of the key personnel who participated in the performance of the contract (not a CV); and</P>
               <P>v) the customers’ contact information, including contact person, email and telephone number.</P>
               <P>By submitting the references, the Candidate accepts that DRS may contact the customers’ contact persons regarding the Candidate’s performance of the contract. The Candidate is obligated to assist DRS in connection with contacting the customer.</P>
               <P>Submission of more than 5 references does not lead to exclusion of the Candidate. However, for the purpose of the evaluation, DRS will only consider the 5 references in the order listed in EU-Supply or in the ESPD.</P>
               <P>In the evaluation of the submitted references, DRS will irrespectively of the number of submitted references only include the 3 references that DRS finds to be the most optimal with regard to the performance of the Contract.</P>
               <P>Furthermore, in regard to Section 157 of the Danish Public Procurement Act, DRS has the following minimum requirements concerning the Candidates’ quality assurance schemes:</P>
               <P>— the Candidates’ quality assurance schemes must be ISO 9000-1 or similar.</P>
               <P>It is stated in the Tender Conditions how the Candidate / Tenderer must document fulfilment of the abovementioned minimum requirements for suitability.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>See contract and appendices.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_COMPETITIVE_NEGOTIATION/>
            <REDUCTION_RECOURSE/>
            <RIGHT_CONTRACT_INITIAL_TENDERS/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-05-11</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>2018-05-28</DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">6</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Candidates / tenderers will be excluded from participation in the procurement procedure if the exclusion grounds listed in Sections 135, 136 and 137(1)-(6) of the Danish Public Procurement Act apply. However, DRS may not exclude a candidate or a tenderer which has provided sufficient documentation that the candidate or tenderer is reliable (self-cleaning) pursuant to Section 138 of the Danish Public Procurement Act.</P>
               <P>Final documentation proving that the relevant grounds for exclusion do not apply and final documentation for fulfillment of the minimum requirements for suitability are described in the Tender Conditions, Section 9.9.</P>
               <P>Tender and negotiation procedure:</P>
               <P>1. Preliminary Tenders:</P>
               <P>In general, DRS encourages that the Preliminary Tender contains the same information as the Tenderer’s Final Tender and comply with the formal requirements as well as the minimum requirements and requirements.</P>
               <P>2. Preliminary Negotiations:</P>
               <P>The Tenderers who have submitted a Preliminary Tender in due time will be invited to participate in individual negotiation meetings.</P>
               <P>DRS expects the meetings to take place in the Copenhagen area.</P>
               <P>DRS will inform the Tenderers of the exact date, time and place via EU-Supply.</P>
               <P>The submitted Preliminary Tender will form the basis for the negotiations, including the strengths and weaknesses of the Preliminary Tender according to the contract award criteria.</P>
               <P>3. Revised Tender:</P>
               <P>DRS may choose to make adjustments to the Tender Documents on the basis of information and knowledge gained from the Preliminary Negotiations.</P>
               <P>The Revised Tender Documents will form the basis for the submission of Revised Tenders. All Tenderers will receive the Revised Tender Documents at the same time and have equal time to prepare their Revised Tenders.</P>
               <P>DRS may as an alternative or supplement to corrigenda upload a revised version of the relevant Tender Documents with mark up.</P>
               <P>4. Shortlisting:</P>
               <P>Based on the evaluation of the Revised Tenders in accordance with the award criteria and the evaluation method, DRS reserves the right to reduce the number of Tenderers to 2. The purpose of the shortlisting is to limit the costs and time consumption for DRS and the Tenderers with a limited chance of being awarded the Contract.</P>
               <P>5. Subsequent Negotiations:</P>
               <P>The negotiations based on the Revised Tenders will be carried out according to the same procedure as for the Preliminary Negotiations.</P>
               <P>6. Final Tender:</P>
               <P>DRS may choose to make adjustments to the Tender Documents on the basis of information and experience gained through the Subsequent Negotiations. The Revised Tender Documents will form the basis for the submission of Final Tenders.</P>
               <P>DRS may apply further negotiations if necessary.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>The Danish Complaints Board for Public Procurement (Klagenævnet for udbud)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Nævnenes Hus, Toldboden 2</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Viborg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>8800</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 72405708</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>klfu@naevneneshus.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.klfu.dk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>The rules concerning deadlines for review procedures are found in the Danish Complaints Board for Public Procurement Act (Act nº 593 of 2.6.2016) available at www.retsinformation.dk</P>
               <P>Complaints concerning a Candidate not being prequalified must be submitted with The Complaints Board for Public Procurement (the Complaints Board) within 20 calendar days starting the day after DRS has sent notification to the candidates involved, cf. Section 7(1) of the Danish Complaints Board for Public Procurement Act.</P>
               <P>Other complaints must be filed with the Complaints Board within 45 calendar days after DRS has published a contract award notice in the Official Journal of the European Union (with effect from the day following the publication date), cf. Section 7(2)(i).</P>
               <P>The complainant must notify DRS of the complaint in writing at the latest simultaneously with the submission as well as whether the complaint has been submitted in the standstill-period, cf. Section 6(4) of the Danish Complaints Board for Public Procurement Act. If the complaint has not been submitted within the standstill-period, the complainant must notify DRS in writing whether the complainant has requested the complaint to be given suspensory effect pursuant to Section 12 of the Act, cf. Section 6(4) of the Act.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>The Danish Competition and Consumer Authority (Konkurrence- og Forbrugerstyrelsen)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Carl Jacobsens Vej 35</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Valby</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2500</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 41715000</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>kfst@kfst.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.kfst.dk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-06</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
