<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="150407-2018"
            EDITION="2018068">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-154942-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20190406</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>68</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180407</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 068-150407</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:150407-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.renfrewshire.gov.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="92521100">Museum-exhibition services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKM83">Inverclyde, East Renfrewshire and Renfrewshire</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKM83">Inverclyde, East Renfrewshire and Renfrewshire</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">1000000</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180406</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="3">Regional or local authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01B01</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги по излагане и представяне на колекции</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Výstavy v muzeích</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Udstilling på museer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Museumsausstellungen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες εκθέσεων μουσείων</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Museum-exhibition services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de exposición en museos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Muuseumi väljapanekute teenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Museonäyttelypalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services d'exposition dans les musées</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Museum-exhibition services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge muzejskih izložbi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Múzeumi kiállítási szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di esposizione in musei</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Muziejų parodų paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Muzeju izstāžu pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi tal-mużewijiet ta' l-esibizzjoni</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Diensten voor museumexposities</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi wystawowe świadczone przez muzea</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de exposições em museus</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de expoziţii în muzee</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Muzeálne výstavy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Muzejske razstave</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paisley</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Utställningstjänster i museer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Renfrewshire Council</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>e50c132c-98f3-424c-8ea5-72a94a814c7b</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F01_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F01" LG="EN">
         <NOTICE TYPE="PRI_ONLY"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Renfrewshire Council</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Renfrewshire House, Cotton Street</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Paisley</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>PA1 1JB</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Euan Walker</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+44 1416187791</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>euan.walker@renfrewshire.gov.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM83"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.renfrewshire.gov.uk</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/search/Search_AuthProfile.aspx?ID=AA00400</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="REGIONAL_AUTHORITY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Paisley Museum Re-imagined — Exhibition Design Team</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>RC-CPU-18-002</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SUPPLIES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>This Prior Information Notice (PIN Notice) is for the appointment of an Exhibition Design Team (EDT) for the extension, refurbishment and re-imagination of the Grade A-listed Paisley Museum complex.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">1000000</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM83"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Paisley.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The procurement is for exhibition design services for the extension, renovation and refurbishment of Paisley Museum (total project cost 42 000 000 GBP). The aim of Paisley Museum Re-Imagined is to provide a visitor experience of international quality, which tells the inspirational stories of Paisley, its heritage and its pattern. The transformation of the Paisley Museum is underpinned by a series of high-level strategic project aims that will turn it into a:</P>
                  <P>— Leading European museum – telling the story of Paisley as a pattern and a town,</P>
                  <P>— Visitor destination drawing its audience from Scotland, UK and overseas,</P>
                  <P>— Platforming institution for learning, skills development, innovation and research, and</P>
                  <P>— Community resource at the heart of Paisley’s local life.</P>
                  <P>The EDT will deliver services as required from RIBA Stage 2 to 6 for the exhibition works, to include:</P>
                  <P>1) Exhibition Design (3-D);</P>
                  <P>2) Graphics Design (2-D);</P>
                  <P>3) Graphics Artworking and Illustration;</P>
                  <P>4) Lighting Design (displays);</P>
                  <P>5) Exhibitions Structural Design.</P>
                  <P>The scope of this contract does not include the design of digital and mechanical (hybrid) interactive displays or software/AV exhibits.</P>
                  <P>The exhibition interpretation role will be undertaken by the Client.</P>
                  <P>The project represents an exciting opportunity to alter and extend a fine neo-Classical building to respond to a unique collection, history and to deliver a fully 21st century facility that places the visitor at its heart.</P>
                  <P>The displays, created by the EDT are required to be delivered through a flexible display system (including plinths and display cases), high-density displays and key attracts that may incorporate multi-media shows and some degree of immersion. The museum’s collections are required to be reinterpreted and redisplayed, increasing the number of objects on display from 600 to 1200, and the EDT should deliver the 3-D, 2-D design, lighting design and exhibition structures as required.</P>
                  <P>The Multi-Disciplinary Design Team (MDDT) will be responsible for designing a High Street-facing extension to deliver a bold new café, shop and reception, to resolve the current building’s problematic vertical circulation, remove accretions and reinstate public areas, renew the services and refurbish the buildings.</P>
                  <P>The Council had previously undertaken a Restricted Procurement Procedure for these requirements however this was withdrawn as the Council considered that there were not any offers which fully met the Council’s requirements in terms of scope, quality and affordability.</P>
                  <P>Accordingly, the Council is issuing this PIN to enable an open market engagement exercise to be arranged which will inform the Councils future strategy for these requirements.</P>
                  <P>The Council invites interested parties to submit expressions of interest to participate in this market engagement exercise.</P>
                  <P>It is envisaged that there will be an open event which will provide information in regards to the background of this project and the Councils requirements and ambitions for exhibition design services. Furthermore, the Council also intends to meet with suitable interested parties on a one to one basis.</P>
                  <P>To register an expression of interest, interested parties should provide a short biography of their organisation as well as providing details / case studies of two or more similar projects that they have undertaken and completed which demonstrates their experience in this area.</P>
                  <P>Al expressions of interest should be submitted via email to euan.walker@renfrewshire.gov.uk</P>
                  <P>Please refer to section VI.3 Additional Information for details on the proposed procurement programme, noting that this is provisional and subject to change.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>The project has been awarded a first round pass from the Heritage Lottery Fund towards an overall grant of 4,9m and will be subject to a second-round application in 2019.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The Paisley Museum Re-Imagined project comprises 4 main buildings; Paisley Museum / Library, the Coats Observatory, Transit House, Philosophical Society Building / Observatory House and will include the creation of a garden to unite them and a new extension to deliver 21 century facilities, including a Café, Reception and Shop all to provide a welcoming, accessible campus. It is a complex of Category A and C listed buildings deemed to be of national or international importance. Paisley is the largest town in the historic county of Renfrewshire in the west central lowlands of Scotland and serves as the administrative centre for the Renfrewshire council area.</P>
               <P>In the 19 century it established itself as a centre of the weaving and thread-making industries, giving its name to the Paisley shawl and the Paisley Pattern. The town’s associations with political Radicalism were highlighted by its involvement in the Radical War of 1820, with striking weavers being instrumental in the protests. Paisley as a town has the second highest concentration of listed buildings anywhere in Scotland (after Edinburgh) with the quality of the built heritage, and in particular for that of buildings which date roughly between 1750 and 1930, is exceptional in terms of its state of repair. The original Paisley Museum building was designed by John Honeyman in 1968 and completed in 1870. The Glasgow firm of Honeyman and Keppie went on the extend the Museum and also design the Coats Observatory from the 1880s onwards. The influence of Charles Rennie Macintosh, Keppie’s most famous partner, can perhaps be seen in the interiors of the Library, designed in 1902 and extended in 1933. The Museum presents significant access challenges to visitors, having a “cascade” vertical circulation system with a building fabric in need of repair, M&amp;E systems at end-of-life, ad-hoc interventions, generally poor facilities and tired, static displays.</P>
               <P>The Council will deliver research, content and interpretation (method and target audience selection) to the EDT. The EDT will design the displays, such story displays, high-density displays, key attracts, graphics, display lighting design and the learning facilities to the agreed programme.</P>
               <P>Collections Significance.</P>
               <P>Renfrewshire Council museums have one of the best museum collections in Scotland. The National Audit of Scotland’s Museums and Galleries (2002) identified Renfrewshire Council as being seventh in the list of organisations with the largest collections of international, UK and national significance.</P>
               <P>This list is of all museums and galleries in Scotland, including the National Museums and University Museums. Only two out of Scotland’s 32 local authorities are higher on this list. The Paisley Museum is in possession of over 350 000 objects, which at time of writing are about to move to new purpose-built stores in Paisley’s High Street – the first publicly accessible museum store on a high street in the country.</P>
               <P>Note: To register your interest in this notice and obtain any additional information please visit the Public Contracts Scotland Web Site at http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/Search/Search_Switch.aspx?ID=537992</P>
               <P>(SC Ref:537992).</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-06</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F01_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
