<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="154154-2018"
            EDITION="2018069">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-156545-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180715</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>69</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180410</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 069-154154</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:154154-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>https://permalink.mercell.com/83142395.aspx</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="48814000">Medical information systems</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="00">Not specified / Other</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="NO">NORGE</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <n2016:TENDERER_NUTS CODE="NO012">Akershus</n2016:TENDERER_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="PROCUREMENT_TOTAL" CURRENCY="NOK">1960000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
         <REF_NOTICE>
            <NO_DOC_OJS>2017/S 017-029005</NO_DOC_OJS>
         </REF_NOTICE>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180406</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="3">Regional or local authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="V">Voluntary ex ante transparency notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="V">Contract award without prior publication</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="6">European Economic Area (EEA)</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="H">Health</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>03B15</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>03</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Норвегия</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Системи за информация в областта на медицината</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Norsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zdravotnické informační systémy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Norge</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Informationssystemer til medicinsk brug</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Norwegen</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Medizinische Informationssysteme</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Νορβηγία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Συστήματα ιατρικών πληροφοριών</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Norway</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Medical information systems</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Noruega</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sistemas de información médica</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Norra</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Meditsiiniinfosüsteemid</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Norja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Terveydenhuollon tietojärjestelmät</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Norvège</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Systèmes d'information dans le domaine médical</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Iorua, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Medical information systems</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Norveška</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Medicinski informacijski sustavi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Norvégia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Gyógyászati információs rendszerek</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Norvegia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sistemi di informazione medica</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Norvegija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Medicininės informacijos sistemos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Norvēģija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Medicīniskās informācijas sistēmas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>in-Norveġja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sistemi ta’ l-informazzjoni medika</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Noorwegen</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Medische-informatiesystemen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Norwegia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Systemy informacji medycznej</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Noruega</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sistemas de informação médica</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Norvegia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sistem de informare în domeniul medical</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Nórsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Lekárske informačné systémy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Norveška</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Medicinski informacijski sistemi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Norge</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Drammen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Medicinska informationssystem</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Drammen Kommune</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F15_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F15" LG="EN">
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Drammen Kommune</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>939214895</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>Engene 1</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Drammen</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>3008</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Kirsten Nordhøy</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+47 32046102</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>kirsten.nordhoy@drmk.no</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="NO"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://permalink.mercell.com/83142395.aspx</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>http://www.drammen.kommune.no/</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="REGIONAL_AUTHORITY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="HEALTH"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Additional delivery of electronic medicine management</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>2018/3716</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="48814000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SUPPLIES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>A procurement was announced in January 2017 for an electronic medicine management system for 9 of 10 institutions in the health and care districts in Drammen municipality. Drammen Helsehus (Helsehuset) was the only institution that was not included in the procurement. This was because Helsehuset already had, at that point in time, procured a system for medicine management. It takes time to implement and develop good routines for using such systems and this work was still ongoing when the competition for the nine nursing homes was announced in January 2017. Vingmed AS won the competition to deliver to these nursing homes, so Drammen municipality then had two suppliers of electronic medicine management systems. One at Helsehuset and another one in the 9 other institutions.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="NOK">1960000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="00"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Drammen municipality</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>After the interaction reform, the patients' health at Helsehuset has become increasingly worse. This has been particularly noticeable in the last 2 years. Patients with bad health, more patients and shorter stays mean that there are constant changes in medicine management. Helsehuset currently has two medicine rooms, but has a need for a further three in order to increase the capacity, have better work flow and increase patient safety. So that there is the same system over all of Helsehuset and a complete system in the municipality as a whole, Drammen municipality intends to procure five installations for electronic medicine management for Helsehuset from Vingmed AS.</P>
                  <P>The future medicine management system was described as such in the tender documentation from January 2017.</P>
                  <P>“The medicine management chain starts when a medicine is prescribed, via delivery from a chemist /wholesaler to the preparation and distribution of the medicine. ICT systems are used in the electronic medicine management system to carry out and document the various stages in the medicine management chain in order to ensure that the correct patient gets the correct medicine, in the correct dose, at the correct time in the correct way.”</P>
                  <P>The aim of the procurement was to: “Increase the quality and patient safety via electronic systems in the medicine management chain...” Drammen municipality is now working in cooperation with its suppliers to reach the target of a closed medicine loop.</P>
                  <P>A closed medicine loop shall be developed, where the systems for medicine management in the municipality's institutions communicate electronically with each other, with the patient journal system and with pharmacies, in accordance with a model from the hospital pharmacies. This has currently not been developed in the municipal health service.</P>
                  <P>Sykehusapotek defines a closed medicine loop as: “An electronically supported process for medicine management, where all information from prescribing to administration is transferred electronically and seamlessly between different systems. All documentation during the process will be electronic and traceable. The closed medicine loop follows each individual medicine”. A closed medicine loop will give uniform, efficient and secure medicine management. The medicine management system that Helsehuset currently has cannot communicate with the system for medicine management at the other nine institutions.</P>
                  <P>If the contracting authority shall hold a competition for the procurement of new systems for Helsehuset, we could potentially end up with 3 different suppliers of electronic medicine management systems for Helsehuset and in the municipality. The development of integrations to and from the EPJ patient journal system and to pharmacies would then have to be done with potentially 3 suppliers. This would give different user interface as there would be different software and different support internally and externally. As a result of this, health and ICT personnel would then have to acquire competence in 2 /3 systems, which would all have the same function. This would give considerable extra costs in the operational phase for licences, service and maintenance, training, etc. The development and operation of these systems is therefore deemed to have disproportionately large costs and use of resources for the contracting authority.</P>
                  <P>The additional delivery from VingMed AS will replace the current electronic medicine management system at Helsehuset and, in addition, increase capacity by a further three medicine rooms. The additional delivery is necessary as, by having the same supplier, all the medicine systems at Helsehuset would be compatible and the development and operation will only be directed at one supplier. This will ensure that the contracting authority achieves the aim in the main delivery of increased quality and patient safety.</P>
                  <P>The original contract value is NOK 9 650 000 and the additional procurement is NOK 1 960 000. The additional procurement is therefore under 50 % of the original contract value.</P>
                  <P>Drammen municipality is of the opinion that the terms in the regulations are met for an additional delivery from Vingmed AS.</P>
                  <P>Drammen municipality intends to enter into a contract with Vingmed AS for the delivery of five installations for electronic medicine management for Drammen Helsehus. The contract will be signed after the 10 day deadline from when the intention notice is published in TED has expired.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <DIRECTIVE_2014_24_EU>
               <PT_AWARD_CONTRACT_WITHOUT_CALL>
                  <D_OUTSIDE_SCOPE/>
                  <D_JUSTIFICATION>
                     <P>See the description of the procurement.</P>
                     <P>Drammen municipality shall develop a closed medicine loop where the systems for medicine management in the municipality's institutions communicate electronically with each other, with the patient journal system and with pharmacies, in accordance with a model from the hospital pharmacies. This has currently not been developed in the municipal health service.</P>
                     <P>A closed medicine loop will give uniform, efficient and secure medicine management. The system for medicine management that Helsehuset currently has cannot “communicate” with the system for medicine management at the other 9 institutions.</P>
                     <P>If the contracting authority shall hold a competition for the procurement of new systems for Helsehuset, we could potentially end up with three different suppliers of electronic medicine management systems for Helsehuset and in the municipality. The development of integrations to and from the EPJ patient journal system (Gerica) and to the pharmacies for the closed medicine loop would then have to be done together with potentially three suppliers. This would give different user interface as there would be different software and different support internally and externally.</P>
                     <P>Health personnel and ICT personnel would then have to acquire competence in two/three system, which would all have the same function. This would give considerable extra costs in an operational phase for licences, service and maintenance, training, etc. The development and operation of these systems is therefore deemed to have disproportionately large costs and use of resources for the contracting authority.</P>
                     <P>The additional delivery from VingMed AS will replace the current electronic medicine management system at Helsehuset and, in addition, increase capacity by a further three medicine rooms. The additional delivery is necessary as, by having the same supplier, all the medicine cupboards at Helsehuset and in the municipality would be compatible and the development and operation would only be directed at one supplier. This will ensure that the contracting authority achieves the aim in the main delivery of increased quality and patient safety.</P>
                     <P>The original contract value was NOK 9 650 000. The additional procurement is NOK 1 960 000.</P>
                     <P>The additional procurement is therefore well under 50 % of the original contract value.</P>
                     <P>Drammen municipality is of the opinion that the terms in the regulations are met for an additional delivery from Vingmed AS.</P>
                  </D_JUSTIFICATION>
               </PT_AWARD_CONTRACT_WITHOUT_CALL>
            </DIRECTIVE_2014_24_EU>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 017-029005</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-04-05</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>Vingmed AS</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <ADDRESS>Solbråveien 13</ADDRESS>
                     <TOWN>Asker</TOWN>
                     <POSTAL_CODE>1383</POSTAL_CODE>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NO012"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="NOK">1960000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Drammen kommune</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Drammen</TOWN>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
               <E_MAIL>innkjop@drmk.no</E_MAIL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-06</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F15_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
