<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="185976-2018" EDITION="2018083"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-184165-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180516</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>83</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180428</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 083-185976</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:185976-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN FR DE</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="32430000">Wide area network</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180424</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180516 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>OB302</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Tyskland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Levering af WAN-tjenester mellem De Europæiske Patentmyndigheder (beliggende i multiple lande) og Luxembourg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Deutschland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bereitstellung von Weitverkehrsnetzen zwischen den Dienstgebäuden des EPA (Standorte in mehreren Ländern) und Luxemburg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Germany</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Alemania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Múnich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>La prestación de servicios de red de área amplia entre oficinas de la OEP (ubicaciones en múltiples países) y Luxemburgo</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Saksa</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Laajaverkkopalveluiden (WAN) toimittaminen Euroopan patenttijärjestön (EPO) (monissa maissa sijaitsevien) toimitilojen ja Luxemburgin välillä</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Allemagne</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>La fourniture de services de réseau étendu (WAN) entre les bureaux de l’OEB (situés dans de nombreux pays) et le Luxembourg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Γερμανία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Μόναχο</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Παροχή υπηρεσιών δικτύου ευρείας περιοχής μεταξύ των γραφείων του ΕΟΔΕ (τοποθεσίες σε πολλές χώρες) και του Λουξεμβούργου</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Germania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Monaco di Baviera</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Prestazione di servizi di rete estesa tra gli uffici dell’OEB (luoghi di esecuzione in più paesi) e Lussemburgo</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Duitsland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>De verlening van WAN-diensten tussen EPO-kantoren (locaties in meerdere landen) en Luxemburg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Alemanha</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munique</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Fornecimento de serviços de Rede de Área Alargada (WAN) entre escritórios OEP (localizações em vários países) e o Luxemburgo</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Tyskland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tillhandahållande av WAN-tjänster mellan Europeiska patentorganisationens kontor (platser i flera länder) och Luxemburg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Německo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Mnichov</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Poskytování služeb rozsáhlé počítačové sítě mezi kancelářemi EPO (lokality v několika zemích) a Lucemburkem</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Saksamaa</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Euroopa Patendiameti (EPO) büroode (asukohad mitmes riigis) ja Luxembourgi vahelise laivõrgu teenuse hankimine</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Németország</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Nagy kiterjedésű hálózati szolgáltatások biztosítása az EPO irodái (több országban található helyszínek) és Luxembourg között</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Vokietija, VFR</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Miunchenas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Plačiojo tinklo paslaugų tarp EPO biurų (vietos keliose šalyse) ir Liuksemburge teikimas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Vācija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Minhene</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Plaša apgabala tīkla pakalpojumu nodrošināšana starp EPO birojiem (vairākās valstīs) un Luksemburgu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Ġermanja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Il-provvista ta’ servizzi għal Netwerk fuq Firxa Wiesgħa bejn uffiċċji tal-EPO (postijiet f’diversi pajjiżi) u l-Lussemburgu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Niemcy</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Monachium</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Świadczenie usług sieci rozległej między biurami EPO (lokalizacje w wielu krajach) a Luksemburgiem</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Nemecko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Mníchov</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Poskytovanie služieb rozsiahlej počítačovej siete medzi kanceláriami EPO (s umiestnením vo viacerých krajinách) a Luxemburskom</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Nemčija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Zagotavljanje storitev širokega omrežja med uradi EPO (lokacije v več državah) in Luksemburgom</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Ghearmáin, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Seirbhísí líonra achair fhairsing a sholáthar idir oifigí OEP (láithreáin i dtíortha ilíocha) agus i Lucsamburg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Гepмaния</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Мюнхен</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Предоставяне на услуги за разширена мрежа (WАN) между офисите на ЕПО (местоположения в няколко държави) и Люксембург</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Germania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Furnizarea de servicii de Rețea de arie largă între birourile OEB (locații în mai multe țări) și Luxemburg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Njemačka</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Nabava usluga mreže širokog područja između ureda EPO-a (s lokacijama u više zemalja) i Luxembourga</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Patentorganisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Organisation européenne des brevets (OEB)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Levering af WAN-tjenester mellem De Europæiske Patentmyndigheder (beliggende i multiple lande) og Luxembourg</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Bereitstellung von Weitverkehrsnetzen zwischen den Dienstgebäuden des EPA (Standorte in mehreren Ländern) und Luxemburg</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Bekanntmachung Beschränkte ausschreibung NR 2688</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Auftraggeber:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Patentorganisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, handelnd durch das Europäische Patentamt mit Hauptsitz in </BLK_BTX><URL>80469</URL><POSTAL_CODE/><TOWN>München</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ADDRESS>Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1</ADDRESS><BLK_BTX>, Postanschrift: EPA, 80298 München, DEUTSCHLAND</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Die Europäische Patentorganisation ist eine zwischenstaatliche Organisation, die durch das 1977 in Kraft getretene Europäische Patentübereinkommen gegründet wurde. Ihr gehören derzeit 38 Mitgliedstaaten an (Albanien, Belgien, Bulgarien, Dänemark, Deutschland, ehemalige jugoslawische Republik Mazedonien, Estland, Finnland, Frankreich, Griechenland, Irland, Island, Italien, Kroatien, Lettland, Liechtenstein, Litauen, Luxemburg, Malta, Monaco, Niederlande, Norwegen, Österreich, Polen, Portugal, Rumänien, San Marino, Schweden, Schweiz, Serbien, Slowakei, Slowenien, Spanien, Tschechische Republik, Türkei, Ungarn, Vereinigtes Königreich und Zypern). Ausführendes Organ der EPO ist das Europäische Patentamt, das die Recherche und Prüfung europäischer Patentanmeldungen und die Erteilung europäischer Patente zur Aufgabe hat.</P><P>Es beschäftigt rund 6 700 Bedienstete am Hauptsitz in München, in einer Zweigstelle in den Haag/Rijswijk (NL) und in zwei Dienststellen in Berlin und Wien. (Die Zahl der Mitgliedstaaten und der Bediensteten kann sich ändern.)</P><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vergabeverfahren:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Beschränkte Ausschreibung im Leistungswettbewerb</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Gegenstand des Auftrags:</P><P>Bereitstellung von Weitverkehrsnetzen zwischen den Dienstgebäuden des EPA (Standorte in mehreren Ländern) und Luxemburg.</P><P>b) Teilung in Lose:</P><P>Los 1: Bereitstellung von WAN-Verbindungen zwischen drei Dienstgebäuden des EPA (Shell-Gebäude in Rijswijk, PschorrHöfe BT7 in München und Dienststelle in Berlin) und Luxemburg: Carrier A,</P><P>Los 2: Bereitstellung von WAN-Verbindungen zwischen drei Dienstgebäuden des EPA (Shell-Gebäude in Rijswijk, Isargebäude in München und Dienststelle in Wien) und Luxemburg: Carrier B.</P><P>c) Erforderliche Sicherheiten und Bürgschaften:</P><P>Nicht zutreffend.</P><P>d) Wichtigste Zahlungsbedingungen:</P><P>Die Zahlung erfolgt für die Installation innerhalb von 30 Tagen nach Abnahme und für die WANDienste und den Support monatlich im Nachhinein.</P><P>e) Rechtlich vorgeschriebene Qualifikationen:</P><P>Nicht zutreffend.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Erfüllungsort und Leistungsfrist:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Erfüllungsort:</P><P>Vier Standorte des EPA (München, Den Haag/Rijswijk, Berlin, Wien) und Luxemburg.</P><P>b) Vertragslaufzeit oder Ausführungsfrist:</P><P>Die Vertragslaufzeit beträgt fünf Jahre ab der Abnahme.</P><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Änderungsvorschläge:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Änderungsvorschläge, die sich in einer erheblichen Einschränkung der Rechte und Sicherheiten der EPO niederschlagen würden, sind nicht zulässig.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Antrag auf Teilnahme an der Ausschreibung und Sprache des Angebots:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Annahmeschluss für Anträge auf Teilnahme an der Ausschreibung und etwaige unter d) geforderte Auskünfte und Nachweise, die zusammen mit dem Antrag einzureichen sind:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12.00 (MEZ)</P><P>Interessenten werden gebeten, die Fragebögen unter nachstehendem Link: http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDoc ument auszufüllen und die dort geforderten Angaben und Nachweise vorzulegen.</P><P>Da die Antworten in den Fragebögen eventuell einer Klarstellung bedürfen, würde es das EPA begrüßen, wenn Interessenten ihre Antworten möglichst früh übermitteln, damit die nachfolgenden Fristen eingehalten werden können.</P><P>b) Bezeichnung und Anschrift der Stelle, an die die Anträge auf Teilnahme zu richten sind:</P><P>Teilnahmeanträge sind per E-Mail und im Original per Post an folgende Anschrift zu senden:</P><P>Europäisches Patentamt,</P><P>Zentrale Beschaffung Den Haag 4.8 (2688),</P><P>Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, Niederlande,</P><P>Postfach 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk,</P><P>E-Mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c) Sprache oder Sprachen, in denen der Antrag auf Teilnahme und das Angebot abzufassen sind:</P><P>Englisch. Die Verdingungsunterlagen sind nur auf Englisch erhältlich.</P><P>d) Kriterien für die Beurteilung der zur Auftragsausführung erforderlichen Fachkunde, Leistungsfähigkeit und Zuverlässigkeit des Bieters:</P><P>Die zur Auftragsausführung erforderliche Leistungsfähigkeit und Zuverlässigkeit des Bieters werden auf der Grundlage der Angaben und Nachweise beurteilt, die in Beantwortung der unter 6 a) genannten Fragebögen vorgelegt werden.</P><P>Interessenten, die nicht die Auswahlkriterien erfüllen und/oder deren finanzielle und professionelle Zuverlässigkeit aufgrund ihrer Verhältnisse ernstlich infrage steht (s. Artikel 2 der Allgemeinen Ausschreibungsbedingungen, abrufbar unter www.epo.org), werden nicht zur Teilnahme an der Ausschreibung aufgefordert.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsform einer Bietergemeinschaft:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Reichen mehrere Bieter ein gemeinsames Angebot ein, so haften sie gesamtschuldnerisch für die Erfüllung der vertraglichen Verpflichtungen. Zusammen mit dem Angebot ist eine entsprechende von allen Mitgliedern der Bietergemeinschaft unterzeichnete Erklärung einzureichen, in der ein Vertreter bestimmt ist, der bevollmächtigt ist, für alle Mitglieder zu handeln.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bindefrist:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Monate ab dem Annahmeschluss für Angebote, der mit dem Versand der Verdingungsunterlagen mitgeteilt wird.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kriterien für die Zuschlagserteilung:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Die Kriterien für die Zuschlagserteilung sind wie folgt gewichtet:</P><P>Technische Aspekte: 40 %, Finanzielle Aspekte: 60 %,</P><P>Die Bewertung der technischen Aspekte beruht auf der Beantwortung des Fragebogens zu den Zuschlagskriterien, der den Verdingungsunterlagen beiliegt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sonstige Angaben:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Derzeit wird davon ausgegangen, dass der Zuschlag im dritten Quartal 2018 erteilt wird.</P><P>Zur Gewährleistung der Redundanz wird von jedem Unternehmen, das den Zuschlag erhält, erwartet, dass es der EPO Einblick in den tatsächlichen Pfad der beauftragten Ende-zu-Ende-Verbindungen gewährt und dass es mit der EPO zusammenarbeitet, um Mängel abzustellen oder einzudämmen.</P><P>Die Bieter können entweder ein Angebot für Los 1 (Carrier A) oder Los 2 (Carrier B) oder für beide Lose unterbreiten, vorausgesetzt die Leistungen werden über getrennte Carrier bereitgestellt.</P><P>Die EPO behält sich jedoch vor, Bietern, die ein Angebot für beide Lose einreichen, den Zuschlag für nur ein Los zu erteilen und in diesem Fall nach eigenem Ermessen zu entscheiden, für welches Los.</P><P>Handelt es sich bei dem Bieter um einen Makler oder Wiederverkäufer von Datenkommunikationsdiensten, darf dieser nicht denselben/dieselben Unterauftragnehmer für Los 1 (Carrier A) und Los 2 (Carrier B) einsetzen, sondern muss die Leistungen gemäß Los 1 (Carrier A) und die gemäß Los 2 (Carrier B) an unterschiedliche Unterauftragnehmer vergeben.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munich: The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Múnich: La prestación de servicios de red de área amplia entre oficinas de la OEP (ubicaciones en múltiples países) y Luxemburgo</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Laajaverkkopalveluiden (WAN) toimittaminen Euroopan patenttijärjestön (EPO) (monissa maissa sijaitsevien) toimitilojen ja Luxemburgin välillä</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munich: La fourniture de services de réseau étendu (WAN) entre les bureaux de l’OEB (situés dans de nombreux pays) et le Luxembourg</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>APPEL À LA CONCURRENCE RESTREINT 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVIS PUBLIÉ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autorité responsable du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>L'</BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Organisation européenne des brevets (OEB)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, agissant par l'intermédiaire de l'Office européen des brevets: Siège, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich; adresse postale: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ALLEMAGNE.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>L'Organisation européenne des brevets est une organisation intergouvernementale instituée par la Convention sur le brevet européen, entrée en vigueur en 1977. Elle compte actuellement 38 États membres (l'Albanie, l’Allemagne, l’Autriche, la Belgique, la Bulgarie, Chypre, la Croatie, le Danemark, l’Espagne, l'Estonie, l'ex-République yougoslave de Macédoine, la Finlande, la France, la Grèce, la Hongrie, l’Irlande, l’Islande, l’Italie, la Lettonie, le Liechtenstein, la Lituanie, le Luxembourg, Malte, Monaco, la Norvège, les Pays-Bas, la Pologne, le Portugal, la Roumanie, le Royaume-Uni, Saint-Marin, la Serbie, la Slovaquie, la Slovénie, la Suède, la Suisse, la République tchèque et la Turquie). L'organe exécutif de l'OEB est l'Office européen des brevets, qui est chargé de la recherche et de l'examen des demandes de brevet européen et de la délivrance de brevets européens. Il emploie environ 6 700 agents en poste au siège de l’OEB à Munich, dans son département à La Haye/Rijswijk (Pays-Bas) et dans ses agences à Berlin et à Vienne (le nombre d'États membres et d'agents indiqués peut changer).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Mode de passation du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Appel à la concurrence restreint avec attribution discrétionnaire.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Objet du marché:</P><P>La fourniture de services de réseau étendu (WAN) entre les bureaux de l’OEB (situés dans de nombreux pays) et le Luxembourg.</P><P>(b) Partage en lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: fourniture de circuits WAN entre les trois sites de l’OEB (Rijswijk Shell, bâtiments BT7 à Munich et l’agence de Berlin) et Luxembourg: Carrier A;</P><P>— Lot 2: fourniture de circuits WAN entre les trois sites de l’OEB (Rijswijk Main, bâtiments Isar à Munich et l’agence de Vienne) et Luxembourg: Carrier B;</P><P>(c) Dépôts et garanties exigés:</P><P>Sans objet.</P><P>(d) Principales conditions relatives au paiement:</P><P>L’installation sera payée dans les 30 jours après acceptation par l’OEB, les services de réseau étendu et l’assistance seront payés mensuellement à terme échu.</P><P>(e) Qualifications exigées par la loi:</P><P>Sans objet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lieu et période d'exécution:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Lieu où le contrat doit être exécuté:</P><P>Sur les quatre sites de l'OEB (Munich, La Haye/Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienne) et à Luxembourg.</P><P>(b) Durée du contrat ou délai de livraison ou d'exécution des prestations/travaux:</P><P>Le contrat aura une durée de cinq ans à compter de l’acceptation.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variantes:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les propositions de variantes susceptibles de réduire de façon significative les droits et garanties de l'OEB ne sont pas autorisées.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Demandes de participation à la procédure d'appel à la concurrence, et langue dans laquelle les offres doivent être rédigées:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Date limite de réception des demandes de participation à la procédure d'appel à la concurrence et de tout renseignement et pièce justificative requis au point (d) ciaprès, lesquels doivent accompagner la demande de participation:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 (CET)</P><P>Les parties intéressées qui veulent participer à l’appel à la concurrence sont priées de répondre aux questionnaires pour lesquels existe le lien suivant:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>Et de fournir les informations et les pièces justificatives indiquées dans ces questionnaires.</P><P>Dans l'éventualité où des précisions seraient nécessaires en ce qui concerne les réponses aux questionnaires, l'OEB saurait gré aux parties intéressées de soumettre leurs réponses le plus tôt possible afin de pouvoir respecter les délais ultérieurs.</P><P>(b) Nom et adresse du service auquel elles doivent être envoyées:</P><P>Les demandes de participation doivent être envoyées par courrier électronique et l’original par la poste à</P><P>Office européen des brevets</P><P>Service central des achats à La Haye 4.8 (2688)</P><P>Patentlaan 2, NL2288 EE Rijswijk, Pays-Bas.</P><P>PO Box 5818, NL2280 HV Rijswijk, Pays-Bas,</P><P>E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c) Langue ou langues dans lesquelles les demandes de participation et les offres doivent être rédigées:</P><P>Anglais. Le cahier des charges ne sera disponible qu’en anglais.</P><P>(d) Critères visant à évaluer les compétences, les capacités et la fiabilité des demandeurs pour pouvoir exécuter le marché:</P><P>Les capacités et la fiabilité des demandeurs pour pouvoir exécuter le marché seront évaluées sur la base des informations et pièces justificatives soumises en réponse aux questionnaires pour lesquels il existe un lien au point 6 (a)</P><P>Les parties intéressées qui ne satisfont pas aux critères de sélection et/ou dont la situation remet sérieusement en cause leur fiabilité financière et professionnelle (cf. article 2 des Conditions générales relatives aux appels à la concurrence, qui figurent à l'adresse www.epo.org) ne seront pas invitées à participer à l’appel à la concurrence.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Forme légale du groupement, en cas d'offre soumise en commun:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Si plusieurs candidats soumettent conjointement une offre, ils seront conjointement et solidairement responsables de l’exécution de leurs obligations au titre du contrat. Une déclaration à cet effet, dûment signée par tous les membres du groupement et désignant un représentant autorisé à agir pour le compte de tous les membres, doit accompagner l’offre.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Durée obligatoire de validité des offres:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 mois à compter de la date limite de dépôt des offres, qui sera indiquée lors de l'envoi du cahier des charges.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critères d'attribution du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les critères d'attribution et leurs pondérations sont les suivants:</P><P>— Aspects techniques: 40 %,</P><P>— Aspects financiers: 60 %</P><P>L'évaluation des aspects techniques sera basée sur les réponses fournies par les candidats au questionnaire «Award criteria» inclus dans le cahier des charges.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autres informations:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L’attribution du marché devrait avoir lieu au troisième trimestre 2018.</P><P>Pour maintenir la redondance, chaque entreprise adjudicataire du contrat devra donner à l’OEB un aperçu du parcours réel des connexions de bout en bout commandées et coopérera avec l’OEB pour réduire ou supprimer toute défaillance.</P><P>Les candidats peuvent proposer de fournir soit les services décrits comme «Carrier A» (Lot 1) ou ceux décrits comme «Carrier B» (Lot 2), ou les deux lots à condition que les services soient fournis par des entreprises distinctes.</P><P>Dans le cas où un candidat propose de fournir les deux lots, l’OEB se réserve le droit d’attribuer un seul lot et le choix du lot concerné reviendra à l’OEB.</P><P>Si le candidat exerce en tant que courtier/revendeur de connexions de communication de données, il n’est pas permis d’engager le ou les même(s) sous-traitant(s) pour les deux services décrits comme «Carrier A» et ceux décrits comme «Carrier B». Dans ce cas, le candidat devra engager des soustraitants différents pour les services décrits comme «Carrier A» et décrits comme «Carrier B».</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Μόναχο: Παροχή υπηρεσιών δικτύου ευρείας περιοχής μεταξύ των γραφείων του ΕΟΔΕ (τοποθεσίες σε πολλές χώρες) και του Λουξεμβούργου</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Monaco di Baviera: Prestazione di servizi di rete estesa tra gli uffici dell’OEB (luoghi di esecuzione in più paesi) e Lussemburgo</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: De verlening van WAN-diensten tussen EPO-kantoren (locaties in meerdere landen) en Luxemburg</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munique: Fornecimento de serviços de Rede de Área Alargada (WAN) entre escritórios OEP (localizações em vários países) e o Luxemburgo</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Tillhandahållande av WAN-tjänster mellan Europeiska patentorganisationens kontor (platser i flera länder) och Luxemburg</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Mnichov: Poskytování služeb rozsáhlé počítačové sítě mezi kancelářemi EPO (lokality v několika zemích) a Lucemburkem</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Euroopa Patendiameti (EPO) büroode (asukohad mitmes riigis) ja Luxembourgi vahelise laivõrgu teenuse hankimine</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Nagy kiterjedésű hálózati szolgáltatások biztosítása az EPO irodái (több országban található helyszínek) és Luxembourg között</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Miunchenas: Plačiojo tinklo paslaugų tarp EPO biurų (vietos keliose šalyse) ir Liuksemburge teikimas</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Minhene: Plaša apgabala tīkla pakalpojumu nodrošināšana starp EPO birojiem (vairākās valstīs) un Luksemburgu</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munich: Il-provvista ta’ servizzi għal Netwerk fuq Firxa Wiesgħa bejn uffiċċji tal-EPO (postijiet f’diversi pajjiżi) u l-Lussemburgu</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Monachium: Świadczenie usług sieci rozległej między biurami EPO (lokalizacje w wielu krajach) a Luksemburgiem</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Mníchov: Poskytovanie služieb rozsiahlej počítačovej siete medzi kanceláriami EPO (s umiestnením vo viacerých krajinách) a Luxemburskom</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Zagotavljanje storitev širokega omrežja med uradi EPO (lokacije v več državah) in Luksemburgom</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Seirbhísí líonra achair fhairsing a sholáthar idir oifigí OEP (láithreáin i dtíortha ilíocha) agus i Lucsamburg</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Мюнхен: Предоставяне на услуги за разширена мрежа (WАN) между офисите на ЕПО (местоположения в няколко държави) и Люксембург</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Furnizarea de servicii de Rețea de arie largă între birourile OEB (locații în mai multe țări) și Luxemburg</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Nabava usluga mreže širokog područja između ureda EPO-a (s lokacijama u više zemalja) i Luxembourga</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Restricted Invitation to Tender 2688</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PUBLISHED NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Germany</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>.</P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 member states (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6 700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague /Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Purpose of the contract:</P><P>The provision of Wide Area Network services between EPO-offices (locations in multiple countries) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Division into lots:</P><P>— Lot 1: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Shell, Munich BT7 buildings and the sub-office in Berlin) and Luxembourg: Carrier A,</P><P>— Lot 2: Provision of WAN circuits between three EPO-offices (Rijswijk Main, Munich Isar buildings and the sub-office in Vienna) and Luxembourg: Carrier B.</P><P>c— Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>d— Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Installation will be paid within 30 days of acceptance by the EPO, wide area network services and support will be paid monthly in arrears.</P><P>e— Qualifications required by law:</P><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Four locations of the EPO (Munich, The Hague /Rijswijk, Berlin, Vienna) and Luxembourg.</P><P>b— Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services /work:</P><P>The contract shall have five years duration from acceptance.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requests to participate in the tender procedure, and language of bids:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a— Final date for receipt of requests to participate in the tender procedure and any information and evidence required under point (d) below, which must accompany the request:</P><P>16.5.2018, 12:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties who want to participate in the tender are asked to reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link here:</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/DEC00D67F257502AC12582780039E39E?OpenDocument</P><P>And provide the information and evidence stated in those questionnaires.</P><P>As clarification of answers to the questionnaires may be needed, the EPO would appreciat if interested parties submit their replies as early as possible in order to keep the subsequent timelines.</P><P>b— Name and address of the department to which they must be sent:</P><P>Requests to participate are to be sent by email and the original by post to European Patent Office Central Procurement the Hague 4.8 (2688) Patentlaan 2, 2288 EE Rijswijk, the Netherlands P.O. Box 5818, 2280 HV Rijswijk, the Netherlands E-mail: dhtenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>c— Language(s) in which requests to participate and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English. The procurement documents will be available in English only.</P><P>d— Criteria for assessing requesters' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</P><P>Requesters' capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaires to which there is a link under point 6 (a)</P><P>Interested parties who do not fulfil the selection criteria and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org ) will not be invited to participate in the tender.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 Months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The award criteria and their relative weightings are as follows:</P><P>Technical aspects: 40 %, Financial aspects: 60 %</P><P>The evaluation of the technical aspects will be based on the bidders' responses the questionnaire “Award criteria” included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract award is expected to take place in the third quarter of 2018.</P><P>To sustain the redundancy, each company awarded the contract will be expected to give the EPO insight into the actual path of the end-to-end connections ordered and will cooperate with the EPO to reduce or remove any deficiencies.</P><P>Bidders may propose to supply either the services described as “Carrier A” (Lot 1) or those described as “Carrier B” (Lot 2), or both lots provided that the services will be supplied through distinct carriers.</P><P>In case that a bidder proposes to supply both lots, the EPO reserves the right to only award a single lot and the choice for the lot concerned will be at the discretion of the EPO.</P><P>If the bidder operates as a broker /reseller of data communication connections it is not allowed to engage the same subcontractor(s) for both the services described as “Carrier A” and those described as “Carrier B”. In that case the bidder should engage different subcontractors for the services described as “Carrier A” and described as “Carrier B”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>