<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="187661-2018"
            EDITION="2018083">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-192526-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180601</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>83</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180428</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 083-187661</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:187661-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/Home</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/Home</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="85100000">Health services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKK23">Somerset</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKK23">Somerset</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">152085750</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180427</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180601 10:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="6">Body governed by public law</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="H">Health</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги на здравеопазването</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zdravotnické zabezpečení</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tjenesteydelser inden for sundhedsvæsenet</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dienstleistungen des Gesundheitswesens</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υγειονομικές υπηρεσίες</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Health services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de salud</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tervishoiuteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Terveyspalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de santé</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Health services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge u području zdravstva</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Egészségügyi szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi sanitari</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sveikatos priežiūros paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Veselības pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi tas-saħħa</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Gezondheidsdiensten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi ochrony zdrowia</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de saúde</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de sănătate</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zdravotnícke služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zdravstvene storitve</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yeovil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Hälsovårdstjänster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Somerset Clinical Commissioning Group</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Somerset Clinical Commissioning Group</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Wynford House, Lufton Way, Lufton</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Yeovil</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>BA22 8HR</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Angela Mortley</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+44 1935381968</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>angelamortley@nhs.net</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK23"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/Home</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>www.somersetccg.nhs.uk</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/Home</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/Home</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="BODY_PUBLIC"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="HEALTH"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Somerset CCG - IUC</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>PR002452</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="85100000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Somerset Clinical Commissioning Group seeks to commission an Integrated Urgent Care service for patients in Somerset, to include 111 (Telephone and Online), a Clinical Assessment Service (CAS), Face-to-Face Consultation and a Single Point of Access (SPoA). The total budget available is 7 149 000 GBP including VAT per annum. The CCG reserves the right to include, at additional value, the following services within any contract ultimately let without recourse to a further advert or formal procurement process: GP 999 Car, Minor Injury Units / Urgent Treatment Centres, Directory of Services, GP Improved Access. Contracts will be for an initial term of 61 months, ending 31.3.2024 with a possible extension of any period up to a further 60 months, as defined and at the discretion of the Commissioner. Services are planned to commence from 25.2.2018. This procurement is being carried out by NHS South, Central and West Commissioning Support Unit (SCW) on behalf of the Commissioners.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">152085750</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="85100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK23"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Somerset.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Somerset Clinical Commissioning Group (SCCG) seeks to commission an Integrated Urgent Care service for patients, residents and visitors to Somerset. The procurement is driven by the need to re-procure an Integrated Urgent Care service, which brings together NHS 111 and GP Out of Hours provision for people with urgent care needs. The procurement seeks to appoint a service which is innovative, meets patients’ expectations and fits the needs of the Somerset population now and throughout the contract period. Contracts will be for an initial term of 61 months, ending on 31.3.2024, with a possible extension of any period up to a further 60 months, as defined and at the discretion of the Commissioner. Services are planned to commence from 25.2.2018. The total budget available is 7 149 000 GBP including VAT per annum. SCCG is responsible for planning and buying healthcare services for over half a million people across Somerset. Led by local doctors and healthcare professionals with knowledge of their specific communities and patient needs, we are committed to improving the health of Somerset’s population. SCCG is made up of 69 GP practices, operating in nine commissioning localities. They work together to ensure the best possible healthcare is available and meets the needs of people in Somerset. The scope and value of the contract with the Provider will be partially determined through the procurement procedure being undertaken. As a minimum, the Provider will be commissioned to be responsible for the delivery of the following core functions with a budget of 7 149 000 GBP: </P>
                  <P>— 111 (Telephone and Online),</P>
                  <P>— Clinical Assessment Service,</P>
                  <P>— Face-to-Face Consultation and Treatment,</P>
                  <P>— Single Point of Access for healthcare professionals SCCG are looking for services to be delivered in an innovative way that meets the needs of the Somerset population now and throughout the contract period, so SCCG expects the service to constantly engage with the public and professionals, and in agreement with commissioners, to evolve the service to ensure it is fit for purpose and meeting patients’ expectations. The service needs to work in an integrated manner with other service providers in the area to offer a seamless experience across the urgent care system, particularly from a patient's view point. Due to the complex nature of the re-commissioning, and the complexity of the urgent care system within which it is being commissioned, SCCG will be using a phased approach in order to secure the transformational change required in Somerset. Once appointed, the Commissioner will work with the Provider to further transform services, the specific scope of which will be determined through discussion with the Provider. The maximum annual value provided within this advert is therefore the maximum value of the core functions defined above. Given the changing urgent care landscape, and the need for integrated provision, SCCG also reserves the right to include the following services within any contract ultimately let without recourse to a further advert or formal procurement process: </P>
                  <P>— GP 999 Car,</P>
                  <P>— Minor Injury Units / Urgent Treatment Centres,</P>
                  <P>— Directory of Services,</P>
                  <P>— GP Improved Access The combined total value of these services is estimated to be c. 6 000 000- 8 000 000 GBP. This procurement is being carried out by NHS South, Central and West Commissioning Support Unit (SCW) on behalf of the Commissioners, through the In-Tend e-procurement system (https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/Home) from where full information can be accessed.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">152085750</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DATE_START>2019-02-25</DATE_START>
               <DATE_END>2024-03-31</DATE_END>
               <RENEWAL/>
               <RENEWAL_DESCR>
                  <P>Contracts will be for an initial term of 61 month, ending on 31.3.2024 months, with a possible extension of any period up to a further 60 months, as defined and at the discretion of the Commissioner. Services are planned to commence from 25.2.2018.</P>
               </RENEWAL_DESCR>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>Contracts will be for an initial term of 61 months, ending on 31.3.2024, with a possible extension of any period up to a further 60 months, as defined and at the discretion of the Commissioner. Services are planned to commence from 25.2.2018.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P/>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P/>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-06-01</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-06-01</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P/>
               </PLACE>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ESTIMATED_TIMING>
               <P>2022.</P>
            </ESTIMATED_TIMING>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Interested providers will be able to view this notice via the 'current tenders' list on the e-procurement portal (In-tend). https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/Home In order to submit a bid, you will need to register on the e-procurement portal and 'express an interest' and then complete all necessary questions as specified within the documents. On registration, please include at least two contacts to allow for access to the portal in times of absence. The services are healthcare services falling within Schedule 3 to the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 (&#x8f;the Regulations&#x8f;) which are not subject to the full regime of the Regulations, but is instead governed by the &#x8f;Light Touch Regime&#x8f; contained within Chapter 3, Section 7 of the Regulations (Regulations 74 to 77). The tendering process will be conducted in accordance with the requirements and flexibilities provided by Articles 74 to 76 of the Directive, and Regulations 74 to 76 of the Regulations. The Authority will run a transparent tender process, treating all Bidders equally. For the avoidance of doubt, the Authority will not be bound by the Regulations or the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union or any other regulations or legislation except for the specific parts or circumstances that apply to the procurement of these Services. Neither the inclusion of a Bidder selection stage, nor the use of any language or terms found in the Directive or Regulations, nor the description of the procedure voluntarily adopted by the Authority (&#x8f;Open&#x8f;, &#x8f;Restricted&#x8f;, &#x8f;Competitive Procedure with Negotiation&#x8f;, &#x8f;Competitive Dialogue&#x8f; or any other description), nor any other indication, shall be taken to mean that the Authority intends to hold itself bound by the Directive or Regulations, save by the provisions applicable to services coming within the scope of Annex XIV of the Directive / Schedule 3 of the Regulations. The Contracting Authority intends to voluntarily observe the award decision notices provisions and 10 day standstill period described in Regulation 86 of the Regulations. Unsuccessful Bidders will receive scores and reasons for the decision, including the characteristics and relative advantages of the winning bid and the reasons why the Bidder/application was unsuccessful. Deadline for lodging of appeals should be in accordance with Regulation 87 and Regulation 91 of the Regulations.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Somerset CCG</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Wynford House, Lufton Way, Lufton</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Yeovil</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>BA22 8HR</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1935381968</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>angelamortley@nhs.net</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.somersetccg.nhs.uk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>As described in VI.3, deadline for lodging of appeals should be in accordance with Regulation 87 and Regulation 91 of the 2015 Regulations.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Somerset CCG</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Wynford House, Lufton Way, Lufton</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Yeovil</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>BA22 8HR</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1935381968</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>angelamortley@nhs.net</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.somersetccg.nhs.uk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
