<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="188735-2018" EDITION="2018083"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-190590-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180528</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>83</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180428</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 083-188735</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:188735-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>https://www.gov.uk/government/organisations/defence-equipment-and-support</IA_URL_GENERAL><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="35723000">Air defence radar</ORIGINAL_CPV><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="CY">ΚΥΠΡΟΣ</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UK">UNITED KINGDOM</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS><VALUES_LIST><VALUES TYPE="GLOBAL"><SINGLE_VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="GBP">15 000 000</VALUE></SINGLE_VALUE></VALUES></VALUES_LIST></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180426</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180528 23:59</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>01217</HEADING><DIRECTIVE VALUE="2009/81/EC"/></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Радари за въздушна защита</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radar protivzdušné obrany</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Luftforsvarsradar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Luftverteidigungsradar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ραντάρ αεράμυνας</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Air defence radar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radares de defensa aérea</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Õhutõrjeradarid</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ilmatorjuntatutka</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radar de défense aérienne</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Air defence radar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radar zračne obrane</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Légvédelmi radar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radar di difesa antiaerea</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Oro erdvės gynybos radarai</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Pretgaisa aizsardzības radars</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radar għad-difiża ta' l-ajru</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Luchtafweerradar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radar obrony powietrznej</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radar de defesa aérea</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radar de apărare aeriană</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radar protivzdušnej obrany</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Radar zračne obrambe</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Henlow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Luftvärnsradar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Ministry of Defence, DE&amp;S Mat Strat, Air Defence &amp; Electronic Warfare Systems</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><CONTRACT_DEFENCE CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="17" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE CTYPE="SUPPLIES"><CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, DE&amp;S Mat Strat, Air Defence &amp; Electronic Warfare Systems</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Building 85, RAF Henlow</ADDRESS><TOWN>Henlow</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>SG16 6DN</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><CONTACT_POINT>Harry Williams</CONTACT_POINT><PHONE>+44 14628515154071</PHONE><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>DESADEWS-ComrclMgrSAS@mod.uk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><URL_GENERAL>https://www.gov.uk/government/organisations/defence-equipment-and-support</URL_GENERAL></INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><FURTHER_INFORMATION><IDEM/></FURTHER_INFORMATION><SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><IDEM/></SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO><IDEM/></TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO></NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY VALUE="MINISTRY"/><TYPE_OF_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF_NO/></PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><TITLE_CONTRACT><P>ADEWS/056 - Deployable Long Range Air Defence Radar System</P></TITLE_CONTRACT><TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><TYPE_CONTRACT VALUE="SUPPLIES"/><TYPE_SUPPLIES_CONTRACT VALUE="PURCHASE"/></TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><LOCATION_NUTS><LOCATION><P>ΚΥΠΡΟΣ, United Kingdom.</P></LOCATION><n2016:NUTS CODE="CY"/><n2016:NUTS CODE="UK"/></LOCATION_NUTS><SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><P>Air defence radar. The requirement is for a deployable longrange air defence radar system for operational use worldwide that is able to detect both co-operative and noncooperativetargets in the UK and overseas. The successful Contractor will supply: -One self-sustaining airdefence radar system, delivered to a location to be confirmed; -In service 3rd and 4th line support, commencingat acceptance, to achieve 95% availability throughout the contract; -Spares to achieve 95% availabilitythroughout the contract, including a deployable spares pack; -Operator and technician training; -Operator andtechnical documentation. The contract will be for two years and six months.</P></SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><CPV><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="35723000"/></CPV_MAIN></CPV><SUBCONTRACTING><INDICATE_ANY_SHARE VALUE="YES"/><INDICATE_ANY_CHANGE VALUE="YES"/><SUBCONTRACT_AWARD_PART VALUE="NO"/><IDENTIFY_SUBCONTRACT VALUE="NO"/></SUBCONTRACTING><F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><DIV_INTO_LOT_NO/></F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><ACCEPTED_VARIANTS VALUE="NO"/></DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><QUANTITY_SCOPE><NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><TOTAL_QUANTITY_OR_SCOPE><P>The successful Contractor shall supplythe Authority with a deployable long range air defence radar system that is able to detect both co-operativeand non-cooperative targets in the UK and overseas. The radar system shall be delivered to a location to beconfirmed; The selected radar system shall be capable of operating in 4 distinct configurations as follows: -UKFixed Site. A well found site with available power and links to existing fixed or deployable C2 system (includingsimultaneous use). Accessible by road/ferry. -UK Gap Fill Site. A site which may be well found or could be greenfield. Communications and power readily available through commercial or mil arrangements, but connected tofixed C2 system on an opportunity basis. Accessible by road/ferry. -Long-term Deployed. For example MiddleEast, where the site communications and power become established with time. Support from other Servicesmay be necessary to deliver the overall requirements. May require transport by organic RAF aircraft types. -Short-term Deployments. Including minimum 10 days readiness to move deployments overseas for ops andwithin the UK for exercise purposes. May require transport by organic RAF aircraft types. The selected radarsystem will meet the following Key User Requirements (KURs): </P><P>KUR 1 - The capability will be able to detectand track cooperative and non-cooperative objects. </P><P>KUR 2 - The capability will be interoperable with the UK ordeployed Air C2 system to enable compilation of the Recognised Air Picture. </P><P>KUR 3 - The capability will enablethe provision of assured Air Traffic Radar Services </P><P>KUR 4 - The capability shall be able to deploy and operateworldwide. </P><P>KUR 5 - The capability shall be self-sustainable anywhere in the world. </P><P>KUR 6 - The capabilityshall be resilient to degradation, deception and denial in the Electro Magnetic (EM), information and cyberdomains. </P><P>KUR 7 - The capability shall be resilient to the effects caused by anomalous propagation and complexclutter (including those associated with wind turbines). The successful Contractor will supply the Authority with3rd and 4th line support to achieve 95% availability throughout the contract. The successful Contractor willsupply the Authority with 1st and 2nd line support equipment, including special-to-type test tools and equipmentneeded to support the system. The successful Contractor will supply the Authority with spares to achieve 95%availability throughout the contract, including a fully deployable spares package. The successful Contractor willsupply the Authority with suitable operator and technician training prior to initial deployment, including trainingdocumentation. The successful Contractor will provide operator and technical documentation. Estimated valueexcluding VAT: 15,000,000 Currency: GBP </P></TOTAL_QUANTITY_OR_SCOPE><COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY CURRENCY="GBP"><VALUE_COST FMTVAL="15000000">15 000 000</VALUE_COST></COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY></NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><NO_OPTIONS/><NO_RECURRENT_CONTRACT/></QUANTITY_SCOPE></OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><P>The authority reserves the right to require an indemnity, guarantee or bank bond if the supplier does not meet the required standard for economic and financial standing.</P></DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><P>Payment will follow delivery and acceptance of the goods and services.</P></MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><LEGAL_FORM><P>If a group of economic operators submits a bid, the group must nominate a lead organisation to deal with the authority. The authority shall require the group to form a legal entity before entering into the contract.</P></LEGAL_FORM><EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS><P>The authority reserves the right to amend any condition related to security of information to reflect any changes in national law or government policy. If any contract documents are accompanied by a security aspects letter, the authority reserves the right to amend the terms of the security aspects letter to reflect any changes in national law or Government Policy whether in respect of the applicable protective marking scheme, specific protective markings given, the aspects to which any protective marking applies or otherwise.</P></EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS></CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><P>The authority will apply all the offences listed in Article 39(1) of Directive 2009/81/EC (implemented as Regulation 23(1) of the Defence and Security Public Contract Regulations (DSPCR) 2011 in the UK) and all of the professional misconducts listed at Article 39(2) of Directive 2009/81/EC (see also Regulation 23(2) in the DSPCR 2011) to the decision of whether a Candidate is eligible to be invited to tender.</P><P>A full list of the Regulation 23(1) and 23(2) criteria are at:</P><P>http://www.contracts.mod.uk/delta/project/reasonsForExclusion.html#dspr</P><P>Candidates will be required to sign a declaration confirming whether they do or do not have any of the listed criteria as part of the pre-qualification process.</P><P>Candidates who have been convicted of any of the offences under Article 39(1) are ineligible and will not be selected to bid, unless there are overriding requirements in the general interest (including defence and security factors) for doing so.</P><P>Candidates who are guilty of any of the offences, circumstances or misconduct under Article 39(2) may be excluded from being selected to bid at the discretion of the authority.</P><P>Candidates will be required to sign a declaration confirming whether they do or do not have any of the listed criteria as part of the pre-qualification process.</P></ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>(b) The presentation of balance-sheets or extracts from the balance-sheets, where publication of the balance-sheet is required under the law of the country in which the economic operator is established,</P><P>(c) where appropriate, a statement, covering the three previous financial years of the economic operator, of:(i) the overall turnover of the business of the economic operator; and (ii) where appropriate, the turnover in respect of the work, works, goods or services which are of a similar type to the subject matter of the contract.</P><P>At least 2 years audited accounts (if available) or equivalent must be submitted as part of the Pre-Qualification Questionnaire response. The Authority reserves the right to request further financial information following receipt of the Pre-Qualification Questionnaire response.</P></EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><EAF_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL><P>A financial assessment will be undertaken on the supplier’s financial status. An overall pass /fail judgement will be made after considering areas such as turnover, profit, net assets, liquidity, gearing and capacity. This assessment will include the parent company where applicable. An independent financial assessment obtained from a reputable credit rating organisation will be utilised as part of this process.</P></EAF_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL></F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY_SUBCONTRACTORS/><TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI><T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>(a) in the case of a supply contract requiring the siting or installation of goods, a services contract or a works contract, the economic operator's technical ability, taking into account in particular that economic operator's skills, efficiency, experience and reliability</P><P>(c) a statement of the principal goods sold or services provided by the supplier or the services provider in the past 5 years, or during a shorter period if necessary, and:</P><P>i— the dates on which the goods were sold or the services provided,</P><P>ii— the consideration received,</P><P>iii— the identity of the person to whom the goods were sold or the service were provided,</P><P>iv— any certificate issued or countersigned by that person confirming the details of the contract for those goods sold or services provided, and</P><P>v— where - (a) that person was not a contracting authority, and (b) the certificate referred to in sub-paragraph (c)(iv) is not available, any declaration by the economic operator attesting the details of the goods sold or services provided.</P><P>(d) A statement of the technicians or technical services available to the economic operator to:</P><P>i— carry out the work under the contract, or</P><P>ii— be involved in the production of goods or the provision of services under the contract, particularly those responsible for quality control, whether or not they are independent of the economic operator.</P><P>(e) a statement of the economic operator's:</P><P>i— technical facilities,</P><P>ii— measures for ensuring quality,</P><P>iii— study and research facilities, and</P><P>iv— internal rules regarding intellectual property.</P><P>(g) In the case of works contracts, services contracts or supply contracts also covering siting and installation operations or services, the economic operator's educational and professional qualifications where the economic operator is an individual and:</P><P>i— if any, those of the economic operator's managerial staff, and</P><P>ii— those of one or more persons who would be responsible for providing the services or carrying out the work or works under the contract.</P><P>(j) A description of the tools, material, technical equipment, staff numbers, know-how and sources of supply (with an indication of their geographical location when it is outside the territory of the EU) available to the economic operator to perform the contract, cope with any additional needs required by the contracting authority as a result of a crisis or carry out the maintenance, modernisation or adaptation of the goods covered by the contract.</P><P>(l) Certification by official quality control institutes or agencies of recognised competence, attesting that the goods to be purchased or hired under the contract conform to standards and technical specifications (within the meaning of regulation 12(1)) identified by the contracting authority.</P><P>(m) In the case of contracts involving, entailing or containing classified information, evidence of the ability to process, store and transmit such information at the level of protection required by the contracting authority.</P><P>(n) A certificate:</P><P>i— attesting conformity to quality management systems standards based on the relevant European standard, and</P><P>ii— from an independent accredited body established in any member State conforming to the European standards concerning accreditation and certification.</P><P>(o) Any other evidence of conformity to quality management systems standards which are equivalent to the standards referred to in sub-paragraph (n)(i)</P><P>As requested at </P><P>a) pre-qualification questionnaire stage, and</P><P>b) Invitation to Tender (ITT) Stage for those companies down selected to participate in the ITT Stage.</P></T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><T_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL><P>Demonstration of capability and capacity to deliver the advertised requirement in the suppliers pre-qualification questionnaire response.</P></T_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL></TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI></F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION></LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><PT_RESTRICTED/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED><OPE_MINIMUM_NUMBER>3</OPE_MINIMUM_NUMBER><OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA><P>Potential contractors will be selected using a Pre-Qualification Questionnaire (PQQ).</P><P>Suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P><P>The information and/or documents for this opportunity are available on http://www.contracts.mod.uk</P><P>You must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password. Please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P><P>Suppliers must log in, go to your response manager and add the following access code: J3H4863EMY</P><P>The authority will use the PQQ response to create a shortlist of tenderers who:</P><P>1) are eligible to participate under Section III.2.1) of this Contract Notice,</P><P>2) fulfill any minimum standards under Sections III.2.2) and III.2.3) of this contract notice, and</P><P>3) best meet in terms of capacity and capability the selection criteria set out Sections III.2.2) and III.2.3) of this contract notice.</P></OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA></MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><MOST_ECONOMICALLY_ADVANTAGEOUS_TENDER><CRITERIA_STATED_IN_OTHER_DOCUMENT/></MOST_ECONOMICALLY_ADVANTAGEOUS_TENDER></AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE><NO_USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION/></IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE></AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><P>ADEWS/056</P></FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17><NO_PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_EXISTS_F17/></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17><CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><NO_PAYABLE_DOCUMENTS/></CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><DAY>28</DAY><MONTH>05</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>23:59</TIME></RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><LANGUAGE><LANGUAGE_EC VALUE="EN"/></LANGUAGE></ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE></PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/><RELATES_TO_EU_PROJECT_NO/><ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><P>The authority reserves the right to amend any condition related to security of information to reflect any changes in national law or government policy. If any contract documents are accompanied by instructions on safeguarding classified information (e.g. a security aspects letter), the authority reserves the right to amend the terms of these instructions to reflect any changes in national law or government policy, whether in respect of the applicable protective marking scheme, specific protective markings given, the aspects to which any protective marking applies, or otherwise. The link below to the Gov.uk website provides information on the Government Security Classification.</P><P>https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/government-security-classifications</P><P>Advertising regime OJEU:</P><P>— This contract opportunity is published in the Official Journal of the European Union (OJEU),the MoD Defence contracts bulletin and www.contracts.mod.uk</P><P>Electronic trading - potential suppliers must note the mandatory requirement for electronic trading using the Contracting, Purchasing and Finance (CP&amp;F) electronic procurement tool. All payments for contractor deliverables under the contract shall only be made via CP&amp;F. You can find details on CP&amp;F at https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/mod-contracting-purchasing-and-finance-e-procurement-system</P><P>Use of electronic tender management system - The authority will use the award tender management system to manage the ITT stage of the competition.</P><P>Suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P><P>The information and /or documents for this opportunity are available on http://www.contracts.mod.uk</P><P>You must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password. Please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P><P>Suppliers must log in, go to your Response Manager and add the following Access Code: J3H4863EMY</P><P>Please ensure you follow any instruction provided to you here.</P><P>The deadline for submitting your response(s) is detailed within this contract notice, you will also have visibility of the deadline date, once you have added the access code via DCO as the opening and closing date is visible within the opportunity.</P><P>Please ensure that you allow yourself plenty of time when responding to this opportunity prior to the closing date and time, especially if you have been asked to upload documents.</P><P>If you experience any difficulties please refer to the online Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ&#x92;s) or the user guides or contact the MOD DCO Helpdesk by emailing support@contracts.mod.uk or Telephone 0800 282 324</P><P>GO Reference: GO-2018426-DCB-12310627</P></ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, DE&amp;S Mat Strat, Air Defence &amp; Electronic Warfare Systems</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><TOWN>Henlow</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>SG16 6DN</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>DESADEWS-ComrclMgrSAS@mod.uk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE></PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE><DAY>26</DAY><MONTH>04</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR></NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE></CONTRACT_DEFENCE></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>