<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="080781-2018"
            EDITION="2018037">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-082639-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180327</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>37</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180222</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 037-080781</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:080781-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>https://www.contracts.mod.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://www.contracts.mod.uk</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71900000">Laboratory services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKK13">Gloucestershire</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKK13">Gloucestershire</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">300000</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180220</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180327 11:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Лабораторни услуги</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratorní služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratorieundersøgelser</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Labordienste</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Εργαστηριακές υπηρεσίες</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratory services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de laboratorio</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboriteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratoriopalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de laboratoire</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratory services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratorijske usluge</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratóriumi szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di laboratorio</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratorijų paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratorijas pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' laboratorju</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratoriumdiensten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi laboratoryjne</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços laboratoriais</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de laborator</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratórne služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratorijske storitve</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Gloucester</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laboratorietjänster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C, Other</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C, Other</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>F10, Innsworth House, Imjin Barracks</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Gloucester</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>GL3 1HW</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Tina Cole (Tel Ext 7487)</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+44 1452712612</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>defcomrclcc-hocs4mu@mod.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK13"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://www.contracts.mod.uk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://www.contracts.mod.uk</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="MINISTRY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>DNA and Genealogy Services</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>HOCS4/00012</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="71900000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The Ministry of Defence (MOD) Joint Casualty and Compassionate Centre (JCCC), Commemorative casework team are responsible for co-ordinating efforts to establish the identity of historic human remains recovered from battlefields and aircraft crash sites involving British service personnel and arranging a fitting burial. DNA analysis may be required to assist with confirming the identities of the remains where other methods have proved inconclusive. Genealogy services may also be required to assist in the identification process. The contract will be for the provision of DNA and Genealogy services.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">300000</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK13"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Gloucestershire.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The Contractor must be complaint with the Forensic Science Society, ISO/IEC 17025:2017, ISO9001:2000 or other appropriate equivalent industry standards.</P>
                  <P>The Contractor will be required to:</P>
                  <P>— obtain DNA profiles from remains (usually from teeth or bone samples);</P>
                  <P>— undertake DNA profiling of the Y chromosome, to access the paternal lineage and mitochondrial DNA to determine the maternal lineage of human remains such a as bone and/or tissue samples (within 1 month of receiving a sample for Y and 2 months for mitochondrial);</P>
                  <P>— provide advice on best possible living source of DNA profile for comparison purposes and genealogy if required;</P>
                  <P>— provide DNA sampling kits to individuals who volunteer to provide a sample for comparison purposes;</P>
                  <P>— analyse test results and compare them with the profile obtained from the historic sample;</P>
                  <P>— retest samples at the request of the Authority and make recommendations as to alternative scientific methods to obtain DNA profiles for comparison where said profiles cannot initially be obtained.</P>
                  <P>And produce various reports.</P>
                  <P>The contractor must ensure that remains are handled in accordance with worldwide legislation and regulations, including data protection requirements.</P>
                  <P>The contractor may be required to visit the location (in Europe, Asia, North America and Africa) where the recovered remains are held.</P>
                  <P>The number of cases will vary depending on the number of remains recovered and therefore it is not possible to say how many cases the Authority will require the Contractor to undertake, however as a guide there have been 15 cases in the last 12 months. The contractor will be requested to undertake cases as required on a call- off basis.</P>
                  <P>No business whatsoever is guaranteed under any resulting framework agreement or contract indeed there is no guarantee that any framework agreement or contract will be put in place in relation to this notice. No compensation etc. will be paid if a tender or resulting framework agreement is withdrawn for any reason. Bidders should take part in this process only on the basis that they fully understand and accept this position.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">300000</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">48</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>An option will be included for the Authority at its discretion to extend beyond the 2 year contract in monthly or annual increments up to an additional 24 months.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>2 years audited accounts or equivalent must be provided with the Suppliers tender response.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>A financial assessment will be undertaken on the supplier's financial status. An overall pass/fail judgement will be made considering areas such as turnover, profit, net assets, liquidity, gearing and capacity. This assessment will include the Parent company where applicable. An independent financial assessment obtained from a reputable credit rating organisation may be utilised as part of this process.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Suppliers are required to complete a Suitability assessment questionnaire (SAQ) which contains all the mandatory suitability and technical standards that are required to perform the contract.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Any resultant contract will be subject to the conditions detailed in the draft HOCS4/00012 Contract document, which uses MOD Standardised contracting template SC2. As well as containing General conditions, it contains conditions relating to supply of contract deliverables, Licences and intellectual property, Pricing and payment, Termination, Framework agreements, Cyber security, Contract price and delivery. Specific Conditions include:</P>
               <P>TUPE – It is the supplier’s responsibility to consider whether or not TUPE applies to this re-let and to tender accordingly. Notwithstanding this, supplier’s may wish to note that it is the Authority’s view that TUPE is unlikely to be applicable as the contractor currently undertaking this task, LGC Ltd, has informed the Authority that no employees are in scope for transfer. The Authority shall not be liable for this opinion and it remains the supplier’s responsibility to ensure that their tender takes full account of all the relevant circumstances of this contract re-let.</P>
               <P>Electronic trading – Potential suppliers must note the mandatory requirement for electronic trading using the Contracting, purchasing and finance (CP&amp;F) electronic procurement tool. All payments for contractor deliverables under the contract shall only be made via CP&amp;F. You can find details on CP&amp;F at https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/mod-contracting-purchasing-and-finance-e-procurement-system</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <FRAMEWORK>
               <SINGLE_OPERATOR/>
            </FRAMEWORK>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-03-27</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>11:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DATE_TENDER_VALID>2018-06-25</DATE_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-03-27</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>11:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Imjin Barracks, Gloucester.</P>
               </PLACE>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>The MOD Tender Board process will apply.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The Contracting Authority considers that this contract may be suitable for economic operators that are small or medium enterprises (SMEs). However, any selection of tenderers will be based solely on the criteria set out for the procurement.The Authority reserves the right to amend any condition related to security of information to reflect any changes in national law or government policy. If any contract documents are accompanied by instructions on safeguarding classified information (e.g. a Security Aspects Letter), the Authority reserves the right to amend the terms of these instructions to reflect any changes in national law or government policy, whether in respect of the applicable protective marking scheme, specific protective markings given, the aspects to which any protective marking applies, or otherwise. The link below to the Gov.uk website provides information on the Government security classification.</P>
               <P>https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/government-security-classifications</P>
               <P>Advertising Regime OJEU: — This contract opportunity is published in the Official Journal of the European Union (OJEU),the MoD Defence contracts bulletin and www.contracts.mod.uk</P>
               <P>Suppliers should complete Part 1 and Part 2 of the Suitability assessment questionnaire (SAQ) (see www.contracts.mod.uk –access Code V7EWKQBKS3) which contains all the mandatory economic and financial grounds for rejection and the minimum levels of capacity and capability that are required to perform the contract. The SAQ will be used to reduce the number of eligible and qualified tenderers; it is a pass/fail test for suitability and minimum levels of capability and capacity. Suppliers who do not meet the minimum capability and capacity criteria will not pass to the Tender evaluation stage.</P>
               <P>Suppliers should be aware that if they decide to submit a tender for this requirement, they must also complete the Supplier Assurance questionnaire (SAQ) via the Supplier cyber protection service (https://supplier-cyber-protection.service.gov.uk/) to demonstrate their compliance with the required cyber risk level. The Cyber risk level for this requirement is “Very Low”. The Risk assessment reference (RAR) for this requirement is RAR-2X2W85VZ.</P>
               <P>Suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P>
               <P>The information and/or documents for this opportunity are available on http://www.contracts.mod.uk</P>
               <P>You must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password. Please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P>
               <P>Suppliers must log in, go to your Response Manager and add the following access code: V7EWKQBKS3.</P>
               <P>Please ensure you follow any instruction provided to you here.</P>
               <P>The deadline for submitting your response(s) is detailed within this contract notice, you will also have visibility of the deadline date, once you have added the Access code via DCO as the opening and closing date is visible within the opportunity.</P>
               <P>Please ensure that you allow yourself plenty of time when responding to this opportunity prior to the closing date and time, especially if you have been asked to upload documents.</P>
               <P>If you experience any difficulties please refer to the online frequently asked questions (FAQ&#x92;s) or the user guides or contact the MOD DCO Helpdesk by emailing support@contracts.mod.uk or Telephone 0800 282 324.</P>
               <P>GO Reference: GO-2018220-DCB-11943296.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C, Other</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>F10, Innsworth House, Imjin Barracks</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Gloucester</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>GL3 1HW</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1452712612</PHONE>
               <FAX>+44 1452510939</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_MEDIATION_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C, Other</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Abbey Wood</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bristol</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>BS34 8JH</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1179132548</PHONE>
            </ADDRESS_MEDIATION_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C, Other</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Abbey Wood</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bristol</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>BS34 8JH</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1179132548</PHONE>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-20</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
