<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="081060-2018"
            EDITION="2018037">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-082225-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180531</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>37</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180222</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 037-081060</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:081060-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>www.fmi.dk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="72000000">IT services: consulting, software development, Internet and support</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="DK0">DANMARK</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="DK0">DANMARK</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <REF_NOTICE>
            <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 012-023202</NO_DOC_OJS>
         </REF_NOTICE>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180220</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="7">Contract award notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="1">Lowest price</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C03</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Дaния</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>ИТ услуги: консултации, разработване на софтуер, Интернет и поддръжка</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Informační technologie: poradenství, vývoj programového vybavení, internet a podpora</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>It-tjenester: rådgivning, programmeludvikling, internet og support</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Dänemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-Dienste: Beratung, Software-Entwicklung, Internet und Hilfestellung</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Δανία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες τεχνολογίας των πληροφοριών: παροχή συμβουλών, ανάπτυξη λογισμικού, Διαδίκτυο και υποστήριξη</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Denmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT services: consulting, software development, Internet and support</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios TI: consultoría, desarrollo de software, Internet y apoyo</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Taani</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-teenused: nõuande-, tarkvaraarendus-, Interneti- ja tugiteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Tanska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tietotekniset palvelut: neuvonta, ohjelmistojen kehittäminen, Internet ja tuki</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Danemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de technologies de l'information, conseil, développement de logiciels, internet et appui</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Danmhairg, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT services: consulting, software development, Internet and support</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge informacijske tehnologije: savjetovanje, razvoj programske podrške, internet i podrška</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Dánia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-szolgáltatások: tanácsadás, szoftverfejlesztés, internet és támogatás</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Danimarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi informatici: consulenza, sviluppo di software, Internet e supporto</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Danija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT paslaugos: konsultavimas, programinės įrangos kūrimas, internetas ir aptarnavimo paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Dānija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT pakalpojumi konsultēšana, programmatūras izstrāde, internets un atbalsts</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>id-Danimarka</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' IT: konsulenza, żvilupp ta' softwer, Internet u appoġġ</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Denemarken</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-diensten: adviezen, softwareontwikkeling, internet en ondersteuning</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Dania</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi informatyczne: konsultacyjne, opracowywania oprogramowania, internetowe i wsparcia</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de TI: consultoria, desenvolvimento de software, Internet e apoio</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Danemarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii IT: consultanţă, dezvoltare de software, internet şi asistenţă</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Služby informačných technológií: konzultácie, vývoj softvéru, internet a podpora</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve informacijske tehnologije: svetovanje, razvoj programske opreme, internet in podpora</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-tjänster: konsultverksamhet, programvaruutveckling, Internet och stöd</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Danish Defence Acquisition and Logistics Organizations</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F03" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Danish Defence Acquisition and Logistics Organizations</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>16-28-71-80</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>Lautrupbjerg 1-5</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Ballerup</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2750</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Peter Thomsen</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+45 25574609</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>fmi-ja-s104@mil.dk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK0"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.fmi.dk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="MINISTRY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Acquisition of services</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="72000000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>This Contract concerns acquisition of Maintenance and Support to DALO´s HP Test Platform. DALO´s HP Test Platform includes software products from the HEWLETT-PACKARD Suite, such as HP ALM used for managing test throughout the application delivery lifecycle. DALO´s HP Test Platform includes the following software: HP QC Enterprise Integrator for SAP, HP QC Ent Site 5 CC Usr Pk SW, HP QC Ent Site USR SW, HP FT Site CC Usr ExistCust SW, HP ALM Site CC Usr SW E-LTU. To ensure a stable, secure, and reliable platform, DALO wants to enter into this Contract, which ensures Maintenance and Support on all current software products, cf. DALO´s HP Test Platform. Furthermore the Contract includes the option to deliver scaling of Maintenance and Support for software products that are included in DALO´s HP test platform.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK0"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>See II.1.4) Short description for more information.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PRICE/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>DALO has the option to deliver scaling includes maintenance and support for: 10 additional HP QC Enterprise Integrator for SAP, 10 additional HP QC Ent Site 5 CC Usr Pk SW, 10 additional HP QC Ent Site USR SW, 10 additional HP FT Site CC Usr ExistCust SW, 10 additional HP ALM Site CC Usr SW E-LTU.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>The Contract is not divided into lots on the grounds that a division of the contract would undermine the economies of scale obtainable by procuring one contract.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 012-023202</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <NO_AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <PROCUREMENT_UNSUCCESSFUL/>
            </NO_AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>This public procurement is transitioning to a competitive procedure with negotiation in accordance with section 80, litra 1, of the Danish Public Procurement Act. Under section 80, litra a, DALO may apply a competitive procedure with negotiation ‘no requests for participation or tenders have been received’ As DALO has received notenders, DALO has assessed that the legal basis for transitioning to a competitive procedure with negotiation is fulfilled.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Klagenævnet for udbud (The Complaints Board for Public Procurement) Nævnenes Hus</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Toldboden 2</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Viborg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>8800</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 72405708</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>klfu@naevneneshus.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>http://erhvervsstyrelsen.dk/klagenaevnet-for-udbud</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Pursuant to Section 3 of the Danish Consolidation Act no. 593 of 2.6.2016 on the Complaints Board for Public Procurement (available at www.retsinformation.dk), the following time limits for filing a complaint apply:</P>
               <P>Complaints regarding public procurements and decisions subject to Chapter II or III of the Public Procurement Act, which does not concern a candidate not being invited to tender, must in accordance with § 7(2) of the Act on The Complaints Board for Public Procurement be filed with The Complaints Board for Public Procurement within:</P>
               <P>1) 45 calendar days after the contracting authority has published a contract award notice in the Official Jour-nal of the European Union (with effect from the day following the publication date).</P>
               <P>2) 30 calendar days starting the day after the contracting authority has informed the tenderers in question, that the contracting authority has entered into a contract based on a framework agreement through reopening of competition or a dynamic purchasing system, provided that the notification includes a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P>
               <P>3) 6 months starting the day after the contracting authority has sent notification to the candidates/tenderers involved that the contracting authority has entered into the framework agreement, cf. § 2(2) or § 171(4) of the Public Procurement Act, provided that the notification included a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P>
               <P>4) 20 calendar days starting the day after the contracting authority has published a notice concerning his deci-sion to uphold the contract, cf. § 185(2) of the Public Procurement Act.</P>
               <P>The complainant must inform the contracting authority of the complaint in writing at the latest simultaneously with the lodge of the complaint to The Complaints Board for Public Procurement stating whether the complaint has been lodged in the stand-still period, cf. § 6(4) of the Act on The Complaints Board for Public Procurement. If the complaint has not been lodged in the stand-still period, the complainant must also state whether it is requested that the appeal is granted delaying effect, cf. § 12(1) of the said Act.</P>
               <P>The e-mail of The Complaints Board for Public Procurement is stated in section VI.4.1.</P>
               <P>The Complaints Board for Public Procurement’s own guidance note concerning complaints is available at the internet address stated in section VI.4.1.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Konkurrence- og Forbrugerstyrelsen (The Danish Competition and Consumer Authority)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Carl Jacobsens Vej 35</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Valby</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2500</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 41715000</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>kfst@kfst.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.kfst.dk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-20</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
