<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="149010-2018"
            EDITION="2018067">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-151946-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180504</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>67</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180406</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 067-149010</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:149010-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.transport.gov.scot</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="73200000">Research and development consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="73000000">Research and development services and related consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="73210000">Research consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKM82">Glasgow City</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKM82">Glasgow City</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">2000000</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180404</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180504 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="N">National or federal Agency/Office</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Глазгоу</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Консултантски услуги, свързани с научни изследвания и експериментални разработки</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Poradenství v oblasti výzkumu a vývoje</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Konsulentvirksomhed inden for forskning og udvikling</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Beratung im Bereich Forschung und Entwicklung</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Γλασκώβη</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σε θέματα έρευνας και ανάπτυξης</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Research and development consultancy services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de consultoría en investigación y desarrollo</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Uurimis- ja arendustöö nõustamisteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tutkimus- ja kehitystoiminnan konsulttipalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de conseil en recherche et développement</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glaschú</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Research and development consultancy services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge savjetovanja na području istraživanja i razvoja</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kutatási és fejlesztési tanácsadó szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Consulenza nel campo della ricerca e dello sviluppo</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Mokslinių tyrimų ir taikomosios veiklos konsultacinės paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glāsgova</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pētniecības un izstrādes konsultāciju pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' konsulenza dwar ir-riċerka u l-iżvilupp</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Advies inzake onderzoek en ontwikkeling</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi doradcze w zakresie badań i rozwoju</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de consultoria em matéria de investigação e desenvolvimento</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de consultanţă în cercetare şi în dezvoltare</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Poradenstvo pre výskum a vývoj</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve svetovanja na področju raziskav in razvoja</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>FoU-rådgivning</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Transport Scotland</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>28062dac-bef9-4066-a8c7-4a1c38c99dae</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Transport Scotland</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Buchanan House, 58 Port Dundas Road</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Glasgow</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>G4 0HF</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1412727100</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>researchmfa@transport.gov.scot</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+44 1412727272</FAX>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM82"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.transport.gov.scot</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/search/Search_AuthProfile.aspx?ID=AA00099</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CENTRAL_PURCHASING/>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="NATIONAL_AGENCY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Multiple Framework Agreement for Transport Research</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>TS/TRBO/SER/2017/04</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73200000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Transport Scotland has identified a continuing need to appoint Consultants to provide transport research services which will include data collection, analysis, evaluation, reviews, reports and recommendations relating to construction, operation, improvement and maintenance of Scottish transport infrastructure. It is anticipated that the service providers will offer Scottish Ministers the benefits of combined industry and academic knowledge and experience.</P>
               <P>The principal services shall comprise the provision of a consultancy service for research, advice and guidance on the development in all aspects of design standards, specifications and materials typically but not exclusive to geotechnics, drainage, road safety, structures, maintenance operation of transport infrastructure assets, traffic and transportation, environment and sustainability and the provision of advice in relation to technical specifications and publications.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">2000000</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="73000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="73210000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM82"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Transport Scotland, Glasgow</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The framework agreement/contract will be in place for a period of 4 years to award research tasks and continue beyond that period until the satisfactory completion of tasks awarded.</P>
                  <P>Transport Scotland is an agency of the Scottish Government and contracts in the name of and on behalf of the Scottish Ministers. Transport Scotland has identified the requirement to appoint a Consultant/Contractor to perform transport related research on behalf of public Roads Authorities in Scotland. It has been concluded that this requirement would be best met through the use of a multiple supplier framework agreement.</P>
                  <P>The intent of this competition is to procure three suitably experienced service providers (“Framework Participants”) that will permit the execution of services/works in relation to projects of varying size, complexity and value.</P>
                  <P>Having 3 Framework Participants will provide flexibility to cover situations where potential conflicts of interest or capacity issues arise.</P>
                  <P>The consultancy services will be called off from the framework agreement on the basis of a rotation beginning with the most economic advantageous tender. However, for services of a particular complexity or value the Employer will have the option to run mini-competitions. Mini-competitions will be automatically held for projects with an estimated value above 75 000 GBP.</P>
                  <P>The Contractor will be procured through a competitive tender procedure, in accordance with the restricted procedure as provided for in the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015.</P>
                  <P>To be considered for this Contract economic operators are required to complete the European Single Procurement Document (ESPD) in accordance with this Contract Notice. Economic operators shall be evaluated in accordance with the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015, on the basis of information they have provided within the ESPD.</P>
                  <P>The ESPD can be downloaded via the Public Contracts Scotland portal (www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk).The scope of works will include, but not limited to:</P>
                  <P>Transport Research Services.</P>
                  <P>The framework agreement shall be the basis of the award of specific contract tasks for the provision of research services.</P>
                  <P>The principal services shall comprise the provision of a consultancy service for research, advice and guidance on the development in all aspects of DMRB design standards, specifications and materials typically but not exclusive to geotechnical, drainage, road transport, safety, structures, maintenance operation of transport infrastructure assets, traffic and transportation, environment and sustainability.</P>
                  <P>The Services shall include data collection, analysis, evaluation, reviews, reports, research and recommendations relating to the construction, operation, improvement and maintenance of road transport infrastructure.</P>
                  <P>This shall include both the performance of the service and the provision of advice in relation to the service. In addition, the service provider shall provide advice in relation to technical specifications or publications. Other services may be required to be undertaken from time to time, including similar services related to railway and other transport infrastructure.</P>
                  <P>The service provider may be required to provide seconded staff to be located in the offices of Transport Scotland.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>The assessment will be on the approach to the execution and programming of the Services; provision of suitable staff; management of resources and risks; innovation; adding value and community benefits</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>70</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>30</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">48</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NB_MIN_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>3</NB_MIN_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>6</NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>It is intended that between three and six economic operators be taken forward to tender stage. These economic operators shall be those who have:</P>
                  <P>(i) submitted a compliant submission, comprising the completed ESPD;</P>
                  <P>(ii) satisfied the relevant selection criteria under the exclusion grounds;</P>
                  <P>(iii) (a) Minimum Standards of Eligibility —- provided evidence of working on specified types of projects over a specified value; and</P>
                  <P>(b) Technical or Professional Ability — provided evidence demonstrating an acceptable level of technical or professional ability.</P>
                  <P>(c) Human Resources — possess the necessary human resources, qualified appropriately to perform the requirement.</P>
                  <P>(iv) has in place quality, environmental and health and safety management systems and/or has in place appropriate sustainability measures which attribute significantly to the requirement;</P>
                  <P>(v) satisfied minimum standards of economic and financial standing;</P>
                  <P>(vi) achieved the first, second, third, fourth or fifth highest combined weighted scores in respect of technical or professional ability calculated in accordance with the responses to Statements (d), (e), (f) and (g) (refer to Section III.1.3).</P>
                  <P>However, if an economic operator has not submitted a compliant submission as described in (i) above, failed in respect of either (ii), (iii), (iv) or (v) above, then that economic operator shall be excluded from the ranking of scores described in (vi) as above.</P>
                  <P>Economic operators shall be required to self-certify their adherence to the above selection criteria via the ESPD (Question Ref. 5.1). Suppliers shall be required to submit appropriate means of proof at a later stage as stated in Regulation 60 of the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015.</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>The statement for an OJEU notice:</P>
                  <P>Economic operators may be excluded from this competition if they are in any of the situations referred to in regulation 58 of the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Economic operators must be enrolled in the relevant professional or trade registers kept in the Member state of its establishment (as described in Schedule 5 of the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015) (i.e. registered under Companies House). Economic operators should provide details under Question Ref. 4A.1.</P>
               <P>Qualifications and Experience.</P>
               <P>It is a requirement of the Contract that staff employed under the Contract shall have minimum levels of experience, education and professional qualifications. In particular, the top management of the frameworks appointee shall be a Chartered Professional or equivalent with considerable experience at a senior level of managing integrated teams and other specialisms relevant to the provision and performance of the services.</P>
               <P>The Framework Manger shall be a Chartered Professional or equivalent with recognised professional qualifications relevant to highway design with considerable post chartered experience in a senior position of managing integrated design teams relevant to the provision and performance of the Services under a Task Order.</P>
               <P>Principal Roads and Related Infrastructure Engineer/Professional shall be a Chartered Professional in a relevant discipline with substantial relevant experience (a minimum of 10 years) relevant to the Services. Membership of a Chartered Institution or equivalent in a relevant profession is also required.</P>
               <P>Senior Roads and Related Infrastructure Engineer/Professional/ Senior Researcher shall be capable of carrying out elements of the task orders under the supervision of the Principal Roads Engineer and be Chartered or working towards achieving Chartered status within two years with a relevant professional body with a minimum of five years post-qualification experience or a Senior Researcher educated to degree level with a minimum of five years post-qualification experience in related transport research projects.</P>
               <P>Roads and Related Infrastructure Engineer/Professional/ Researcher shall be capable of carrying out elements of the task orders under direct supervision, be educated to degree level and have a minimum of three years of post-qualification experience relevant to the commission.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>Economic Operators shall be required to satisfy minimum standards of economic and financial standing. To determine these standards, Economic Operators shall:</P>
               <P>(a) in response to ESPD, Question Ref. 4B.1.1 provide the specified annual turnover for the last two years of trading, or for the period which is available if trading for less than 2 years;</P>
               <P>(b) in response to ESPD, Question Ref. 4B.4 provide the name, value and/or range of NINE financial criteria for the last two years of trading, or for the period which is available if trading for less than two years; and</P>
               <P>(c) in response to ESPD, Question Ref. 4B.5.1 confirm they already have or can commit to obtain, prior to commencement of the contract the required levels of insurance.</P>
               <P>In addition to the information requested under (a) and (b), economic operators are required to provide a link / copies of the associated annual accounts as filed at Companies House (or equivalent if not a UK registered company) for the last two years of trading, or for the period which is available if less than 2 years.</P>
               <P>This information has been requested to enable Transport Scotland to perform their own assessment and confirm the financial ratios submitted. Ultimately, ensuring the correct score is allocated, and to ensure no misinterpretation. Where there exist differences in ratios, between those provided and those calculated by Transport Scotland, clarification will be sought.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Economic operators shall be required to satisfy minimum standards of economic and financial standing. These are described below:</P>
               <P>Evaluation Criteria Ratios (Question Ref. 4B.4).</P>
               <P>The financial information received under ESPD, Question Ref. 4B.4 shall be evaluated and scored out of 50 by allocating a score against nine individual economic and financial standing evaluation criteria, namely:</P>
               <P>1) Acid Test Ratio</P>
               <P>2) Cash Interest Cover Ratio</P>
               <P>3) Return on Capital Employed</P>
               <P>4) Operating Profit Ratio</P>
               <P>5) Net Worth</P>
               <P>6) Gearing</P>
               <P>7) Annual Contract Value to Turnover</P>
               <P>8) Filed Accounts</P>
               <P>9) Audit Report</P>
               <P>The individual scores shall be weighted, with the most recent (Year 1) financial statements weighted at 67 % and the previous (Year 2) statements being weighted at 33 %, to form an aggregated score for each of the nine criteria over the two years.</P>
               <P>The maximum cumulative score resulting from the summation of the nine economic and financial standing aggregated scores shall be 50 marks. A submission shall be marked as a FAIL and will not be considered further if the score achieved by a Single Economic Operator or a Group of Economic Operators is less than 50 percent of the available marks. The scoring mechanism can be downloaded via the Public Contracts Scotland portal www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk.</P>
               <P>Where the submission has been submitted by a Group of Economic Operators, the information submitted by each Group Member will be evaluated in the proportion of the percentage shareholdings or percentage equity/interest of each Group Member and a score determined for such Group of Economic Operators on that basis.</P>
               <P>Insurance (Question Ref. 4B.5).</P>
               <P>In response to Question Ref. 4B.5.1 economic operators must confirm they already have or can commit to obtain, prior to the commencement the following levels of insurance:</P>
               <P>Public Liability Insurance = 5 000 000 GBP</P>
               <P>Professional Indemnity Insurance = 5 000 000 GBP</P>
               <P>And, in response to Question Ref. 4B.5.2 economic operators must confirm they already have or can commit to obtain any other insurance, including Employers Liability, required by the Contract or by the appropriate legislation, with a sum insured / limit of indemnity to satisfy the Contract or legal requirements.</P>
               <P>In responding to Question Ref. 4B.5.1 and 4B.5.2 of the ESPD, where the bidder ticks the box “No, and I cannot commit to obtain it” they shall be marked as FAIL and shall be excluded from this procurement competition.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>ESPD: Question Ref. 4C.1.2 — Using the tables provided economic operators shall be required to insert suitable responses to Statements (a) to (g) set out below, demonstrating that they have the required minimum standards of eligibility and technical and professional ability. Answers to these statements shall be answered by single economic operators and by groups of economic operators (group members should not respond individually). A "group of economic operators" is defined as an unincorporated consortium or joint venture.</P>
               <P>Responses to Statements (a), (b) and (c)* shall be assessed on the basis of PASS or FAIL. Economic Operators who fail to satisfy these minimum standards (either they answer ‘No’ or fail to provide an acceptable answer) shall be excluded from the procurement competition.</P>
               <P>The responses to Statements (d), (e), (f) and (g)*** shall be assessed on the basis of a score with a minimum threshold, using the following scoring mechanism:</P>
               <P>— Nil or inadequate response. Fails to demonstrate previous experience/capacity/capability relevant to this criterion (0 – 2 Unacceptable),</P>
               <P>— Response is partially relevant but generally poor. The response shows some elements of relevance to the criterion but contains insufficient/limited detail or explanation to demonstrate previous relevant experience/ capacity/capability (3 - 4 Weak),</P>
               <P>— Response is relevant and acceptable. The response demonstrates broad previous experience, knowledge and skills/capacity/capability but may lack in some aspects of similarity e.g. previous experience, knowledge or skills may not be of a similar nature (5 - 6 Acceptable),</P>
               <P>— Response is relevant and good. The response is sufficiently detailed to demonstrate a good amount of experience, knowledge or skills/capacity/capability relevant to providing similar services to similar clients (7 – 8 Good),</P>
               <P>— Response is completely relevant and excellent overall. The response is comprehensive, unambiguous and demonstrates thorough experience, knowledge or skills/capacity/capability relevant to providing similar services to similar clients (9 -10 Excellent).</P>
               <P>Under ESPD, Question Ref. 4C.7 economic operators shall be required to insert suitable responses to Statements (g), (h), and (i) demonstrating that they have in place an appropriate quality, environmental and health and safety management systems. Economic Operators should specify their recognised accredited system or own non-accredited system, which will ultimately shall be adopted if awarded the contract. Subsequently, under ESPD, Question Ref. 4D.1 economic operators are required to confirm their compliance and be able to provide the appropriate certification.</P>
               <P>The responses to Statements (g), (h) and (i) shall each be assessed on the basis of PASS or FAIL. Economic operators who obtain a FAIL in either of their responses shall not be considered further in this procurement competition.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Statement (a) — Within the last 5 years have you led on a transport research task for a client to the value of at least 20,000 GBP Sterling excluding VAT per annum? If yes, please provide details.</P>
               <P>Statement (b) — Within the last 5 years have you carried out research involving a specialist third party body or academic institution to produce validated conclusions for a client to the value of at least 20 000 GBP Sterling excluding VAT per annum? If yes, please provide details.</P>
               <P>Statement (c) — Within the last 5 years have you completed transport research tasks on differing subjects simultaneously for a client, each to the value of at least 20 000 GBP Sterling excluding VAT per annum? If yes, please provide details.</P>
               <P>Statement (d) — Contract performance (weighting 25 %) — From your reference projects, provide details on how you have maintained the availability of experienced and qualified key personnel to deliver the services required by the Employer on a series of projects, to the required standards, timescales and budgets.</P>
               <P>Statement (e) — Stakeholder Engagement (Weighting 25 %) — From your reference projects, provide details of your approach to working, managing and interfacing with key stakeholders including, but not limited partnering, skills transfer, knowledge sharing, links to academia, innovation, environmental performance, and flexibility of approach.</P>
               <P>Statement (f) — Best Practice and Innovation (Weighting 35 %) — From your reference projects, provide details of your approach to using and capturing best practice and forward thinking in research project delivery driven by innovation, while the rights, interests and requirements of all parties are protected.</P>
               <P>Statement (g) — Project management (Weighting 15 %) — From your reference projects, demonstrate the implementation of project management and quality controls to ensure the Services are delivered in accordance with the Employer’s requirements and best practice.</P>
               <P>Statement (h) — Quality Management System. This may be European Foundation Quality Model (EFQM) or equivalent; BS EN ISO 9001:2015 (Quality Management Systems); Other accredited management system; or Own non-accredited management system.</P>
               <P>Statement (i) — Environmental Management System. This may BS EN ISO 14001:2015 (Environmental Management Systems); Other accredited management system; or Own non-accredited management system.</P>
               <P>Statement (j) — Health and Safety Management System. This may BS EN ISO 18001:2007 (Occupational Health and Safety Management Systems) and associated standards; Other accredited management system; or Own non-accredited management system.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>It is the Employer’s policy to measure the performance of each Consultant on a regular basis.</P>
               <P>In the event that the Consultant’s performance falls below a satisfactory level, the Consultant will be invited to determine a means of rectifying the situation. Repeated or continual service failures may result in suspension or termination of the contract.</P>
               <P>Further details will be contained within the tender documents.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_RESTRICTED/>
            <FRAMEWORK>
               <SEVERAL_OPERATORS/>
               <NB_PARTICIPANTS>3</NB_PARTICIPANTS>
            </FRAMEWORK>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-05-04</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>2018-06-06</DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">3</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Transport Scotland will conduct the proposed procurement process for the Framework Agreement on behalf of the Scottish Ministers. In the event of the conclusion of the Framework Agreement, it is the intention that the Framework Agreement will be entered into between the Scottish Ministers and the most economically advantageous tenderers.</P>
               <P>Each selected economic operator shall be invited to submit a Tender on the same contract terms.</P>
               <P>The duration of the Framework Agreement referred to in paragraph II.2.7) of this notice is the original period of the proposed Framework Agreement.</P>
               <P>Each economic operator shall submit four paper copies (one marked "ORIGINAL" and three marked COPY 1, 2, or 3 as relevant) together with one USB flash drive copy of the completed ESPD, in a sealed package to arrive by no later than 12 noon BST/GMT on 4th May 2018 to the following addressee and address:</P>
               <P>Procurement Support Manager</P>
               <P>Transport Scotland</P>
               <P>Buchanan House</P>
               <P>58 Port Dundas Road</P>
               <P>Glasgow</P>
               <P>G4 0HF</P>
               <P>United Kingdom</P>
               <P>The submission, comprising the completed ESPD, shall be submitted via the Public Contracts Scotland portal, by no later than 12:00 hrs BST/GMT on 4.5.2018.</P>
               <P>The Scottish Ministers shall not evaluate any submission received past the specified deadline, unless the delay is caused by a situation out with the control of the economic operator, the determination of which shall be at the sole discretion of the Scottish Ministers. Compliance with achieving the specified deadline is the sole responsibility of the economic operator.</P>
               <P>Economic operators which alter their composition after making a submission will be the subject of re-evaluation.</P>
               <P>Any request by Economic Operators for clarification of any part of the documentation shall be made through the Public Contracts Scotland website. The deadline to submit questions relating to the submission via the Public Contracts Scotland portal is 12:00 hrs BST/GMT on 18.4.2018 with responses posted by 25.4.2018.</P>
               <P>Neither Transport Scotland nor the Scottish Ministers shall be responsible in any way to Economic Operators as a result of any delay or failure in answering any request for clarification or any decision not to answer a request for clarification (either in full or in part). Absence of a response from Transport Scotland or the Scottish Ministers shall not entitle Economic Operators to qualify their submission.</P>
               <P>The Scottish Ministers reserve the right not to conclude any Framework Agreement as a result of the procurement process initiated by this notice and to make whatever changes the Scottish Minsters deem appropriate to the content, process, timing and structure of the procurement process.</P>
               <P>Transport Scotland and the Scottish Ministers shall have no liability for any costs howsoever incurred by those participating in the competition.</P>
               <P>Economic operators should be aware that all information submitted to the Scottish Ministers may need to be disclosed and / or published by the Scottish Ministers in compliance with the Freedom of Information (Scotland) Act 2002 as amended.</P>
               <P>NOTE: To register your interest in this notice and obtain any additional information please visit the Public Contracts Scotland Web Site at http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/Search/Search_Switch.aspx?ID=537357</P>
               <P>(SC Ref:537357).</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Transport Scotland</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Buchanan House, 58 Port Dundas Road</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Glasgow</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>G4 0HF</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1412727100</PHONE>
               <FAX>+44 1412727272</FAX>
               <URL>http://www.transport.gov.scot</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-04</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
