<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="011434-2018"
            EDITION="2018007">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-009787-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20190108</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>7</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180111</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 007-011434</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:011434-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.nwsurreyccg.nhs.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="85100000">Health services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKJ2">Surrey, East and West Sussex</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKJ2">Surrey, East and West Sussex</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">44500000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180108</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="6">Body governed by public law</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="H">Health</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C01</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги на здравеопазването</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zdravotnické zabezpečení</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tjenesteydelser inden for sundhedsvæsenet</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dienstleistungen des Gesundheitswesens</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υγειονομικές υπηρεσίες</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Health services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de salud</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tervishoiuteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Terveyspalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de santé</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Health services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge u području zdravstva</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Egészségügyi szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi sanitari</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sveikatos priežiūros paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Veselības pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi tas-saħħa</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Gezondheidsdiensten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi ochrony zdrowia</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de saúde</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de sănătate</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zdravotnícke služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zdravstvene storitve</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Weybridge</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Hälsovårdstjänster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">East Surrey, Guildford &amp; Waverley, North West Surrey and Surrey Downs Clinical Commissioning Groups - North West Surrey CCG being the lead Commissioner)</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F01_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F01" LG="EN">
         <NOTICE TYPE="PRI_ONLY"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>East Surrey, Guildford &amp; Waverley, North West Surrey and Surrey Downs Clinical Commissioning Groups - North West Surrey CCG being the lead Commissioner)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Weybridge</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>KT13 8DP</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <E_MAIL>NHSCS.commissioning@nhs.net</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKJ2"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.nwsurreyccg.nhs.uk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="BODY_PUBLIC"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="HEALTH"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Procurement for the provision of a Surrey Integrated Urgent Care Service (Including NHS111, Clinical Assessment Service and GP Out-of-hours)</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="85100000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The Clinical Commissioning Groups identified in Section I.1 will be referred to in this Notice as the Awarding Authority.</P>
               <P>The Awarding Authority intends to approach the market to procure and award, for registered and resident patients within the commissioning geography, a contract to ensure the provision of a fully integrated 24/7 Integrated Urgent Care Service incorporating a combined NHS 111 and GP Out-of-Hours Treatment service which will provide clinical assessment and face to face treatment.</P>
               <P>Market Engagement:</P>
               <P>— since November 2016, the Awarding Authorities have been running a comprehensive market engagement process open to all. — — the outcomes of this engagement can be viewed via this web link:</P>
               <P>— — http://www.nwsurreyccg.nhs.uk/Get-involved/111/Pages/Potential-Providers.aspx.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">44500000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="85100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKJ2"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>The geographic area in Surrey covered by the referenced CCGs.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Current Service Provision:</P>
                  <P>— the NHS 111 service is currently managed at a regional level, with two local GP Out-of-Hours services which are managed by the nominated Clinical Commissioning Groups.</P>
                  <P>— this procurement has arisen as a consequence of the forthcoming expiry of the existing independent contracts coinciding with the latest NHSE guidance.</P>
                  <P>— the NHS 111 service in Surrey rates in the top 15 % in the country for clinical excellence, so this is an opportunity to make the service even better. The existing NHS 111 contract covers Kent, Medway, Surrey and Sussex (KMSS) and is due to expire on 31st March 2019. GP Out-of-Hours service provision is currently provided by 2 separate contracts, 1 that covers Guildford and Waverley, North West Surrey and Surrey Downs CCG areas and a 2nd that covers the East Surrey CCG area and Sussex. Both GP Out-of-Hours contracts are also due to expire on 31st March 2019.</P>
                  <P>— the Awarding Authority seeks to award a contract to a single legal entity responsible for the provision and operation of a visionary IUC Service.</P>
                  <P>— this includes responsibility for the financial and budgetary management, budgetary analysis, clinical governance and overall contract management of the call center and interconnectivity with community services, emergency departments, primary care and ambulance services to maximise patient care efficiency within the system pathway.</P>
                  <P>— the Provider will be required to deliver a service that offers a seamless patient journey from NHS 111 contact/online access, to the establishment of a treatment plan (including direct electronic appointment booking) or closure on advice.</P>
                  <P>Envisaged Tender Process:</P>
                  <P>— full explanatory tender documentation will be made available via the Bravo system on the publication of the PQQ. See Section V1.3 for the indicative timetable and Bravo registration information.</P>
                  <P>— the Awarding Authorities wish to establish the Most Economically Advantageous Tender (“MEAT”) for the Contract.</P>
                  <P>— the envisaged for contract award will be for a five year period, with an option to extend once for up to three years.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>See Section VI.3.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>2018-02-05</DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>All interested parties should note that this Service Procurement falls within the scope of the “Light Touch Regime” as defined in the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 (as amended) and Directive 2014/24/EU. Therefore the 2015 Regulations and the 2014 Directive are only applicable to the Service Procurement to the extent required for the Services.</P>
               <P>The Awarding Authority has decided to follow a tendering procedure for the Service Procurement which is akin to the Restricted Procedure, as provided for under the 2015 regulations and the 2014 Directive, and throughout this tender and associated documentation, the terminology linked to a Restricted Procedure is used.</P>
               <P>This should not, however, be taken as an acceptance by The Awarding Authority that any part of the 2015 Regulations or the 2014 Directive (other than those provisions specifically applicable to the Light Touch Regime Procurement) apply to this Service Procurement.</P>
               <P>The Awarding Authority will also observe the requirements of the Procurement Patient Choice and Competition Regulations 2013 (PPCCR 2013).</P>
               <P>The Invitation to Tender will be open to all suitably qualified providers. This notice is voluntary and does not mean that the Awarding Authority accepts that the Regulations apply to this intended procurement to any greater extent just by virtue of the publication of the notice or utilization of a particular procurement process. The Awarding Authority reserves the right to amend any or all procedures and timescales indicated in this PIN.</P>
               <P>The following timetable is provided for the information of potential bidders. The Awarding Authorities reserve the right at their absolute discretion to amend this timetable, or not to proceed with the procurement process at all.</P>
               <P>— 5th February 2018: the release of PQQ,</P>
               <P>— 6th March 2018 12:00 noon: closing date for PQQ submissions,</P>
               <P>— 29th March 2018: all bidders notified of PQQ outcome,</P>
               <P>— 4th April 2018: Issue ITT to qualified Bidders,</P>
               <P>— 18th May 2018 12: noon: closing date for ITT submissions,</P>
               <P>— June 2018: Presentation/clarification meetings (date to be confirmed).</P>
               <P>— July 2018: Governing Body ratifications of Recommended Provider,</P>
               <P>— July/August 2018: notification of contract award and begin of standstill-period,</P>
               <P>— August 2018: contract signature followed by mobilization,</P>
               <P>— 1 April 2019: service commencement.</P>
               <P>Registration Information for Potential Providers:</P>
               <P>— the tender will be conducted via the NHS Commercial Solutions Bravo e tendering system. Bidders wishing to Express an Interest (EOI) in participating will be required to register on the Bravo system if they have not previously done so. This can be done at any time via this web link:</P>
               <P>— — https://commercialsolutions.bravosolution.co.uk</P>
               <P>— NHS Commercial Solutions is utilizing the Bravo system to administer this Procurement and to communicate with potential Bidders. Accordingly, there will be no hard copy documents issued to potential Bidders. Once the tender is published, all Provider communications with the Awarding Authority and NHS Commercial Solutions will only be conducted via the Bravo secure messaging service within the portal hosted by BravoSolution, the managed service provider for the NHS Commercial Solutions e-Tendering system.</P>
               <P>— it is free to register on the portal, and it can be accessed at any time of day. Should Bidders have any queries, or if Bidders are having problems registering on the portal, they should contact the BravoSolution dedicated Supplier Support, available from the Bravo Help-desk:</P>
               <P>— — phone: 0800 368 4850 (Monday to Friday 9 am to 6 pm),</P>
               <P>— — e-mail: help@bravosolution.co.uk</P>
               <P>— the Bravo Project number for this tender will be Project 2663.</P>
               <P>— the Bravo Pre-Qualification Questionnaire number will be pqq_951.</P>
               <P>NOTE: The project and PQQ areas on Bravo can only be accessed once the PQQ is published (see indicative timetable above).</P>
               <P>After the publication of the PQQ, all communication with NHSCS and the Awarding Authority must be through the Bravo portal messaging system.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-01-08</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F01_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
