<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="012187-2018"
            EDITION="2018007">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-010522-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180419</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>7</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180111</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 007-012187</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012187-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>www.ons.gov.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="72300000">Data services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKL21">Monmouthshire and Newport</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKL21">Monmouthshire and Newport</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <n2016:TENDERER_NUTS CODE="UKI44">Lewisham and Southwark</n2016:TENDERER_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180109</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="9">Not applicable</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="K">Modification of a contract/concession during its term</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="9">Not applicable</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="9">Not applicable</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C20</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги по предаване и обработка на данни</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Datové služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Datatjenester</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Datendienste</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες δεδομένων</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Data services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios relacionados con datos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Andmeteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Datapalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de commutation de données</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Data services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Podatkovne usluge</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Adatkezelési szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di elaborazione dati</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Duomenų paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Datu pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi tad-data</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Uitwerken van gegevens</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi w zakresie danych</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços relacionados com dados</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de înlocuire de date</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dátové služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Podatkovne storitve</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Newport</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Datatjänster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Office for National Statistics</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F20_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F20" LG="EN">
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Office for National Statistics</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Government Buildings, Cardiff Road</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Newport</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>NP10 8XG</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Gary Williams</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+44 1633456577</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>gary.williams@ons.org.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKL21"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.ons.gov.uk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>UK-Newport: Data collection services</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="72300000"/>
               <CPV_SUPPLEMENTARY_CODE CODE="JA17"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKL21"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>In 2013, the Office for National Statistics (ONS) undertook a competition in accordance with the Restricted Procedure pursuant to the Public Contracts Regulations 2006, in respect of the servicing, collection, cleaning and delivery of nationally representative price data to produce inflation indices, the Consumer Prices Index (CPI) and the Retail Prices Index (RPI) (the Contract). ONS awarded the Contract to TNS UK Ltd (TNS). The term was advertised as 3 years, with an option for ONS to extend for a further 2 periods of 1-year. The Contract commenced on 1/2/15 and was subsequently extended until 2020. It had become necessary for ONS to extend the Contract for a further 2 years for the reasons set out below. ONS has, therefore, extended the Contract to 31 January 2022 in accordance with Regulation 72(1)(b) of the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 (PCR).</P>
                  <P>ONS produces a wide range of key economic/social statistics. The Contract involves the collection of nationally representative price data from retail outlets for the UK's monthly inflation indicators, the CPI and the RPI. Services provided by TNS include: </P>
                  <P>i) Item selection: the participation, with ONS staff, in the periodic review and selection of items for a basket of goods and services and of a subset of those items for which the service provider will collect prices; </P>
                  <P>ii) Sourcing of products and outlets: finding products that comply with the item specifications, and outlets in which to price those products;</P>
                  <P> iii) Location enumeration; the enumeration of, and supply of information on, locations where this is needed for outlet selection; </P>
                  <P>iv) Collection of prices: the collection of representative price data and descriptions of the products being priced for the subset of items for which the service provider will collect prices; </P>
                  <P>v) Data cleaning: the checking of the data for quality; </P>
                  <P>vi) Data delivery: the delivery of the data to ONS; and </P>
                  <P>vii) Associated services: including but not limited to market information on prices, retailers, goods and services; and the twice-yearly collection of price data (in London) for the Purchasing Power Parities surveys.</P>
                  <P>At the point ONS applied for funding to facilitate the Contract, HM Treasury required ONS to comply with a number of obligations. One of which included exploration of alternative innovative mechanisms to collect data, following the expiry of the Contract. ONS had, over the last few years, identified a number of technologies which may streamline and modernise the collection process. In particular, web scraping and scanner data. However, ONS had identified issues in respect of both methods. For example, in respect of web scraping, this method relies on the website structure remaining static, and that website terms and conditions do not preclude web scraping. ONS was concerned that in light of the levels of consistency required in order to generate the CPI and RPI, it would not be able to place reliance on this technology and it may not be possible to scrape prices providing little or no prior notice. In respect of scanner data, this would require retailers to agree to provide their data to ONS. Whilst some progress has been achieved in this regard, use of this method would be solely reliant on the continued cooperation of retailers, which will not provide the level of certainty required to maintain the CPI and RPI. For these reasons, ONS has struggled to find a mechanism which would suit its requirements. The contract value at the conclusion of the contract was £9 300 000.00 based on the maximum advertised 5-year term.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <DATE_START>2015-02-01</DATE_START>
               <DATE_END>2020-01-31</DATE_END>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2014/S 062-105807</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT>
            <CONTRACT_NO>1</CONTRACT_NO>
            <TITLE>
               <P>UK-Newport: Data collection services</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2014-03-25</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>KNATAR TNS</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <NATIONALID>1469541</NATIONALID>
                     <ADDRESS>6 More London Place</ADDRESS>
                     <TOWN>London</TOWN>
                     <POSTAL_CODE>SE1 2QY</POSTAL_CODE>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
                     <PHONE>+44 2076565383</PHONE>
                     <E_MAIL>debbie.creasy@kantartns.com</E_MAIL>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKI44"/>
                     <URL>www.tnsglobal.com</URL>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">9300000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The contract value at the conclusion of the contract was £9 300 000.00 based on the maximum advertised 5-year term.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>High Court of England and Wales</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Royal Courts of Justice, Strand</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>London</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>WC2A 2LL</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 2079477882</PHONE>
               <URL>www.justice.gov.uk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-01-09</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <MODIFICATIONS_CONTRACT>
            <DESCRIPTION_PROCUREMENT>
               <CPV_MAIN>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72300000"/>
                  <CPV_SUPPLEMENTARY_CODE CODE="JA17"/>
               </CPV_MAIN>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKL21"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The scope of the Contract has not changed and TNS will continue to perform the same services as those described in Section II.2.4 above. The only change to the Contract from the opportunity which was originally advertised on 4 April 2013, is that the term of the Contract has been extended by 2 years (i.e. the Contract will now expire on 31 January 2022, rather than 31 January 2020). The justification for extending the Contract for a further 2 years is that on 27/4/2017, the Digital Economy Act (DEA) received Royal Assent. The introduction of the DEA brings about a fundamental change to the availability of data from retailers. In short, the effect of the DEA is that ONS is able to compel retailers to provide specific pricing information, which will enable ONS to seek certainty in respect of the acquisition of regular and up to date data in order to maintain the CPI and RPI. This makes scanner data (as referred to in Section II.2.4 above) an attractive mechanism to replace the existing method of data collection.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <DATE_START>2015-02-01</DATE_START>
               <DATE_END>2022-01-31</DATE_END>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">13200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>KNATAR TNS</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <NATIONALID>1469541</NATIONALID>
                     <ADDRESS>6 More London Place</ADDRESS>
                     <TOWN>London</TOWN>
                     <POSTAL_CODE>SE1 2QY</POSTAL_CODE>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
                     <PHONE>+44 2076565383</PHONE>
                     <E_MAIL>debbie.creasy@kantartns.com</E_MAIL>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKI44"/>
                     <URL>www.tnsglobal.com</URL>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
            </DESCRIPTION_PROCUREMENT>
            <INFO_MODIFICATIONS>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The only modification to the Contract is the date of expiry as explained above. Before making any changes to the coverage or the basic calculation of the RPI, ONS must obtain the prior consent of the Bank of England pursuant to the Statistics and Registration Services Act 2007. This process, therefore, constrains how and when changes can be made to the RPI and its underlying data sources and it requires a long lead time in order for the impact on the RPI to be established, the Bank of England to be properly consulted and consent to the change to be given. It had, therefore, become necessary to temporarily extend the current contract with TNS, as data collection in the future will fundamentally change, such that a different type of supplier is likely to be interested in the 'new' contract, and if a new supplier was appointed on an interim basis (i.e. between 2020-2022), this would give rise to substantial cost and duplication on the part of ONS. As explained above, an extension to the Contract had become necessary in order to react to recent changes in legislation which will now enable ONS to move forward with a more innovative data collection mechanism at the earliest opportunity pursuant an obligation placed on ONS by HM Treasury. </P>
                  <P>A long lead time is required in order for ONS to: </P>
                  <P>i) Conclude its analysis of alternative data collection sources and develop the systems and processes to support them; </P>
                  <P>ii) Obtain the Bank of England's approval; and </P>
                  <P>iii) Implement a procurement plan for future data collection services. </P>
                  <P>This task could not be completed prior to the expiry of the Contract, as an appropriate alternative collection mechanism has only recently been identified, and ONS is only now able to commence the above-mentioned approval process. In turn, this impacts on the timescales within which ONS is able to commence a new procurement procedure for the new data collection method.</P>
                  <P>A change of contractor in 2020 could not be made for economic/technical reasons. ONS must ensure a consistent and uninterrupted provision of price collection services under the existing model, contributing to the delivery of the CPI; CPIH (the new measure of consumer price inflation including owner occupiers’ housing costs) and the RPI to meet ONS's legislative requirements. Both indices are heavily relied upon by industry. Any inconsistencies/inaccuracies in those statistics could have catastrophic results. A change in contractor would have caused significant inconvenience and substantial duplication of costs for ONS. If a separate tender process was undertaken to appoint a supplier for an interim 2020-2022 period, this would equally require a significant 'lead in' time to prepare for that process. Any alternative supplier would be required to undertake a parallel run of the data collection process with TNS for at least one year prior to TNS's exit. The costs associated with both such a procurement process and remunerating 2 suppliers in order to conduct the parallel transition exercise, will far outweigh any perceived cost savings which an alternative supplier might be able to offer ONS. On balance, ONS did not consider such costs viable in light of (what would have been) a very short contract. TNS has provided the current services for a period of 20 years and has the necessary capacity, knowledge and equipment in place for the task. Replacement of TNS would have been disproportionate in light of the costs and resources involved in a further procurement exercise.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <ADDITIONAL_NEED>
                  <P>A change of contractor in 2020 cannot be made for the reasons described in the final paragraph of Section VII.2.1 above. ONS's intention to extend the Contract, and the reasons why ONS considered this approach compliant with Article 72(1)(b) of Directive 2014/24/EU/Regulation 72(1)(b) of the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 was set out in a voluntary ex-ante transparency notice published in the Official Journal of the European Union on 23/12/2017 with reference 2017/S 247-520663.</P>
               </ADDITIONAL_NEED>
               <VAL_TOTAL_BEFORE CURRENCY="GBP">9300000.00</VAL_TOTAL_BEFORE>
               <VAL_TOTAL_AFTER CURRENCY="GBP">13200000.00</VAL_TOTAL_AFTER>
            </INFO_MODIFICATIONS>
         </MODIFICATIONS_CONTRACT>
      </F20_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
