<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="017693-2018"
            EDITION="2018010">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-017914-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180215</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>10</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180116</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 010-017693</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:017693-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>https://www.dansk-retursystem.dk/dk/</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=202208&amp;B=DRS</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="42000000">Industrial machinery</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="DK02">Sjælland</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="DK">DANMARK</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="EUR">4500000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180112</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180215 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="8">Other</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="B">Competitive procedure with negotiation</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="E">Environment</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01B02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Дaния</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Машини за промишлена употреба</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Průmyslové stroje</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrimaskiner</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Dänemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrielle Maschinen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Δανία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Μηχανήματα βιομηχανικών εγκαταστάσεων</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Denmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrial machinery</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Maquinaria industrial</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Taani</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tööstusmasinad</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Tanska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Teollisuuskoneet</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Danemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Machines industrielles</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Danmhairg, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrial machinery</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrijski strojevi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Dánia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ipari gépek</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Danimarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Macchinari industriali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Danija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pramoninės mašinos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Dānija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ražošanas iekārtas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>id-Danimarka</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Makkinarju industriali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Denemarken</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Bedrijfsmachines</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Dania</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Maszyny przemysłowe</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Máquinas industriais</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Danemarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Echipamente industriale</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Priemyselné mechanizmy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrijski stroji</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hedehusene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Industrimaskiner</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Dansk Retursystem A/S</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>f8784287-e568-4b80-8b84-b308674b0f60</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Dansk Retursystem A/S</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>25 49 61 40</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>Baldersbuen 1</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Hedehusene</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2640</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Steen Aagaard</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+45 43323232</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>saa@dansk-retursystem.dk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://www.dansk-retursystem.dk/dk/</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://eu.eu-supply.com/ctm/Company/CompanyInformation/Index/290789</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=202208&amp;B=DRS</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=202208&amp;B=DRS</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE_OTHER>Privatejet non-profit environmental undertaking</CA_TYPE_OTHER>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="ENVIRONMENT"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Compacted Line</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="42000000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SUPPLIES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Dansk Retursystem A/S (DRS) has initiated this Tender Procedure concerning a Compacted Line. The Compacted Line is an electromechanical production facility (turnkey contract), which must be designed, engineered, procured, installed, tested and commissioned for DRS’s new production plant by the contractor. The Compacted Line sorts and Bales Beverage Packaging, including e.g. plastic bottles and aluminum cans. The material output of the Compacted Line are Bales of either plastic or aluminum meant for recycling. For further description see Section II.2.4.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">4500000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="42000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK02"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>2630 Taastrup</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Dansk Retursystem A/S (DRS) has initiated this Tender Procedure concerning a Compacted Line. The Compacted Line is an electromechanical production facility (turnkey contract), which must be designed, engineered, procured, installed, tested and commissioned for DRS’s new production plant by the contractor. The compacted line sorts and Bales Beverage Packaging, including e.g. plastic bottles and aluminum cans. The material output of the Compacted Line are Bales of either plastic or aluminum meant for recycling.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">4500000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">39</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>3</NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>This selection will be based on the following: Candidates’ submitted references. DRS will assess which candidates that have the most relevant experience in relation to electromechanical delivery contracts within the fields of waste handling, recycling or similar of equivalent scope and complexity to the contract.</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>The tenderer must fix a price in the Price List (Appendix T2) for the option “Strategic Spare Parts” described below.</P>
                  <P>Strategic Spare Parts are defined as parts with an expected lifetime of more than 2 years, but recommended for availability purposes, cf. Appendix A4 (General Technical Requirements).</P>
                  <P>Strategic Spare Parts shall be defined by the tenderer in the tender and negotiation phase and specified in Appendix T2 (Price List) when the tenderer submits its tender.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>The Contract is not divided into lots due to the complexity of the Compacted Line. DRS needs one main contractor to design, engineer, procure, install, test and commission a complete electromechanical Compacted Line (turnkey contract). Furthermore, it is DRS's assessment that there will be no competition for a contract of a Compacted Line if divided into lots.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>DRS has the following minimum requirements concerning the Candidates’ economical and financial standing:</P>
               <P>— the candidate must have equity of at least EUR 1 000 000 at the end of the past financial year,</P>
               <P>— the candidate must have a turnover of at least EUR 10 000 000 on average for the past 3 financial years,</P>
               <P>— the candidate must have ordinary and sufficient liquidity in normal operations, including access to the necessary credits from a bank in the European Union.</P>
               <P>It is stated in the tender conditions how the Candidate/Tenderer must document fulfilment of the abovementioned minimum requirements for suitability.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>DRS has the following minimum requirements concerning the Candidates’ technical and professional ability:</P>
               <P>The candidate must provide a minimum of 3 and a maximum 5 of references meeting the following minimum requirements:</P>
               <P>— the references must concern ongoing or completed works within the past 3 years,</P>
               <P>— the references must concern electromechanical delivery contracts within the field of waste handling, recycling or similar of equivalent scope and complexity to the contract,.</P>
               <P>— for at least one of the references, the candidate must as a primary delivery have performed works according to the contract with a value of at least EUR 3 000 000,</P>
               <P>— the references must contain a description of the contract, including:</P>
               <P>i) the location of performance;</P>
               <P>ii) the time of performance;</P>
               <P>iii) the scope;</P>
               <P>iv) name and title of the key personnel who participated in the performance of the contract (not a CV); and</P>
               <P>v) the customers’ contact information, including contact person, email and telephone number.</P>
               <P>By submitting the references, the candidate accepts that DRS may contact the customers’ contact person regarding the candidates performance of the contract. The candidate is obligated to assist DRS in connection with contacting the customer.</P>
               <P>Submission of more than 5 references does not lead to exclusion of the Candidate. However, DRS will only evaluate the first 5 references in the order listed in EU-Supply or in the ESPD.</P>
               <P>Furthermore, in regard to Section 157 of the Danish Public Procurement Act, DRS has the following minimum requirements concerning the Candidates’ quality assurance schemes:</P>
               <P>— the candidates’ quality assurance schemes must be ISO 9000-1 or similar.</P>
               <P>It is stated in the tender conditions how the candidate/tenderer must document fulfilment of the abovementioned minimum requirements for suitability.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>See Contract and appendices.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_COMPETITIVE_NEGOTIATION/>
            <REDUCTION_RECOURSE/>
            <RIGHT_CONTRACT_INITIAL_TENDERS/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-02-15</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>2018-03-01</DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">6</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Candidates/tenderers will be excluded from participation in the procurement procedure if the exclusion grounds listed in Sections 135, 136 and 137(1)-(6) of the Danish Public Procurement Act apply. However, DRS may not exclude a candidate or a tenderer which has provided sufficient documentation that the candidate or tenderer is reliable (self-cleaning) pursuant to Section 138 of the Danish Public Procurement Act.</P>
               <P>Final documentation proving that the relevant grounds for exclusion does not apply and final documentation for fulfillment of the minimum requirements for suitability are described in the Tender Conditions, Section 8.9.</P>
               <P>Tender and negotiation procedure:</P>
               <P>1. Preliminary Tenders:</P>
               <P>DRS encourages that the Preliminary Tender contains the same information as the Tenderers Final Tender and comply with the formal requirements as well as the minimum requirements and requirements. DRS reserves the right to award the Contract on the basis of Preliminary Tenders.</P>
               <P>2. Preliminary Negotiations:</P>
               <P>The Tenderers who have submitted a Preliminary Tender in due time will be invited to participate in individual negotiation meetings.</P>
               <P>DRS expects the meetings to take place in the Copenhagen area.</P>
               <P>DRS will inform the Tenderers of the exact date, time and place via EU-Supply.</P>
               <P>The submitted Preliminary Tender will form the basis for the negotiations, including the strengths and weaknesses of the Preliminary Tender according to the contract award criteria.</P>
               <P>3. Revised Tender:</P>
               <P>DRS may choose to make adjustments to the Tender Documents on the basis of information and knowledge gained from the Preliminary Negotiations. The Revised Tender Documents will form the basis for the submission of Revised Tenders. DRS reserves the right to award the Contract on the basis of Revised Tenders.</P>
               <P>4. Shortlisting:</P>
               <P>Based on the evaluation of the Revised Tenders in accordance with the award criteria and the evaluation method, DRS reserves the right to reduce the number of tenderers to 2.</P>
               <P>5. Subsequent Negotiations:</P>
               <P>The negotiations based on the Revised Tender will be carried out according to the same procedure as for the Preliminary Negotiations.</P>
               <P>6. Final Tender:</P>
               <P>DRS may choose to make adjustments to the Tender Documents on the basis of information and experience gained through the Subsequent Negotiations. The Revised Tender Documents will form the basis for the submission of Final Tenders.</P>
               <P>DRS may apply further negotiations if necessary.</P>
               <P>There will be no remuneration for the Candidates/Tenderers in connection with the Tender Procedure.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>The Danish Complaints Board for Public Procurement (Klagenævnet for Udbud)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Nævnenes Hus, Toldboden 2</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Viborg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>8800</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 72405708</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>klfu@naevneneshus.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.klfu.dk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>The rules concerning deadlines for review procedures are found in the Danish Complaints Board for Public Procurement Act (Act nº 593 of 2.6.2016) available at www.retsinformation.dk</P>
               <P>Complaints concerning a candidate not being prequalified must be submitted with The Complaints Board for Public Procurement (the Complaints Board) within 20 calendar days starting the day after DRS has sent notification to the candidates involved, cf. Section 7(1) of the Danish Complaints Board for Public Procurement Act.</P>
               <P>Other complaints must be filed with the Complaints Board within 45 calendar days after DRS has published a contract award notice in the Official Journal of the European Union (with effect from the day following the publication date), cf. Section 7(2)(i).</P>
               <P>The complainant must notify DRS of the complaint in writing at the latest simultaneously with the submission as well as whether the complaint has been submitted in the standstill-period, cf. Section 6(4) of the Danish Complaints Board for Public Procurement Act. If the complaint has not been submitted within the standstill-period, the complainant must notify DRS in writing whether the complainant has requested the complaint to be given suspensory effect pursuant to Section 12 of the Act, cf. Section 6(4) of the Act.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>The Danish Competition and Consumer Authority (Konkurrence- og Forbrugerstyrelsen)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Carl Jacobsens Vej 35</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Valby</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2500</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 41715000</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>kfst@kfst.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.kfst.dk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-01-12</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
