<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="050090-2018" EDITION="2018024"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-044507-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180322</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN CS DA DE ET EL ES FR IT LV LT HR HU MT NL PL PT SK SL FI SV RO GA BG </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>24</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180203</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 024-050090</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:050090-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BA"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45252126">Drinking-water treatment plant construction work</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180129</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180322 11:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="1">Corrigendum</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="Z">Not specified</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="1">Lowest price</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="W">Water</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>BI302</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Босна и Херцеговина</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕИБ - Проектиране и изграждане на пречиствателна станция за отпадъчни води</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Bosna a Hercegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Návrh a výstavba čistíren odpadních vod</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Bosnien-Hercegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Projektering og opførelse af rensningsanlæg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Bosnien und Herzegowina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Planung und Bau der Kläranlage für die Städte Tazarka, Somâa und Maâmoura</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Βοσνία-Ερζεγοβίνη</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΕπ - Μελέτη και κατασκευή μονάδων καθαρισμού λυμάτων</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Bosnia and Herzegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Bosnia y Herzegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Diseño y construcción de plantas depuradoras</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Bosnia ja Hertsegoviina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIP - Reoveepuhasti projekteerimine ja ehitamine</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Bosnia ja Hertsegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIP - Jätevesipuhdistamoiden suunnittelu ja rakentaminen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Bosnie-Herzégovine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Conception et réalisation de stations d'épuration</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Bhoisnia agus an Heirseagaivéin, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Design and construction of water treatment plants</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Bosna i Hercegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Projektiranje i gradnja uređaja za pročišćavanje voda</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Bosznia-Hercegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBB - Szennyvíztisztító telep tervezése és építése</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Bosnia-Erzegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Progettazione e realizzazione di impianti di depurazione</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Bosnija ir Hercegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Nuotekų valymo įrenginio projektavimas ir statyba</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Bosnija un Hercegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Notekūdeņu attīrīšanas stacijas projektēšana un būvniecība</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Bosnja-Ħerzegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Disinn u kostruzzjoni ta’ impjant għat-trattament tal-ilma tad-drenaġġ</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Bosnië en Herzegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Ontwerp en bouw van waterzuiveringsstations</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Bośnia i Hercegowina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBI - Zaprojektowanie i budowa oczyszczalni ścieków</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Bósnia-Herzegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Conceção e construção das estações de tratamento de águas residuais</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Bosnia şi Herţegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Proiectare şi realizare de staţii de epurare</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Bosna a Hercegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Návrh a výstavba čistiarne odpadových vôd</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Bosna in Hercegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Projektiranje in gradnja čistilne naprave za odpadne vode</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Bosnien och Hercegovina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Orasje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Projektering och anläggning av reningsverk för avloppsvatten</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DA">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Design and construction of water treatment plants (BA-Orasje)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Promoter: Orasje Municipality, Bosnia and Herzegovina — nº 01-23-1173/15</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>International Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Federation Bosnia and Herzegovina (hereinafter referred to as “the Borrower”) has received a loan from the European Investment Bank — EIB (hereinafter referred to as “the Bank”) — towards the cost of the project Water and Sanitation Federation BiH. This International Invitation for Tenders relates to the contract for the Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant (WTP) in Orasje promoted by the Municipality of Orasje, FBiH (hereinafter referred to as “the Employer”).</P><P>The contract will include:</P><P>— preparation of design documentation as required by the Employer to obtain necessary approvals and permits for the construction and commissioning of the works,</P><P>— construction of the WTP (capacity 50 l/s) including testing, start-up and trial operation,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality for the existing operating production well,</P><P>— testing and start up all process equipment to ensure functionality of the existing but out of operation well at the Works site.</P><P>This contract is expected to commence in 6.2018 with the period for completion of 18 months.</P><P>Qualification Criteria:</P><P>To be qualified for the award of the contract, Tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria.</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Annual Turnover</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Average annual turnover as lead contractor (defined as billing for works in progress and completed) over the last 5 years of EUR 1 300 000 per year equivalent.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financial Capacity</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real estate, lines of credit and other financial assets sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract for a period of 4 months, estimated at not less than the equivalent amount of EUR 200 000, taking into account the applicant's commitments for other contracts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Experience</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Tenderer shall demonstrate that it has successfully completed experience under contracts in the role of contractor in the last 5 years prior to the applications submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year.</P><P>Experience as contractor in at least 3 water treatment plant design and construction projects within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 450 000, that have been successfully completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics.</P><P>For the above or other contracts executed during the period stipulated above, an experience in the following key activities:</P><P>(i) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating aeration;</P><P>(ii) design and construction of water treatment facilities incorporating high rate pressure filters;</P><P>(iii) design and construction of wells for potable water abstraction;</P><P>(iv) design and construction of water treatment facilities for at least 50 l/s under FIDIC Conditions of Contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personnel Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall demonstrate availability of suitably qualified and professional key personnel to fill the following positions. Each candidate shall meet the experience requirements specified below: (Key personnel position – Total experience, years – In similar works, years)</P><P>— Project Manager — 15 — 10,</P><P>— Site Manager — 10 — 8,</P><P>— Hydrogeology Engineer or comparable profile in tenderer’s country — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Process Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Mechanical Engineer — 10 — 5,</P><P>— Electrical-automatic and SCADA Engineer — 10 — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Equipment Capabilities</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall own, or have assured access to (through hire, lease, purchase agreement, availability of manufacturing equipment, or other means), at least the following key equipment in in full working order and safe, and must demonstrate that, based on known commitments, the equipment will be available for use in the proposed contract.</P><P>(Main equipment — Minimum number required)</P><P>— Tower crane minimum — 25 m radius 1,</P><P>— Mobile crane minimum — 50 tonnes 1,</P><P>— Excavators for the civil works — 3,</P><P>— Mini excavator — 2,</P><P>— Dozer and caterpillar base — 2,</P><P>— Concrete trucks with conveyor bend and Concrete pumps — 2,</P><P>— Vehicles and Trucks — 5.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Litigation History</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The applicant shall sign the Litigation History Form confirming that he is not involved in any current or past litigation or arbitration resulting from contracts completed or under execution by him over the last 5 years.</P><P>All firms are invited to participate in the tender. The EIB shall not provide finance, directly or indirectly, to or for the benefit of, award a contract under any EIB Project to, or enter into any relationship with, an individual or entity who is subject to financial sanctions imposed by the European Union pursuant to Chapter 2 of Title V of the Treaty on European Union or Article 215 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, either autonomously or pursuant to the financial sanctions decided by the United Nations Security Council on the basis of Article 41 of the UN Charter.</P><P>Tender Evaluation:</P><P>Evaluation of tenders shall be carried out in accordance with the European Investment Bank’s Guide to Procurement, version dated 6.2011. The evaluation shall proceed in 2 steps (called the twoenvelope procedure), each with a public opening.</P><P>Award Criteria:</P><P>The Employer shall award the Contract to the Tenderer whose offer has been determined to be the lowest evaluated tender of all substantially responsive tenders to the Tender Document.Tenders not achieving at least 75 % of the available Technical Evaluation marks will be considered non-responsive and, in such cases, the Financial Offer shall not be opened.</P><P>In case of the joint venture/consortium an agreement shall be signed confirming joint and several liabilities of all members for Contract performance.</P><P>Interested eligibleTenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: Mrs Ph D RuzaNedic (Head of PIT), </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>The Project Implementation Team (PIT)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Orasje</TOWN><BLK_BTX> Municipality, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+387 31712322</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+387 31712011</FAX><BLK_BTX>; Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>opcina@orasje.ba, ruza.nedic@orasje.ba </E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>Bosnie-Herzégovine.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tender documents may be purchased on the submission of an application to the Orasje Municipality office (see address below), and upon payment of a non-refundable fee of EUR 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The methods of payment will be as follows:</P><P>(a) For payment within Bosnia and Herzegovinain BAM: Payment will be done through Unicredit Bank d.d Bosnia and Herzegovina account nº 3380002200022831 infavour of The Municipality vrsta prihoda/income code: 722612, Opcina: 068, budget organization: 0000, reference number: 01-23-1173/15 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the“Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”.</P><P>(b) For payment in a freely convertible currency from abroad: Payment in a freely convertible currency will be done through intermediary bank LHB International Bank AGFrankfurt AM Main SWIFT code: LHBIDEFF, account with institution/UniCredit Bank d.d Mostar SWIFT code: UNCRBA22 Beneficiary customer: IBAN: BA39 3380 0022 00022831 indicating purchase of Tender Document for the “Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje”</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of anappropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A Bid Security of EUR 25 000, or its equivalent in a freely convertible currency, must accompany all bids.</P><P>All bids must be delivered in closed sealed envelopes bearing the mention “Bid for Design and Construction of Kostrc Water Treatment Plant; Orasje” not later than 22.3.2018 (11:00) local time to the address given below. Bids will be opened immediately in the presence of Bidders’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The address referred to above is: Orasje Municipality, TrecaUlica 45, 76270, Orasje, Bosnia and Herzegovina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>