<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="180386-2018" EDITION="2018081"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-173348-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20190417</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>81</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180426</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 081-180386</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180386-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="TR"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71356200">Technical assistance services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180417</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>AP301</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Tyrkiet</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ipa - Teknisk bistand til styrkelse af revisionskapacitet og forbedring af datadeling på tværs af agenturer inden for omfanget af reduktion af den uformelle økonomi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>die Türkei</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Technische Hilfe zur Stärkung der Prüfkapazität und Verbesserung des agenturübergreifenden Datenaustauschs im Rahmen der Verringerung der Schattenwirtschaft</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Turkey</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Technical Assistance for Strengthening the Audit Capacity and Improving Inter-agency Data Sharing within the scope of Reducing the Informal Economy</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Turquía</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Asistencia técnica para el refuerzo de la capacidad para realizar auditorías y la mejora del intercambio de información entre agencias dentro del objetivo de reducción de la economía informal</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Turkki</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Tekninen tuki tarkastusvalmiuksien vahvistamiseksi ja virastojen välisen tiedonvaihdon parantamiseksi tavoitteena epävirallisen talouden vähentäminen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Turquie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IAP - Une assistance technique pour améliorer les capacités d’audit et améliorer le partage des données inter-agences dans le cadre de réduire l’économie informelle</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Τουρκία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Άγκυρα</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Τεχνική βοήθεια για την ενίσχυση της ικανότητας ελέγχου και τη βελτίωση της ανταλλαγής δεδομένων μεταξύ των οργανισμών στο πλαίσιο της μείωσης της άτυπης οικονομίας</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Turchia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Assistenza tecnica per rafforzare le capacità di audit e migliorare la condivisione dei dati tra le agenzie, al fine di ridurre l’economia informale</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Turkije</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Technische bijstand ter versterking van de auditcapaciteit en ter verbetering van de gegevensuitwisseling tussen agentschappen in het kader van de terugdringing van de informele economie</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Turquia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ancara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Assistência técnica para o reforço da capacidade de auditoria e melhoria da partilha de dados inter-agências no âmbito da redução da economia informal</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Turkiet</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Tekniskt stöd för att förstärka granskningskapaciteten och förbättra datadelningen mellan byråer inom ramen för en minskning av den informella ekonomin</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Turecko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>NPP - Technická pomoc pro posílení funkce auditu a zlepšení sdílení údajů mezi agenturami v rámci snižování neformální ekonomiky</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Türgi</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Tehniline abi auditeerimissuutlikkuse tugevdamiseks ja ametkondadevahelise andmevahetuse täiustamiseks mitteametliku majanduse vähendamise raames</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Törökország</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Szakmai segítségnyújtás az ellenőrzési felkészültség megerősítésére és az ügynökségek közötti adatmegosztás fejlesztésére irányulóan az informális gazdaság visszaszorításának hatókörén belül</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Turkija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>PNPP - Techninė pagalba, skirta audito gebėjimams stiprinti ir agentūrų dalijimuisi duomenimis gerinti mažinant šešėlinę ekonomiką</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Turcija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Tehniskā palīdzība revīzijas spēju stiprināšanai un starpaģentūru datu koplietošanas uzlabošanai ēnu ekonomikas samazināšanas ietvaros</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>it-Turkija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>SGħQD - Għajnuna Teknika għat-Tisħiħ tal-Kapaċità tal-Awditjar u għat-Titjib fil-Kondiviżjoni tad-Dejta Bejn l-Aġenziji fl-ambitu tat-Tnaqqis tal-Ekonomija Informali</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Turcja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Pomoc techniczna w celu wzmocnienia zdolności do przeprowadzania audytu i poprawy wymiany danych między agencjami w zakresie ograniczania szarej strefy w gospodarce</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Turecko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Technická pomoc na posilnenie kapacity auditu a zlepšenie zdieľania údajov medzi agentúrami v rámci potláčania tieňovej ekonomiky</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Turčija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Tehnična pomoč za okrepitev revizijske zmogljivosti in medagencijske zmogljivosti za izmenjavo podatkov za zmanjšanje neformalnega gospodarstva</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Tuirc, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Cúnamh teicniúil do neartú chumas iniúchóireachta agus feabhsú chomhroinnt sonraí idirghníomhaireachta laistigh de raon feidhme um laghdú an gheilleagair neamhfhoirmiúil</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Typция</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Анкара</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ИПП - Техническа помощ за подсилване на капацитета за одит и подобряване на споделянето на данни между агенциите в обхвата на намаляване на сивата икономика</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Turcia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Asistență tehnică pentru consolidarea capacității de audit și îmbunătățirea schimbului de date între agenții în domeniul de aplicare al reducerii economiei informale</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Turska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Tehnička pomoć jačanju kapaciteta za reviziju i unaprjeđenje razmjene podataka unutar agencije u sklopu smanjenja sive ekonomije</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den centrale finans- og kontraktenhed (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Zentrale Abteilung Finanzen und Verträge (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">Central Finance and Contracts Unit (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">Unidad Central de Finanzas y Contratos</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Rahoitus- ja sopimusasioiden keskusyksikkö (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Unité centrale de financement et de passation de contrats (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Κεντρική μονάδα χρηματοδότησης και ανάθεσης συμβάσεων (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Unità centrale per i finanziamenti e gli appalti (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Centrale eenheid Financiën en Contracten (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">Unidade Central de Finanças e Contratos (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Centrala finansierings- och upphandlingsenheten (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Ústřední finanční a kontraktační jednotka (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Rahastamise ja lepingute kesktalitus (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Központi Pénzügyi és Szerződéskötő Egység (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Centrinis finansų ir sutarčių skyrius (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Centrālā finanšu un līgumu aģentūra (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">It-Taqsima Ċentrali tal-Finanzi u l-Kuntratti (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Centralna Jednostka Finansująco-Kontraktująca (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Centrálne finančné a zmluvné oddelenie (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Centralna enota za finance in javna naročila (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An Láraonad Airgeadais agus Conarthaí (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Централно звено за финансиране и договориране (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Unitatea centrală pentru finanțe și contracte (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Središnji odjel za financiranje i ugovaranje (CFCU)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: Ipa - Teknisk bistand til styrkelse af revisionskapacitet og forbedring af datadeling på tværs af agenturer inden for omfanget af reduktion af den uformelle økonomi</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sted — Tyrkiet</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VEJLEDENDE FORHÅNDSMEDDELELSE OM TJENESTEYDELSER</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udbudsreference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Begrænset.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programtitel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Det årlige handlingsprogram for Tyrkiet for 2014 inden for rammerne af instrumentet til førtiltrædelsesbistand (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA-budgetpost 22.02 03 01 i EU's almindelige budget (90 %) og nationalt bidrag (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den centrale finans- og kontraktenhed (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Tyrkiet.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontraktens art</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Samlet pris.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivelse af kontrakten</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projektets overordnede formål er at reducere den uformelle økonomis niveau. Særligt har kontrakten til hensigt at forbedre revisionen og datadelingskapaciteten på tværs af de relevante agenturer for effektivt at kunne bekæmpe den uformelle økonomi. Gennem denne kontrakt vil:</P><P>— revisionskapaciteten blive styrket og den relevante lovgivning revideret via gennemførelsen af undersøgelser inden for forskellige sektorer, tilrettelæggelse af workshopper, uddannelser og studiebesøg samt via udarbejdelsen af rapporter om revisionsstandarder</P><P>— datadelingen på tværs af agenturer mellem det tyrkiske skattevæsen og de relevante myndigheder blive udviklet og problemer under gennemførelsen af datadeling vil blive fjernet ved at udveksle synspunkter og forbedre samarbejdet via studiebesøg, workshopper, undersøgelser hos relevante interessenter og uddannelser.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vejledende budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Foreløbig dato for offentliggørelse af udbudsbekendtgørelsen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juni 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yderligere oplysninger</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ikke relevant.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Retsgrundlag</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 236/2014 af 11.3.2014 angående fælles regler og procedurer for gennemførelsen af instrumenterne til finansiering af Unionens optræden udadtil og Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 231/2014 af 11.3.2014 om oprettelse af et instrument til førtiltrædelsesbistand (IPA II), EUT L 77, 15.3.2014, s. 11. Se bilag A2 i den praktiske vejledning.</P><P>Vær opmærksom på, at efter Det Forenede Kongeriges udtræden fra EU vil reglerne om adgang til EU's udbudsprocedurer for økonomiske aktører, der er etableret i tredjelande, gælde for ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige, alt afhængigt af resultatet af forhandlingerne. Hvis en sådan adgang ikke gives ved retlige bestemmelser, der er gældende på tidspunktet for kontrakttildelingen, vil ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige kunne blive udelukket fra udbudsproceduren.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Bemærkninger:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Der skal være en periode på mindst 30 kalenderdage mellem offentliggørelsen af denne forhåndsmeddelelse og offentliggørelsen af den tilsvarende udbudsbekendtgørelse.</P><P>Der kan ikke fremsendes ansøgninger eller anmodninger om oplysninger på nuværende tidspunkt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Technische Hilfe zur Stärkung der Prüfkapazität und Verbesserung des agenturübergreifenden Datenaustauschs im Rahmen der Verringerung der Schattenwirtschaft</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Standort — Türkei</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VORINFORMATION FÜR EINEN DIENSTLEISTUNGSAUFTRAG</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verfahren</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nichtoffen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmbezeichnung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jährliches Aktionsprogramm für die Türkei für das Jahr 2014 im Rahmen des Instruments für Heranführungshilfe (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanzierung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA-Haushaltsposten 22.02 03 01 des Gesamthaushaltsplans der EU (90 %) und nationaler Beitrag (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Öffentlicher Auftraggeber</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Zentrale Abteilung Finanzen und Verträge (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Türkei.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Art des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Gesamtpreis.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Das übergeordnete Ziel des Projekts besteht darin, die Rate der Schattenwirtschaft zu verringern. Konkret zielt der Vertrag darauf ab, die Kapazitäten der relevanten Institutionen für die Prüfung und den Datenaustausch zwischen den Behörden zu verbessern, um eine wirksame Bekämpfung der Schattenwirtschaft zu erreichen. Durch diesen Vertrag:</P><P>— werden die Prüfungskapazitäten gestärkt und die einschlägigen Rechtsvorschriften werden durch Studien in verschiedenen Bereichen, durch Organisation von Workshops, Schulungen und Studienaufenthalte sowie durch Erstellung von Berichten über Prüfungsstandards überprüft,</P><P>— wird ein Datenaustausch zwischen der türkischen Finanzverwaltung und den zuständigen Institutionen entwickelt, und Probleme bei der Umsetzung der gemeinsamen Nutzung von Daten werden durch Meinungsaustausch und verstärkte Zusammenarbeit durch Studienaufenthalte, Workshops, Studien mit relevanten Interessenträgern und Schulungen beseitigt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veranschlagtes Budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Geplanter Zeitpunkt für die Veröffentlichung der Auftragsbekanntmachung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juni 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zusätzliche Informationen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Entfällt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsgrundlage</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verordnung (EU) Nr. 236/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Festlegung gemeinsamer Vorschriften und Verfahren für die Anwendung der Instrumente der Union für die Finanzierung des auswärtigen Handelns und Verordnung (EU) Nr. 231/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Schaffung eines Instruments für Heranführungshilfe (IPA II) (ABI. L 77, 15.3.2014, S. 11). Siehe Anhang A2 des Handbuchs.</P><P>Es gilt zu beachten, dass für Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich nach dem Austritt des Vereinigten Königreichs aus der EU in Abhängigkeit des Ausgangs der Verhandlungen die Bestimmungen über den Zugang zu Beschaffungsverfahren der EU für in Drittländern ansässige Wirtschaftsteilnehmer gelten werden. Falls dieser Zugang gemäß den bei Auftragsvergabe geltenden Bestimmung nicht gewährt wird, können Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich vom Beschaffungsverfahren ausgeschlossen werden.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Hinweise:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Es muss ein Zeitraum von mindestens 30 Kalendertagen zwischen der Veröffentlichung der Vorinformation und der Veröffentlichung der entsprechenden Auftragsbekanntmachung liegen.</P><P>Derzeit ist von der Einreichung von Bewerbungen oder weiteren Anfragen abzusehen.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Technical Assistance for Strengthening the Audit Capacity and Improving Inter-agency Data Sharing within the scope of Reducing the Informal Economy</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Location — Turkey</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SERVICE PRIOR INFORMATION NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publication reference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programme title</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Annual Action Programme for Turkey for the Year 2014 under the Instrument for Pre-Accession Assistance (IPA-II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financing</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA budget item 22.02 03 01 of the general budget of the EU (90%) and national contribution (10%).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contracting Authority</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Central Finance and Contracts Unit (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, TURKEY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature of contract</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Global Price.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contract description</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The overall objective of the project is to reduce the rate of the informal economy. Specifically, the contract aims to improve the auditing and inter-agency data sharing capacity of relevant institutions for effective fight against informal economy. Through this contract:</P><P>— the auditing capacity will be strengthened and relevant legislation will be reviewed by conducting studies in different sectors, organising workshops, trainings and study visits and preparing reports on audit standards,</P><P>— inter-agency data sharing between the Turkish Revenue Administration and the relevant institutions will be developed and problems during implementation of data sharing will be eliminated by exchanging views and enhancing the cooperation via study visits, workshops, studies with relevant stakeholders and trainings.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicative budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intended timing of publication of the contract notice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Additional information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Not applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal basis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulation (EU) nº 236/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 laying down common rules and procedures for the implementation of the Union's instruments for financing external action and Regulation (EU) nº 231/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 establishing an Instrument for Pre-Accession Assistance (IPA II), OJ L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11. See Annex A2 of the Practical Guide.</P><P>Please be aware that after the United Kingdom’s withdrawal from the EU, the rules of access to EU procurement procedures of economic operators established in third countries will apply to candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom depending on the outcome of negotiations. In case such access is not provided by legal provisions in force at the time of the contract award, candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom could be rejected from the procurement procedure.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarks:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>There must be a minimum period of 30 calendar days between the publication of this Prior Information Notice and the publication of the corresponding Contract Notice.</P><P>No applications or requests for information should be sent at this stage.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Asistencia técnica para el refuerzo de la capacidad para realizar auditorías y la mejora del intercambio de información entre agencias dentro del objetivo de reducción de la economía informal</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lugar: Turquía</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNCIO DE INFORMACIÓN PREVIA DE CONTRATO DE SERVICIOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referencia de publicación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedimiento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restringido.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Título del programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de acción anual para el año 2014 a favor de Turquía en el marco del Instrumento de Ayuda Preadhesión (IAP II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Partida presupuestaria 22.02 03 01 del IAP con cargo al presupuesto general de la Unión Europea (90 %) y a la contribución nacional (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de contratación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unidad Central de Finanzas y Contratos</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turquía.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naturaleza del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Precio global.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El objetivo global del proyecto es la reducción de la tasa de la economía informal. Específicamente, el contrato aspira a mejorar la capacidad para realizar auditorías y de intercambio de información entre agencias de las instituciones relevantes para la lucha efectiva contra la economía informal. A través de este contrato:</P><P>— se reforzará la capacidad para realizar auditorías y se revisará la legislación pertinente mediante la realización de estudios en diferentes sectores, la organización de talleres, cursos de formación y visitas de estudio y la preparación de informes sobre normas de auditoría,</P><P>— se desarrollará el intercambio de información entre agencias de la Administración Tributaria turca y las instituciones pertinentes y se eliminarán los problemas que surjan durante la implementación del intercambio de información a través del intercambio de perspectivas y la mejora de la cooperación mediante visitas de estudio, talleres, estudios con partes interesadas pertinentes y cursos de formación.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Presupuesto indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha prevista de publicación del anuncio de licitación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Junio de 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información adicional</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>No aplicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fundamento jurídico</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Reglamento (UE) n.º 236/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establecen normas comunes y procedimientos de ejecución de los instrumentos de la Unión para la financiación de la acción exterior y Reglamento (UE) n.º 231/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establece un Instrumento de Ayuda Preadhesión (IAP II), DO L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11. Véase el anexo A2 de la Guía Práctica.</P><P>Téngase en cuenta que tras la salida del Reino Unido de la Unión Europea, las normas de acceso a los procedimientos de contratación pública de la Unión Europea de los operadores económicos establecidos en terceros países se aplicarán a candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido en función del resultado de las negociaciones. En caso de que las disposiciones jurídicas en vigor en el momento de la adjudicación del contrato no permitan dicho acceso, los candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido podrían ser excluidos del procedimiento de contratación.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observaciones:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deben pasar al menos 30 días naturales desde la publicación de este anuncio de información previa hasta la publicación del correspondiente anuncio de licitación.</P><P>Por el momento, no deben enviarse solicitudes ni peticiones de información complementaria.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Tekninen tuki tarkastusvalmiuksien vahvistamiseksi ja virastojen välisen tiedonvaihdon parantamiseksi tavoitteena epävirallisen talouden vähentäminen</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sijainti – Turkki</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PALVELUJA KOSKEVA ENNAKKOTIETOILMOITUS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen viite</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menettely</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rajoitettu menettely.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ohjelman nimi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Turkkia koskeva vuotuinen toimintaohjelma vuodelle 2014 liittymistä valmistelevan tukivälineen (IPA II) yhteydessä.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahoitus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan unionin yleisen talousarvion IPA-budjettikohta 22.02 03 01 (90%) ja kansallinen rahoitusosuus (10%).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Rahoitus- ja sopimusasioiden keskusyksikkö (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turkki.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuslaji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kokonaishinta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuksen kuvaus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tämän hankkeen yleistavoitteena on epävirallisen talouden osuuden vähentäminen. Täsmällisemmin sopimus pyrkii parantamaan asiaankuuluvien laitosten tarkastustoimintaa ja virastojen välistä tiedonvaihtokykyä, jotta voitaisiin taistella tehokkaasti epävirallista taloutta vastaan. Tämän sopimuksen avulla</P><P>— vahvistetaan tarkastusvalmiuksia ja käydään läpi asiaankuuluvaa lainsäädäntöä tekemällä selvityksiä eri aloilta, järjestämällä työpajoja, koulutusta ja opintokäyntejä sekä laatimalla raportteja tarkastusnormeista,</P><P>— kehitetään virastojen välistä tiedonvaihtoa Turkin verohallinnon ja asiaankuuluvien laitosten kanssa sekä poistetaan tietojen jakamisen toteutuksen aikana ilmenneet ongelmat vaihtamalla näkemyksiä ja parantamalla yhteistyötä opintokäyntien, työpajojen, asiaankuuluvien sidosryhmien kanssa tehtyjen selvitysten ja koulutuksen avulla.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Alustava budjetti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintailmoituksen ennakoitu julkaisemisajankohta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kesäkuu 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisätiedot</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ei saatavilla.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oikeusperusta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) n:o 236/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, unionin ulkoisen toiminnan rahoitusvälineiden täytäntöönpanoa koskevista yhteisistä säännöistä ja menettelyistä sekä Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) n:o 231/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, liittymistä valmistelevan tukivälineen (IPA II) perustamisesta (EUVL L 77, 15.3.2014, s.11). Katso EU:n ulkoisten toimien sopimusmenettelyjä koskevan käytännön oppaan liite A2.</P><P>On syytä ottaa huomioon, että Yhdistyneen kuningaskunnan EU:sta irtautumisen jälkeen kolmansiin maihin sijoittautuneisiin talouden toimijoihin sovellettavia EU:n hankintamenettelyihin osallistumista koskevia sääntöjä sovelletaan Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin oleviin hakijoihin tai tarjoajiin neuvottelujen lopputuloksesta riippuen. Mikäli sopimuksenteon hetkellä voimassa olevassa lainsäädännössä ei anneta lupaa tällaiseen osallistumiseen, Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin olevat hakijat tai tarjoajat voidaan hylätä hankintamenettelystä.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Huom.:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Tämän ennakkotietoilmoituksen ja vastaavan hankintailmoituksen julkaisemisen välillä on oltava vähintään 30 kalenteripäivää.</P><P>Hakemuksia tai lisätietopyyntöjä ei pidä lähettää tässä vaiheessa.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IAP - Une assistance technique pour améliorer les capacités d’audit et améliorer le partage des données inter-agences dans le cadre de réduire l’économie informelle</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lieu(x) d'exécution : Turquie</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVIS DE PRÉINFORMATION RELATIF À UN MARCHÉ DE SERVICES</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Référence de la publication</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restreinte.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intitulé du programme</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programme d'action annuel en faveur de la Turquie au titre de l'instrument d'aide de préadhésion (IAP II) pour l'année 2014.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financement</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ligne 22.02 03 01 (IAP) du budget général de l'UE (90 %) et contribution nationale (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pouvoir adjudicateur</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unité centrale de financement et de passation de contrats (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turquie.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature du contrat</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>À prix forfaitaire.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L’objectif global du projet est de réduire le taux de l’économie informelle. Le contrat vise à améliorer la capacité de l’audit et du partage des données inter-agences des institutions concernées pour une lutte efficace contre l’économie informelle. Grâce à ce marché :</P><P>— la capacité d’audit sera améliorée et la législation pertinente sera réexaminée en menant des études dans différents secteurs, en organisant des ateliers, formations et visites d’étude et en préparant des rapports sur les standards d’audit,</P><P>— un partage de données inter-agences entre l’administration turque des recettes publiques et les institutions concernées sera développé et les problèmes apparus lors de l’exécution du partage des données seront éliminés en échangeant les points de vue et en améliorant la coopération par des visites d’étude, ateliers, études avec les parties prenantes concernées et des formations.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Budget indicatif</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date prévue pour la publication de l'avis de marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juin 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Renseignements complémentaires</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sans objet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base juridique</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Règlement (UE) no 236/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 fixant des règles communes et des procédures pour la mise en œuvre des instruments de l'Union pour le financement de l'action extérieure et règlement (UE) no 231/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 instituant un instrument d’aide de préadhésion (IAP II), (JO L 77, 15.3.2014, p.11. Voir annexe A2 du Guide pratique.</P><P>Il convient de noter qu'à la suite du retrait du Royaume-Uni de l'UE, les règles d'accès aux procédures de passation des marchés de l'UE pour les opérateurs économiques établis dans des pays tiers s'appliqueront aux candidats ou aux soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni, en fonction du résultat des négociations. Si les dispositions légales en vigueur au moment de l'attribution du contrat ne prévoient pas un tel accès, les candidats ou les soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni pourraient être exclus de la procédure de passation des marchés.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarques :</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Un délai minimal de 30 jours calendaires doit être respecté entre la publication du présent avis de préinformation et celle de l'avis de marché correspondant.</P><P>Aucune candidature ni demande de renseignements complémentaires ne sera envoyée à ce stade de la procédure.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Άγκυρα: IPA - Τεχνική βοήθεια για την ενίσχυση της ικανότητας ελέγχου και τη βελτίωση της ανταλλαγής δεδομένων μεταξύ των οργανισμών στο πλαίσιο της μείωσης της άτυπης οικονομίας</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Τόπος — Τουρκία</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ΠΡΟΚΑΤΑΡΚΤΙΚΗ ΑΝΑΚΟΙΝΩΣΗ ΓΙΑ ΥΠΗΡΕΣΙΕΣ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αριθ. αναφοράς της δημοσίευσης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Διαδικασία</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κλειστή.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τίτλος προγράμματος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ετήσιο Πρόγραμμα Δράσης για την Τουρκία για το έτος 2014 στο πλαίσιο του μηχανισμού προενταξιακής βοήθειας (ΜΠΒ II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Χρηματοδότηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κονδύλιο προϋπολογισμού ΜΠΒ 22.02 03 01 του γενικού προϋπολογισμού της ΕΕ (90 %) και εθνική συνεισφορά (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα αρχή</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Κεντρική μονάδα χρηματοδότησης και ανάθεσης συμβάσεων (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Άγκυρα</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Τουρκία.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τύπος σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Συνολική τιμή.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Περιγραφή της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ο γενικός στόχος του έργου είναι η μείωση του ποσοστού της άτυπης οικονομίας. Συγκεκριμένα, η σύμβαση αποσκοπεί στη βελτίωση της ικανότητας των αρμόδιων φορέων να ελέγχουν και να ανταλλάσσουν πληροφορίες μεταξύ των υπηρεσιών για την αποτελεσματική καταπολέμηση της άτυπης οικονομίας. Μέσω αυτής της σύμβασης:</P><P>— θα ενισχυθεί η ικανότητα ελέγχου και θα επανεξεταστεί η σχετική νομοθεσία με τη διεξαγωγή μελετών σε διάφορους τομείς, τη διοργάνωση εργαστηρίων, προγραμμάτων κατάρτισης και επισκέψεων μελέτης και την προετοιμασία εκθέσεων σχετικά με τα πρότυπα ελέγχου,</P><P>— θα αναπτυχθεί η ανταλλαγή δεδομένων μεταξύ υπηρεσιών ανάμεσα στην τουρκική διοικητική αρχή εσόδων και τα σχετικά θεσμικά όργανα και θα εξαλειφθούν τα προβλήματα κατά την εφαρμογή της ανταλλαγής δεδομένων με την ανταλλαγή απόψεων και την ενίσχυση της συνεργασίας μέσω επισκέψεων μελέτης, εργαστηρίων, μελετών με τους σχετικούς ενδιαφερόμενους φορείς και προγραμμάτων κατάρτισης.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ενδεικτικός προϋπολογισμός</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης της προκήρυξης σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ιούνιος 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Άνευ αντικειμένου.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Νομική βάση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 236/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τον καθορισμό κοινών κανόνων και διαδικασιών για την εφαρμογή των μηχανισμών χρηματοδότησης της εξωτερικής δράσης της Ένωσης και κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 231/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τη θέσπιση Μηχανισμού Προενταξιακής Βοήθειας (ΜΠΒ II), ΕΕ L 77, 15.3.2014, σ. 11. Βλέπε παράρτημα Α2 του Πρακτικού Οδηγού.</P><P>Πρέπει να ληφθεί υπόψη ότι μετά την αποχώρηση του Ηνωμένου Βασιλείου από την ΕΕ, οι κανόνες πρόσβασης σε διαδικασίες διαγωνισμού της ΕΕ για οικονομικούς φορείς που είναι εγκατεστημένοι σε τρίτες χώρες θα ισχύουν για τους υποψήφιους ή προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο ανάλογα με το αποτέλεσμα των διαπραγματεύσεων. Σε περίπτωση που η πρόσβαση αυτή δεν παρέχεται από νομικές διατάξεις που ίσχυαν κατά τον χρόνο ανάθεσης της σύμβασης, οι υποψήφιοι ή οι προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο θα μπορούσαν να απορριφθούν από τη διαδικασία διαγωνισμού.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Παρατηρήσεις:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Μεταξύ της δημοσίευσης της παρούσας προκαταρκτικής ανακοίνωσης και της δημοσίευσης της αντίστοιχης προκήρυξης σύμβασης θα πρέπει να παρεμβληθεί χρονικό διάστημα τουλάχιστον 30 ημερολογιακών ημερών.</P><P>Κατά το παρόν στάδιο δεν πρέπει να αποστέλλονται υποψηφιότητες ή αιτήματα για παροχή πληροφοριών.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Assistenza tecnica per rafforzare le capacità di audit e migliorare la condivisione dei dati tra le agenzie, al fine di ridurre l’economia informale</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ubicazione — Turchia</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVISO DI PREINFORMAZIONE RELATIVO A SERVIZI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Riferimento della pubblicazione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titolo del programma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programma d'azione annuale per la Turchia per l'anno 2014 nell'ambito dello strumento di assistenza preadesione (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanziamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Voce del bilancio IPA 22.02 03 01 del bilancio generale dell'Unione europea (90 %) e contributo nazionale (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ente appaltante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unità centrale per i finanziamenti e gli appalti (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turchia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prezzo globale.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L’obiettivo generale del progetto consiste nella riduzione del tasso di economia informale. Nello specifico, l’appalto mira a migliorare la capacità di audit e di condivisione dei dati tra le agenzie delle istituzioni pertinenti per una lotta efficace contro l'economia informale. Mediante il presente appalto:</P><P>— sarà rafforzata la capacità di audit e sarà rivista la normativa pertinente tramite la realizzazione di studi in diversi settori, l’organizzazione di seminari, corsi di formazione e visite di studio, nonché la redazione di rapporti sugli standard di audit,</P><P>— verrà sviluppata la condivisione dei dati tra l’agenzia turca delle entrate e le istituzioni competenti e saranno eliminati i problemi durante l'attuazione della condivisione dei dati attraverso lo scambio di opinioni e il rafforzamento della cooperazione attraverso visite di studio, seminari, studi con le parti interessate e corsi di formazione.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Importo indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista per la pubblicazione del bando di gara</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Giugno 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informazioni complementari</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Non applicabile.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base giuridica</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regolamento (UE) n. 236/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, recante norme e procedure comuni per l'attuazione degli strumenti per il finanziamento dell'azione esterna dell'Unione e regolamento (UE) n. 231/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che istituisce uno strumento di assistenza preadesione (IPA II), GU L 77, 15.3.2014, pag. 11. Cfr. allegato A2 della Guida pratica.</P><P>Si prega di notare che, dopo il ritiro del Regno Unito dall'UE, ai candidati o agli offerenti provenienti dal Regno Unito si applicheranno le regole di accesso alle procedure di appalto dell'UE per gli operatori economici stabiliti nei paesi terzi, in funzione dell'esito delle negoziazioni. Nel caso in cui tale accesso non sia previsto dalle disposizioni giuridiche vigenti al momento dell'aggiudicazione del contratto, i candidati o gli offerenti del Regno Unito potranno essere esclusi dalla procedura di gara.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Osservazioni:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Dovrà intercorrere un periodo minimo di 30 giorni di calendario tra la pubblicazione dell'avviso di preinformazione e quella del corrispondente bando di gara.</P><P>Si prega di non inviare candidature o richieste di ulteriori informazioni durante questa fase della procedura.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Technische bijstand ter versterking van de auditcapaciteit en ter verbetering van de gegevensuitwisseling tussen agentschappen in het kader van de terugdringing van de informele economie</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Locatie — Turkije</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VOORAANKONDIGING VOOR DIENSTEN</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referentie van de bekendmaking:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet-openbaar.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titel van het programma:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jaarlijks actieprogramma voor Turkije voor het jaar 2014 in het kader van het instrument voor pretoetredingssteun (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiering:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA-begrotingspost 22.02 03 01 van de algemene begroting van de EU (90 %) en nationale bijdrage (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centrale eenheid Financiën en Contracten (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turkije.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aard van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Totaalprijs.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschrijving van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De algemene doelstelling van het project is de terugdringing van de omvang van de informele economie. De opdracht is specifiek gericht op de verbetering van de auditcapaciteit en de capaciteit voor gegevensuitwisseling tussen agentschappen voor relevante instellingen voor de doeltreffende bestrijding van de informele economie. Via deze opdracht:</P><P>— moet de auditcapaciteit worden versterkt en moet relevante wetgeving worden herzien aan de hand van de uitvoering van onderzoeken in verschillende sectoren, de organisatie van workshops, opleidingen en studiebezoeken en de voorbereiding van verslagen met betrekking tot auditnormen,</P><P>— moet de gegevensuitwisseling tussen agentschappen, met name de Turkse belastingdienst en de relevante instellingen, worden ontwikkeld en moeten problemen bij de tenuitvoerlegging van de gegevensuitwisseling worden weggewerkt door de uitwisseling van standpunten en de verbetering van de samenwerking aan de hand van studiebezoeken, workshops, onderzoeken met relevante belanghebbenden en opleidingen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicatieve begroting:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beoogde datum voor bekendmaking van de aankondiging van opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juni 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nadere inlichtingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet van toepassing.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Juridische basis:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verordening (EU) nr. 236/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van gemeenschappelijke voorschriften en procedures voor de tenuitvoerlegging van de instrumenten van de Unie ter financiering van extern optreden en Verordening (EU) nr. 231/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van een instrument voor pretoetredingssteun (IPA II), PB L 77 van 15.3.2014, blz. 11. Zie bijlage A2 bij de „Praktische gids”.</P><P>Gelieve op te merken dat, na de uitstap van het Verenigd Koninkrijk uit de EU en afhankelijk van het resultaat van de onderhandelingen, de regels voor toegang tot EU-aanbestedingsprocedures voor ondernemers die gevestigd zijn in derde landen van toepassing zullen zijn op gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk. Indien dergelijke toegang niet is voorzien door de geldende wettelijke bepalingen op het tijdstip van de gunning van de opdracht, kunnen gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk worden geweigerd voor de aanbestedingsprocedure.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Noot:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Er moet een minimumtermijn van 30 kalenderdagen liggen tussen de bekendmaking van deze vooraankondiging en de bekendmaking van de overeenstemmende aankondiging van een opdracht.</P><P>In dit stadium mogen er geen aanvragen of verzoeken om inlichtingen worden verzonden.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ancara: IPA - Assistência técnica para o reforço da capacidade de auditoria e melhoria da partilha de dados inter-agências no âmbito da redução da economia informal</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Localização — Turquia</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANÚNCIO DE PRÉ-INFORMAÇÃO DE SERVIÇOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referência da publicação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Limitado.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Título do programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de ação anual para a Turquia para 2014, no âmbito do Instrumento de Assistência de Pré-Adesão (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rubrica orçamental do programa IPA 22.02 03 01 do orçamento geral da UE (90%) e contribuição nacional (10%).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unidade Central de Finanças e Contratos (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ancara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turquia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natureza do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Preço Global.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O objetivo geral do projeto consiste em reduzir a taxa de economia informal. Especificamente, o contrato visa melhorar a capacidade de auditoria e partilha de dados inter-agências de instituições relevantes para o combate eficiente contra a economia informal. Através deste contrato:</P><P>— a capacidade de auditoria será reforçada e a legislação relevante será revista através da realização de estudos em vários setores, organização de workshops, formações e visitas de estudo e pela preparação de relatórios sobre normas de auditoria,</P><P>— a partilha de dados inter-agências entre a Administração da Receita Turca e as instituições relevantes será desenvolvida e os problemas durante a implementação da partilha de dados serão eliminados por meio do intercâmbio de pontos de vista e a melhoria da cooperação através de visitas de estudo, workshops, estudos com partes interessadas relevantes e formações.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orçamento indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista para a publicação do anúncio de concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Junho de 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Outras informações</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Não aplicável.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base jurídica</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulamento UE n.º 236/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho de 11.3.2014 que estabelece regras e procedimentos comuns para a execução dos instrumentos da União para o financiamento da ação externa e regulamento (UE) n.º 231/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho de 11.3.2014 que cria um instrumento de assistência de pré-adesão (IPA II), JO L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11. Ver anexo A2 do «Guia Prático».</P><P>Importa notar que após a saída do Reino Unido da UE, as regras de acesso aos procedimentos de adjudicação de contratos da UE de operadores económicos estabelecidos em países terceiros aplicar-se-ão aos candidatos ou proponentes provenientes do Reino Unido consoante o resultado das negociações. Caso tal acesso não esteja previsto pelas disposições legais em vigor, os candidatos ou proponentes do Reino Unido poderão ser excluídos do concurso.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observações:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deve ser respeitado um período mínimo de 30 dias de calendário entre a publicação do presente anúncio de informação prévia e a publicação do anúncio de concurso correspondente.</P><P>Não devem ser enviadas candidaturas ou efetuados pedidos de informação nesta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Tekniskt stöd för att förstärka granskningskapaciteten och förbättra datadelningen mellan byråer inom ramen för en minskning av den informella ekonomin</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Plats – Turkiet</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÖRHANDSMEDDELANDE OM TJÄNSTER</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publikationsreferens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Förfarande</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Selektivt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Namn på program</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Årligt åtgärdsprogram för Turkiet för 2014 inom ramen för instrumentet för stöd inför anslutningen (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA-budgetrubrik 22.02 03 01 i EU:s allmänna budget (90 %) och nationellt bidrag (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centrala finansierings- och upphandlingsenheten (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turkiet.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Typ av kontrakt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Totalpris.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivning av kontraktet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Det övergripande syftet med projektet är att minska den andel, som utgörs av den informella ekonomin. Kontraktet syftar i synnerhet till att förbättra kapaciteten för granskning och datadelning mellan byråer vid berörda institutioner för en effektiv bekämpning av den informella ekonomin. Genom detta kontrakt:</P><P>- kommer granskningskapaciteten att förstärkas och relevant lagstiftning kommer att utvärderas genom genomförande av undersökningar i olika sektorer, organisering av workshoppar, utbildningar och studiebesök samt utarbetande av rapporter avseende granskningsstandarder,</P><P>- kommer datadelning mellan den turkiska skatteförvaltningen och berörda institutioner att utvecklas, och problem som uppstår under implementeringen av datadelning kommer att undanröjas genom utbyte av perspektiv och förbättrat samarbete genom studiebesök, workshoppar, undersökningar med berörda intressenter och utbildning.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Preliminär budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerad tidsplan för publicering av meddelandet om upphandling</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juni 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kompletterande information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ej tillämplig.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rättslig grund</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 236/2014 av den 11.3.2014 om fastställande av gemensamma bestämmelser och förfaranden för genomförandet av unionens instrument för finansiering av yttre åtgärder och Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 231/2014 av den 11.3.2014 om inrättande av ett instrument för stöd inför anslutningen (IPA II), EUT L 77, 15.3.2014, sidan 11. Se bilaga A2 till den praktiska handledningen.</P><P>Observera att efter det förenade kungariket Storbritanniens utträde ur EU kommer reglerna om tillgång till EU:s upphandlingsförfaranden för ekonomiska aktörer etablerade i tredjeländer att tillämpas på sökande eller anbudsgivare från det förenade kungariket Storbritannien beroende på resultatet av förhandlingarna. Om sådan tillgång inte tillhandahålls av rättsliga bestämmelser som gäller vid tidpunkten för kontraktstilldelningen kan sökande eller anbudsgivare från det förenade kungariket Storbritannien komma att uteslutas från upphandlingsförfarandet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Anmärkningar:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>En period på minst 30 kalenderdagar ska förflyta mellan publikationen av detta förhandsmeddelande och publikationen av motsvarande meddelande om upphandling.</P><P>Inga ansökningar eller begäranden av information ska skickas i detta skede.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: NPP - Technická pomoc pro posílení funkce auditu a zlepšení sdílení údajů mezi agenturami v rámci snižování neformální ekonomiky</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokalita – Turecko</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>OZNÁMENÍ PŘEDBĚŽNÝCH INFORMACÍ O SLUŽBÁCH</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenční číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užší.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Název programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Roční akční program pro Turecko pro rok 2014 v rámci nástroje předvstupní pomoci (NPP II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financování</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozpočtová položka NPP 22.02 03 01 souhrnného rozpočtu EU (90 %) a národní příspěvek (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veřejný zadavatel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ústřední finanční a kontraktační jednotka (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turecko.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Povaha zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Celková cena.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popis zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Celkovým cílem projektu je snížit míru neformální ekonomiky. Konkrétně je cílem zakázky zlepšit funkci auditu a schopnost příslušných institucí sdílet údaje mezi agenturami pro efektivní boj proti neformální ekonomice. Prostřednictvím této zakázky:</P><P>— bude posílena funkce auditu a příslušná legislativa bude přezkoumána vypracováním studií v různých odvětvích, organizací workshopů, školení a studijních pobytů a vypracováním zpráv o auditních standardech,</P><P>— dojde k rozvoji sdílení údajů mezi agenturami mezi tureckou daňovou správou a příslušnými institucemi a k odstranění problémů během realizace sdílení údajů, a to výměnou stanovisek a posílením spolupráce prostřednictvím studijních pobytů, workshopů, studií s příslušnými zúčastněnými stranami a školení.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Směrný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zamýšlené datum zveřejnění oznámení o zakázce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>červen 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Další informace</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nepoužije se.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právní základ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 236/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se stanoví společná pravidla a postupy pro provádění nástrojů Unie pro financování vnější činnosti, a nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 231/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se zřizuje nástroj předvstupní pomoci (NPP II), Úř. věst. L 77, 15.3.2014, s.11. Viz příloha A2 Praktického průvodce.</P><P>Připomínáme, že po vystoupení Spojeného království z EU se na zájemce nebo uchazeče ze Spojeného království, v závislosti od výsledku jednání, budou uplatňovat pravidla přístupu k postupům výběrového řízení EU ze strany hospodářských subjektů se sídlem ve třetích zemích. V případě, že takový přístup není zabezpečen právními předpisy platnými v době zadání zakázky, mohli by být uchazeči nebo účastníci ze Spojeného království vyloučeni z výběrového řízení.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Mezi zveřejněním těchto předběžných informací o zakázce a zveřejněním odpovídajícího oznámení o zakázce musí uplynout minimálně 30 kalendářních dnů.</P><P>V této fázi nesmí být zasílány žádné přihlášky ani žádosti o informace.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Tehniline abi auditeerimissuutlikkuse tugevdamiseks ja ametkondadevahelise andmevahetuse täiustamiseks mitteametliku majanduse vähendamise raames</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Asukoht – Türgi</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>TEENUSTE EELTEADE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaldamise viide</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menetlus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Piiratud.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmi pealkiri</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Türgi 2014. aasta tegevusprogramm ühinemiseelse abi rahastamisvahendi (IPA II) raames.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahastamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ELi üldeelarve IPA eelarvepunkt 22.02 03 01 (90 %) ja riiklik panus (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaliku sektori hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Rahastamise ja lepingute kesktalitus (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Türgi.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu laad</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Koguhind.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekti üldeesmärk on mitteametliku majanduse osatähtsuse vähendamine. Eriti seab leping eesmärgiks asjakohaste institutsioonide auditeerimis- ja ametkondadevahelise andmevahetuse suutlikkuse parendamise tõhusaks võitluseks mitteametliku majanduse vastu. Kõnealune leping on suunatud järgmiste eesmärkide saavutamisele:</P><P>– auditeerimissuutlikkust tugevdatakse ja asjakohased õigusaktid vaadatakse läbi, milleks viiakse läbi õppetöö erinevates sektorites, korraldades õpikodasid, koolitusi ja õppekülastusi ning valmistades ette aruandeid auditeerimisnormide kohta;</P><P>– täiustatakse ametkondadevahelist andmevahetust Türgi maksuameti (Turkish Revenue Administration) ja asjakohaste institutsioonide vahel ning andmevahetuse juurutamisel kerkivad probleemid kõrvaldatakse arvamuste vahetamisega ning koostöö parendamisega õppekülastuste, õpikodade, asjaomaste sidusrühmadega läbiviidava õppetöö ja koolituste kaudu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Soovituslik eelarve</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hanketeate avaldamise esialgne aeg</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juuni 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisateave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ei kohaldata.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Õiguslik alus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 236/2014, milles sätestatakse liidu välistegevuse rahastamisvahendite rakendamise ühiseeskirjad ja menetlused, ning Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 231/2014, millega luuakse ühinemiseelse abi rahastamisvahend (IPA II), (ELT L 77, 15.3.2014, lk 11). Vt praktilise juhendi lisa A2.</P><P>Palume tähele panna, et olenevalt läbirääkimiste tulemustest kehtivad pärast Ühendkuningriigi EList lahkumist Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaatidele või pakkujatele kolmandates riikides asutatud ettevõtjatele kehtivad ELi hankemenetlustele juurdepääsu käsitlevad eeskirjad. Juhul, kui selline juurdepääs ei ole tagatud lepingu sõlmimise ajal kehtivate õiguslike sätete kaudu, võidakse Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaadid või pakkujad hankemenetlusest kõrvale jätta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Märkused</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Eelteate ja vastava hanketeate avaldamise vahele peab jääma vähemalt 30 kalendripäeva.</P><P>Taotlusi ega teabenõudeid ei või selles etapis veel saata.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Szakmai segítségnyújtás az ellenőrzési felkészültség megerősítésére és az ügynökségek közötti adatmegosztás fejlesztésére irányulóan az informális gazdaság visszaszorításának hatókörén belül</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Helyszín: Törökország</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SZOLGÁLTATÁSRA IRÁNYULÓ ELŐZETES TÁJÉKOZTATÓ HIRDETMÉNY</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A közzététel hivatkozási száma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Eljárás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Meghívásos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A program címe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2014. évi cselekvési program Törökország számára az Előcsatlakozási Támogatási Eszköz (IPA II) keretében.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanszírozás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Az EU általános költségvetésének 22.02 03 01. számú IPA költségvetési tétele (90 %-ban) és nemzeti hozzájárulás (10 %-ban).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Központi Pénzügyi és Szerződéskötő Egység (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Törökország.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés típusa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Egyösszegű ár.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés meghatározása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A projekt általános célkitűzése az informális gazdaság arányának csökkentése. Konkrétabban, a szerződés célja a releváns intézmények ellenőrzési és az ügynökségek közötti adatmegosztási felkészültségének fejlesztése az informális gazdaság elleni hatásos küzdelem érdekében. A szerződés célja:</P><P>— az ellenőrzési felkészültség megerősítése és a vonatkozó jogszabályok felülvizsgálata a különböző ágazatokban végzett tanulmányok, valamint workshopok, képzések és tanulmányutak szervezése, továbbá az ellenőrzési szabványokról szóló jelentések elkészítése révén,</P><P>— a török adóhivatal és a releváns intézmények közötti intézményközi adatmegosztás fejlesztése; valamint az adatmegosztás megvalósítása során felmerülő problémák megszüntetése eszmecsere, képzések, továbbá az érdekelt felekkel folytatott együttműködés tanulmányutakkal, workshopokkal, tanulmányokkal történő fejlesztése segítségével.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Várható költségvetés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlati felhívás közzétételének tervezett időpontja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018. június</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>További információk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nem alkalmazható.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Jogalap</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A külső tevékenységek finanszírozására vonatkozó uniós eszközök végrehajtására vonatkozó közös szabályok és eljárások megállapításáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű 236/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet, valamint az IPA II Előcsatlakozási Támogatási Eszköz létrehozásáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű 231/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet (HL L 77., 15.3.2014, 11. o.). Lásd a „Gyakorlati útmutató” A2 mellékletét.</P><P>Figyelembe kell venni, hogy az Egyesült Királyságnak az EU-ból való kilépése után az Egyesült Királyságból származó jelentkezőkre vagy ajánlattevőkre – a tárgyalások kimenetelétől függően – az EU közbeszerzési eljárásaihoz való hozzáférés tekintetében a harmadik országok gazdasági szereplői számára érvényes szabályok vonatkoznak. Amennyiben a részvételről nem rendelkezik hatályban lévő jogszabály, az Egyesült Királyságból származó ajánlattevők kizárásra kerülhetnek a közbeszerzési eljárásból.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Megjegyzések:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Legalább 30 naptári napnak kell eltelnie a jelen előzetes tájékoztató hirdetmény megjelenése és a vonatkozó ajánlati felhívás közzététele között.</P><P>Ezen időszak alatt jelentkezések benyújtásának, illetve információkérésnek nincs helye.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: PNPP - Techninė pagalba, skirta audito gebėjimams stiprinti ir agentūrų dalijimuisi duomenimis gerinti mažinant šešėlinę ekonomiką</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vieta – Turkija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PASLAUGŲ IŠANKSTINIS INFORMACINIS SKELBIMAS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nuoroda į publikaciją</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ribotas konkursas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programos pavadinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2014 m. metinė veiksmų programa, skirta Turkijai, pagal Pasirengimo narystei pagalbos priemonę (PNPP II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansavimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ES bendrojo biudžeto PNPP biudžeto išlaidų kategorija 22.02 03 01 (90 %) ir nacionalinis indėlis (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Perkančioji organizacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centrinis finansų ir sutarčių skyrius (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turkija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties pobūdis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bendra kaina.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties apibūdinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bendras projekto tikslas – mažinti šešėlinės ekonomikos mastą. Konkrečiai sutartimi siekiama gerinti atitinkamų institucijų audito ir agentūrų dalijimosi duomenimis gebėjimus siekiant efektyviai kovoti su šešėline ekonomika. Įgyvendinant šią sutartį:</P><P>— bus stiprinami audito gebėjimai ir peržiūrimi susiję teisės aktai atliekant tyrimus įvairiuose sektoriuose, rengiant praktinius seminarus, mokymus, tiriamuosius vizitus ir rengiant audito standartų ataskaitas,</P><P>— bus nustatyta Turkijos pajamų administravimo tarnybos ir susijusių institucijų dalijimosi duomenimis tvarka, problemos, kylančios dalijantis duomenimis, bus išspręstos keičiantis nuomonėmis ir gerinant bendradarbiavimą; tam bus rengiami tiriamieji vizitai, praktiniai seminarai, tyrimai kartu su susijusiomis suinteresuotosiomis šalimis ir mokymai.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatomas biudžetas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatoma skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo data</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018 m. birželio mėn.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildoma informacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Netaikoma.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teisinis pagrindas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 236/2014, kuriuo nustatomos bendros Sąjungos išorės veiksmų finansavimo priemonių įgyvendinimo taisyklės ir procedūros, ir 11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 231/2014, kuriuo nustatoma Pasirengimo narystei paramos priemonė (PNPP II) (OL L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11). Žr. Praktinio vadovo A2 priedą.</P><P>Prašome atkreipti dėmesį, kad Jungtinei Karalystei pasitraukus iš ES, ekonominės veiklos vykdytojų, įsikūrusių trečiosiose šalyse, prieigos prie ES pirkimo procedūrų taisyklės bus taikomos kandidatams ar konkurso dalyviams iš Jungtinės Karalystės, priklausomai nuo derybų rezultato. Jeigu tokia prieiga nebus suteikta galiojančiomis teisinėmis nuostatomis, kandidatai arba konkurso dalyviai iš Jungtinės Karalystės gali būti pašalinti iš pirkimo procedūros.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Pastabos</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Nuo šio išankstinio informacinio skelbimo publikavimo iki atitinkamo skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo turi praeiti mažiausiai 30 kalendorinių dienų.</P><P>Šiuo etapu negalima siųsti paraiškų ar kreiptis dėl informacijos.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Tehniskā palīdzība revīzijas spēju stiprināšanai un starpaģentūru datu koplietošanas uzlabošanai ēnu ekonomikas samazināšanas ietvaros</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vieta – Turcija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IEPRIEKŠĒJS INFORMATĪVS PAZIŅOJUMS PAR PAKALPOJUMU LĪGUMU</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsauce uz publikāciju</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Slēgta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmas nosaukums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2014. gada rīcības programma Turcijai Pirmspievienošanās palīdzības instrumenta (IPA II) ietvaros</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansējums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ES vispārējā budžeta IPA budžeta pozīcija 22.02 03 01 (90 %) un valsts ieguldījums (10 %)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centrālā finanšu un līgumu aģentūra (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turcija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma veids</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Gala izmaksu līgums</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekta vispārējais mērķis ir samazināt ēnu ekonomikas īpatsvaru. Konkrētāk, līguma mērķis ir uzlabot attiecīgo iestāžu revīzijas un starpaģentūru datu koplietošanas spējas efektīvā cīņā pret ēnu ekonomiku. Šī līguma ietvaros:</P><P>— tiks stiprināta revīzijas spēja un tiks pārskatīti attiecīgie tiesību akti, veicot pētījumus dažādās nozarēs, organizējot darbseminārus, apmācības un mācību braucienus, kā arī sagatavojot ziņojumus par revīzijas standartiem;</P><P>— tiks izstrādāta starpaģentūru datu koplietošana starp Turcijas Ieņēmumu administrāciju un attiecīgajām iestādēm, kā arī tiks novērstas problēmas datu koplietošanas īstenošanas laikā, apmainoties ar viedokļiem un uzlabojot sadarbību ar attiecīgajām ieinteresētajām personām izpētes braucienu, darbsemināru, pētījumu un apmācību veidā.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Provizoriskais budžets</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paziņojuma par līgumu paredzamais publicēšanas datums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018. gada jūnijs</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildu informācija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nav</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tiesiskais pamats</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 236/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko paredz kopīgus noteikumus un procedūras, lai īstenotu Savienības instrumentus ārējās darbības finansēšanai, un Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 231/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko izveido Pirmspievienošanās palīdzības instrumentu (IPA II), OV L 77, 15.3.2014, 11. lpp. Skatīt “Praktiskās rokasgrāmatas” A2. pielikumu.</P><P>Lūdzam ņemt vērā, ka pēc Apvienotās Karalistes izstāšanās no ES uz kandidātiem un pretendentiem no Apvienotās Karalistes atkarībā no sarunu iznākuma attieksies noteikumi par trešo valstu uzņēmēju tiesībām piedalīties ES iepirkuma procedūrās. Ja līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas brīdī spēkā esošajās tiesību normās šāda piekļuve nebūs paredzēta, kandidāti vai pretendenti no Apvienotās Karalistes var tikt izslēgti no iepirkuma procedūras.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Piezīmes</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Starp šā iepriekšējā informatīvā paziņojuma un attiecīgā paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datumiem jāpaiet vismaz 30 kalendārajām dienām.</P><P>Šajā posmā nekādus pieteikumus vai informācijas pieprasījumus nesūtīt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: SGħQD - Għajnuna Teknika għat-Tisħiħ tal-Kapaċità tal-Awditjar u għat-Titjib fil-Kondiviżjoni tad-Dejta Bejn l-Aġenziji fl-ambitu tat-Tnaqqis tal-Ekonomija Informali</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Il-post — it-Turkija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVIŻ TA' TAGĦRIF MINN QABEL DWAR SERVIZZ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-proċedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-titlu tal-programm</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-Programm Annwali ta' Azzjoni għat-Turkija għas-Sena 2014 taħt l-Istrument għall-Assistenza ta' Qabel l-Adeżjoni (IPA-II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-iffinanzjar</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-punt tal-baġit tal-IPA 22.02 03 01 tal-baġit ġenerali tal-UE (90%) u l-kontribuzzjoni nazzjonali (10%).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>It-Taqsima Ċentrali tal-Finanzi u l-Kuntratti (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, it-Turkija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-tip ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prezz Globali.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-deskrizzjoni tal-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-għan ġenerali tal-proġett huwa li jnaqqas ir-rata tal-ekonomija informali. Speċifikament, il-kuntratt għandu l-għan li jtejjeb il-kapaċità tal-awditjar u tal-kondiviżjoni tad-dejta bejn l-aġenziji ta' istituzzjonijiet rilevanti fil-ġlieda effettiva kontra l-ekonomija informali. Permezz ta' dan il-kuntratt:</P><P>— il-kapaċità tal-awditjar se tissaħħaħ u l-leġiżlazzjoni rilevanti se tiġi riveduta bit-twettiq ta' studji f'setturi differenti, l-organizzazzjoni ta' workshops, taħriġ u żjarat ta' studju u t-tħejjija ta' rapporti dwar l-istandards tal-awditjar,</P><P>— il-kondiviżjoni tad-dejta bejn l-aġenziji bejn l-Amministrazzjoni tad-Dħul tat-Turkija u l-istituzzjonijiet rilevanti se tiġi żviluppata u l-problemi matul l-implimentazzjoni tal-kondiviżjoni tad-dejta se jiġu eliminati bl-iskambju ta' opinjonijiet u bit-tisħiħ tal-kooperazzjoni permezz ta' żjarat ta' studju, workshops, studji ma' partijiet interessati rilevanti u taħriġ.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-baġit indikattiv</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Iż-żmien maħsub għall-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ġunju 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif addizzjonali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mhux applikabbli.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-bażi legali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 236/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi regoli u proċeduri komuni għall-implimentazzjoni tal-istrumenti tal-Unjoni għall-finanzjament tal-azzjoni esterna u r-Regolament (UE) Nru 231/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi Strument għall-Assistenza ta' Qabel l-Adeżjoni (IPA II), ĠU L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11. Ara l-Anness A2 tal-Gwida Prattika.</P><P>Jekk jogħġbok kun af li wara l-irtirar tar-Renju Unit mill-UE, ir-regoli tal-aċċess għall-proċeduri ta' ksib tal-UE ta' operaturi ekonomiċi mwaqqfa f'pajjiżi terzi se japplikaw għall-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit skont ir-riżultat tan-negozjati. F'każ li tali aċċess mhux ipprovdut minn dispożizzjonijiet legali fis-seħħ fil-ħin tal-għoti tal-kuntratt, il-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit jistgħu jiġu mwarrba mill-proċedura tal-ksib.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Kummenti:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Irid ikun hemm perijodu minimu ta' 30 jum kalendarju bejn il-pubblikazzjoni ta' dan l-avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel u l-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt li għandu x'jaqsam miegħu.</P><P>M'għandhomx jintbagħtu applikazzjonijiet jew talbiet għal tagħrif f'dan l-istadju.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Pomoc techniczna w celu wzmocnienia zdolności do przeprowadzania audytu i poprawy wymiany danych między agencjami w zakresie ograniczania szarej strefy w gospodarce</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokalizacja – Turcja</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>WSTĘPNE OGŁOSZENIE INFORMACYJNE DOTYCZĄCE ZAMÓWIENIA NA USŁUGI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numer referencyjny publikacji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograniczona.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nazwa programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Roczny program działania na rzecz Turcji na rok 2014 w ramach Instrumentu Pomocy Przedakcesyjnej (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansowanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Linia budżetowa IPA 22.02 03 01 budżetu ogólnego UE (90 %) oraz wkład krajowy (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Instytucja zamawiająca</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centralna Jednostka Finansująco-Kontraktująca (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turcja.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rodzaj zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cena ryczałtowa</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ogólnym celem projektu jest zmniejszenie udziału szarej strefy w gospodarce. Konkretnie umowa ma na celu poprawę zdolności odpowiednich instytucji do kontroli i wymiany danych między agencjami w celu skutecznego zwalczania szarej strefy. Dzięki zawarciu niniejszej umowy:</P><P>— wzmocnione zostaną zdolności w zakresie audytu, a odpowiednie przepisy zostaną poddane przeglądowi poprzez prowadzenie badań w różnych sektorach, organizowanie warsztatów, szkoleń i wizyt studyjnych oraz przygotowywanie sprawozdań na temat standardów audytu,</P><P>— wymiana danych między turecką administracją podatkową a odpowiednimi instytucjami zostanie rozwinięta, a problemy związane z wymianą danych zostaną wyeliminowane dzięki wymianie poglądów i zacieśnianiu współpracy poprzez wizyty studyjne, warsztaty, badania z zainteresowanymi stronami oraz szkolenia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orientacyjny budżet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planowana data publikacji ogłoszenia o zamówieniu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Czerwiec 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacje dodatkowe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nie dotyczy.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Podstawa prawna</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 236/2014 z dnia 11.3.2014 ustanawiające wspólne zasady i procedury wdrażania unijnych instrumentów na rzecz finansowania działań zewnętrznych oraz rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 231/2014 z dnia 11.3.2014 ustanawiające Instrument Pomocy Przedakcesyjnej (IPA II), Dz.U. L 77 z 15.3.2014, s. 11. Zob. załącznik A2 do „Praktycznego przewodnika”.</P><P>Należy mieć świadomość, że po wystąpieniu Zjednoczonego Królestwa z UE brytyjscy kandydaci i oferenci będą podlegać zasadom dostępu do unijnych procedur udzielania zamówień podmiotom gospodarczym w państwach trzecich w zależności od wyniku negocjacji. W sytuacji gdy przepisy prawa obowiązujące w chwili udzielenia zamówienia nie będą przewidywać takiego dostępu, kandydaci lub oferenci ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa mogą zostać wykluczeni z postępowania o udzielenie zamówienia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Uwagi:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Między publikacją niniejszego wstępnego ogłoszenia informacyjnego a publikacją odpowiedniego ogłoszenia o zamówieniu musi upłynąć co najmniej 30 dni kalendarzowych.</P><P>Na tym etapie nie należy przesyłać wniosków ani zapytań o informacje.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Technická pomoc na posilnenie kapacity auditu a zlepšenie zdieľania údajov medzi agentúrami v rámci potláčania tieňovej ekonomiky</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Miesto – Turecko</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDBEŽNÉ OZNÁMENIE O OBSTARÁVANÍ SLUŽIEB</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčné číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Konanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užšia súťaž.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Názov programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ročný akčný program pre Turecko na rok 2014 v rámci nástroja predvstupovej pomoci (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zdroj financovania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozpočtová položka IPA 22.02 03 01 všeobecného rozpočtu EÚ (90 %) a národné spolufinancovanie (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verejný obstarávateľ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centrálne finančné a zmluvné oddelenie (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turecko.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Charakter verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Paušálna cena.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Celkovým cieľom projektu je znížiť mieru tieňovej ekonomiky. Konkrétne sa zmluva zameriava na zlepšenie kapacity príslušných inštitúcií v oblasti auditu a výmeny údajov medzi agentúrami na účinný boj proti tieňovej ekonomike. Prostredníctvom tohto obstarávania sa:</P><P>— realizáciou štúdií v rôznych odvetviach, organizáciou workshopov, školení a študijných návštev a prípravou správ o normách auditu posilní audítorská kapacita a preskúmajú sa príslušné právne predpisy,</P><P>— výmenou názorov a posilnením spolupráce za pomoci študijných návštev, workshopov, štúdií s príslušnými zúčastnenými stranami a školení sa vytvorí spoločné zdieľanie údajov medzi tureckou správou príjmov a príslušnými inštitúciami a odstránia sa problémy pri realizácii zdieľania údajov.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predbežný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plánovaný dátum zverejnenia oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jún 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatočné informácie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Neuplatniteľné.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právny základ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 236/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovujú spoločné pravidlá a postupy pre vykonávanie nástrojov Únie na financovanie vonkajšej činnosti, a nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 231/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj predvstupovej pomoci (IPA II), Ú. v. EÚ L 77, 15.3.2014, s.11. Pozri prílohu A2 k Praktickej príručke.</P><P>Pripomíname, že po vystúpení Spojeného kráľovstva z EÚ sa na záujemcov alebo uchádzačov zo Spojeného kráľovstva, v závislosti od výsledku rokovaní, budú uplatňovať pravidlá prístupu k postupom obstarávania EÚ zo strany hospodárskych subjektov so sídlom v tretích krajinách. V prípade, že takýto prístup sa nezabezpečí ustanoveniami platnými v čase pridelenia zákazky, záujemcovia alebo uchádzači zo Spojeného kráľovstva by mohli byť vylúčení z obstarávacieho konania.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Medzi uverejnením predbežného oznámenia a uverejnením príslušného oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania musí uplynúť minimálne 30 kalendárnych dní.</P><P>V tomto období sa nemajú zasielať žiadne prihlášky ani žiadosti o informácie.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Tehnična pomoč za okrepitev revizijske zmogljivosti in medagencijske zmogljivosti za izmenjavo podatkov za zmanjšanje neformalnega gospodarstva</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokacija – Turčija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDHODNO INFORMATIVNO OBVESTILO O NAROČILU STORITEV</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčna številka dokumenta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postopek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Omejeni.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Letni akcijski program za Turčijo za leto 2014 v okviru instrumenta za predpristopno pomoč (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proračunska postavka IPA 22.02 03 01 splošnega proračuna EU (90 %) in nacionalno sofinanciranje (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centralna enota za finance in javna naročila (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turčija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vrsta naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Globalna cena.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Splošni cilj projekta je zmanjšati raven neformalnega gospodarstva. Specifični cilj naročila je izboljšati revizijsko in medagencijsko zmogljivost za izmenjavo podatkov ustreznih institucij za učinkovit boj proti neformalnemu gospodarstvu. S tem naročilom bo:</P><P>— okrepljena revizijska sposobnost in ustrezna zakonodaja bo pregledana s pomočjo izvedbe študij v različnih sektorjih, organizacijo delavnic, usposabljanj in študijskih obiskov ter pripravo poročil o revizijskih standardih,</P><P>— razvita medagencijska izmenjava podatkov med turško upravo za prihodke in ustreznimi institucijami, težave pa se bodo med izvajanjem izmenjave podatkov odpravile z izmenjavo mnenj in okrepitvijo sodelovanja s študijskimi obiski, delavnicami, študijami z ustreznimi zainteresiranimi stranmi in usposabljanji.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Okvirni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predvideni datum objave obvestila o naročilu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Junij 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ni navedeno.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravna podlaga</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uredba (EU) št. 236/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o določitvi skupnih pravil in postopkov za izvajanje instrumentov Unije za financiranje zunanjega delovanja in Uredba (EU) št. 231/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o vzpostavitvi instrumenta za predpristopno pomoč (IPA II), UL L 77, 15.3.2014, str. 11. Glejte Prilogo A2 k Praktičnemu vodiču.</P><P>Upoštevajte, da se bodo po izstopu Združenega kraljestva iz EU pravila za dostop do razpisnih postopkov EU s strani gospodarskih subjektov, ustanovljenih v tretjih državah, za kandidate ali ponudnike iz Združenega kraljestva uporabljala v skladu z rezultati pogajanj. V primeru, da v času oddaje naročila veljavne pravne določbe ne zagotavljajo tovrstnega dostopa, se lahko kandidatom ali ponudnikom iz Združenega kraljestva sodelovanje v razpisnem postopku zavrne.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opombe:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Med objavo tega predhodnega informativnega obvestila in objavo ustreznega obvestila o naročilu mora preteči vsaj 30 koledarskih dni.</P><P>V tej fazi ne pošiljajte prijav ali zahtevkov za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Cúnamh teicniúil do neartú chumas iniúchóireachta agus feabhsú chomhroinnt sonraí idirghníomhaireachta laistigh de raon feidhme um laghdú an gheilleagair neamhfhoirmiúil</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Láthair — an Tuirc</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÓGRA RÉAMHAISNÉISE SEIRBHÍSE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nós imeachta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Teoranta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teideal an chláir</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>An clár gníomhaíochta bliantúil don Tuirc le haghaidh na bliana 2014 faoin Ionstraim um Chúnamh Réamhaontachais (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Maoiniú</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mír bhuiséid IPA 22.02 03 01 de bhuiséad ginearálta AE (90 %) agus an cion tairbhe náisiúnta (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás Conarthach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An Láraonad Airgeadais agus Conarthaí (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Tuirc.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cineál an chonartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>An praghas iomlán.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ar an gconradh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Is é cuspóir foriomlán an tionscadail chun ráta an gheilleagair neamhfhoirmiúil a laghdú. Is í aidhm shonrach leis an gconradh chun cumas iniúchóireachta agus comhroinnte sonraí idirghníomhaireachta na n-údarás ábhartha a fheabhsú chun comhrac go héifeachtach i gcoinne an gheilleagair neamhfhoirmiúil. Is leis an gconradh seo:</P><P>— a neartófar an cumas iniúchóireachta agus a athbhreithneofar an reachtaíocht ábhartha ach staidéir a stiúradh sna hearnálacha éagsúla, ceardlanna, cuairteanna staidéir a eagrú, agus tuairiscí faoi chaighdeáin iniúchóireachta a ullmhú,</P><P>— a fhorbrófar an chomhroinnt sonraí idirghníomhaireachta idir Riarachán Ioncaim na Tuirce agus na hinstitiúidí ábhartha; agus a bhainfear fadhbanna le linn fhorfheidhmiú na comhroinnte sonraí ach tuairimí a idirmhalartú agus an comhar a fheabhsú trí chuairteanna staidéir, ceardlanna, staidéir le geallsealbhóirí ábhartha agus oiliúintí.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buiséad táscach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>An sprioc atá beartaithe d'fhoilsiú an fhógra conartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Meitheamh 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis bhreise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Neamhbhainteach.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bunús dlí</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 236/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 ina leagtar síos rialacha agus nósanna imeachta comhchoiteanna le haghaidh chur chun feidhme ionstraimí an Aontais chun an ghníomhaíocht sheachtrach a mhaoiniú; agus Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 231/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 lena mbunaítear Ionstraim le haghaidh Cúnaimh Réamhaontachais (IPA II), IO L 77, 15.3.2014, lch. 11. Féach Iarscríbhinn A2 den Treoir Phraiticiúil.</P><P>Tabhair faoi deara go gcuirfear na rialacha um rochtain ar nósanna imeachta soláthair an AE ag oibreoirí eacnamaíocha atá bunaithe i dtríú tíortha i bhfeidhm ar iarrthóirí nó ar thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe tar éis di tarraingt siar ón AE, ag brath ar thorthaí na n-idirbheartaíochtaí. Sa chás nach gcuirfear a leithéid de rochtain ar fáil trí fhorálacha dlíthiúla a bheidh i bhfeidhm nuair a dhámhfar an conradh, d'fhéadfaí diúltú do thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe ón nós imeachta soláthair.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Nótaí:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Ní mór tréimhse 30 lá féilire ar a laghad a bheith idir foilsiú an fhógra réamhaisnéise seo agus foilsiú an fhógra conartha chomhfhreagraigh.</P><P>Níor cheart aon iarratais ná iarrataí ar fhaisnéis a sheoladh faoi láthair.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Анкара: ИПП - Техническа помощ за подсилване на капацитета за одит и подобряване на споделянето на данни между агенциите в обхвата на намаляване на сивата икономика</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Местоположение — Турция</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ОБЯВЛЕНИЕ ЗА ПРЕДВАРИТЕЛНА ИНФОРМАЦИЯ ЗА УСЛУГИ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Референтен номер на публикация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Процедура</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ограничена.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Заглавие на програма</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Годишна програма за действие за Турция за 2014 година по Инструмента за предприсъединителна помощ (ИПП II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Финансиране</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Бюджетна позиция на ИПП 22.02 03 01 от общия бюджет на ЕС (90 %) и национално участие (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Централно звено за финансиране и договориране (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Анкара</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Турция.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Вид на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Обща цена.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Описание на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Общата цел на проекта е да намали процента на сивата икономика. По-конкретно, поръчката цели да подобри капацитета за одити и споделяне на данни между агенциите на релевантни институции за ефективна борба със сивата икономика. Чрез тази поръчка:</P><P>— капацитетът за одит ще бъде подсилен и съответното законодателство ще бъде прегледано чрез провеждане на проучвания в различи сектори, организиране на работилници, обучения и посещения за обучение и подготовка на доклади за стандартите за одит;</P><P>— споделянето на данни между турската данъчна администрация и релевантните институции ще се разработи и проблемите по време на изпълнението на споделянето на данни ще се елиминират чрез обмен на възгледи и подобряване на сътрудничеството с посещения за обучение, работилници, проучвания с релевантни заинтересовани лица и обучения.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Индикативен бюджет</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Очакван срок за публикуване на обявлението за поръчка</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>юни 2018 г.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Допълнителна информация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Не е приложимо.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Правно основание</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Регламент (ЕС) № 236/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за определяне на общи правила и процедури за изпълнението на инструментите на Съюза за финансиране на външната дейност и Регламент (ЕС) № 231/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за създаване на Инструмент за предприсъединителна помощ (ИПП II), ОВ L 77, 15.3.2014 г, стр. 11. Вж. приложение А2 към Практическото ръководство.</P><P>Моля, имайте предвид, че след оттеглянето на Обединеното кралство от ЕС, правилата за достъп до процедури за обществени поръчки на ЕС за икономически оператори, установени в трети държави, ще се прилагат за кандидати или оференти от Обединеното кралство, в зависимост от резултата от преговорите. В случай че такъв достъп не е предвиден в действащите правни разпоредби, които са в сила по време на възлагането на поръчката, кандидатите или оферентите от Обединеното кралство могат да бъдат отхвърлени от процедурата за обществена поръчка.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Забележки:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Трябва да има минимален период от 30 календарни дни между публикуването на това обявление за предварителна информация и публикуването на съответното обявление за поръчка.</P><P>На този етап не трябва да се изпращат никакви молби или искания за информация.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Asistență tehnică pentru consolidarea capacității de audit și îmbunătățirea schimbului de date între agenții în domeniul de aplicare al reducerii economiei informale</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Locație – Turcia</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNȚ DE INTENȚIE PRIVIND UN CONTRACT DE ACHIZIȚII PUBLICE DE SERVICII</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referința publicației</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedură</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restrânsă.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titlul programului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programul anual de acțiune pentru Turcia pentru anul 2014, în baza Instrumentului de asistență pentru preaderare (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanțare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Articolul bugetar IPA 22.02 03 01 din bugetul general al UE (90%) și contribuție națională (10%).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea contractantă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unitatea centrală pentru finanțe și contracte (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turcia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Preț global.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Obiectivul general al proiectului este de a reduce rata economiei informale. Mai exact, contractul vizează îmbunătățirea capacității de audit și de partajare a datelor între agențiile instituțiilor relevante pentru combaterea economiei informale. Prin acest contract:</P><P>— capacitatea de audit va fi consolidată, iar legislația relevantă va fi revizuită prin realizarea de studii în diferite sectoare, prin organizarea de ateliere, cursuri de formare și vizite de studiu și prin pregătirea rapoartelor privind standardele de audit,</P><P>— vor fi elaborate schimburi de date între agenții între administrația fiscală din Turcia și instituțiile relevante, iar problemele legate de punerea în aplicare a schimbului de date vor fi eliminate prin schimbul de opinii și consolidarea cooperării prin vizite de studiu, ateliere de lucru, studii cu părțile interesate relevante și cursuri de formare.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buget indicativ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevăzută de publicare a anunțului de participare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Iunie 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informații suplimentare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nu se aplică.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Temeiul juridic</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulamentul (UE) nr. 236/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de stabilire a normelor și procedurilor comune pentru punerea în aplicare a instrumentelor Uniunii pentru finanțarea acțiunii externe și Regulamentul (UE) nr. 231/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de instituire a unui instrument de asistență pentru preaderare (IPA II), JO L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11. A se vedea anexa A2 la Ghidul practic.</P><P>A se avea în vedere că, după retragerea Marii Britanii din UE, normele de acces al operatorilor economici stabiliți în țări terțe la procedurile de achiziții publice ale UE se vor aplica ofertanților sau candidaților din Marea Britanie în funcție de rezultatul negocierilor. În cazul în care accesul nu este prevăzut de dispozițiile juridice în vigoare la momentul atribuirii contractului, candidații sau ofertanții din Regatul Unit ar putea fi respinși de la procedura de achiziții publice.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observații:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Trebuie respectată o perioadă de minimum 30 de zile calendaristice între publicarea prezentului anunț de intenție și publicarea anunțului de participare corespunzător.</P><P>În această etapă nu se acceptă candidaturi sau cereri de informații.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Tehnička pomoć jačanju kapaciteta za reviziju i unaprjeđenje razmjene podataka unutar agencije u sklopu smanjenja sive ekonomije</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokacija — Turska</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PRETHODNA INFORMACIJSKA OBAVIJEST O USLUGAMA</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uputa na objavu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139646/IH/SER/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postupak</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograničeni.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Godišnji akcijski program za Tursku u okviru Instrumenta pretpristupne pomoći (IPA II) za 2014.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA proračunska stavka 22.02 03 01 općeg proračuna EU-a (90 %) i nacionalni doprinos (10 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Središnji odjel za financiranje i ugovaranje (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turska.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Priroda ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ukupna cijena.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ukupni je cilj ovog projekta smanjenje sive ekonomije. Ugovor je posebno usmjeren na unaprjeđenje kapaciteta relevantnih institucija za potrebe revizije razmjene podataka unutar agencije, kako bi se siva ekonomija onemogućila na učinkovit način. Ovim će se ugovorom:</P><P>— ojačati kapaciteti za provedbu revizija i provjeriti relevantno zakonodavstvo, provođenjem studija u različitim sektorima, organiziranjem radionica, osposobljavanja i studijskih posjeta te pripremom izvješća o revizijskim normama,</P><P>— razviti međusobna razmjena podataka između agencija turske uprave za financije i relevantnih institucija i ukloniti problemi koji se javljaju tijekom provedbe, i to razmjenom mišljenja i jačanjem suradnje kroz studijske posjete, radionice, studije koje obuhvaćaju relevantne dionike i osposobljavanja.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indikativni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 160 800 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predviđeni datum objave poziva na nadmetanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>lipanj 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nije primjenjivo.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravni temelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uredba (EU) br. 236/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o utvrđivanju zajedničkih pravila i postupaka za provedbu instrumenata Unije za financiranje vanjskog djelovanja i Uredba (EU) br. 231/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o uspostavi Instrumenta za pretpristupnu pomoć (IPA II), SL L 77, 15.3.2014., str. 11. Vidjeti Prilog A2 Praktičnom vodiču.</P><P>Napominjemo da će se nakon povlačenja Ujedinjene Kraljevine iz EU-a na natjecatelje ili ponuditelje iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine primjenjivati pravila pristupa postupcima nabave EU-a za gospodarske subjekte s poslovnim nastanom u trećim zemljama, ovisno o rezultatima pregovora. U slučaju da pristup nije omogućen putem pravnih odredbi koje su na snazi u vrijeme sklapanja ugovora, natjecatelji ili ponuditelji iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine mogu biti odbijeni iz postupka javne nabave.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Napomene:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Između objave ove prethodne informacijske obavijesti i objave odgovarajućeg poziva na nadmetanje mora proći najmanje 30 kalendarskih dana.</P><P>U toj se fazi ne smiju slati prijave ili zahtjevi za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>