<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="180391-2018" EDITION="2018081"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-180221-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180618</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN CS DA DE ET EL ES FR IT LV LT HR HU MT NL PL PT SK SL FI SV RO GA BG </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>81</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180426</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 081-180391</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180391-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="RS"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45210000">Building construction work</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180420</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180618 11:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="2">Additional information</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="Z">Not specified</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="8">Other</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>BI102</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Сърбия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Белград</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕИБ - ЕИБ - Научно-технологичен парк в Ниш (STP Ниш) – Изпълнение на строителни работи по изграждане на нова сграда</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Srbsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bělehrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Vědecko-technologický park v Niši (VTP Niš) – provedení stavebních prací na nové budově</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Serbien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Beograd</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Videnskabs- og teknologipark i Niš – udførelse af bygge-og anlægsarbejder i forbindelse med nye bygninger</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Serbien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Wissenschafts- und Technologiepark in Niš (STP Niš) – Ausführung der Bauarbeiten für den Neubau</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Σερβία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Βελιγράδι</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΕπ - ΕΤΕπ - Επιστημονικό και τεχνολογικό πάρκο της Νις (STP Niš) – Εκτέλεση των εργασιών κατασκευής νέου κτιρίου</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrade</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrado</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - BEI - Parque Científico y Tecnológico de Niš (PCT Niš): ejecución de las obras para la construcción de un nuevo edificio</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIP - EIP - Nišis asuv teadus- ja tehnoloogiapark (STP Niš) – uue hoone ehitustööde tegemine</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIP - EIP - Nišin tiede- ja teknologiapuiston tilojen rakennustyöt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Serbie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrade</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - BEI - Parc scientifique et technologique de Niš – Exécution de travaux de construction d’un nouveau bâtiment</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Seirbia, an t</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Béalgrád</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - BEI - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Srbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Beograd</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Znanstveno-tehnološki park u Nišu (STP Niš) – Provedba radova izgradnje nove zgrade</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Szerbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrád</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBB - EBB - Niši Tudományos és Technológiai Park (STP Niš) – Új épület építési munkáinak kivitelezése</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrado</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - BEI - Parco scientifico e tecnologico di Niš (PST Niš) – Esecuzione dei lavori di costruzione di un nuovo edificio</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Serbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgradas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Mokslo ir technologijų parkas Niše (MTP Niše) – naujų pastatų statybos darbų vykdymas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Serbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrada</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Zinātnes un tehnoloģiju parks Nišā (ZTP Nišā) — jaunas ēkas būvdarbu izpilde</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>is-Serbja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - BEI - Il-Park tax-Xjenza u t-Teknoloġija f’Niš (STP Niš) – L-eżekuzzjoni ta’ xogħlijiet għall-kostruzzjoni ta’ binja ġdida</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Servië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrado</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Wetenschaps- en technologiepark in Niš – Bouw van nieuwe gebouwen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBI - EBI - Park Nauki i Technologii w Niszu – realizacja robót budowlanych dotyczących nowego budynku</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Sérvia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrado</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - BEI - Parque de Ciência e Tecnologia em Niš (PCT Niš) – Execução das obras de construção do novo edifício</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - BEI - Parcul științific și tehnologic din Niš (STP Niš) – Executarea de noi lucrări de construcții de clădiri</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Srbsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belehrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Vedecký a technologický park v meste Niš (STP Niš) – Vykonanie stavebných prác potrebných pre vznik novej budovy</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Srbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Beograd</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Znanstveni in tehnološki park v Nišu (STP Niš) – Izvedba gradbenih del za novo stavbo</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Serbien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - EIB - Vetenskaps- och teknologipark i Niš (STP Niš) – utförande av byggentreprenad för uppförande av en ny byggnad</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DA">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - EIB - Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš) – New building construction works execution (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hereby ANNOUNCE</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>THE REPUBLIC OF SERBIA Public Investment Management Office As the Employer</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>The Republic of Serbia has received financing from the European Investment Bank in the form of a loan toward the cost of the project: Research and Development in the Public Sector. The Public Investment Management Office of the Government of the Republic of Serbia, an implementing agency of the Borrower, intends to apply a portion of the proceeds of this loan to eligible payments under the contract for Sub-project: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution in accordance with the European Investment Bank Guide to Procurement.</P><P>Pursuant to Art.7, para.1, item 2a) of the Public Procurement Law RS 124/2012, 14/2015 and 68/2015, respectively pursuant to Finance Contract (Public Sector Research and Development) between the Republic of Serbia and the European Investment Bank dated 4.3.2010, Public Investment Management Office, as the Purchaser, has decided to initiate an international open procurement procedure for the following construction works: Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD, and now invites bids from eligible tenderers to provide the already mentioned construction works.</P><P>Estimated value is 8 750 000,00 EUR excluding VAT.</P><P>Expected commencement date of construction works is August 2018.</P><P>Brief description of the works:</P><P>Construction of Science and Technology Park Niš, with underground, ground floor and 3 levels, ground and above ground levels gross surface of 10 625,37 m2 and underground level gross surface of 3 352,22 m2, is planned to be built at cadastre parcel “1929/6 KO Niš – Crveni krst” gross surface of 9 429,00 m2. Subject parcel is located within vicinity of High School Institutions and other facilities for fulfilling required students’ standards.</P><P>Content:</P><P>— Underground level is multi-functional space with major function as underground garage with capacity of 75 parking places, extended within the limits of complete building, having technical rooms, 2 staircases, 2 elevator lobbies with 3 elevators and additional spaces as for fitness club with sanitary block included,</P><P>— Ground level is “opened by the penetration” positioned transversally against longitudinal facade plane. Ground level (business space) clear height is from 5,40m up to about 5,70m. Meeting room with restaurant and kitchen, showroom with technical and sanitary block, staircases and elevators are projected at ground level,</P><P>— Business space with offices, kitchenette, dining room, terrace, sanitary block, technical rooms, staircases and elevators are at levels 1, 2 and 3.</P><P>Tenders with variant solutions will not be accepted.</P><P>Contract will be signed with the best tenderer in an open international procurement procedure. The contract is expected to be implemented from August 2018 to October 2019 (excluding Defects Notification Period).</P><P>The tender evaluation criterion is the Lowest Evaluated Tender Price.</P><P>The right to participate in this international tender belongs to all interested entities that fulfill the mandatory conditions for the participation in the procedure. The tenderer is obliged to submit the evidence on the fulfillment of the conditions that are determined in the Tender documents.</P><P>The conditions which must be met by a tenderer, and also a way of proving whether the conditions are met, are specified in the Tender documents.</P><P>Interested parties may obtain further information from Public Investment Management Office Belgrade via e-mail: procurement.rd@pim.gov.rs</P><P>The Tender Documents are available in the English language except for detailed design files that are given in Serbian.</P><P>A complete set of Tender Documents shall be posted on the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and will be available to any interested tenderer.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a bank guarantee for Tender Security to be submitted in the amount of 100 000 EUR or equivalent in a convertible currency in RSD calculated according to the average exchange rate of the National Bank of Serbia on the day of the payment. The Bank guarantee for Tender Security must be valid at least thirty (30) days after the expiration of Tender validity.</P><P>The Tender Security, Performance and Advance Payment Guarantee, which the chosen Tenderer is required to present following the execution of contract, must be verified by a domestic bank, i.e. the Tenderer is required to present, together with a foreign bank’s guarantee, a counter guarantee from a domestic bank.</P><P>All bank guarantees must be irrevocable, i.e. without protest, unconditional and payable at first call.</P><P>Tender validity period is at least 120 calendar days from the final tender submission date.</P><P>If necessary, the Ordering Authority shall organize a pre-tender meeting and site visit of which all parties that have collected the Tender Documents will be duly informed in writing by posting an information on the Employer’s website: http://www.obnova.gov.rs/english/public-procurement and http://www.obnova.gov.rs/cirilica/javne-nabavke</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the following address not later than 18.6.2018 at 11/00 am:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>”Kancelarija za upravljanje javnim ulaganjima”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Nemanjina street no.22-26, Belgrade, Administration for Joint Services of the Republic Bodies registry, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Tenders have to be made according to the” two-envelope” procedure, in which both the technical and financial offers are submitted together, but in separate envelopes. The technical offers are opened first and evaluated for compliance. The financial envelopes of the technically responsive tenders only are then opened.</P><P>Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope, marked with the reference "Bid for Science and Technology Park in Niš (STP Niš), New building construction works execution no. IOP/13-2018/RD" in person or by post at the abovementioned address no later than 18.6.2018, until 11:00 am.</P><P>Bids received after the deadline specified in the preceding paragraph shall be considered untimely. Untimely bids shall not be opened and after opening procedure shall be returned to the bidder, with an indication stating that the bid is not submitted timely.</P><P>The tender opening (the technical offers) shall take place on the same day 18.6.2018 at 1pm at the address: Belgrade, Krunska street No. 58 in the presence of the authorized representatives of those tenderers who choose to attend the tender opening with the provision of the authorization to attend the tender opening session.</P><P>Opening of financial part of the tenders shall be performed after the examination of the technical part of the bids. The Employer shall submit, to all tenderers who sent bids, a reasoned Decision on the eligibility of the tenderer, as well as an invitation to all qualified tenderers to participate in the opening of financial bids.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>