<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="180388-2018" EDITION="2018081"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-173438-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20190417</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>81</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180426</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 081-180388</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180388-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>FR</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BF"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71356200">Technical assistance services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180417</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>AP301</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EUF - Internationalt udbud vedrørende rekruttering af teknisk bistand til støtte for skatteændringer i Vestafrika</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EEF - Internationale Ausschreibung für die Bereitstellung technischer Unterstützung für die Steuerreform in Westafrika</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EDF - International invitation to tender for the recruitment of technical assistance to support fiscal transition in West Africa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Uagadugu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>FED - Licitación internacional para la contratación de asistencia técnica en apoyo de la transición fiscal en África Occidental</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EKR - Kansainvälinen tarjouspyyntö teknisen tukihenkilöstön hankkimiseksi tukemaan Länsi-Afrikan maiden verojärjestelmien muutosta</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Burkina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>FED - Appel d'offre international pour le recrutement d'une assistance technique en appui à la transition fiscale en Afrique de l'Ouest</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Μπουρκίνα</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ουαγκαντούγκου</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑ - Διεθνής διαγωνισμός για την πρόσληψη ομάδας τεχνικής βοήθειας προς υποστήριξη της φορολογικής μετάβασης στη Δυτική Αφρική</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>FES - Bando di gara internazionale per assumere l'assistenza tecnica a sostegno della transizione fiscale nell'Africa occidentale</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EOF - Internationale oproep tot inschrijving voor de verwerving van technische bijstand ter ondersteuning van de fiscale omschakeling in West-Afrika</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Burquina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Uagadugu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>FED - Anúncio de concurso internacional para o recrutamento de uma assistência técnica de apoio à transição fiscal na África Ocidental</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EUF - Internationell anbudsinbjudan för rekrytering av teknisk assistans som stöd vid skatteomvandlingen i Västafrika.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERF - Mezinárodní výběrové řízení na získání technické podpory pro daňovou transformaci v západní Africe</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EAF - Rahvusvaheline pakkumiskutse Lääne-Aafrikas maksusüsteemi ümberkorraldamise toetamiseks tehnilise abi värbamiseks</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EFA - Nemzetközi nyílt ajánlati felhívás az adóügyi átmenet támogatására irányuló szakmai segítségnyújtás igénybevétele vonatkozásában Nyugat-Afrikában</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Burkina Fasas</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Uagadugu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EPF - Tarptautinis konkursas dėl techninės pagalbos suteikimo mokesčių sistemos pereinamojo laikotarpio paramos programai Vakarų Afrikoje</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Burkinafaso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Vagadugu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EAF - Starptautisks uzaicinājums uz konkursu par tehniskās palīdzības darbinieku nolīgšanu nodokļu pārejas atbalstam Rietumāfrikā</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>FEŻ - Sejħa għall-offerti internazzjonali għar-reklutaġġ ta' għajnuna teknika li tappoġġja t-transizzjoni fiskali fl-Afrika tal-Punent</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Wagadugu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EFR - Procedura międzynarodowa dotycząca pozyskania pomocy technicznej w celu wsparcia transformacji systemu podatkowego w Afryce Zachodniej</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Burkina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERF - Medzinárodná verejná výzva na predloženie ponúk týkajúca sa náboru odbornej pomoci na podporu pri zmene daňového systému v západnej Afrike</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERS - Mednarodni razpis za najem tehnične pomoči v podporo davčnemu prehodu v zahodni Afriki</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Buircíne Fasó</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>CEF - Cuireadh chun tairisceana idirnáisiúnta chun cúnamh teicniúil a earcú chun tacú le sochar idirthréimhseach san Afraic Thiar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Буркина Фасо</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Уагадугу</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕФР - Международна покана за участие в търг за набиране на техническа помощ в подкрепа на данъчния преход в Западна Африка</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>FED - Licitație internațională pentru recrutarea de asistență tehnică în sprijinul tranziției fiscale în Africa de Vest</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERF - Poziv na međunarodno nadmetanje za zapošljavanje tehničke pomoći za podršku poreznoj tranziciji u Zapadnoj Africi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Kommissionen for Den Vestafrikanske Økonomiske og Monetære Union (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Kommission der Westafrikanischen Wirtschafts- und Währungsunion (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">Commission of the West African Economic and Monetary Union (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">La Comisión de la Unión Económica y Monetaria del África Occidental (UEMAO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Länsi-Afrikan talous- ja rahaliiton (Union économique et monétaire ouest-africaine – UEMOA) komissio</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Commission de l'union économique et monétaire Ouest africaine (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Επιτροπή της Δυτικοαφρικανικής Οικονομικής και Νομισματικής Ένωσης (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Commissione dell'Unione economica e monetaria dell'Africa occidentale (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Commissie van de West-Afrikaanse economische en monetaire unie (Waemu)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">Comissão da União Económica e Monetária da África Ocidental (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Västafrikanska ekonomiska och monetära unionens (WAEMU) kommission</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Komise Západoafrické hospodářské a měnové unie (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Lääne-Aafrika majandus- ja rahaliidu (West African Economic and Monetary Union (WAEMU)) komisjon</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">A Nyugat-afrikai Gazdasági és Monetáris Unió (UEMOA) bizottsága</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Vakarų Afrikos ekonominės ir pinigų sąjungos (VAEPS) komisija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Rietumāfrikas Ekonomiskās un monetārās savienības (Union économique et monétaire ouest-africaine – UEMOA) komisija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">Il-Kummissjoni tal-Unjoni Ekonomika u Monetarja tal-Afrika tal-Punent (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Komisja Zachodnioafrykańskiej Unii Gospodarczej i Walutowej (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Komisia Západoafrickej hospodárskej a menovej únie (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Komisija Zahodnoafriške ekonomske in monetarne unije (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">Coimisiún Aontas Eacnamaíoch agus Airgeadaíochta na hAfraice Thiar (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Комисия на Западноафриканския икономически и валутен съюз (ЗАИВС)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Comisia Uniunii economice și monetare vest-africane (UEMA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Komisija Zapadnoafričke ekonomske i monetarne unije (WAEMU)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: EUF - Internationalt udbud vedrørende rekruttering af teknisk bistand til støtte for skatteændringer i Vestafrika</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>De vestafrikanske staters økonomiske fællesskab (ECOWAS) + Mauritanien / Vestafrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FORHÅNDSMEDDELELSE OM TJENESTEYDELSER</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udbudsreference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Begrænset</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programtitel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Støtteprogram vedrørende skatteændringer i Vestafrika</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt CRIS nr. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Kommissionen for Den Vestafrikanske Økonomiske og Monetære Union (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontraktens art</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Enhedspris</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivelse af kontrakten</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kontraktens formål er levering af lang- og kortsigtet teknisk bistand, udførelse af uddannelsesaktiviteter vedrørende programmet og gennemførelse af andre tiltag, der vil kunne forbedre den interne skatteforvaltning i ECOWAS-medlemsstater og forstærkning af koordinerings-, opfølgnings- og evalueringssystemet af programmerne for skatteændringer i begge kommissioner (ECOWAS og WAEMU) samt på medlemsstatsniveau.</P><P>Der påmindes om, at støtteprogrammet for skatteændringer i Vestafrika har til formål at støtte gennemførelsen af programmer for disse ændringer i Vestafrika som følge af gennemførelsen af regionale politikker for handelsliberalisering (toldunion, fælles toldtarif over for tredjelande, ØPA). Der forventes 3 resultater:</P><P>(i) forbedring af intern skatteforvaltning i medlemsstater og bedre koordinering på regionsniveau</P><P>(ii) forstærket bekæmpelse af svig, skatteundgåelse, ulovlige kapitalstrømme og korruption, hvilket bidrager til forøget skatteprovenu</P><P>(iii) forstærkede koordinerings-, opfølgnings- og evalueringsprogrammer for skatteændringer på kommissions- og medlemsstatsniveau.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vejledende budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planlagt dato for offentliggørelse af udbudsbekendtgørelsen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yderligere oplysninger</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ingen</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Retsgrundlag (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bilag IV til partnerskabsaftalen mellem medlemmerne af gruppen af stater i Afrika, Vestindien og Stillehavet og Det Europæiske Fællesskab og dets medlemsstater, underskrevet i Cotonou 23.6.2000, som ændret i Luxembourg 25.6.2005 og i Ouagadougou 22.6.2010. Der henvises til bilag IV som ændret ved AVS-EU-Ministerrådets afgørelse nr. 1/2014 af 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Angiv venligst enhver specificitet, der kan have konsekvens for deltagelsesreglerne (f.eks. geografisk, tematisk, kortsigtet eller langsigtet).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Bemærkninger:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Der skal gå mindst 30 kalenderdage mellem offentliggørelsen af denne forhåndsmeddelelse og offentliggørelsen af den tilhørende udbudsbekendtgørelse.</P><P>Der bør ikke fremsendes ansøgninger eller anmodninger om oplysninger på nuværende tidspunkt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: EEF - Internationale Ausschreibung für die Bereitstellung technischer Unterstützung für die Steuerreform in Westafrika</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Länder der Wirtschaftsgemeinschaft der westafrikanischen Staaten (Ecowas) + Mauretanien/Westafrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VORINFORMATION ÜBER EINEN DIENSTLEISTUNGSAUFTRAG</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verfahren</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nichtoffen</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmbezeichnung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Unterstützungsprogramm für die Steuerreform in Westafrika</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanzierung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>CRIS-Projekt Nr. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ausschreibende Behörde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Kommission der Westafrikanischen Wirtschafts- und Währungsunion (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Art des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Einheitspreis</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Im Rahmen dieses Auftrags werden die Bereitstellung einer langfristigen wie auch kurzfristigen technischen Unterstützung, die Übernahme von Schulungsaktionen des Programms und die Umsetzung weiterer Supports, die sich für die Verbesserung der Verwaltung der inneren Steuerfragen der Mitgliedstaaten von ECOWAS und die Stärkung des Koordinierungs-, Kontroll- und Bewertungssystems der Programme für die Steuerreform auf der Ebene jeder einzelnen Kommission (ECOWAS und UEMOA) sowie auf der Ebene der Mitgliedstaaten eignen.</P><P>Zur Erinnerung: Das Unterstützungsprogramm für die Steuerreform in Westreform soll die Umsetzung der Programme für die Steuerreform in Westafrika unterstützen, die aus der Umsetzung von regionalen Freigabe des Austauschs (Zollunion, TEC, WPA) resultieren. Es werden 3 Ergebnisse erwartet:</P><P>(i) Die Verwaltung der inneren Steuerfragen der Mitgliedstaaten wird verbessert und innerhalb der Region besser koordiniert;</P><P>(ii) Die Bekämpfung von Betrug, Steuerflucht, unzulässigen Geldflüssen und Korruption wird verstärkt und trägt zu einer Erhöhung der Steuereinnahmen bei;</P><P>(iii) Das Koordinierungs-, Kontroll- und Bewertungssystem der Programme für die Steuerreform wird auf der Ebene der einzelnen Kommissionen sowie auf der Ebene der Mitgliedstaaten verstärkt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veranschlagter Auftragswert</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vorgesehener Zeitpunkt der Veröffentlichung der Auftragsbekanntmachung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zusätzliche Informationen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Entfällt</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsgrundlage (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anhang IV des Partnerschaftsabkommens zwischen den Mitgliedern der Gruppe der Staaten in Afrika, im Karibischen Raum und im Pazifischen Ozean einerseits und der Europäischen Gemeinschaft und ihren Mitgliedstaaten andererseits, unterzeichnet in Cotonou am 23.6.2000, in der am 25.6.2005 in Luxemburg und am 22.6.2010 in Ouagadougou geänderten Fassung. Es wird auf Anhang IV in der Fassung gemäß Beschluss Nr. 1/2014 des AKP-EU-Ministerrates vom 20.6.2014 verwiesen.</P><P>(1) Geben Sie bitte alle Besonderheiten an, die sich auf die Teilnahmebedingungen auswirken könnten (zum Beispiel geographische, Besonderheit, kurz- oder langfristige Thematik).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Hinweise:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Zwischen der Veröffentlichung der vorliegenden Vorinformation und der Veröffentlichung der zugehörigen Auftragsbekanntmachung ist eine Mindestfrist von 30 Kalendertagen einzuhalten.</P><P>Zum gegenwärtigen Zeitpunkt sind weder Bewerbungen einzureichen noch Auskünfte anzufordern.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: EDF - International invitation to tender for the recruitment of technical assistance to support fiscal transition in West Africa</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Countries of the Community of West African States (Ecowas) + Mauritania / West Africa</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PRIOR INFORMATION NOTICE REGARDING THE SERVICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publication reference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programme name</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fiscal transition support programme in West Africa</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financing</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>CRIS project No FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contracting authority</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Commission of the West African Economic and Monetary Union (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature of the contract</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Unit price</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contract description</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract covers the provision of long and short-term technical assistance, support for programme training and implementation of other contributions aimed at improving the management of domestic taxation in Ecowas Member States and strengthening the coordination, monitoring and evaluation system of fiscal transition programmes for each commission (ECOWAS and UEMOA) and for the Member States.</P><P>As a reminder, the fiscal transition support programme in West Africa aims to support the implementation of fiscal transition programmes in West Africa, following the implementation of regional trade liberalisation policies (Customs Union, CET, EPA, etc.). 3 results are expected:</P><P>(i) the management of Member States' internal taxation is improved and better coordinated in the region;</P><P>(ii) the fight against fraud, tax evasion, illicit financial flows and corruption is strengthened and contributes to increasing tax revenues;</P><P>(iii) the system for coordination, monitoring and evaluation of fiscal transition programmes is strengthened at the commission and Member State level.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicative budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Scheduled date for publication of the contract notice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Additional Information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>None</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal basis (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Annex IV to the Partnership Agreement between the members of the African, Caribbean and Pacific Group of States of one part, and the European Community and its Member States, of the other part, signed in Cotonou on 23.6.2000 as amended in Luxembourg on 25.6.2005 and in Ouagadougou on 22.6.2010. Reference is made to Annex IV as revised by Decision 1/2014 of the ACP-EU Council of Ministers of 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Please indicate any aspect that may have an impact on the rules of participation (e.g. geographical, thematic, short-term or long-term).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarks:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>At least 30 calendar days must elapse between publication of this prior information notice and publication of the corresponding contract notice.</P><P>Applications or requests for information must not be sent at this stage.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Uagadugu: FED - Licitación internacional para la contratación de asistencia técnica en apoyo de la transición fiscal en África Occidental</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Países de la Comunidad de los Estados del África Occidental (CEDEAO) + Mauritania/África Occidental</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNCIO DE PREVISIÓN DE CONTRATO DE SERVICIOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referencia de publicación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedimiento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restringido</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Denominación del programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de apoyo para la transición fiscal en África Occidental</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proyecto CRIS n.º FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de contratación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>La Comisión de la Unión Económica y Monetaria del África Occidental (UEMAO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Uagadugu</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naturaleza del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Precio unitario</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El contrato tiene como objetivo proporcionar asistencia técnica a largo y corto plazo, hacerse cargo de las actividades de capacitación del programa e implementar otras contribuciones que podrían mejorar la gestión de la tributación interna de los Estados miembros de la CEDEAO y fortalecer el sistema de coordinación, supervisión y evaluación de los programas de transición fiscal a nivel de cada comisión (CEDEAO y UEMAO) y a nivel de los Estados miembros.</P><P>Como recordatorio, el programa de apoyo a la transición fiscal en África Occidental tiene como objetivo apoyar la implementación de programas de transición fiscal en África Occidental, siguiendo la implementación de las políticas regionales de liberalización del comercio (unión aduanera, CET, EPA). Se prevén 3 resultados:</P><P>(i) mejora de la gestión y la coordinación en la región de los impuestos internos de los Estados miembros;</P><P>(ii) refuerzo de la lucha contra el fraude, la evasión fiscal, los flujos financieros ilícitos y la corrupción y contribución a aumentar los ingresos fiscales;</P><P>(iii) refuerzo del sistema de coordinación, seguimiento y evaluación de los programas de transición tributaria a nivel de cada comisión y de la EM.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Presupuesto indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha prevista para la publicación del anuncio de licitación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información complementaria</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>No aplicable</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fundamento jurídico (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anexo IV del Acuerdo de asociación entre los miembros del grupo de los Estados de África, del Caribe y del Pacífico, por una parte, y la Comunidad Europea y sus Estados miembros, por otra parte, firmado en Cotonú el 23.6.2000, en su versión modificada en Luxemburgo el 25.6.2005, y en Uagadugu el 22.6.2010. Se hace referencia aquí al anexo IV modificado por la Decisión 1/2014 del Consejo de Ministros ACP-UE de 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Indique cualquier particularidad ( geográfica, temática o de largo/corto plazo) que pueda tener consecuencias en las modalidades de participación.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observaciones:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deben pasar al menos 30 días naturales entre la publicación del presente anuncio de previsión y la publicación del anuncio de contrato correspondiente.</P><P>No se deben enviar candidaturas ni pedidos de información en esta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: EKR - Kansainvälinen tarjouspyyntö teknisen tukihenkilöstön hankkimiseksi tukemaan Länsi-Afrikan maiden verojärjestelmien muutosta</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Länsi-Afrikan valtioiden talousyhteisön (Ecowas) maat sekä Mauritania / Länsi-Afrikka</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Palvelua koskeva ennakkotietoilmoitus</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen viite</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menettely</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rajoitettu menettely</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ohjelman nimi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tukiohjelma Länsi-Afrikan maiden verojärjestelmien muutosta varten</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahoitus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>CRIS-hanke nro FED/2017/039-133.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Länsi-Afrikan talous- ja rahaliiton (Union économique et monétaire ouest-africaine – UEMOA) komissio</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuslaji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Yksikköhinta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuksen kuvaus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sopimuksen tarkoituksena on pitkä- ja lyhytaikaisen tuen antaminen, ohjelman koulutustoimista huolehtiminen sekä muiden sellaisten toimien toteuttaminen, jotka parantavat Ecowasin jäsenmaiden sisäistä verohallintoa ja tukevat verojärjestelmien muutosohjelmien koordinointi-, seuranta- ja arviointijärjestelmää Länsi-Afrikan valtioiden talousyhteisön (Ecowas) ja Länsi-Afrikan talous- ja rahaliiton (UEMOA) komissioiden sekä jäsenvaltioiden tasolla.</P><P>Muistutettakoon, että Länsi-Afrikan maiden verojärjestelmien muutosta varten laaditun tukiohjelman tarkoituksena on tukea Länsi-Afrikan maiden verojärjestelmien muutoksen toteuttamista, joka on seurausta alueellisen valuutanvaihdon rajoitusten vähentämisen toteuttamisesta (tulliliitto, Ecowasin yhteinen tulliraja (Tarif extérieur commun de la CEDEAO - TEC), talouskumppanuussopimus EU:n kanssa jne.). Seuraavia 3:a tulosta odotetaan:</P><P>i) jäsenmaiden sisäisen verojärjestelmän hoito ja sen alueellinen koordinaatio paranee,</P><P>ii) petosten, veronkierron, laittomien rahavirtojen ja korruption vastainen taistelu vahvistuu ja edistää verotulojen kasvua,</P><P>iii) verojärjestelmien muutosohjelmien koordinointi-, seuranta- ja arviointijärjestelmät vahvistuvat kunkin komission ja jäsenvaltioiden tasolla.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Alustava budjetti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintailmoituksen suunniteltu julkaisuajankohta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisätiedot</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ei saatavilla</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oikeusperusta (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cotonoussa 23.6.2000 allekirjoitetun Afrikan, Karibian ja Tyynenmeren valtioiden ryhmän jäsenten sekä Euroopan yhteisön ja sen jäsenvaltioiden välisen kumppanuussopimuksen liite IV, sellaisena kuin sopimus on muutettuna Luxemburgissa 25.6.2005 ja Ouagadougoussa 22.6.2010. Viitataan liitteeseen IV, sellaisena kuin se on muutettuna 20.6.2014 annetulla AKT–EU-ministerineuvoston päätöksellä nro 1/2014.</P><P>(1) Mainitse seikat, joilla voisi olla vaikutusta osallistumissääntöihin (kuten esimerkiksi maantieteellinen tai aihepiirikohtainen tai pitkä/lyhyt kesto).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Huom.:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Tämän ennakkotietoilmoituksen ja varsinaisen hankintailmoituksen julkaisuajankohtien välillä on oltava vähintään 30 kalenteripäivää.</P><P>Hakemuksia tai tietopyyntöjä ei pidä lähettää tässä vaiheessa.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: FED - Appel d'offre international pour le recrutement d'une assistance technique en appui à la transition fiscale en Afrique de l'Ouest</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Pays de la Communauté des États de l'Afrique de l'Ouest (Cedeao) + Mauritanie / Afrique de l'Ouest</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVIS DE PRÉ-INFORMATION CONCERNANT LE SERVICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Référence de la publication</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restreinte</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nom du programme</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programme d'appui à la transition fiscale en Afrique de l'Ouest</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financement</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projet CRIS nº FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Administration contractante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Commission de l'union économique et monétaire Ouest africaine (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, BURKINA FASO.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature du contrat</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prix unitaire</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du contrat</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le contrat vise la mise à disposition d’une assistance technique de long et de court terme, la prise en charge d'action de formation du programme et la mise en œuvre d’autres apports susceptibles d'améliorer la gestion de la fiscalité intérieure des États membres de la Cedeao et de renforcer le système de coordination, de suivi et d’évaluation des programmes de transition fiscale au niveau de chaque commission (CEDEAO et UEMOA) et au niveau des EM.</P><P>En rappel, le programme d'appui à la transition fiscale en Afrique de l'Ouest a pour objectif d'appuyer la mise en œuvre de programmes de transition fiscale en Afrique de l'Ouest, consécutifs à la mise en œuvre des politiques régionales de libération des échanges (Union douanière, TEC, APE,). 3 produits sont attendus:</P><P>(i) la gestion de la fiscalité intérieure des États membres est améliorée et mieux coordonnée dans la région;</P><P>(ii) la lutte contre la fraude, l'évasion fiscale, les flux financiers illicites et la corruption est renforcée et contribue à l’accroissement des recettes fiscales;</P><P>(iii) le système de coordination, suivi et d’évaluation des programmes de transition fiscale est renforcé au niveau de chaque commission et au niveau des EM.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Budget indicatif</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date prévue pour la publication de l'avis de marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informations supplémentaires</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Néant</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base juridique(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Annexe IV de l'accord de partenariat entre les membres du groupe des États d’Afrique, des Caraïbes et du Pacifique, d’une part, et la Communauté européenne et ses États membres, d’autre part, signé à Cotonou le 23.6.2000, tel que modifié à Luxembourg le 25.6.2005 et à Ouagadougou le 22.6.2010. Il est fait référence à l'annexe IV, telle que révisée par la décision 1/2014 du Conseil des ministres ACP-UE du 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Veuillez indiquer toute particularité qui pourrait avoir des conséquences sur les modalités de participation (telle que géographique ou thématique ou long/court terme).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarques:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Au moins 30 jours calendaires doivent s'écouler entre la publication du présent avis de pré-information et la publication de l'avis de marché correspondant.</P><P>Aucune candidature ni demande d'informations ne doit être envoyée à ce stade.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ουαγκαντούγκου: ΕΤΑ - Διεθνής διαγωνισμός για την πρόσληψη ομάδας τεχνικής βοήθειας προς υποστήριξη της φορολογικής μετάβασης στη Δυτική Αφρική</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Χώρες της Οικονομικής Κοινότητας των Δυτικοαφρικανικών Κρατών (ECOWAS) + Μαυριτανία / Δυτική Αφρική</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ΠΡΟΚΑΤΑΡΚΤΙΚΉ ΑΝΑΚΟΊΝΩΣΗ ΣΧΕΤΙΚΆ ΜΕ ΤΗΝ ΥΠΗΡΕΣΊΑ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αριθ. αναφοράς της δημοσίευσης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Διαδικασία</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κλειστή</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ονομασία του προγράμματος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Πρόγραμμα στήριξης για τη φορολογική μετάβαση στη Δυτική Αφρική</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Χρηματοδότηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Σχέδιο CRIS αριθ. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα διοίκηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Επιτροπή της Δυτικοαφρικανικής Οικονομικής και Νομισματικής Ένωσης (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ουαγκαντούγκου</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Μπουρκίνα Φάσο.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Φύση της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Τιμή ανά μονάδα</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Περιγραφή της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Η σύμβαση αποσκοπεί στην παροχή μακροπρόθεσμης και βραχυπρόθεσμης τεχνικής βοήθειας, στην ανάληψη δραστηριοτήτων για τον σχεδιασμό του προγράμματος και στην παροχή συνεισφορών που θα μπορούσαν να βελτιώσουν τη διαχείριση της εσωτερικής φορολογίας στα κράτη μέλη της ECOWAS και την ενίσχυση του συστήματος συντονισμού, παρακολούθησης και αξιολόγησης των προγραμμάτων φορολογικής μετάβασης στο επίπεδο κάθε επιτροπής (ECOWAS και UEMOA) και σε επίπεδο κρατών μελών.</P><P>Υπενθυμίζεται ότι το πρόγραμμα στήριξης της φορολογικής μετάβασης στη Δυτική Αφρική αποσκοπεί στη στήριξη της υλοποίησης των προγραμμάτων φορολογικής μετάβασης στη Δυτική Αφρική, μετά την εφαρμογή των περιφερειακών πολιτικών για την ελευθέρωση του εμπορίου (τελωνειακή ένωση, κοινό εξωτερικό δασμολόγιο, συμφωνία οικονομικής εταιρικής σχέσης). Αναμένεται η επίτευξη 3 αποτελεσμάτων:</P><P>(i) βελτίωση και καλύτερος συντονισμός της διαχείρισης της εσωτερικής φορολογίας των κρατών μελών στην περιοχή·</P><P>(ii) ενίσχυση της καταπολέμησης της απάτης, της φοροδιαφυγής, των παράνομων χρηματοοικονομικών ροών και της διαφθοράς και συμβολή στην αύξηση των φορολογικών εσόδων·</P><P>(iii) ενίσχυση του συστήματος συντονισμού, παρακολούθησης και αξιολόγησης των προγραμμάτων φορολογικής μετάβασης σε επίπεδο κάθε επιτροπής και σε επίπεδο κρατών μελών.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ενδεικτικός προϋπολογισμός</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης της προκήρυξης σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Άνευ αντικειμένου</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Νομική βάση (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Παράρτημα IV της συμφωνίας εταιρικής σχέσης μεταξύ των μελών της ομάδας των κρατών της Αφρικής, της Καραϊβικής και του Ειρηνικού, αφενός, και της Ευρωπαϊκής Κοινότητας και των κρατών μελών αυτής, αφετέρου, η οποία υπεγράφη στην Κοτονού στις 23.6.2000, όπως τροποποιήθηκε στο Λουξεμβούργο στις 25.6.2005 και στην Ουαγκαντούγκου στις 22.6.2010. Γίνεται αναφορά στο παράρτημα IV όπως αναθεωρήθηκε με την απόφαση 1/2014 του Συμβουλίου Υπουργών ΑΚΕ-ΕΕ στις 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Παρακαλείστε να αναφέρετε κάθε ιδιαιτερότητα που θα μπορούσε να φέρει συνέπειες στους τρόπους συμμετοχής (όπως γεωγραφική ή θεματική ή βραχυπρόθεσμη/μακροπρόθεσμη).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Παρατηρήσεις:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Θα πρέπει να παρέλθει ελάχιστο χρονικό διάστημα 30 ημερολογιακών ημερών μεταξύ της δημοσίευσης της παρούσας προκαταρκτικής ανακοίνωσης και της δημοσίευσης της αντίστοιχης προκήρυξης σύμβασης.</P><P>Καμία υποψηφιότητα ή αίτηση για περαιτέρω πληροφορίες δεν θα πρέπει να αποστέλλεται σε αυτό το στάδιο.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: FES - Bando di gara internazionale per assumere l'assistenza tecnica a sostegno della transizione fiscale nell'Africa occidentale</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paesi della Comunità degli Stati dell'Africa occidentale (Ecowas) + Mauritania/Africa occidentale</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVISO DI PREINFORMAZIONE RELATIVO AL SERVIZIO</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Riferimento della pubblicazione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ristretta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nome del programma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programma di sostegno alla transizione fiscale nell'Africa occidentale</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanziamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Progetto CRIS n. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ente appaltante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Commissione dell'Unione economica e monetaria dell'Africa occidentale (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prezzo unitario</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L'appalto mira a fornire assistenza tecnica a breve e a lungo termine, per gestire le attività di formazione del programma e attuare altre azioni che potranno contribuire a migliorare la gestione fiscale interna degli Stati membri dell'Ecowas e rafforzare il sistema di coordinamento, monitoraggio e valutazione dei programmi di transizione fiscale a livello di ciascuna commissione (Ecowas e UEMOA) e a livello degli Stati membri.</P><P>Ricordiamo che il programma di sostegno alla transizione fiscale in Africa occidentale mira a sostenere l'attuazione dei programmi di transizione fiscale nell'Africa occidentale, in conseguenza dell'attuazione delle politiche regionali di liberalizzazione degli scambi (unione doganale, TEC, APE). I risultati previsti sono 3:</P><P>(i) la gestione della fiscalità interna degli Stati membri sarà migliorata e meglio coordinata nella regione;</P><P>(ii) la lotta contro la frode, l'evasione fiscale, i flussi finanziari illeciti e la corruzione sarà rafforzata e contribuirà ad aumentare le entrate fiscali;</P><P>(iii) il sistema di coordinamento, monitoraggio e valutazione dei programmi di transizione fiscale sarà rafforzato a livello di ciascuna commissione e a livello degli Stati membri.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bilancio indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista per la pubblicazione del bando di gara</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informazioni complementari</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Non applicabile</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base giuridica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Allegato IV all'accordo di partenariato tra i membri del gruppo degli Stati dell'Africa, dei Caraibi e del Pacifico, da un lato, e la Comunità europea ed i suoi Stati membri, dall'altro, firmato a Cotonou il 23.6.2000, come modificato a Lussemburgo il 25.6.2005 e a Ouagadougou il 22.6.2010. Si fa riferimento all'allegato IV come modificato dalla decisione n. 1/2014 del Consiglio dei ministri ACP-UE del 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Indicare qualsiasi particolarità che possa avere conseguenze sulle modalità di partecipazione (come geografica o tematica o a lungo/breve termine).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Osservazioni:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Dovranno intercorrere almeno 30 giorni di calendario tra la pubblicazione del presente avviso di preinformazione e quella del bando di gara corrispondente.</P><P>Si prega di non inviare candidature o richieste di informazioni durante questa fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: EOF - Internationale oproep tot inschrijving voor de verwerving van technische bijstand ter ondersteuning van de fiscale omschakeling in West-Afrika</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Landen van de Gemeenschap van West-Afrikaanse Staten (Ecowas) + Mauritanië/West-Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VOORAANKONDIGING VOOR EEN DIENST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referentie van de bekendmaking:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet-openbaar.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naam van het programma:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programma ter ondersteuning van de fiscale omschakeling in West-Afrika.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiering:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Project CRIS nr. FED/2017/039-133.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Commissie van de West-Afrikaanse economische en monetaire unie (Waemu)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aard van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eenheidsprijs.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschrijving van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De opdracht beoogt de terbeschikkingstelling van technische bijstand op lange en korte termijn, de tenuitvoerlegging van de actie voor opleiding van het programma en de tenuitvoerlegging van andere acties die het beheer van de binnenlandse fiscaliteit van de lidstaten van Ecowas kunnen verbeteren en het systeem voor de coördinatie, opvolging en evaluatie van de programma's voor de fiscale omschakeling op het niveau van elke commissie (Ecowas en Waemu) en op het niveau van de lidstaten kunnen versterken.</P><P>Zoals reeds is opgemerkt, beoogt het programma ter ondersteuning van de fiscale omschakeling in West-Afrika de ondersteuning van de tenuitvoerlegging van programma's voor de fiscale omschakeling in West-Afrika na de tenuitvoerlegging van de regionale beleidslijnen voor de liberalisering van de handel (douane-unie, gemeenschappelijk buitentarief, economische partnerschapsovereenkomsten). Er worden 3 resultaten verwacht:</P><P>i) het beheer van de binnenlandse fiscaliteit van de lidstaten is verbeterd en beter gecoördineerd in de regio;</P><P>ii) de bestrijding van fraude, belastingontwijking, illegale geldstromen en corruptie is versterkt en draagt bij tot de verhoging van de belastingopbrengsten;</P><P>iii) het systeem voor de coördinatie, opvolging en evaluatie van de programma's voor de fiscale omschakeling is versterkt op het niveau van elke commissie en op het niveau van de lidstaten.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicatieve begroting:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beoogde datum van bekendmaking van de aankondiging van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nadere inlichtingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>N.v.t.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Juridische basis (1):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bijlage IV bij de Partnerschapsovereenkomst tussen de leden van de groep van Staten in Afrika, het Caribisch gebied en de Stille Oceaan enerzijds, en de Europese Gemeenschap en haar lidstaten anderzijds, ondertekend te Cotonou op 23.6.2000, zoals gewijzigd in Luxemburg op 25.6.2005 en in Ouagadougou op 22.6.2010. Er wordt verwezen naar bijlage IV zoals gewijzigd bij Besluit nr. 1/2014 van de ACS-EU-Raad van ministers van 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Gelieve elke specificiteit te vermelden die een effect kan hebben op de deelnemingsregels (bijvoorbeeld geografische of thematische specificiteiten op korte of lange termijn).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Noot:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Er moeten minstens 30 kalenderdagen liggen tussen de bekendmaking van onderhavige vooraankondiging en de bekendmaking van de bijbehorende aankondiging van opdracht.</P><P>In dit stadium mogen geen aanvragen of verzoeken om inlichtingen worden verzonden.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Uagadugu: FED - Anúncio de concurso internacional para o recrutamento de uma assistência técnica de apoio à transição fiscal na África Ocidental</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Países da Comunidade de Estados da África Ocidental (Cedeao) + Mauritânia/África Ocidental</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANÚNCIO DE PRÉ-INFORMAÇÃO RELATIVO A SERVIÇOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referência da publicação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Limitado</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nome do programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de apoio à transição fiscal na África Ocidental</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projeto CRIS n.º FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Comissão da União Económica e Monetária da África Ocidental (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Uagadugu</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burquina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natureza do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Preço unitário</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O contrato visa a disponibilização de uma assistência técnica de longo e curto prazo, a tomada a cargo da ação de formação do programa e a implementação de outros encargos suscetíveis de melhorar a gestão dos impostos nacionais dos Estados-Membros da Cedeao e reforçar o sistema de coordenação, de acompanhamento e de avaliação dos programas de transição fiscal ao nível de cada comissão (CEDEAO e UEMOA) e ao nível dos Estados-Membros.</P><P>A título informativo, o programa de apoio à transição fiscal na África Ocidental tem por objetivo apoiar a implementação dos programas de transição fiscal na África Ocidental, no seguimento à implementação das políticas regionais de liberalização de trocas comerciais (União alfandegária, TEC, APE,). Estão previstos 3 resultados:</P><P>(i) a gestão dos impostos nacionais dos Estados-Membros é melhorada e melhor coordenada na região;</P><P>(ii) o combate contra a fraude, a evasão fiscal, os fluxos financeiros ilícitos e a corrupção é reforçada e contribui para o crescimento das receitas fiscais;</P><P>(iii) o sistema de coordenação, acompanhamento e avaliação dos programas de transição fiscal é reforçado ao nível de cada comissão e ao nível dos Estados-Membros.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orçamento indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista para a publicação do anúncio de concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informações suplementares</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Não constam</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base jurídica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anexo IV do Acordo de Parceria entre os Estados-Membros do Grupo de Estados de África, das Caraíbas e do Pacífico, por um lado, e a Comunidade Europeia e os seus Estados-Membros, por outro lado, assinado em Cotonu em 23.6.2000, tal como alterado no Luxemburgo, em 25.6.2005, e em Uagadugu, em 22.6.2010. É feita referência ao anexo IV revisto pela Decisão n.º 1/2014 do Conselho de Ministros ACP-UE de 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Indique qualquer particularidade que possa ter consequências nos métodos de participação (como geográfica ou temática ou longo/curto prazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observações:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Devem decorrer pelo menos 30 dias de calendário entre a publicação do presente anúncio de pré-informação e a publicação do anúncio de concurso correspondente.</P><P>Não devem ser apresentadas candidaturas nem enviados pedidos de informação nesta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: EUF - Internationell anbudsinbjudan för rekrytering av teknisk assistans som stöd vid skatteomvandlingen i Västafrika.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>De Västafrikanska staternas gemenskap (Ecowas) + Mauritanien/Västafrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÖRHANDSMEDDELANDE OM TJÄNSTEN</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publikationsreferens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Förfarande</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Selektivt</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Benämning på programmet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Stödprogram vid skatteomvandlingen i Västafrika</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projet CRIS nº FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Västafrikanska ekonomiska och monetära unionens (WAEMU) kommission</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontraktstyp</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Enhetspris</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivning av kontraktet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kontraktet har som syfte att tillhandahålla teknisk assistans på lång och kort sikt, att ta ansvar för det av utbildningssatsningen avseende programmet och att genomföra andra insatser, som kan tänkas förbättra den inhemska skatteförvaltningen i medlemsstaterna i Ecowas och stärka samordningssystemet för uppföljning och utvärdering av programmen för skatteomvandling avseende varje kommission (Ecowas och Uemoa) och avseende medlemsstaterna.</P><P>Stödprogram vid skatteomvandlingen i Västafrika har som syfte att stödja genomförandet av programmen för skatteomvandling i Västafrika, som följer av genomförandet av de regionalpolitiska liberaliseringssatsningarna avseende handel (tullunion, TEC, APE). 3 tjänster förväntas:</P><P>(i) Medlemsstaternas inhemska skatteförvaltning förbättras och blir bättre samordnad i regionen.</P><P>(ii) Kampen stärks mot bedrägerier, skatteflykt, illegala kapitalrörelser och korruption, samt bidrar till tillväxt i skatteintäkterna.</P><P>(iii) samordnings- uppföljnings- och utvärderingssystem för skatteomvandlingsprogrammen stärks på varje kommissionsnivå och på medlemsstatsnivå.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerad budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerat datum för publicering av upphandlingsmeddelandet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kompletterande information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finns ej</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rättslig grund (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bilaga IV till partnerskapsavtalet mellan medlemmarna i gruppen av stater i Afrika, Västindien och Stillahavsområdet och Europeiska gemenskapen och dess medlemsstater, undertecknat i Cotonou 23.6.2000, ändrat i Luxemburg 25.6.2005 och i Ouagadougou 22.6.2010. Hänvisning görs till bilaga IV enligt ändring genom beslut 1/2014 av AVS–EU-ministerrådet av den 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Ange alla detaljer som kan påverka deltagandeförfarandet (såsom geografiska, tematiska eller på lång/kort sikt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>OBS:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Minst 30 kalenderdagar ska förflyta mellan publiceringen av detta förhandsmeddelande och publiceringen av meddelandet om upphandling.</P><P>Ansökningar eller beställningar av information ska inte skickas i detta skede.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: ERF - Mezinárodní výběrové řízení na získání technické podpory pro daňovou transformaci v západní Africe</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Země Společenství států západní Afriky (Ecowas) + Mauritánie / západní Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>OZNÁMENÍ PŘEDBĚŽNÝCH INFORMACÍ O SLUŽBĚ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenční číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užší</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Název programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program podpory daňové transformace v západní Africe</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financování</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt CRIS č. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veřejný zadavatel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komise Západoafrické hospodářské a měnové unie (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Povaha zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cena za jednotku</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popis zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cílem smlouvy je poskytnout dlouhodobou a krátkodobou technickou pomoc, převzít vzdělávací aktivity programu a realizovat další příspěvky, které by mohly zlepšit správu vnitřního zdanění Členských států Ecowas a posílit systém koordinace, sledování a hodnocení programů daňových přechodů na úrovni každé komise (ECOWAS a WAEMU) a na úrovni členských států.</P><P>Je třeba připomenout, že program podpory daňové transformace v západní Africe je zaměřen na podporu provádění programů daňových přechodů v západní Africe po zavedení regionální daňové politiky liberalizace obchodu (celní unie, CET, EPA). Očekávají se 3 výstupy:</P><P>i) zlepšení a lepší koordinace řízení vnitřních daní členských států v regionu;</P><P>ii) posílení boje proti podvodům, daňovým únikům, nezákonným finančním tokům a korupci a zvýšení daňových příjmů;</P><P>iii) systém koordinace, sledování a hodnocení programů daňové transformace je posílen na úrovni každé komise a na úrovni členských států.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Směrný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zamýšlený termín zveřejnění oznámení o zakázce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Doplňující informace</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Žádné</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právní základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Příloha IV k dohodě o partnerství mezi členy skupiny afrických, karibských a tichomořských států a Evropským společenstvím a jeho členskými státy podepsané v Cotonou dne 23.6.2000 a pozměněné v Lucemburku dne 25.6.2005 a v Ouagadougou dne 22.6.2010. Odkazujeme na přílohu IV pozměněnou rozhodnutím Rady ministrů AKT–EU 1/2014 ze dne 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Uveďte jakékoli zvláštnosti, které by mohly ovlivnit pravidla účasti (např. zeměpisná nebo tematická či dlouhodobá/krátkodobá).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Mezi zveřejněním těchto předběžných informací o zakázce a zveřejněním oznámení o zakázce musí uplynout nejméně 30 kalendářních dní.</P><P>V této fázi nesmí být zasílány žádné přihlášky ani žádosti o informace.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: EAF - Rahvusvaheline pakkumiskutse Lääne-Aafrikas maksusüsteemi ümberkorraldamise toetamiseks tehnilise abi värbamiseks</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lääne-Aafrika Riikide Majandusühenduse (Ecowas) riigid + Mauritaania / Lääne-Aafrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>TEENUSE EELTEADE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaldamise viide</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menetlus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Piiratud</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmi nimetus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lääne-Aafrika maksusüsteemi ümberkorraldamise tugiprogramm</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahastamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>CRISi projekt nr FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Lääne-Aafrika majandus- ja rahaliidu (West African Economic and Monetary Union (WAEMU)) komisjon</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu laad</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ühikuhind</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lepingu eesmärk on pakkuda pika- ja lühiajalist tehnilist abi, võtta üle koolitusprogrammi läbiviimine ning rakendada muid sisendeid, mis võivad parandada Ecowasi riikide siseriikliku maksustamise juhtimist ja tugevdada maksusüsteemi ümberkorraldamise programmide koordineerimis-, järelevalve- ja hindamissüsteemi mõlema komisjoni (ECOWAS ja WAEMU) ja liikmesriikide tasandil.</P><P>Meeldetuletuseks: Lääne-Aafrika maksusüsteemi ümberkorraldamise tugiprogrammi eesmärk on toetada Lääne-Aafrikas maksusüsteemi ümberkorraldamise programmide rakendamist, mis tuleneb kaubavahetuse liberaliseerimise piirkondliku poliitika rakendamisest (tolliliit, TEC, EPA). Eeldatakse 3 tulemuse saavutamist:</P><P>i) liikmesriikide siseriikliku maksustamise juhtimine on piirkonnas paremaks muutunud ja see on paremini koordineeritud;</P><P>ii) pettuste, maksudest kõrvalehoidmise, ebaseaduslike rahavoogude ja korruptsiooni vastane võitlus on tugevamaks muutunud ja see aitab kaasa maksutulude suurendamisele;</P><P>iii) maksusüsteemi ümberkorraldamise programmide koordineerimis-, järelevalve- ja hindamissüsteemi on tugevdatud iga komisjoni ja liikmesriikide tasandil.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kavandatav eelarve</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hanketeate avaldamise ettenähtud kuupäev</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisateave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Puudub</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Õiguslik alus (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aafrika, Kariibi mere piirkonna ja Vaikse ookeani piirkonna riikide rühma ning Euroopa Ühenduse ja selle liikmesriikide vahel sõlmitud koostöölepingu (mis allkirjastati 23.6.2000 Cotonous ning mida muudeti 25.6.2005 Luxembourgis ja 22.6.2010 Ouagadougous) IV lisa. Siinkohal viidatakse IV lisale, nagu seda on muudetud AKV-ELi ministrite nõukogu 20.6.2014 otsusega 1/2014.</P><P>(1) Palun esitage kõik asjaolud, mis võivad mõjutada osalemistingimusi (geograafilised, valdkonna ja lühema/pikema kestuse tegurid).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Märkused:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Eelteate ja vastava hanketeate avaldamise vahele peab jääma vähemalt 30 kalendripäeva.</P><P>Taotlusi ega teabenõudeid ei või selles etapis veel saata.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: EFA - Nemzetközi nyílt ajánlati felhívás az adóügyi átmenet támogatására irányuló szakmai segítségnyújtás igénybevétele vonatkozásában Nyugat-Afrikában</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>A Nyugat-afrikai Államok Közösségének országai (Cedeao) + Mauritánia / Nyugat-Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SZOLGÁLTATÁSNYÚJTÁSRA IRÁNYULÓ ELŐZETES TÁJÉKOZTATÓ HIRDETMÉNY</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A közzététel hivatkozási száma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Eljárás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Meghívásos</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A program címe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A nyugat-afrikai adóügyi átmenetet támogató program</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanszírozás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>FED/2017/039-133. számú CRIS projekt</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>A Nyugat-afrikai Gazdasági és Monetáris Unió (UEMOA) bizottsága</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés típusa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Egységáras</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés meghatározása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A szerződés célja hosszú és rövid távú szakmai segítségnyújtás biztosítása, a Cedeao tagállamainak belső adóügyeinek irányításának javítását célzó további hozzájárulások végrehajtása és a képzési programra irányuló intézkedés átvétele, valamint az irányítási rendszer megerősítése, az adóügyi átmenetre irányuló programok nyomon követése és értékelése az egyes bizottságok (Cedeao és Uemoa) és a tagállamok szintjén.</P><P>Emlékeztetőül: a nyugat-afrikai adóügyi átmenetet támogató program célkitűzése a nyugat-afrikai adóügyi átmeneti programok végrehajtásának támogatása, a kereskedelem liberalizálására irányuló regionális szakpolitikák (vámunió, közös vámtarifa [TEC], gazdasági partnerségi megállapodások [APE]) megvalósítását követően. A szerződéstől az alábbi 3 eredményt várják:</P><P>(i) a tagállamok belső adóügyeinek hatékonyabb irányítása és jobb koordinálása a régióban;</P><P>(ii) a csalás, adócsalás, jogellenes pénzmozgások és a korrupció elleni harc megerősítése és az adóbevételek növekedéséhez történő hozzájárulás;</P><P>(iii) a koordinációs rendszer, az adóügyi átmenetre irányuló programok nyomon követésének és értékelésének megerősítése valamennyi bizottsági és tagállami szinten.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Várható költségvetés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlattételi felhívás közzétételének tervezett időpontja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>További információk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nincsenek</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Jogalap (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Az egyrészt az afrikai, karibi és csendes-óceáni államok csoportjának tagjai, másrészt az Európai Közösség, illetve annak tagállamai között létrejött partnerségi megállapodás IV. melléklete, amelyet a 23.6.2000 dátumú napon Cotonouban írtak alá, és a 25.6.2005 dátumú napon Luxembourgban, valamint a 22.6.2010 dátumú napon Ouagadougouban módosítottak. Hivatkozással az AKCS-EU Miniszteri Tanácsának 20.6.2014 dátumú 1/2014 határozatával felülvizsgált IV. mellékletre.</P><P>(1) Kérjük, jelezzen minden olyan sajátosságot, amely hatással lehet a részvétel feltételeire (pl. földrajzi, tematikus vagy hosszú/rövid távú sajátosság).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Megjegyzések:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>A jelen előzetes összesített hirdetmény megjelenése és a vonatkozó ajánlati felhívás közzététele között legalább 30 naptári napnak kell eltelnie.</P><P>Ebben a szakaszban jelentkezés benyújtásának, illetve információkérésnek nincs helye.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Uagadugu: EPF - Tarptautinis konkursas dėl techninės pagalbos suteikimo mokesčių sistemos pereinamojo laikotarpio paramos programai Vakarų Afrikoje</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vakarų Afrikos valstybių ekonominės bendrijos šalys (ECOWAS) + Mauritanija / Vakarų Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IŠANKSTINIS INFORMACINIS SKELBIMAS APIE PASLAUGAS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nuoroda į publikaciją</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ribota</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programos pavadinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mokesčių sistemos pereinamojo laikotarpio Vakarų Afrikoje paramos programa</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansavimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projektas CRIS Nr. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Perkančioji organizacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Vakarų Afrikos ekonominės ir pinigų sąjungos (VAEPS) komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Uagadugu</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Fasas.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties pobūdis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kaina už vienetą</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties apibūdinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sutarties tikslas – suteikti ilgalaikę ir trumpalaikę techninę pagalbą, atsakomybę už programos parengimo veiklą ir kitų priemonių įgyvendinimą, kurios galėtų pagerinti ECOWAS valstybių narių vidaus mokesčių valdymą ir stiprinti mokesčių programų koordinavimo, stebėsenos ir vertinimo sistemą pereinamuoju laikotarpiu kiekvienos komisijos (ECOWAS ir VAEPS) ir valstybių narių lygiu.</P><P>Primename, kad techninės pagalbos mokesčių sistemos pereinamojo laikotarpio paramos programos Vakarų Afrikoje tikslas – remti mokesčių pereinamojo laikotarpio programų įgyvendinimą Vakarų Afrikoje, kartu įgyvendinant regioninę prekybos liberalizavimo politiką (Muitų sąjunga, TCF, EPS). Tikimasi pasiekti 3 rezultatus:</P><P>(i) regiono valstybių narių vidaus mokesčių administravimo tobulinamą ir geresnį koordinavimą;</P><P>(ii) kovos su sukčiavimu, mokesčių vengimu, neteisėtais finansiniais srautais ir korupcija sustiprinamas leis prisidėti prie didesnių mokestinių pajamų;</P><P>(iii) mokesčių pereinamojo laikotarpio programų koordinavimo, stebėjimo ir vertinimo sistemos yra sustiprinamos kiekvienos komisijos ir valstybių narių lygiu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Preliminarus biudžetas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatyta skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo data</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildoma informacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nėra</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teisinis pagrindas (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Partnerystės susitarimo tarp Afrikos, Karibų jūros ir Ramiojo vandenyno valstybių grupės narių iš vienos pusės bei Europos Bendrijos ir jos valstybių narių iš kitos pusės, pasirašyto Kotonu 23.6.2000, su pakeitimais, padarytais 25.6.2005 Liuksemburge ir 22.6.2010 Vagadugu, IV priedas. Pateikiama nuoroda į IV priedą, iš dalies pakeistą 20.6.2014 AKR ir ES Ministrų Tarybos sprendimu Nr. 1/2014.</P><P>(1) Nurodykite bet kokį požymį, galintį turėti įtakos dalyvavimo tvarkai (pvz., geografinį ar teminį, ilguoju ar trumpuoju laikotarpiu).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Pastabos.</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Nuo šio išankstinio informacinio skelbimo publikavimo ir atitinkamo kvietimo pateikti pasiūlymus paskelbimo turi praeiti ne mažiau kaip 30 kalendorinių dienų.</P><P>Šiuo etapu siųsti paraiškų ar kreiptis dėl informacijos negalima.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Vagadugu: EAF - Starptautisks uzaicinājums uz konkursu par tehniskās palīdzības darbinieku nolīgšanu nodokļu pārejas atbalstam Rietumāfrikā</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rietumāfrikas valstu ekonomikas kopienas (ECOWAS) valstis un Mauritānija / Rietumāfrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IEPRIEKŠĒJS INFORMATĪVS PAZIŅOJUMS PAR PAKALPOJUMU LĪGUMU</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsauce uz publikāciju</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Slēgta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmas nosaukums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nodokļu pārejas atbalsta programma Rietumāfrikā</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansējums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>CRIS projekts Nr. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Rietumāfrikas Ekonomiskās un monetārās savienības (Union économique et monétaire ouest-africaine – UEMOA) komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Vagadugu</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkinafaso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma veids</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Vienības cenas līgums</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Līguma mērķis ir nodrošināt īstermiņa un ilgtermiņa tehnisko palīdzību, vadīt programmas apmācības pasākumus un sniegt citu ieguldījumu, lai uzlabotu ECOWAS dalībvalstu iekšējo nodokļu sistēmas vadību un nostiprinātu nodokļu pārejas programmu koordinēšanas, pārraudzības un novērtēšanas sistēmu katras komisijas līmenī (ECOWAS un UEMOA) un dalībvalstu līmenī.</P><P>Nodokļu pārejas atbalsta programmas Rietumāfrikā mērķis ir sniegt atbalstu nodokļu pārejas programmu īstenošanai Rietumāfrikā, ko veic secīgi tirdzniecības liberalizācijas reģionālās politikas īstenošanas rezultātā (Muitas savienība, kopējais ārējais tarifs (Tarif Extérieur Commun – TEC), EPN u. c.). Paredzēts sasniegt 3 rezultātus:</P><P>i) uzlabota un reģionā labāk koordinēta dalībvalstu iekšējās nodokļu sistēmas vadība;</P><P>ii) nostiprināta cīņa pret krāpšanu, nodokļu apiešanu, nelikumīgām kapitāla plūsmām un korupciju, kā arī sekmēta nodokļu ieņēmumu palielināšana;</P><P>iii) nostiprināta nodokļu pārejas programmu koordinēšanas, pārraudzības un izvērtēšanas sistēma katras komisijas un dalībvalstu līmenī.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Provizoriskais budžets</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plānotais paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildu informācija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nav</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tiesiskais pamats (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IV pielikums Partnerattiecību nolīgumam starp Āfrikas, Karību jūras reģiona un Klusā okeāna valstu grupas locekļiem, no vienas puses, un Eiropas Kopienu un tās dalībvalstīm, no otras puses, kas parakstīts Kotonū 2000. gada 23. jūnijā, kā tas grozīts Luksemburgā 2005. gada 25. jūnijā un kā tas grozīts Vagadugu 2010. gada 22. jūnijā. Atsauce sniegta uz IV pielikumu, kas pārskatīts ar ĀKK un ES Ministru padomes Lēmumu Nr. 1/2014 (2014. gada 20. jūnijs).</P><P>(1) Lūdzam norādīt visus specifiskos iemeslus (piemēram, ģeogrāfiskus, tematiskus, īstermiņa vai ilgtermiņa), kas var ietekmēt dalības noteikumus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Piezīmes</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Starp šā iepriekšējā informatīvā paziņojuma un attiecīgā paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datumiem ir jāpaiet vismaz 30 kalendārajām dienām.</P><P>Šajā posmā nekādus pieteikumus vai informācijas pieprasījumus nesūtīt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: FEŻ - Sejħa għall-offerti internazzjonali għar-reklutaġġ ta' għajnuna teknika li tappoġġja t-transizzjoni fiskali fl-Afrika tal-Punent</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Il-pajjiżi tal-Komunità Ekonomika tal-Istati tal-Afrika tal-Punent (ECOWAS) + il-Mauritania / l-Afrika tal-Punent</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVIŻ TA' TAGĦRIF MINN QABEL DWAR SERVIZZ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-proċedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-isem tal-programm</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programm ta' appoġġ għat-transizzjoni fiskali fl-Afrika tal-Punent</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-iffinanzjar</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-proġett CRIS Nru FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Il-Kummissjoni tal-Unjoni Ekonomika u Monetarja tal-Afrika tal-Punent (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-tip ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-prezz għal kull unità</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-deskrizzjoni tal-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-għan tal-kuntratt hu l-provvista ta' għajnuna teknika fuq żmien twil u qasir, it-tmexxija ta' azzjoni ta' tfassil tal-programm u l-implimentazzjoni ta' kontribuzzjonijiet oħra li jistgħu jtejbu l-immaniġġjar tat-tassazzjoni interna tal-Istati Membru tal-ECOWAS u jsaħħu s-sistema ta' koordinazzjoni, monitoraġġ u evalwazzjoni tal-programmi ta' transizzjoni fiskali fil-livell ta' kull kummissjoni (ECOWAS u UEMOA) u fil-livell tal-Istati Membri.</P><P>Bħala tfakkira, il-programm ta' appoġġ għat-transizzjoni fiskali fl-Afrika tal-Punent għandu l-għan li jappoġġja l-implimentazzjoni tal-programmi ta' transizzjoni fiskali fl-Afrika tal-Punent, li tirriżulta mill-implimentazzjoni tal-politiki reġjonali ta' libertà tal-iskambji (l-Unjoni Doganali, TEC, FSE). Huma mistennija 3 prodotti:</P><P>(i) it-titjib u koordinazzjoni aħjar tal-immaniġġjar tat-tassazzjoni interna tal-Istati Membri fir-reġjun;</P><P>(i) it-tisħiħ tal-ġlieda kontra l-frodi, l-evitar tat-taxxa, id-dħul illegali u l-korruzzjoni u l-kontribuzzjoni għaż-żieda fid-dħul mit-taxxa;</P><P>(iii) it-tisħiħ tas-sistema ta' koordinazzjoni, monitoraġġ u evalwazzjoni tal-programmi ta' transizzjoni fiskali fil-livell ta' kull kummissjoni u fil-livell tal-Istati Membri.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-baġit indikattiv</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-data għall-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif addizzjonali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mhux applikabbli</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-bażi legali (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-Anness IV tal-Ftehim ta' Sħubija bejn il-membri tal-Grupp tal-Istati Afrikani, tal-Karibew u l-Paċifiku u l-Komunità Ewropea u l-Istati Membri tagħha, iffirmat f'Cotonou nhar it-23.6.2000, kif emendat fil-Lussemburgu nhar il-25.6.2005 u f'Ouagadougou nhar it-22.6.2010. Qed issir referenza għall-Anness IV kif irrivedut mid-Deċiżjoni Nru 1/2014 tal-Kunsill tal-Ministri tal-AKP-UE tal-20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Jekk jogħġbok indika kwalunkwe speċifiċità li jista' jkollha effett fuq il-metodi ta' kif wieħed jieħu sehem (speċifiċità ġeografika jew tematika u fi żmien qasir/twil).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Kummenti:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Iridu jgħaddu mill-inqas 30 jum kalendarji bejn il-pubblikazzjoni ta' dan l-avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel u l-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż dwar kuntratt li għandu x'jaqsam miegħu.</P><P>M'għandhomx jintbagħtu applikazzjonijiet jew talbiet għal tagħrif f'dan l-istadju.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Wagadugu: EFR - Procedura międzynarodowa dotycząca pozyskania pomocy technicznej w celu wsparcia transformacji systemu podatkowego w Afryce Zachodniej</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Kraje Wspólnoty Gospodarczej Państw Afryki Zachodniej (ECOWAS) + Mauretania / Afryka Zachodnia</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>WSTĘPNE OGŁOSZENIE INFORMACYJNE DOTYCZĄCE ZAMÓWIENIA NA USŁUGI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numer referencyjny publikacji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograniczona</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nazwa programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program wsparcia transformacji systemu podatkowego w Afryce Zachodniej</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansowanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt CRIS nr FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zamawiający</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komisja Zachodnioafrykańskiej Unii Gospodarczej i Walutowej (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Wagadugu</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rodzaj zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cena jednostkowa</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Celem zamówienia jest zapewnienie długoterminowej i krótkoterminowej pomocy technicznej, realizacja działań związanych z przygotowywaniem programu i wdrażaniem innych środków, które pomogą poprawić zarządzanie wewnętrznymi systemami podatkowymi państw członkowskich ECOWAS oraz wzmocnić system koordynacji, nadzoru i oceny programów dotyczących transformacji systemu podatkowego na poziomie każdej komisji (ECOWAS i WAEMU) i na poziomie państw członkowskich.</P><P>W ramach przypomnienia, celem programu wsparcia transformacji systemu podatkowego w Afryce Zachodniej jest realizacja programów transformacji systemu podatkowego w Afryce Zachodniej, będących następstwem wdrożenia regionalnych strategii liberalizacji handlu (unia celna, wspólna zewnętrzna taryfa celna, umowa o partnerstwie gospodarczym itp.). Oczekuje się, że zostaną wypracowane 3 produkty:</P><P>(i) poprawa zarządzania wewnętrznymi systemami podatkowymi państw członkowskich i koordynacji zarządzania na poziomie regionalnym;</P><P>(ii) wzmocnienie walki z oszustwami, ucieczkami podatkowymi, niedozwolonymi przepływami finansowymi i korupcją, które przyczyni się do zwiększenia dochodów podatkowych;</P><P>(iii) wzmocnienie systemu koordynacji, nadzoru i oceny programów transformacji systemu podatkowego na poziomie każdej komisji i na poziomie państw członkowskich.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orientacyjny budżet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Przewidywana data publikacji ogłoszenia o zamówieniu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatkowe informacje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Brak</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Podstawa prawna (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Załącznik IV do Umowy o partnerstwie między członkami grupy państw Afryki, Karaibów i Pacyfiku z jednej strony a Wspólnotą Europejską i jej państwami członkowskimi z drugiej strony, podpisana w Kotonu dnia 23.6.2000, zmieniona w Luksemburgu dnia 25.6.2005 i w Wagadugu dnia 22.6.2010. Odniesienie dotyczy załącznika IV zmienionego na mocy decyzji nr 1/2014 Rady Ministrów AKP–UE z dnia 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Proszę wskazać jakąkolwiek szczególną okoliczność, która mogłaby mieć wpływ na warunki uczestnictwa (taką jak geograficzna lub tematyczna lub długo-/krótkoterminowa).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Uwagi:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Między publikacją niniejszego wstępnego ogłoszenia informacyjnego a publikacją ogłoszenia o zamówieniu musi upłynąć co najmniej 30 dni kalendarzowych.</P><P>Na obecnym etapie nie należy przesyłać wniosków ani zapytań o dodatkowe informacje.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: ERF - Medzinárodná verejná výzva na predloženie ponúk týkajúca sa náboru odbornej pomoci na podporu pri zmene daňového systému v západnej Afrike</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Krajiny Hospodárskeho spoločenstva západoafrických štátov (ECOWAS) a Mauritánia/západná Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDBEŽNÉ OZNÁMENIE O VEREJNOM OBSTARÁVANÍ SLUŽIEB</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčné číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Konanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užšia súťaž</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Názov programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program na podporu pri zmene daňového systému v západnej Afrike</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zdroj financovania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt CRIS č. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verejný obstarávateľ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komisia Západoafrickej hospodárskej a menovej únie (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Charakter verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jednotková cena</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cieľom obstarávania je poskytnúť dlhodobú a krátkodobú odbornú pomoc, vykonať vzdelávacie činnosti programu a realizovať ďalšie formy pomoci na zlepšenie riadenia vnútorného daňového systému členských štátov ECOWAS a posilniť systém koordinácie, monitorovania a hodnotenia programov zmeny daňového systému na úrovni každej komisie (ECOWAS a WAEMU) a na úrovni členských štátov.</P><P>Je potrebné pripomenúť, že program na podporu pri zmene daňového systému v západnej Afrike má za cieľ podporiť realizáciu programov zmeny daňového systému v západnej Afrike vyplývajúcich z realizácie regionálnych politík týkajúcich sa liberalizácie obchodu (colná únia, spoločný colný sadzobník – CET, dohody o hospodárskom partnerstve – EPA). Očakávajú sa 3 výsledky:</P><P>(i) zlepšenie riadenia vnútorného daňového systému členských štátov a jeho koordinácie v regióne;</P><P>(ii) posilnenie boja proti podvodom, daňovým únikom, nezákonným finančným tokom a korupcii, ktorý prispeje k zvýšeniu daňových príjmov;</P><P>(iii) posilnenie systému koordinácie, monitorovania a hodnotenia programov zmeny daňového systému na úrovni každej komisie a na úrovni členských štátov.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predbežný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predpokladaný dátum zverejnenia oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatočné informácie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Žiadne</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právny základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Príloha IV k Dohode o partnerstve medzi členmi skupiny afrických, karibských a tichomorských štátov na jednej strane a Európskym spoločenstvom a jeho členskými štátmi na strane druhej, podpísanej v Cotonou 23.6.2000, zmenenej v Luxemburgu 25.6.2005 a v Ouagadougou 22.6.2010. Uvádza sa odkaz na prílohu IV, v znení zmien rozhodnutia Rady ministrov krajín AKT – EÚ č. 1/2014 z 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Uveďte všetky špecifiká, ktoré by mohli mať vplyv na podmienky účasti (napríklad geografické, tematické alebo dlhodobé/krátkodobé).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Medzi zverejnením tohto predbežného oznámenia a zodpovedajúceho oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania musí uplynúť najmenej 30 kalendárnych dní.</P><P>V tejto fáze sa nemajú zasielať žiadne prihlášky ani žiadosti o ďalšie informácie.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: ERS - Mednarodni razpis za najem tehnične pomoči v podporo davčnemu prehodu v zahodni Afriki</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Države Gospodarske skupnosti zahodnoafriških držav (ECOWAS) + Mavretanija – zahodna Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDHODNO INFORMATIVNO OBVESTILO O NAROČILU STORITEV</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčna številka dokumenta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postopek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Omejeni</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program podpore davčnemu prehodu v zahodni Afriki</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt CRIS št. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komisija Zahodnoafriške ekonomske in monetarne unije (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vrsta naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cena na enoto</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Naročilo obsega zagotavljanje dolgoročne in kratkoročne tehnične pomoči, prevzem izvajanja dejavnosti usposabljanja v okviru programa in izvedbo drugih ukrepov, ki bi lahko izboljšali upravljanje notranjega obdavčevanja v državah članicah ECOWAS in okrepili sistem usklajevanja, spremljanja in vrednotenja programov davčnega prehoda na ravni obeh komisij (ECOWAS in WAEMU) ter na ravni držav članic.</P><P>Upoštevajte, da je cilj programa podpore davčnemu prehodu v zahodni Afriki zagotoviti podporo pri izvajanju programov davčnega prehoda v zahodni Afriki, ki so rezultat izvajanja regionalnih politik liberalizacije trgovine (Carinska unija, skupna zunanja tarifa, sporazum o gospodarskem partnerstvu). Pričakujejo se 3 rezultati:</P><P>(i) upravljanje notranjega obdavčevanja v državah članicah regije je izboljšano in bolje usklajeno;</P><P>(ii) boj proti goljufijam, davčnim utajam, nezakonitim finančnim tokovom in korupciji je učinkovitejši in prispeva k povečanju davčnih prihodkov;</P><P>(iii) sistem usklajevanja, spremljanja in vrednotenja programov davčnega prehoda je okrepljen na ravni obeh komisij ter na ravni držav članic.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Okvirni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predvideni datum objave obvestila o naročilu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ni navedeno</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravna podlaga (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Priloga IV k Sporazumu o partnerstvu med članicami skupine afriških, karibskih in pacifiških držav na eni strani ter Evropsko skupnostjo in njenimi državami članicami na drugi, podpisanemu v Cotonouju dne 23.6.2000, kakor je bil spremenjen v Luxembourgu dne 25.6.2005 in v Ouagadougouju dne 22.6.2010. Sklic se nanaša na Prilogo IV, kakor je bila revidirana s Sklepom št. 1/2014 Sveta ministrov AKP-EU z dne 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Prosimo, navedite kakršne koli posebnosti, ki bi lahko vplivale na pravila za sodelovanje (na primer geografske, tematske ali dolgo-/kratkoročne posebnosti).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opombe:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Med objavo tega predhodnega informativnega obvestila in objavo pripadajočega obvestila o naročilu mora preteči najmanj 30 koledarskih dni.</P><P>V tej fazi ne pošiljajte prijav ali zahtevkov za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: CEF - Cuireadh chun tairisceana idirnáisiúnta chun cúnamh teicniúil a earcú chun tacú le sochar idirthréimhseach san Afraic Thiar</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tíortha le Comhphobal Eacnamaíoch Stáit na hAfraice Thiar (Ecowas) + an Mháratáin / an Afraic Thiar</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÓGRA RÉAMHAISNÉISE MAIDIR LEIS AN tSEIRBHÍS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nós imeachta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Teoranta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ainm an chláir</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Clár tacaíochta sochar idirthréimhseach san Afraic Thiar</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Maoiniú</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>CRIS tionscadal Uimh. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás conarthach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Coimisiún Aontas Eacnamaíoch agus Airgeadaíochta na hAfraice Thiar (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Buircíne Fasó.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cineál an chonartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Praghas aonaid</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ar an gconradh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cumhdaítear leis an gconradh cúnamh teicniúil fadtéarmach agus gearrthéarmach, tacaíocht do chlár oiliúna agus forfheidhmiú rannchuidithe eile leis an aidhm chun bainistiú cánachais intíre a bhainistiú i mBallstáit Chomhphobal Eacnamaíoch Stáit na hAfraice Thiar (ECOWAS) agus córas comhordaithe, faireacháin agus meastóireachta na gclár sochar idirthréimhseach a neartú do gach coimisiún (ECOWAS agus WAEMU) agus do na Ballstáit.</P><P>Mar nóta meabhrúcháin, tá sé mar aidhm ag an gclár tacaíochta sochar idirthréimhseach san Afraic Thiar tacú le forfheidhmiú clár sochar idirthréimhseach san Afraic Thiar, tar éis cur chun feidhme beartas léirscaoilte na trádála réigiúnaí (Aontas Custaim, CET, ETA, etc.). Táthar ag súil le 3 thoradh:</P><P>(I) go bhfeabhsófar bainistiú ar chánachas inmheánach na mBallstát agus go ndéanfar é a chomhordú níos fearr sa réigiún;</P><P>(ii) go neartaítear an comhrac i gcoinne calaoise, imghabhála cánach, sreafraí airgeadais aindleathacha agus an éillithe, agus go rannchuidítear le hioncam cánach a mhéadú;</P><P>(iii) go neartaítear an córas le haghaidh comhordaithe, faireacháin agus meastóireachta ar chláir shochar idirthréimhseach ag leibhéal an choimisiúin agus ag leibhéal na mBallstát.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buiséad táscach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>An dáta atá socraithe d'fhoilsiú an fhógra conartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis bhreise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Faisnéis ar bith</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bunús dlí (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Iarscríbhinn IV leis an gComhaontú Comhpháirtíochta idir comhaltaí Ghrúpa Stát na hAfraice, Mhuir Chairib agus an Aigéin Chiúin de pháirt, agus an Comhphobal Eorpach agus a Bhallstáit, den pháirt eile, arna shíniú in Cotonou an 23.6.2000 mar a leasaíodh i Lucsamburg an 25.6.2005 agus in Ouagadougou an 22.6.2010. Déantar tagairt d'Iarscríbhinn IV arna hathbhreithniú le Cinneadh 1/2014 ó Chomhairle Airí ACC-AE an 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Cuir aon sainiúlacht in iúl a d’fhéadfadh tionchar a imirt ar rialacha na rannpháirtíochta (e.g. sainiúlacht gheografach, sainiúlacht ghearrthréimhseach nó fhadtréimhseach).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Nótaí:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Ní foláir nó go mbeidh 30 lá féilire ar a laghad idir foilsiú an fhógra réamhaisnéise agus foilsiú an fhógra conartha chomhfhreagraigh.</P><P>Níor cheart aon iarratais ná iarrataí ar fhaisnéis a sheoladh faoi láthair.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Уагадугу: ЕФР - Международна покана за участие в търг за набиране на техническа помощ в подкрепа на данъчния преход в Западна Африка</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Държавите от Икономическата общност на западноафриканските държави (Ecowas) + Мавритания/Западна Африка</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ОБЯВЛЕНИЕ ЗА ПРЕДВАРИТЕЛНА ИНФОРМАЦИЯ ОТНОСНО УСЛУГАТА</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Референтен номер на публикация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Процедура</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ограничена</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Наименование на програмата</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Програма за подкрепа на данъчния преход в Западна Африка</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Финансиране</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Проект CRIS № FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Комисия на Западноафриканския икономически и валутен съюз (ЗАИВС)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Уагадугу</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Буркина Фасо.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Вид на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Единична цена</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Описание на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Договорът има за цел да предостави дългосрочна и краткосрочна техническа помощ, поемане на дейностите по обучение по програмата и да използва други видове подход, които биха могли да подобрят управлението на вътрешната данъчна система на страните-членки на ECOWAS и да укрепи системата за координиране, наблюдение и оценка на програмите за данъчни преходи на равнище комисии (ECOWAS и ЗАИВС) и на равнище държави-членки.</P><P>Припомняме, че програмата за подкрепа на данъчния преход в Западна Африка има за цел да подкрепи изпълнението на програмите за данъчен преход в Западна Африка, вследствие на осъществяването на регионалните политики за либерализация на търговията (митнически съюз, TEC, APE,). Очакват се 3 продукта:</P><P>(i) управлението на вътрешната данъчна система на държавите-членки се подобрява и е по-добре координирано в региона;</P><P>(ii) борбата с измамите, укриването на данъци, незаконните финансови потоци и корупцията се засилва и допринася за увеличаване на данъчните приходи;</P><P>(iii) системата за координиране, наблюдение и оценка на програмите за данъчен преход се засилва на равнище комисия и на равнище държави-членки.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Индикативен бюджет</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Планирана дата на публикуване на обявлението за поръчка</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018 г.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Допълнителна информация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Няма</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Правно основание (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Приложение IV към Споразумението за партньорство между членовете на Групата на държавите от Африка, Карибите и Тихоокеанския басейн и Европейската общност и нейните държави-членки, подписано в Котону на 23.6.2000 г., изменено в Люксембург на 25.6.2005 г. и в Уагадугу на 22.6.2010 г. Направена е препратка към приложение IV, ревизирано с Решение № 1/2014 на Съвета на министрите АКТБ-ЕС от 20.6.2014 г.</P><P>(1) Моля да посочите всяка особеност, която може да има последици за условията за участие (географска или тематична или кратко/дългосрочна).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Забележки:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Между публикуването на това обявление за предварителна информация и публикуването на обявлението за поръчка трябва да изминат поне 30 календарни дни.</P><P>На този етап не трябва да се изпращат молби или искания за информация.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: FED - Licitație internațională pentru recrutarea de asistență tehnică în sprijinul tranziției fiscale în Africa de Vest</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Țările Comunității Statelor din Africa de Vest (ECOWAS) + Mauritania / Africa de Vest</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNȚ DE INTENȚIE PRIVIND UN CONTRACT DE ACHIZIȚII PUBLICE DE SERVICII</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referința publicației</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedură</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restrânsă</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titlul programului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program de sprijin pentru tranziția fiscală în Africa de Vest</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanțare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proiectul CRIS nr. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea contractantă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Comisia Uniunii economice și monetare vest-africane (UEMA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Preț unitar</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contractul vizează asigura unei asistențe tehnică pe termen lung și pe termen scurt, preluarea activității de formare a programului și implementarea altor contribuții care ar putea îmbunătăți gestionarea impozitării interne a Statelor membre ECOWAS și consolidarea sistemului de coordonare, monitorizare și evaluare a programelor de tranziție fiscală la nivelul fiecărei comisii (ECOWAS și UEMOA) și la nivelul statelor membre.</P><P>Reamintim că programul de susținere a tranziției fiscale din Africa de Vest are ca obiectiv de a sprijinii implementarea programelor de tranziție fiscală în Africa de Vest, ca urmare a implementării politicilor regionale de liberalizare a comerțului (Uniunea vamală, TEC, APE). Se așteaptă 3 produse:</P><P>(i) gestionarea impozitării interne a statelor membre este îmbunătățită și mai bine coordonată în regiune;</P><P>(ii) lupta împotriva fraudei, a evaziunii fiscale, a fluxurilor financiare ilicite și a corupției este consolidată și contribuie la creșterea veniturilor fiscale;</P><P>(iii) sistemul de coordonare, monitorizare și evaluare a programelor de tranziție fiscală este consolidat la nivelul fiecărei comisii și la nivelul statelor membre.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buget indicativ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevăzută pentru publicarea anunțului de participare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informații suplimentare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nu există</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Temeiul juridic (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anexa IV la Acordul de parteneriat între membrii grupului statelor din Africa, zona Caraibilor și Pacific și Comunitatea Europeană și statele membre ale acesteia, semnat la Cotonou, la 23.6.2000, astfel cum a fost modificat la Luxemburg, la 25.6.2005, și la Ouagadougou, la 22.6.2010. Se face referire la anexa IV, astfel cum a fost revizuită prin Decizia nr. 1/2014 a Consiliului de miniștri ACP-UE din 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Indicați orice particularitate care ar putea avea consecințe asupra modalităților de participare (de ex, de ordin geografic sau tematic, sau termeni pe termen scurt/lung).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observații:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Trebuie respectată o perioadă de cel puțin 30 de zile calendaristice între publicarea prezentului anunț de intenție și publicarea anunțului de participare corespunzător.</P><P>În această etapă nu trebuie trimise candidaturi sau cereri de informații.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: ERF - Poziv na međunarodno nadmetanje za zapošljavanje tehničke pomoći za podršku poreznoj tranziciji u Zapadnoj Africi</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Države Zajednice zapadnoafričkih država (Ecowas) + Mauritanija / Zapadna Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PRETHODNA INFORMACIJSKA OBAVIJEST O USLUGAMA</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uputa na objavu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139648/IH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postupak</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograničeni</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naziv programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program podrške poreznoj tranziciji u Zapadnoj Africi</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt CRIS br. FED/2017/039-133</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komisija Zapadnoafričke ekonomske i monetarne unije (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> / </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Priroda ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jedinična cijena</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cilj je ugovora pružanje dugoročne i kratkoročne tehničke pomoći, preuzimanje odgovornosti za aktivnosti osposobljavanja programa i provođenje drugih mjera koje bi mogle poboljšati upravljanje unutarnjim oporezivanjem Ecowas-a i ojačati sustav koordinacije, praćenja i procjene programa porezne tranzicije na razini svake komisije (ECOWAS i WAEMU) i na razini MS-a.</P><P>Cilj je programa podrške poreznoj tranziciji u Zapadnoj Africi podržati provedbu programa porezne tranzicije u Zapadnoj Africi, nastavno na provedbu regionalnih politika liberalizacije trgovine (Carinska unija, CET, EPA). Očekuju se 3 proizvoda:</P><P>(i) upravljanje unutarnjim oporezivanjem država članica poboljšano je i bolje usklađeno u regiji;</P><P>(ii) borba protiv prijevara, utaje poreza, nedopuštenih financijskih tokova i korupcije pojačana je i pridonosi povećanju poreznih prihoda;</P><P>(iii) sustav koordinacije, praćenja i evaluacije programa porezne tranzicije poboljšan je na razini svake komisije i na razini MS-a.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indikativni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predviđeni datum objave poziva na nadmetanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne pojedinosti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ne postoje</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravni temelj (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prilog IV. Sporazumu o partnerstvu između članica afričke, karipske i pacifičke skupine država i Europske zajednice i njezinih država članica, potpisan u Cotonouu 23.6.2000, kako je izmijenjen u Luxembourgu 25.6.2005 i u Ouagadougouu 22.6.2010. Uputa se daje na Prilog IV. koji je revidiran Odlukom br. 1/2014 Vijeća ministara AKP-a i EU-a od 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Navedite sve pojedinosti koje bi mogle utjecati na oblike sudjelovanja (geografske ili tematske, kratkoročne ili dugoročne).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Napomene:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Između objave ove prethodne informacijske obavijesti i objave odgovarajućeg poziva na nadmetanje mora proći najmanje 30 kalendarskih dana.</P><P>U toj se fazi ne smiju slati prijave ili zahtjevi za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>