<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="180387-2018" EDITION="2018081"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-173514-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20190417</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>81</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180426</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 081-180387</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:180387-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>FR</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BF"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71356200">Technical assistance services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180417</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>AP301</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Langsigtet teknisk bistand til Den Vestafrikanske Udviklingsbank (WADB) inden for rammerne af EU’s eksterne investeringsplan.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Langfristige technische Unterstützung für die westafrikanische Entwicklungsbank (Banque ouest africaine de développement BOAD) im Hinblick auf den Plan für auswärtige Investitionen (Plan d'investissement extérieur) der Europäischen Union.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Long-term technical assistance to be given to the West African Development Bank (WADB) in the context of the European Union's External Investment Plan.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Uagadugu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Asistencia técnica a largo plazo para el Banco de Desarrollo de África Occidental (BOAD) en la perspectiva del Plan de inversiones externas de la Unión Europea.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Pitkäaikainen tekninen tuki Länsi-Afrikan kehityspankille (BOAD) Euroopan unionin ulkoista investointisuunnitelmaa silmällä pitäen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Burkina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Assistance technique long terme à placer auprès de la Banque ouest africaine de développement (BOAD) dans la perspective du Plan d'investissement extérieur de l'Union européenne.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Μπουρκίνα</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ουαγκαντούγκου</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Παροχή μακροπρόθεσμης τεχνικής βοήθειας στην Τράπεζα Ανάπτυξης της Δυτικής Αφρικής (BOAD) στο πλαίσιο του εξωτερικού επενδυτικού σχεδίου της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Assistenza tecnica a lungo termine alla Banca per lo sviluppo dell'Africa occidentale (BOAD) nella prospettiva del piano di investimenti esterni dell'Unione europea.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Technische bijstand op lange termijn voor de West-Afrikaanse Ontwikkelingsbank in het kader van het plan voor buitenlandse investeringen van de Europese Unie</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Burquina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Uagadugu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Assistência técnica a longo prazo a favor do Banco de Desenvolvimento da África Ocidental (BDAO) na perspetiva do Plano de investimento exterior da União Europeia.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Teknisk långsiktig assistans till den Västafrikanska utvecklingsbanken (BOAD) med sikte på den Europeiska unionens externa investeringsplan</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Poskytnutí dlouhodobé technické pomoci Západoafrické rozvojové bance (BOAD) v rámci plánu vnějších investic EU.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Pikaajaline tehniline abi Lääne-Aafrika Arengupangale (BOAD) Euroopa Liidu välisinvesteeringute kava perspektiivis</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Hosszú távú szakmai segítségnyújtás a Nyugat-afrikai Fejlesztési Banknak az Európai Unió külső beruházási tervének kontextusában.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Burkina Fasas</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Uagadugu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ilgalaikė techninė pagalba, teikiama Vakarų Afrikos plėtros bankui (VAPB), atsižvelgiant į Europos Sąjungos išorės investicijų planą.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Burkinafaso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Vagadugu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ilgtermiņa tehniskā palīdzība Rietumāfrikas attīstības bankai (WADB), ņemot vērā Eiropas Savienības ārējo investīciju plānu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Għajnuna teknika fit-tul fi ħdan il-Bank ta' Żvilupp tal-Afrika tal-Punent (BOAD) fid-dawl tal-Pjan ta' Investiment Estern tal-Unjoni Ewropea.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Wagadugu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Długoterminowa pomoc techniczna na rzecz Zachodnioafrykańskiego Banku Rozwoju (BOAD) w perspektywie planu inwestycji zewnętrznych Unii Europejskiej.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Burkina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Dlhodobá odborná pomoc pre Západoafrickú rozvojovú banku (BOAD) v súvislosti s vonkajším investičným plánom Európskej únie.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Zagotavljanje dolgoročne tehnične pomoči Zahodnoafriški razvojni banki (WADB) z vidika načrta za zunanje naložbe Evropske unije</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Buircíne Fasó</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Cúnamh teicniúil fadtéarmach le soláthar do Bhanc Forbraíochta na hAfraice Thiar (WADB - West African Development Bank) i gcomhthéacs Phlean Infheistíochta Seachtrach an Aontais Eorpaigh.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Буркина Фасо</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Уагадугу</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Дългосрочната техническа помощ да бъде предоставена от Банката за развитие на Западна Африка (BOAD) в контекста на плана за външна инвестиция на Европейския съюз.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Asistența tehnică pe termen lung care urmează să fie acordată băncii de dezvoltare din Africa de Vest în perspectiva Planului de investiții externe al Uniunii europene.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Burkina Faso</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ouagadougou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Pružanje dugoročne tehnički pomoći Zapadnoafričkoj razvojnoj banci (WADB) u okviru plana vanjskog ulaganja Europske unije.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Kommissionen for Den Vestafrikanske Økonomiske og Monetære Union (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Die Kommission der Westafrikanischen Wirtschafts- und Währungsunion (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">Commission of the West African Economic and Monetary Union (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">La Comisión de la Unión Económica y Monetaria del África Occidental (UEMAO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Länsi-Afrikan talous- ja rahaliiton (Union économique et monétaire ouest-africaine – UEMOA) komissio</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">La Commission de l'union économique et monétaire Ouest Africaine (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Η Επιτροπή της Δυτικοαφρικανικής Οικονομικής και Νομισματικής Ένωσης (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Commissione dell'Unione economica e monetaria dell'Africa occidentale (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">De commissie van de West-Afrikaanse Economische en Monetaire Unie (Waemu)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">A Comissão da União Económica e Monetária da África Ocidental (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Västafrikanska ekonomiska och monetära unionens (WAEMU) kommission</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Komise Západoafrické hospodářské a měnové unie (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Lääne-Aafrika majandus- ja rahaliidu (WAEMU) komisjon</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">A Nyugat-afrikai Gazdasági és Monetáris Unió (UEMOA) bizottsága</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Vakarų Afrikos ekonominės ir pinigų sąjungos (VAEPS) komisija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Rietumāfrikas Ekonomiskās un monetārās savienības (UEMOA) komisija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">il-Kummissjoni tal-Unjoni Ekonomika u Monetarja tal-Afrika tal-Punent (UEMOA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Komisja Zachodnioafrykańskiej Unii Gospodarczej i Walutowej (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Komisia Západoafrickej hospodárskej a menovej únie (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Komisija Zahodnoafriške ekonomske in monetarne unije (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">Coimisiún Aontas Eacnamaíoch agus Airgeadaíochta na hAfraice Thiar (WAEMU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Комисия на Западноафриканския икономически и валутен съюз (ЗАИВС)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Comisia Uniunii economice și monetare vest-africane (UEMA)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Komisija Zapadnoafričke ekonomske i monetarne unije (WAEMU)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Langsigtet teknisk bistand til Den Vestafrikanske Udviklingsbank (WADB) inden for rammerne af EU’s eksterne investeringsplan.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou — kommissionen for Den Vestafrikanske Økonomiske og Monetære Union (WAEMU)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FORHÅNDSMEDDELELSE VEDRØRENDE TJENESTEYDELSERNE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udbudsreference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Begrænset</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programtitel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>WAEMU's støtteprogram for institutionel kapacitetsopbygning (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finansieringsaftale nr. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Kommissionen for Den Vestafrikanske Økonomiske og Monetære Union (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontraktens art</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Enhedspriser</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivelse af kontrakten</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kontrakten har til formål at indsætte et teknisk bistandshold til støtte for Den Vestafrikanske Udviklingsbank (WADB) i dennes gennemførelse af reformer forbundet med søjlerevision.</P><P>Den tekniske bistand, hvis varighed er 36 måneder, skal ledsage WADB i gennemførelsen af reformer inden for systemer, kontrol, regler og procedurer i forbindelse med søjljerevision med henblik på at sætte banken i stand til indføre standarder, der kan anerkendes internationalt og overholde Europa-Kommissionens kriterier for indirekte forvaltning af EU-midler.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vejledende budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Den institutionelle budgetstøtte til WADB beløber sig til 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planlagt dato for offentliggørelse af udbudsbekendtgørelsen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yderligere oplysninger</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finder ikke anvendelse</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Retsgrundlag (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bilag IV til partnerskabsaftalen mellem medlemmerne af gruppen af stater i Afrika, Vestindien og Stillehavet og Det Europæiske Fællesskab og dets medlemsstater, underskrevet i Cotonou 23.6.2000, som ændret i Luxembourg 25.6.2005 og i Ouagadougou 22.6.2010. Der henvises til bilag IV som ændret ved AVS-EU-Ministerrådets afgørelse nr. 1/2014 af 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Angiv venligst enhver specificitet, der kan have konsekvens for deltagelsesreglerne (f.eks. geografisk, tematisk, kortsigtet eller langsigtet).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Bemærkninger:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Der skal gå mindst 30 kalenderdage mellem offentliggørelsen af denne forhåndsmeddelelse og offentliggørelsen af den tilhørende udbudsbekendtgørelse.</P><P>— Der bør ikke fremsendes ansøgninger eller anmodninger om oplysninger på nuværende tidspunkt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Langfristige technische Unterstützung für die westafrikanische Entwicklungsbank (Banque ouest africaine de développement BOAD) im Hinblick auf den Plan für auswärtige Investitionen (Plan d'investissement extérieur) der Europäischen Union.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou – Westafrikanische Wirtschafts- und Währungsunion (UEMOA)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VORINFORMATION ÜBER EINEN DIENSTLEISTUNGSVERTRAG</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verfahren</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nichtoffen</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmbezeichnung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Förderprogramm zur Erhöhung der institutionellen Leistungsfähigkeit der UEMOA (PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanzierung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finanzierungsabkommen Nr. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ausschreibende Behörde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Die Kommission der Westafrikanischen Wirtschafts- und Währungsunion (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Art des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Preise pro Einheit</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Im Rahmen dieses Auftrags wird die Umsetzung eines technischen Unterstützungsteams, das mit der Unterstützung der westafrikanischen Entwicklungsbank (Banque ouest africaine de développement BOAD) bei der Umsetzung der mit dem Audit der Grundlagen verbundenen Reformen beauftragt wird, angestrebt.</P><P>Während einer Dauer von 36 Monaten begleitet die technische Unterstützung die BOAD bei der Umsetzung der mit den Systemen, Kontrollen, Vorschriften und Verfahren des Audits der Grundlagen verbundenen Reformen, um der BOAD eine Umsetzung der auf internationaler Ebene geltenden Normen und der von der Europäischen Kommission im Bereich der indirekten Verwaltung der Geldmittel der Europäischen Union von der Europäischen Kommission festgelegten Kriterien zu ermöglichen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veranschlagter Auftragswert</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Das für die institutionelle Unterstützung der BOAD vorgesehene Budget beträgt 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vorgesehener Zeitpunkt der Veröffentlichung der Auftragsbekanntmachung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zusätzliche Informationen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Entfällt</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsgrundlage (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anhang IV des Partnerschaftsabkommens zwischen den Mitgliedern der Gruppe der Staaten in Afrika, im Karibischen Raum und im Pazifischen Ozean einerseits und der Europäischen Gemeinschaft und ihren Mitgliedstaaten andererseits, unterzeichnet in Cotonou am 23.6.2000, in der am 25.6.2005 in Luxemburg und am 22.6.2010 in Ouagadougou geänderten Fassung. Es wird auf Anhang IV in der Fassung gemäß Beschluss Nr. 1/2014 des AKP-EU-Ministerrates vom 20.6.2014 verwiesen.</P><P>(1) Geben Sie bitte alle Besonderheiten an, die sich auf die Teilnahmebedingungen auswirken könnten (zum Beispiel geographische, Besonderheit, kurz- oder langfristige Thematik).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Hinweise:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Zwischen der Veröffentlichung der vorliegenden Vorinformation und der Veröffentlichung der zugehörigen Auftragsbekanntmachung ist eine Mindestfrist von 30 Kalendertagen einzuhalten,</P><P>— Zum gegenwärtigen Zeitpunkt sind weder Bewerbungen einzureichen noch Auskünfte anzufordern.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Long-term technical assistance to be given to the West African Development Bank (WADB) in the context of the European Union's External Investment Plan.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou — Commission of the West African Economic and Monetary Union (WAEMU)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PRIOR INFORMATION NOTICE REGARDING THE SERVICE:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publication reference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programme name</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>WAEMU institutional capacity building support programme (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financing</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Financing agreement No ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contracting authority</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Commission of the West African Economic and Monetary Union (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature of the contract</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Unit price</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contract description</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract covers the establishment of a technical assistance team to support the West African Development Bank (WADB) in the implementation of reforms related to pillar audits.</P><P>The 36-month technical assistance will support WADB in the implementation of reforms related to pillar audit systems, controls, rules and procedures so that it can develop internationally accepted standards and criteria set by the European Commission in the area of indirect management of EU funds.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicative budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The budget for institutional support to WADB is 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Scheduled date for publication of the contract notice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Additional Information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>NA</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal basis (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Annex IV to the Partnership Agreement between the members of the African, Caribbean and Pacific Group of States of one part, and the European Community and its Member States, of the other part, signed in Cotonou on 23.6.2000 as amended in Luxembourg on 25.6.2005 and in Ouagadougou on 22.6.2010. Reference is made to Annex IV as revised by Decision 1/2014 of the ACP-EU Council of Ministers of 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Please indicate any aspect that may have an impact on the rules of participation (e.g. geographical, thematic, short-term or long-term).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarks:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— At least 30 calendar days must elapse between publication of this prior information notice and publication of the corresponding contract notice,</P><P>— Applications or requests for information must not be sent at this stage.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Uagadugu: Asistencia técnica a largo plazo para el Banco de Desarrollo de África Occidental (BOAD) en la perspectiva del Plan de inversiones externas de la Unión Europea.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Uagadugu, Comisión de la Unión Económica y Monetaria del África Occidental (UEMAO)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNCIO DE PREVISIÓN DE CONTRATO DE SERVICIOS:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referencia de publicación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedimiento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restringido</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Denominación del programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de apoyo al refuerzo de las capacidades institucionales de la UEMAO (PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Convenio de financiación n<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de contratación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>La Comisión de la Unión Económica y Monetaria del África Occidental (UEMAO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Uagadugu</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naturaleza del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Precios unitarios</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El contrato tiene como objetivo establecer un equipo de asistencia técnica para apoyar al Banco de Desarrollo de África Occidental (BOAD) en la implementación de reformas relacionadas con la auditoría de los pilares.</P><P>La asistencia técnica de 36 meses acompañará al BOAD en la implementación de reformas relacionadas con los sistemas, controles, reglas y procedimientos de la auditoría de los pilares para que pueda adoptar estándares aceptados a nivel internacional y los criterios establecidos por la Comisión Europea en el ámbito de la gestión indirecta de los fondos de la UE.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Presupuesto indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El presupuesto para apoyo institucional a BOAD es de 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha prevista para la publicación del anuncio de licitación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información complementaria</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>N/A</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fundamento jurídico (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anexo IV del Acuerdo de asociación entre los miembros del grupo de los Estados de África, del Caribe y del Pacífico, por una parte, y la Comunidad Europea y sus Estados miembros, por otra parte, firmado en Cotonú el 23.6.2000, en su versión modificada en Luxemburgo el 25.6.2005, y en Uagadugu el 22.6.2010. Se hace referencia aquí al anexo IV modificado por la Decisión 1/2014 del Consejo de Ministros ACP-UE de 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Indique cualquier particularidad ( geográfica, temática o de largo/corto plazo) que pueda tener consecuencias en las modalidades de participación.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observaciones:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Deben pasar al menos 30 días naturales entre la publicación del presente anuncio de previsión y la publicación del anuncio de contrato correspondiente,</P><P>— No se deben enviar candidaturas ni pedidos de información en esta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Pitkäaikainen tekninen tuki Länsi-Afrikan kehityspankille (BOAD) Euroopan unionin ulkoista investointisuunnitelmaa silmällä pitäen</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou – Länsi-Afrikan talous- ja rahaliiton (Union économique et monétaire ouest-africaine – UEMOA) komissio</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Palvelua koskeva ennakkotietoilmoitus</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen viite</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menettely</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rajoitettu menettely</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ohjelman nimi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>UEMOA:n institutionaalisten valmiuksien kehittämistä koskeva ohjelma (Programme de renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahoitus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rahoitussopimus nro ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Länsi-Afrikan talous- ja rahaliiton (Union économique et monétaire ouest-africaine – UEMOA) komissio</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuslaji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Yksikköhinta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuksen kuvaus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sopimuksen tarkoituksena on pitkäaikaisen teknisen tukiryhmän asettaminen Länsi-Afrikan kehityspankin (Banque ouest-africaine de développement – BOAD) tukemiseksi toteutettaessa pilareiden tarkastukseen liittyviä uudistuksia.</P><P>Sopimuksen kestoaika on 36 kuukautta, ja teknistä tukea annetaan Länsi-Afrikan kehityspankille (BOAD) sen toteuttaessa uudistuksia, jotka liittyvät pilareiden tarkastuksessa käytettäviin järjestelmiin, suoritettaviin tarkistuksiin, sääntöihin ja menetelmiin, jotta BOAD voisi omaksua kansainvälisesti hyväksytyt normit ja Euroopan komission kriteerit Euroopan unionin varojen epäsuoran hallinnoinnin alalla.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Alustava budjetti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>BOAD:ille varatun institutionaalisen tuen budjetti on 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintailmoituksen suunniteltu julkaisuajankohta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisätiedot</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ei sovelleta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oikeusperusta (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cotonoussa 23.6.2000 allekirjoitetun Afrikan, Karibian ja Tyynenmeren valtioiden ryhmän jäsenten sekä Euroopan yhteisön ja sen jäsenvaltioiden välisen kumppanuussopimuksen liite IV, sellaisena kuin sopimus on muutettuna Luxemburgissa 25.6.2005 ja Ouagadougoussa 22.6.2010. Viitataan liitteeseen IV, sellaisena kuin se on muutettuna 20.6.2014 annetulla AKT–EU-ministerineuvoston päätöksellä nro 1/2014.</P><P>(1) Mainitse seikat, joilla voisi olla vaikutusta osallistumissääntöihin (kuten esimerkiksi maantieteellinen tai aihepiirikohtainen tai pitkä/lyhyt kesto).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Huom.:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Tämän ennakkotietoilmoituksen ja varsinaisen hankintailmoituksen julkaisuajankohtien välillä on oltava vähintään 30 kalenteripäivää.</P><P>Hakemuksia tai tietopyyntöjä ei pidä lähettää tässä vaiheessa.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Assistance technique long terme à placer auprès de la Banque ouest africaine de développement (BOAD) dans la perspective du Plan d'investissement extérieur de l'Union européenne.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou-Commission de l'Union Economique et Monétaire Ouest Africaine (UEMOA)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVIS DE PRÉINFORMATION CONCERNANT LE SERVICE:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Référence de la publication</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restreinte</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nom du programme</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programme d’appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles de l'UEMOA (PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financement</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Convention de financement n<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Administration contractante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>La Commission de l'union économique et monétaire Ouest Africaine (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, BURKINA FASO.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature du contrat</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prix unitaires</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du contrat</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le contrat vise la mise en place d'une équipe d'assistance technique chargée d'appuyer la Banque ouest africaine de développement (BOAD) dans la mise en œuvre des réformes liées à l'audit des piliers.</P><P>D'une durée de 36 mois, l’assistance technique accompagnera la BOAD dans la mise en œuvre des réformes liées aux systèmes, aux contrôles, aux règles et aux procédures de l'audit des piliers afin qu'elle puisse se doter de normes admises au niveau international et aux critères fixés par la Commission européenne dans le domaine de la gestion indirecte des fonds de l'Union européenne.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Budget indicatif</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le budget de l'appui institutionnel à la BOAD est de 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date prévue pour la publication de l'avis de marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informations supplémentaires</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>NA</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base juridique(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Annexe IV de l'accord de partenariat entre les membres du groupe des États d’Afrique, des Caraïbes et du Pacifique, d’une part, et la Communauté européenne et ses États membres, d’autre part, signé à Cotonou le 23.6.2000, tel que modifié à Luxembourg le 25.6.2005 et à Ouagadougou le 22.6.2010. Il est fait référence à l'annexe IV, telle que révisée par la décision 1/2014 du Conseil des ministres ACP-UE du 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Veuillez indiquer toute particularité qui pourrait avoir des conséquences sur les modalités de participation (telle que géographique ou thématique ou long/court terme).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarques:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Au moins 30 jours calendaires doivent s'écouler entre la publication du présent avis de pré-information et la publication de l'avis de marché correspondant,</P><P>— Aucune candidature ni demande d'informations ne doit être envoyée à ce stade.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ουαγκαντούγκου: Παροχή μακροπρόθεσμης τεχνικής βοήθειας στην Τράπεζα Ανάπτυξης της Δυτικής Αφρικής (BOAD) στο πλαίσιο του εξωτερικού επενδυτικού σχεδίου της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ουαγκαντούγκου — Επιτροπή της Δυτικοαφρικανικής Οικονομικής και Νομισματικής Ένωσης (UEMOA)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ΠΡΟΚΑΤΑΡΚΤΙΚΉ ΑΝΑΚΟΊΝΩΣΗ ΣΧΕΤΙΚΆ ΜΕ ΤΗΝ ΥΠΗΡΕΣΊΑ:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αριθ. αναφοράς της δημοσίευσης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Διαδικασία</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κλειστή</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ονομασία του προγράμματος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Πρόγραμμα στήριξης της ενίσχυσης των θεσμικών ικανοτήτων της UEMOA (PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Χρηματοδότηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Χρηματοδοτική συμφωνία αριθ. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα διοίκηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Η Επιτροπή της Δυτικοαφρικανικής Οικονομικής και Νομισματικής Ένωσης (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ουαγκαντούγκου</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Μπουρκίνα Φάσο.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Φύση της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Τιμές μονάδας</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Περιγραφή της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Σκοπός της σύμβασης είναι η σύσταση ομάδας τεχνικής βοήθειας για την υποστήριξη της Τράπεζας Ανάπτυξης της Δυτικής Αφρικής (BOAD) για την εφαρμογή των μεταρρυθμίσεων που σχετίζονται με τον έλεγχο των πυλώνων.</P><P>Η τεχνική βοήθεια διάρκειας 36 μηνών θα συνδράμει την BOAD στην εφαρμογή μεταρρυθμίσεων που σχετίζονται με τα συστήματα, τους ελέγχους, τους κανόνες και τις διαδικασίες του ελέγχου των πυλώνων ώστε να είναι σε θέση να υιοθετήσει τα τυποποιημένα πρότυπα σε διεθνές επίπεδο και τα κριτήρια που έχει θέσει η Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή στον τομέα της έμμεσης διαχείρισης των κονδυλίων της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ενδεικτικός προϋπολογισμός</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ο προϋπολογισμός για τη θεσμική υποστήριξη της BOAD ανέρχεται στα 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης της προκήρυξης σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Άνευ αντικειμένου</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Νομική βάση (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Παράρτημα IV της συμφωνίας εταιρικής σχέσης μεταξύ των μελών της ομάδας των κρατών της Αφρικής, της Καραϊβικής και του Ειρηνικού, αφενός, και της Ευρωπαϊκής Κοινότητας και των κρατών μελών αυτής, αφετέρου, η οποία υπεγράφη στην Κοτονού στις 23.6.2000, όπως τροποποιήθηκε στο Λουξεμβούργο στις 25.6.2005 και στην Ουαγκαντούγκου στις 22.6.2010. Γίνεται αναφορά στο παράρτημα IV όπως αναθεωρήθηκε με την απόφαση 1/2014 του Συμβουλίου Υπουργών ΑΚΕ-ΕΕ στις 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Παρακαλείστε να αναφέρετε κάθε ιδιαιτερότητα που θα μπορούσε να φέρει συνέπειες στους τρόπους συμμετοχής (όπως γεωγραφική ή θεματική ή βραχυπρόθεσμη/μακροπρόθεσμη).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Παρατηρήσεις:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Θα πρέπει να παρέλθει ελάχιστο χρονικό διάστημα 30 ημερολογιακών ημερών μεταξύ της δημοσίευσης της παρούσας προκαταρκτικής ανακοίνωσης και της δημοσίευσης της αντίστοιχης προκήρυξης σύμβασης,</P><P>— Καμία υποψηφιότητα ή αίτηση για περαιτέρω πληροφορίες δεν θα πρέπει να αποστέλλεται σε αυτό το στάδιο.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Assistenza tecnica a lungo termine alla Banca per lo sviluppo dell'Africa occidentale (BOAD) nella prospettiva del piano di investimenti esterni dell'Unione europea.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou — commissione dell'Unione economica e monetaria dell'Africa occidentale (UEMOA)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVISO DI PREINFORMAZIONE RELATIVO AL SERVIZIO:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Riferimento della pubblicazione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ristretta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nome del programma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programma di sostegno per il rafforzamento delle capacità istituzionali dell'UEMOA (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles de l'UEMOA — PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanziamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Accordo di finanziamento n. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ente appaltante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Commissione dell'Unione economica e monetaria dell'Africa occidentale (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prezzi unitari</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L'appalto mira a costituire un'équipe di assistenza tecnica per sostenere la Banca per lo sviluppo dell'Africa occidentale (BOAD) nell'attuazione delle riforme relative alla revisione dei pilastri.</P><P>L'assistenza tecnica avrà la durata di 36 mesi e accompagnerà la BOAD nell'attuazione delle riforme relative ai sistemi, controlli, norme e procedure della revisione dei pilastri, in modo da adottare norme accettate a livello internazionale e i criteri stabiliti dalla Commissione europea nel settore della gestione indiretta dei fondi dell'Unione europea.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bilancio indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il bilancio per il sostegno istituzionale alla BOAD è di 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista per la pubblicazione del bando di gara</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informazioni complementari</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Non applicabile</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base giuridica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Allegato IV all'accordo di partenariato tra i membri del gruppo degli Stati dell'Africa, dei Caraibi e del Pacifico, da un lato, e la Comunità europea ed i suoi Stati membri, dall'altro, firmato a Cotonou il 23.6.2000, come modificato a Lussemburgo il 25.6.2005 e a Ouagadougou il 22.6.2010. Si fa riferimento all'allegato IV come modificato dalla decisione n. 1/2014 del Consiglio dei ministri ACP-UE del 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Indicare qualsiasi particolarità che possa avere conseguenze sulle modalità di partecipazione (come geografica o tematica o a lungo/breve termine).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Osservazioni:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Dovranno intercorrere almeno 30 giorni di calendario tra la pubblicazione del presente avviso di preinformazione e quella del bando di gara corrispondente,</P><P>— si prega di non inviare candidature o richieste di informazioni durante questa fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Technische bijstand op lange termijn voor de West-Afrikaanse Ontwikkelingsbank in het kader van het plan voor buitenlandse investeringen van de Europese Unie</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou - Commissie van de West-Afrikaanse Economische en Monetaire Unie (Waemu)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VOORAANKONDIGING VOOR EEN DIENST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referentie van de bekendmaking:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet-openbaar.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naam van het programma:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programma ter ondersteuning van de versterking van de institutionele capaciteiten van de Waemu (Parci).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiering:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Financieringsovereenkomst nr. ROC/FED/2013/024-224.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>De commissie van de West-Afrikaanse Economische en Monetaire Unie (Waemu)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aard van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eenheidsprijzen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschrijving van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De opdracht beoogt de inzet van een team technische assistenten belast met de ondersteuning van de West-Afrikaanse Ontwikkelingsbank bij de tenuitvoerlegging van de hervormingen die verband houden met de audit van de pijlers.</P><P>De technische bijstand heeft een looptijd van 36 maanden en moet de West-Afrikaanse Ontwikkelingsbank begeleiden bij de tenuitvoerlegging van de hervormingen van de systemen, de controles, de regels en de procedures van de audit van de pijlers, zodat deze kan voldoen aan de internationaal aanvaarde normen en aan de criteria die door de Europese Commissie zijn vastgesteld op het gebied van het indirect beheer van fondsen van de Europese Unie.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicatieve begroting:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De institutionele begrotingssteun voor de West-Afrikaanse Ontwikkelingsbank bedraagt 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beoogde datum van bekendmaking van de aankondiging van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nadere inlichtingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet van toepassing.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Juridische basis (1):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bijlage IV bij de Partnerschapsovereenkomst tussen de leden van de groep van Staten in Afrika, het Caribisch gebied en de Stille Oceaan enerzijds, en de Europese Gemeenschap en haar lidstaten anderzijds, ondertekend te Cotonou op 23.6.2000, zoals gewijzigd in Luxemburg op 25.6.2005 en in Ouagadougou op 22.6.2010. Er wordt verwezen naar bijlage IV zoals gewijzigd bij Besluit nr. 1/2014 van de ACS-EU-Raad van ministers van 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Gelieve elke specificiteit te vermelden die een effect kan hebben op de deelnemingsregels (bijvoorbeeld geografische of thematische specificiteiten op korte of lange termijn).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Noot:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Er moeten minstens 30 kalenderdagen liggen tussen de bekendmaking van onderhavige vooraankondiging en de bekendmaking van de bijbehorende aankondiging van opdracht.</P><P>— In dit stadium mogen geen aanvragen of verzoeken om inlichtingen worden verzonden.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Uagadugu: Assistência técnica a longo prazo a favor do Banco de Desenvolvimento da África Ocidental (BDAO) na perspetiva do Plano de investimento exterior da União Europeia.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Uagadugu-Comissão da União Económica e Monetária da África Ocidental (UEMOA)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANÚNCIO DE PRÉ-INFORMAÇÃO RELATIVO AO SERVIÇO:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referência da publicação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Limitado</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nome do programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de apoio ao reforço das capacidades institucionais da UEMOA (PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Acordo de financiamento n.º ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>A Comissão da União Económica e Monetária da África Ocidental (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Uagadugu</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burquina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natureza do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Preços unitários</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O contrato visa a implementação de uma equipa de assistência técnica encarregada de apoiar o Banco de desenvolvimento da África Ocidental (BDAO) na implementação de reformas relacionadas com a auditoria dos pilares.</P><P>Com uma duração de 36 meses, a assistência técnica acompanhará a BDAO na implementação de reformas relacionadas com os sistemas, os controlos, as regras e os procedimentos de auditoria dos pilares para que esta se possa equipar com as normas reconhecidas a nível internacional e com os critérios fixados pela Comissão Europeia no domínio da gestão indireta dos fundos da União Europeia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orçamento indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O orçamento de apoio institucional a favor do BDAO é de 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista para a publicação do anúncio de concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informações suplementares</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Não aplicável</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base jurídica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anexo IV do Acordo de Parceria entre os Estados-Membros do Grupo de Estados de África, das Caraíbas e do Pacífico, por um lado, e a Comunidade Europeia e os seus Estados-Membros, por outro lado, assinado em Cotonu em 23.6.2000, tal como alterado no Luxemburgo, em 25.6.2005, e em Uagadugu, em 22.6.2010. É feita referência ao anexo IV revisto pela Decisão n.º 1/2014 do Conselho de Ministros ACP-UE de 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Indique qualquer particularidade que possa ter consequências nos métodos de participação (como geográfica ou temática ou longo/curto prazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observações:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Devem decorrer pelo menos 30 dias de calendário entre a publicação do presente anúncio de pré-informação e a publicação do anúncio de concurso correspondente,</P><P>— Não devem ser apresentadas candidaturas nem enviados pedidos de informação nesta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Teknisk långsiktig assistans till den Västafrikanska utvecklingsbanken (BOAD) med sikte på den Europeiska unionens externa investeringsplan</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Quagadougou-Västafrikanska ekonomiska och monetära unionens kommission (UEMOA - WAEMU)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÖRHANDSMEDDELANDE OM TJÄNSTEN</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publikationsreferens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Förfarande</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Selektivt</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Benämning på programmet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Stödprogram för institutionell kapacitetsuppbyggnad för WAEMU (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finansieringsavtal nr ROC//FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Västafrikanska ekonomiska och monetära unionens (WAEMU) kommission</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontraktstyp</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Enhetspriser</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivning av kontraktet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kontraktet har som syfte att upprätta ett tekniskt stödteam som ska bistå den Västafrikanska utvecklingsbanken (BOAD) i genomförandet av de reformer, som är förbundna med pelarnas revision.</P><P>Under en period på 36 månader ska det tekniska biståndet följa den Västafrikanska utvecklingsbanken i genomförandet av reformerna som hänger samman med systemen, kontrollerna, bestämmelserna och förfarandena för pelarnas revision, så att banken ska kunna utrustas med internationellt godkända normer och kriterier fastställda av den Europeiska kommissionen inom området för indirekt förvaltning av den Europeiska unionens medel.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerad budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Den institutionella stödbudgeten till BOAD är 1 250 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerat datum för publicering av upphandlingsmeddelandet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kompletterande information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ej tillämplig</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rättslig grund (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bilaga IV till partnerskapsavtalet mellan medlemmarna i gruppen av stater i Afrika, Västindien och Stillahavsområdet och Europeiska gemenskapen och dess medlemsstater, undertecknat i Cotonou 23.6.2000, ändrat i Luxemburg 25.6.2005 och i Ouagadougou 22.6.2010. Hänvisning görs till bilaga IV enligt ändring genom beslut 1/2014 av AVS–EU-ministerrådet av den 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Ange alla detaljer som kan påverka deltagandeförfarandet (såsom geografiska, tematiska eller på lång/kort sikt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>OBS:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>- Minst 30 kalenderdagar ska förflyta mellan publiceringen av detta förhandsmeddelande och publiceringen av meddelandet om upphandling.</P><P>- Ansökningar eller beställning av information ska inte skickas i detta skede.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Poskytnutí dlouhodobé technické pomoci Západoafrické rozvojové bance (BOAD) v rámci plánu vnějších investic EU.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou-Komise Západoafrické hospodářské a měnové unie (WAEMU)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>OZNÁMENÍ PŘEDBĚŽNÝCH INFORMACÍ O SLUŽBĚ:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenční číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užší</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Název programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program na podporu budování institucionálních kapacit WAEMU (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financování</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Dohoda o financování č. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veřejný zadavatel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komise Západoafrické hospodářské a měnové unie (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Povaha zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jednotkové ceny</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popis zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cílem zakázky je zřízení týmu technické pomoci na podporu Západoafrické rozvojové banky (BOAD) při provádění reforem týkajících se auditu pilířů.</P><P>Technická pomoc ve prospěch BOAD po dobu 36 měsíců v rámci provádění reforem souvisejících se systémy, kontrolami, pravidly a postupy auditu pilířů tak, aby tato banka mohla přijmout mezinárodní standardy a kritéria stanovená Evropskou komisí v oblasti nepřímého řízení fondů EU.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Směrný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozpočet na institucionální podporu BOAD činí 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zamýšlený termín zveřejnění oznámení o zakázce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Doplňující informace</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>nepoužije se</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právní základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Příloha IV k dohodě o partnerství mezi členy skupiny afrických, karibských a tichomořských států a Evropským společenstvím a jeho členskými státy podepsané v Cotonou dne 23.6.2000 a pozměněné v Lucemburku dne 25.6.2005 a v Ouagadougou dne 22.6.2010. Odkazujeme na přílohu IV pozměněnou rozhodnutím Rady ministrů AKT–EU 1/2014 ze dne 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Uveďte jakékoli zvláštnosti, které by mohly ovlivnit pravidla účasti (např. zeměpisná nebo tematická či dlouhodobá/krátkodobá).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Mezi zveřejněním těchto předběžných informací o zakázce a zveřejněním oznámení o zakázce musí uplynout nejméně 30 kalendářních dní,</P><P>— V této fázi nesmí být zasílány žádné přihlášky ani žádosti o informace.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Pikaajaline tehniline abi Lääne-Aafrika Arengupangale (BOAD) Euroopa Liidu välisinvesteeringute kava perspektiivis</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou, Lääne-Aafrika majandus- ja rahaliidu (West African Economic and Monetary Union (WAEMU)) komisjon</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>TEENUSE EELTEADE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaldamise viide</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menetlus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Piiratud</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmi nimetus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lääne-Aafrika majandus- ja rahaliidu institutsioonilise suutlikkuse parandamise toetamise programm (PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahastamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rahastamisleping nr ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Lääne-Aafrika majandus- ja rahaliidu (WAEMU) komisjon</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu laad</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ühikuhinnad</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lepingu eesmärk on luua tehnilise abi meeskond, mille ülesanne on toetada Lääne-Aafrika Arengupanka (Banque ouest africaine de développement (BOAD)) sammaste auditeerimisega seotud reformide elluviimisel.</P><P>36 kuu jooksul antakse Lääne-Aafrika Arengupangale (BOAD) tehnilist abi sammaste auditeerimise süsteemide, kontrollide, eeskirjade ja protseduuridega seotud reformide elluviimisel, et tagada standardite kasutuselevõtt, mis on rahvusvahelisel tasandil vastuvõetavad ja vastavad Euroopa Komisjoni poolt Euroopa Liidu rahaliste vahendite kaudse juhtimise valdkonnas kehtestatud kriteeriumidele.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kavandatav eelarve</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>BOADile antava institutsioonilise abi eelarve on 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hanketeate avaldamise ettenähtud kuupäev</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisateave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ei ole kohaldatav</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Õiguslik alus (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aafrika, Kariibi mere piirkonna ja Vaikse ookeani piirkonna riikide rühma ning Euroopa Ühenduse ja selle liikmesriikide vahel sõlmitud koostöölepingu (mis allkirjastati 23.6.2000 Cotonous ning mida muudeti 25.6.2005 Luxembourgis ja 22.6.2010 Ouagadougous) IV lisa. Siinkohal viidatakse IV lisale, nagu seda on muudetud AKV-ELi ministrite nõukogu 20.6.2014 otsusega 1/2014.</P><P>(1) Palun esitage kõik asjaolud, mis võivad mõjutada osalemistingimusi (geograafilised, valdkonna ja lühema/pikema kestuse tegurid).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Märkused:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Eelteate ja vastava hanketeate avaldamise vahele peab jääma vähemalt 30 kalendripäeva;</P><P>— Taotlusi ega teabenõudeid ei või selles etapis veel saata.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Hosszú távú szakmai segítségnyújtás a Nyugat-afrikai Fejlesztési Banknak az Európai Unió külső beruházási tervének kontextusában.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou – A Nyugat-afrikai Gazdasági és Monetáris Unió (UEMOA) bizottsága</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SZOLGÁLTATÁSNYÚJTÁSRA IRÁNYULÓ ELŐZETES TÁJÉKOZTATÓ HIRDETMÉNY:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A közzététel hivatkozási száma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Eljárás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Meghívásos</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A program címe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Az UEMOA intézményi felkészültségfejlesztési programja (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanszírozás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ROC/FED/2013/024-224. számú finanszírozási megállapodás</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>A Nyugat-afrikai Gazdasági és Monetáris Unió (UEMOA) bizottsága</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés típusa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Egységáras</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés meghatározása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A szerződés célkitűzése egy szakmai segítségnyújtási csapat létrehozása a Nyugat-afrikai Fejlesztési Bank támogatása céljából a pillérek ellenőrzésével kapcsolatos reformok megvalósítására irányulóan.</P><P>A szakmai segítségnyújtási csapat 36 hónapon át segíti a Nyugat-afrikai Fejlesztési Bankot a pillérek ellenőrzéséhez kapcsolódó rendszerekre, ellenőrzésekre, szabályokra és eljárásokra irányuló reformok megvalósításában, annak érdekében, hogy a bank megfeleljen a nemzetközi szinten elfogadott szabványoknak és az Európai Bizottság által az európai uniós finanszírozási alapok közvetett kezelésére vonatkozóan megadott kritériumoknak.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Várható költségvetés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A Nyugat-afrikai Fejlesztési Bank intézményi támogatásának költségvetése 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlattételi felhívás közzétételének tervezett időpontja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>További információk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>n.a.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Jogalap (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Az egyrészt az afrikai, karibi és csendes-óceáni államok csoportjának tagjai, másrészt az Európai Közösség, illetve annak tagállamai között létrejött partnerségi megállapodás IV. melléklete, amelyet a 23.6.2000 dátumú napon Cotonouban írtak alá, és a 25.6.2005 dátumú napon Luxembourgban, valamint a 22.6.2010 dátumú napon Ouagadougouban módosítottak. Hivatkozással az AKCS-EU Miniszteri Tanácsának 20.6.2014 dátumú 1/2014 határozatával felülvizsgált IV. mellékletre.</P><P>(1) Kérjük, jelezzen minden olyan sajátosságot, amely hatással lehet a részvétel feltételeire (pl. földrajzi, tematikus vagy hosszú/rövid távú sajátosság).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Megjegyzések:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— A jelen előzetes összesített hirdetmény megjelenése és a vonatkozó ajánlati felhívás közzététele között legalább 30 naptári napnak kell eltelnie,</P><P>— Ebben a szakaszban jelentkezés benyújtásának, illetve információkérésnek nincs helye.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Uagadugu: Ilgalaikė techninė pagalba, teikiama Vakarų Afrikos plėtros bankui (VAPB), atsižvelgiant į Europos Sąjungos išorės investicijų planą.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vagadugu – Vakarų Afrikos ekonominės ir pinigų sąjungos (VAEPS) komisija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IŠANKSTINIS INFORMACINIS SKELBIMAS APIE PASLAUGAS:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nuoroda į publikaciją</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ribota</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programos pavadinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Paramos programa VAEPS instituciniams gebėjimams stiprinti (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles (PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansavimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finansavimo susitarimas Nr. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Perkančioji organizacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Vakarų Afrikos ekonominės ir pinigų sąjungos (VAEPS) komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Uagadugu</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Fasas.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties pobūdis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Vieneto kainos</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties apibūdinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sutarties tikslas – įsteigti techninės pagalbos komandą, skirtą Vakarų Afrikos plėtros bankui (VAPB) remti įgyvendinant reformas, susijusias su audito pakopomis.</P><P>36 mėnesių trukmės techninė pagalba lydės VAPB įgyvendinant reformas, susijusias su audito pakopų sistemomis, kontrole, taisyklėmis ir procedūromis, kad ji galėtų atitikti priimtinus standartus tarptautiniu lygiu ir Europos Komisijos netiesioginio Europos Sąjungos lėšų valdymo srityje nustatytus kriterijus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Preliminarus biudžetas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Institucinės paramos VAPB biudžetas yra 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatyta skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo data</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildoma informacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>NA</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teisinis pagrindas (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Partnerystės susitarimo tarp Afrikos, Karibų jūros ir Ramiojo vandenyno valstybių grupės narių iš vienos pusės bei Europos Bendrijos ir jos valstybių narių iš kitos pusės, pasirašyto Kotonu 23.6.2000, su pakeitimais, padarytais 25.6.2005 Liuksemburge ir 22.6.2010 Vagadugu, IV priedas. Pateikiama nuoroda į IV priedą, iš dalies pakeistą 20.6.2014 AKR ir ES Ministrų Tarybos sprendimu Nr. 1/2014.</P><P>(1) Nurodykite bet kokį požymį, galintį turėti įtakos dalyvavimo tvarkai (pvz., geografinį ar teminį, ilguoju ar trumpuoju laikotarpiu).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Pastabos.</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Nuo šio išankstinio informacinio skelbimo publikavimo ir atitinkamo kvietimo pateikti pasiūlymus paskelbimo turi praeiti ne mažiau kaip 30 kalendorinių dienų,</P><P>— Šiuo etapu siųsti paraiškų ar kreiptis dėl informacijos negalima.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Vagadugu: Ilgtermiņa tehniskā palīdzība Rietumāfrikas attīstības bankai (WADB), ņemot vērā Eiropas Savienības ārējo investīciju plānu</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vagadugu – Rietumāfrikas Ekonomiskās un monetārās savienības (Union économique et monétaire ouest-africaine – UEMOA) komisija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IEPRIEKŠĒJS INFORMATĪVS PAZIŅOJUMS PAR PAKALPOJUMU LĪGUMU</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsauce uz publikāciju</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Slēgta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmas nosaukums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>UEMOA institucionālo spēju veidošanas atbalsta programma (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansējums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finansēšanas līgums Nr. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Rietumāfrikas Ekonomiskās un monetārās savienības (UEMOA) komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Vagadugu</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkinafaso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma veids</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Vienību cenas līgums</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Līguma mērķis ir izveidot tehniskās palīdzības grupu, kas Rietumāfrikas attīstības bankai (WADB) sniegs atbalstu ar pīlāru revīzijas saistītu reformu īstenošanā.</P><P>Tehniskā palīdzība WADB tiks sniegta 36 mēnešu laikposmā ar pīlāru revīzijas sistēmām, kontroli, noteikumiem un procedūrām saistītu reformu īstenošanā, lai tā varētu piemērot starptautiskajā līmenī noteiktos standartus un Eiropas Komisijas izvirzītos kritērijus Eiropas Savienības līdzekļu netiešas pārvaldības jomā.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Provizoriskais budžets</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rietumāfrikas attīstības bankai (WADB) paredzēta institucionālā atbalsta budžets ir 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plānotais paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildu informācija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nav</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tiesiskais pamats (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IV pielikums Partnerattiecību nolīgumam starp Āfrikas, Karību jūras reģiona un Klusā okeāna valstu grupas locekļiem, no vienas puses, un Eiropas Kopienu un tās dalībvalstīm, no otras puses, kas parakstīts Kotonū 2000. gada 23. jūnijā, kā tas grozīts Luksemburgā 2005. gada 25. jūnijā un kā tas grozīts Vagadugu 2010. gada 22. jūnijā. Atsauce sniegta uz IV pielikumu, kas pārskatīts ar ĀKK un ES Ministru padomes Lēmumu Nr. 1/2014 (2014. gada 20. jūnijs).</P><P>(1) Lūdzam norādīt visus specifiskos iemeslus (piemēram, ģeogrāfiskus, tematiskus, īstermiņa vai ilgtermiņa), kas var ietekmēt dalības noteikumus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Piezīmes</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Starp šā iepriekšējā informatīvā paziņojuma un attiecīgā paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datumiem ir jāpaiet vismaz 30 kalendārajām dienām.</P><P>— Šajā posmā nekādus pieteikumus vai informācijas pieprasījumus nesūtīt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Għajnuna teknika fit-tul fi ħdan il-Bank ta' Żvilupp tal-Afrika tal-Punent (BOAD) fid-dawl tal-Pjan ta' Investiment Estern tal-Unjoni Ewropea.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou - il-Kummissjoni tal-Unjoni Ekonomika u Monetarja tal-Afrika tal-Punent (UEMOA)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVIŻ TA' TAGĦRIF MINN QABEL DWAR SERVIZZ:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-proċedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-isem tal-programm</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>il-programm ta' appoġġ għat-trawwim tal-ħiliet istituzzjonali tal-UEMOA (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-iffinanzjar</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-ftehim tal-iffinanzjar Nru ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>il-Kummissjoni tal-Unjoni Ekonomika u Monetarja tal-Afrika tal-Punent (UEMOA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-tip ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-prezz għal kull unità</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-deskrizzjoni tal-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-għan tal-kuntratt huwa l-provvista ta' għajnuna teknika responsabbli li tappoġġja l-Bank tal-Iżvilupp għall-Afrika tal-Punent (BOAD) fl-implimentazzjoni tar-riformi marbuta mal-awditjar tal-pilastri.</P><P>Fi żmien 36 xahar, l-għajnuna teknika se takkumpanja lill-BOAD fl-implimentazzjoni tar-riformi marbuta mas-sistemi, mal-kontrolli, mar-regoli u mal-proċeduri tal-awditjar tal-pilastri, sabiex ikunu jistgħu jużaw standards permessi fil-livell internazzjonali, u mal-kriterji stabbiliti mill-Kummissjoni Ewropea fil-qasam tal-immaniġġjar indirett tal-fondi tal-Unjoni Ewropea.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-baġit indikattiv</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-baġit tal-appoġġ istituzzjonali lill-BOAD huwa ta' 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-data għall-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif addizzjonali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mhux applikabbli</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-bażi legali (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-Anness IV tal-Ftehim ta' Sħubija bejn il-membri tal-Grupp tal-Istati Afrikani, tal-Karibew u l-Paċifiku u l-Komunità Ewropea u l-Istati Membri tagħha, iffirmat f'Cotonou nhar it-23.6.2000, kif emendat fil-Lussemburgu nhar il-25.6.2005 u f'Ouagadougou nhar it-22.6.2010. Qed issir referenza għall-Anness IV kif irrivedut mid-Deċiżjoni Nru 1/2014 tal-Kunsill tal-Ministri tal-AKP-UE tal-20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Jekk jogħġbok indika kwalunkwe speċifiċità li jista' jkollha effett fuq il-metodi ta' kif wieħed jieħu sehem (speċifiċità ġeografika jew tematika u fi żmien qasir/twil).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Kummenti:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Iridu jgħaddu mill-inqas 30 jum kalendarji bejn il-pubblikazzjoni ta' dan l-avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel u l-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż dwar kuntratt li għandu x'jaqsam miegħu,</P><P>— M'għandhomx jintbagħtu applikazzjonijiet jew talbiet għal tagħrif f'dan l-istadju.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Wagadugu: Długoterminowa pomoc techniczna na rzecz Zachodnioafrykańskiego Banku Rozwoju (BOAD) w perspektywie planu inwestycji zewnętrznych Unii Europejskiej.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Wagadugu — Komisja Zachodnioafrykańskiej Unii Gospodarczej i Walutowej (WAEMU)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>WSTĘPNE OGŁOSZENIE INFORMACYJNE DOTYCZĄCE ZAMÓWIENIA NA USŁUGI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numer referencyjny publikacji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograniczona</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nazwa programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program wsparcia wzmocnienia zdolności instytucjonalnych WAEMU.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansowanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Porozumienie finansowe nr ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zamawiający</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komisja Zachodnioafrykańskiej Unii Gospodarczej i Walutowej (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Wagadugu</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rodzaj zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ceny jednostkowe</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Celem zamówienia jest stworzenie zespołu pomocy technicznej odpowiedzialnej za wsparcie Zachodnioafrykańskiego Banku Rozwoju (Banque Ouest-Africaine de Developpement – BOAD) we wdrażaniu reform związanych z audytem filarów.</P><P>W ciągu 36 miesięcy pomoc techniczna będzie towarzyszyć Zachodnioafrykańskiemu Bankowi Rozwoju we wdrażaniu reform dotyczących systemu, kontroli, zasad i procedur związanych z audytem filarów, tak aby mógł on dostosować normy do wymogów międzynarodowych i kryteriów ustalonych przez Komisję Europejską w dziedzinie pośredniego zarządzania funduszami Unii Europejskiej.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orientacyjny budżet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Wartość budżetu na pomoc instytucjonalną na rzecz Zachodnioafrykańskiego Banku Rozwoju wynosi 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Przewidywana data publikacji ogłoszenia o zamówieniu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatkowe informacje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>nie dotyczy</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Podstawa prawna (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Załącznik IV do Umowy o partnerstwie między członkami grupy państw Afryki, Karaibów i Pacyfiku z jednej strony a Wspólnotą Europejską i jej państwami członkowskimi z drugiej strony, podpisana w Kotonu dnia 23.6.2000, zmieniona w Luksemburgu dnia 25.6.2005 i w Wagadugu dnia 22.6.2010. Odniesienie dotyczy załącznika IV zmienionego na mocy decyzji nr 1/2014 Rady Ministrów AKP–UE z dnia 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Proszę wskazać jakąkolwiek szczególną okoliczność, która mogłaby mieć wpływ na warunki uczestnictwa (taką jak geograficzna lub tematyczna lub długo-/krótkoterminowa).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Uwagi:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Między publikacją niniejszego wstępnego ogłoszenia informacyjnego a publikacją ogłoszenia o zamówieniu musi upłynąć co najmniej 30 dni kalendarzowych.</P><P>Na obecnym etapie nie należy przesyłać wniosków ani zapytań o dodatkowe informacje.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Dlhodobá odborná pomoc pre Západoafrickú rozvojovú banku (BOAD) v súvislosti s vonkajším investičným plánom Európskej únie.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou – Komisia Západoafrickej hospodárskej a menovej únie (WAEMU)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDBEŽNÉ OZNÁMENIE O VEREJNOM OBSTARÁVANÍ SLUŽIEB:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčné číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Konanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užšia súťaž</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Názov programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program na podporu budovania inštitucionálnych kapacít WAEMU (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zdroj financovania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finančná dohoda č. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verejný obstarávateľ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komisia Západoafrickej hospodárskej a menovej únie (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Charakter verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jednotkové ceny</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cieľom obstarávania je zriadiť tím odbornej pomoci, ktorý bude pomáhať Západoafrickej rozvojovej banke (Banque ouest africaine de développement – BOAD) pri vykonávaní reforiem súvisiacich s auditom pilierov.</P><P>Odborná pomoc bude trvať 36 mesiacov a bude sa týkať pomoci pre BOAD pri vykonávaní reforiem súvisiacich so systémami, kontrolami, pravidlami a postupmi auditu pilierov, aby mohla zaviesť prijaté normy na medzinárodnej úrovni, a s kritériami stanovenými Európskou komisiou v oblasti nepriameho riadenia finančných prostriedkov Európskej únie.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predbežný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozpočet na inštitucionálnu podporu pre BOAD je 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predpokladaný dátum zverejnenia oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatočné informácie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Neuplatniteľné</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právny základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Príloha IV k Dohode o partnerstve medzi členmi skupiny afrických, karibských a tichomorských štátov na jednej strane a Európskym spoločenstvom a jeho členskými štátmi na strane druhej, podpísanej v Cotonou 23.6.2000, zmenenej v Luxemburgu 25.6.2005 a v Ouagadougou 22.6.2010. Uvádza sa odkaz na prílohu IV, v znení zmien rozhodnutia Rady ministrov krajín AKT – EÚ č. 1/2014 z 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Uveďte všetky špecifiká, ktoré by mohli mať vplyv na podmienky účasti (napríklad geografické, tematické alebo dlhodobé/krátkodobé).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— medzi zverejnením tohto predbežného oznámenia a zodpovedajúceho oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania musí uplynúť najmenej 30 kalendárnych dní,</P><P>— v tejto fáze sa nemajú zasielať žiadne prihlášky ani žiadosti o ďalšie informácie.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Zagotavljanje dolgoročne tehnične pomoči Zahodnoafriški razvojni banki (WADB) z vidika načrta za zunanje naložbe Evropske unije</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou – Komisija Zahodnoafriške ekonomske in monetarne unije (WAEMU)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDHODNO INFORMATIVNO OBVESTILO O NAROČILU STORITEV</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčna številka dokumenta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postopek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Omejeni</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Podporni program za krepitev institucionalnih zmogljivosti WAEMU (PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sporazum o financiranju št. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komisija Zahodnoafriške ekonomske in monetarne unije (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vrsta naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cena na enoto</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Namen naročila je vzpostavitev ekipe tehnične pomoči, ki bo Zahodnoafriški razvojni banki (WADB) zagotavljala podporo pri izvajanju reform, povezanih z revizijo stebrnih področij.</P><P>V obdobju 36 mesecev bo tehnična pomoč podpirala WADB pri izvajanju reform, povezanih s sistemi, pregledi, pravili in postopki revizije stebrnih področij, da bi lahko dosegla standarde, sprejete na mednarodni ravni, in izpolnjevala merila Evropske komisije na področju posrednega upravljanja sredstev Evropske unije.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Okvirni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proračun za institucionalno podporo WADB znaša 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predvideni datum objave obvestila o naročilu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ni navedeno</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravna podlaga (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Priloga IV k Sporazumu o partnerstvu med članicami skupine afriških, karibskih in pacifiških držav na eni strani ter Evropsko skupnostjo in njenimi državami članicami na drugi, podpisanemu v Cotonouju dne 23.6.2000, kakor je bil spremenjen v Luxembourgu dne 25.6.2005 in v Ouagadougouju dne 22.6.2010. Sklic se nanaša na Prilogo IV, kakor je bila revidirana s Sklepom št. 1/2014 Sveta ministrov AKP-EU z dne 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Prosimo, navedite kakršne koli posebnosti, ki bi lahko vplivale na pravila za sodelovanje (na primer geografske, tematske ali dolgo-/kratkoročne posebnosti).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opombe:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Med objavo tega predhodnega informativnega obvestila in objavo pripadajočega obvestila o naročilu mora preteči najmanj 30 koledarskih dni,</P><P>— v tej fazi ne pošiljajte prijav ali zahtevkov za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Cúnamh teicniúil fadtéarmach le soláthar do Bhanc Forbraíochta na hAfraice Thiar (WADB - West African Development Bank) i gcomhthéacs Phlean Infheistíochta Seachtrach an Aontais Eorpaigh.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou — Coimisiún Aontas Eacnamaíoch agus Airgeadaíochta na hAfraice Thiar (WAEMU)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÓGRA RÉAMHAISNÉISE MAIDIR LEIS AN tSEIRBHÍS:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nós imeachta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Teoranta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ainm an chláir</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Clár tacaíochta um fhorbairt cumais institiúidigh WAEMU (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Maoiniú</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Comhaontú maoinithe Uimh. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás conarthach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Coimisiún Aontas Eacnamaíoch agus Airgeadaíochta na hAfraice Thiar (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Buircíne Fasó.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cineál an chonartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Praghas aonaid</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ar an gconradh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Leis an gconradh seo cumhdaítear foireann um chúnamh teicniúil a bhunú d’fhonn tacú le Banc Forbraíochta na hAfraice Thiar maidir le forfheidhmiú athchóirithe a bhaineann le hiniúchadh na gcolún.</P><P>Tacóidh cúnamh teicniúil 36 mí leis an WADB chun athchóirithe a chur i bhfeidhm i ndáil le córais, rialuithe, rialacha agus nósanna imeachta d’iniúchadh na gcolún chun é féin a threalmhú le caighdeáin inghlactha idirnáisiúnta agus le critéir bhunaithe ag an gCoimisiún Eorpach i limistéar bhainistiú indíreach chistí an AE.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buiséad táscach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Is é 1 250 000 EUR an buiséad le haghaidh tacaíochta institiúidí don WADB.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>An dáta atá socraithe d'fhoilsiú an fhógra conartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis bhreise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ní bhaineann le hábhar</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bunús dlí (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Iarscríbhinn IV leis an gComhaontú Comhpháirtíochta idir comhaltaí Ghrúpa Stát na hAfraice, Mhuir Chairib agus an Aigéin Chiúin de pháirt, agus an Comhphobal Eorpach agus a Bhallstáit, den pháirt eile, arna shíniú in Cotonou an 23.6.2000 mar a leasaíodh i Lucsamburg an 25.6.2005 agus in Ouagadougou an 22.6.2010. Déantar tagairt d'Iarscríbhinn IV arna hathbhreithniú le Cinneadh 1/2014 ó Chomhairle Airí ACC-AE an 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Cuir aon sainiúlacht in iúl a d’fhéadfadh tionchar a imirt ar rialacha na rannpháirtíochta (e.g. sainiúlacht gheografach, sainiúlacht ghearrthréimhseach nó fhadtréimhseach).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Nótaí:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Ní foláir nó go mbeidh 30 lá féilire ar a laghad idir foilsiú an fhógra réamhaisnéise agus foilsiú an fhógra conartha chomhfhreagraigh,</P><P>— Níor cheart aon iarratais ná iarrataí ar fhaisnéis a sheoladh faoi láthair.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Уагадугу: Дългосрочната техническа помощ да бъде предоставена от Банката за развитие на Западна Африка (BOAD) в контекста на плана за външна инвестиция на Европейския съюз.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Уагадугу – Комисия на Западноафриканския икономически и валутен съюз (ЗАИВС)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ОБЯВЛЕНИЕ ЗА ПРЕДВАРИТЕЛНА ИНФОРМАЦИЯ ОТНОСНО УСЛУГАТА</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Референтен номер на публикация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Процедура</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ограничена</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Наименование на програмата</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Програма за подпомагане на създаването на институционални възможности на ЗАИВС (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Финансиране</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Споразумение за финансиране № ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Комисия на Западноафриканския икономически и валутен съюз (ЗАИВС)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Уагадугу</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Буркина Фасо.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Вид на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Единични цени</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Описание на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Договорът има за цел да създаде екип за техническа помощ в подкрепа на Банката за развитие на Западна Африка (BOAD) при изпълнението на реформите, свързани с одита на стълбовете.</P><P>36-месечната техническа помощ ще съпътства BOAD при изпълнението на реформите, свързани със системите, контрола, правилата и процедурите на одита на стълбовете, така че да може да приеме приетите стандарти на международно ниво и критериите, определени от Европейската комисия в областта на непрякото управление на средствата от Европейския съюз.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Индикативен бюджет</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Бюджетът за институционална подкрепа на BOAD е 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Планирана дата на публикуване на обявлението за поръчка</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018 г.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Допълнителна информация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Няма</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Правно основание (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Приложение IV към Споразумението за партньорство между членовете на Групата на държавите от Африка, Карибите и Тихоокеанския басейн и Европейската общност и нейните държави-членки, подписано в Котону на 23.6.2000 г., изменено в Люксембург на 25.6.2005 г. и в Уагадугу на 22.6.2010 г. Направена е препратка към приложение IV, ревизирано с Решение № 1/2014 на Съвета на министрите АКТБ-ЕС от 20.6.2014 г.</P><P>(1) Моля да посочите всяка особеност, която може да има последици за условията за участие (географска или тематична или кратко/дългосрочна).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Забележки:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Между публикуването на това обявление за предварителна информация и публикуването на обявлението за поръчка трябва да изминат поне 30 календарни дни,</P><P>— На този етап не трябва да се изпращат молби или искания за информация.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Asistența tehnică pe termen lung care urmează să fie acordată băncii de dezvoltare din Africa de Vest în perspectiva Planului de investiții externe al Uniunii europene.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou-Comisia Uniunii economice și monetare vest-africane (UEMA)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNȚ DE INTENȚIE PRIVIND UN CONTRACT DE ACHIZIȚII PUBLICE DE SERVICII:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referința publicației</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedură</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restrânsă</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titlul programului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programul de susținere a consolidării capacităților instituționale ale UEMA (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanțare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Acordul de finanțare nr. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea contractantă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Comisia Uniunii economice și monetare vest-africane (UEMA)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prețuri unitare</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contractul vizează înființarea unei echipe de asistență tehnică care să sprijine Banca de Dezvoltare a Africii de Vest pentru implementarea reformelor privind auditul pilonilor.</P><P>Având o durată de 36 de luni, asistența tehnică va asista Banca de Dezvoltare a Africii de Vest în implementarea reformelor privind sistemele, controalele, regulile și procedurile de audit a pilonilor, astfel încât să poată adopta standardele acceptate la nivel internațional și criteriile stabilite de către Comisia Europeană în domeniul gestionării indirecte a fondurilor Uniunii Europene.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buget indicativ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bugetul pentru sprijinul instituțional al BOAD este de 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevăzută pentru publicarea anunțului de participare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informații suplimentare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>NA</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Temeiul juridic (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anexa IV la Acordul de parteneriat între membrii grupului statelor din Africa, zona Caraibilor și Pacific și Comunitatea Europeană și statele membre ale acesteia, semnat la Cotonou, la 23.6.2000, astfel cum a fost modificat la Luxemburg, la 25.6.2005, și la Ouagadougou, la 22.6.2010. Se face referire la anexa IV, astfel cum a fost revizuită prin Decizia nr. 1/2014 a Consiliului de miniștri ACP-UE din 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Indicați orice particularitate care ar putea avea consecințe asupra modalităților de participare (de ex, de ordin geografic sau tematic, sau termeni pe termen scurt/lung).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observații:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Trebuie respectată o perioadă de cel puțin 30 de zile calendaristice între publicarea prezentului anunț de intenție și publicarea anunțului de participare corespunzător,</P><P>În această etapă nu trebuie trimise candidaturi sau cereri de informații.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BF-Ouagadougou: Pružanje dugoročne tehnički pomoći Zapadnoafričkoj razvojnoj banci (WADB) u okviru plana vanjskog ulaganja Europske unije.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ouagadougou — Komisija Zapadnoafričke ekonomske i monetarne unije (WAEMU)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PRETHODNA INFORMACIJSKA OBAVIJEST O USLUGAMA:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uputa na objavu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postupak</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograničeni</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naziv programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Program podrške jačanju institucijske sposobnosti WAEMU-a (Programme d'appui au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles – PARCI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sporazum o financiranju br. ROC/FED/2013/024-224</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komisija Zapadnoafričke ekonomske i monetarne unije (WAEMU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ouagadougou</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Burkina Faso.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Priroda ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jedinične cijene</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cilj je ugovora uspostavljanje tima za tehničku pomoć za podršku Zapadnoafričkoj razvojnoj banci (WADB) u provedbi reformi povezanih s revizijom stupova.</P><P>36-mjesečna tehnička pomoć pratit će WADB u provedbi reformi vezanih za sustave, kontrole, pravila i postupke revizije stupova kako bi mogla usvojiti prihvaćene norme na međunarodnoj razini i prema fiksnim kriterijima koje je postavila Europska komisija u području neizravnog upravljanja sredstvima Europske unije.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indikativni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proračun je institucionalne podrške WADBU-u 1 250 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predviđeni datum objave poziva na nadmetanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>5.6.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne pojedinosti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nije navedeno</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravni temelj (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prilog IV. Sporazumu o partnerstvu između članica afričke, karipske i pacifičke skupine država i Europske zajednice i njezinih država članica, potpisan u Cotonouu 23.6.2000., kako je izmijenjen u Luxembourgu 25.6.2005. i u Ouagadougouu 22.6.2010. Uputa se daje na Prilog IV. koji je revidiran Odlukom br. 1/2014 Vijeća ministara AKP-a i EU-a od 20.6.2014.</P><P>(1) Navedite sve pojedinosti koje bi mogle utjecati na oblike sudjelovanja (geografske ili tematske, kratkoročne ili dugoročne).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Napomene:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>— Između objave ove prethodne informacijske obavijesti i objave odgovarajućeg poziva na nadmetanje mora proći najmanje 30 kalendarskih dana,</P><P>— U toj se fazi ne smiju slati prijave ili zahtjevi za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>