<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="181512-2018"
            EDITION="2018081">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-185326-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180525</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>81</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180426</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 081-181512</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:181512-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.nhshighland.scot.nhs.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>www.publictendersscotland.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71000000">Architectural, construction, engineering and inspection services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKM6">Highlands and Islands</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKM62">Inverness &amp; Nairn and Moray, Badenoch &amp; Strathspey</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">434436</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180424</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180525 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="H">Health</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Архитектурни, строителни, инженерни и инспекционни услуги</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Architektonické, stavební, technické a inspekční služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Arkitekt-, konstruktions-, ingeniør- og inspektionsvirksomhed</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dienstleistungen von Architektur-, Konstruktions- und Ingenieurbüros und Prüfstellen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες αρχιτεκτονικής, κατασκευαστικών έργων, έργων πολιτικού μηχανικού και επίβλεψης</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Architectural, construction, engineering and inspection services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de arquitectura, construcción, ingeniería e inspección</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Arhitektuuri-, ehitus-, inseneri- ja ehitusjärelevalveteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Arkkitehti-, rakennus-, insinööri- ja tarkastuspalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services d'architecture, services de construction, services d'ingénierie et services d'inspection</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Architectural, construction, engineering and inspection services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Arhitektonske, građevne, tehničke i inspekcije usluge</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Építészeti, építési, mérnöki és vizsgálati szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi architettonici, di costruzione, ingegneria e ispezione</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Architektūros, statybų, inžinerijos ir inspektavimo paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Arhitektūras, būvniecības, inženiertehniskie un pārbaudes pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' perizja, kostruzzjoni, inġinerija u spezzjoni</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dienstverlening op het gebied van architectuur, bouwkunde, civiele techniek en inspectie</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi architektoniczne, budowlane, inżynieryjne i kontrolne</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de arquitectura, construção, engenharia e inspecção</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de arhitectură, de construcţii, de inginerie şi de inspecţie</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Architektonické, stavebné, inžinierske a inšpekčné služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Arhitekturne, gradbeniške, inženirske in inšpekcijske storitve</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Inverness</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Arkitekt-, bygg-, ingenjörs- och besiktningstjänster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">NHS Highland</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>4a040309-748a-49d2-8bf5-a3b2af7126c3</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>NHS Highland</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Assynt House, Beechwood Park</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Inverness</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>IV2 3BW</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1463706274</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>high-uhb.tenders@nhs.net</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM62"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.nhshighland.scot.nhs.uk</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/search/Search_AuthProfile.aspx?ID=AA00302</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CENTRAL_PURCHASING/>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>www.publictendersscotland.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>www.publictendersscotland.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="MINISTRY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="HEALTH"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>HH064-18 Periodic Electrical Inspection, Testing and Reporting</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="71000000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The NHS Highland Estate Management Department currently look after a large number of properties in the region, varying in size from small Health Care units to large hospitals. Part of the team’s responsibilities includes the maintenance and upkeep of the electrical infrastructure within each of these properties.</P>
               <P>To ensure the electrical infrastructure is maintained in an efficient and safe condition, to protect the people within the properties from possible electric shock and also the facility itself from damage due to faults within the installation, it is necessary to carry out an Electrical Installation Condition Report of the electrical installation, in accordance with the current version of BS7671 IET Wiring Regulations.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">434436</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM6"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>The NHS Highland Estate Management Department currently look after a large number of properties in the region, varying in size from small Health Care units to large hospitals.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>To ensure the electrical infrastructure is maintained in an efficient and safe condition, to protect the people within the properties from possible electric shock and also the facility itself from damage due to faults within the installation, it is necessary to carry out an Electrical Installation Condition Report of the electrical installation, in accordance with the current version of BS7671 IET Wiring Regulations.</P>
                  <P>The Electrical Installation Condition Report will be produced in line with guidance provided within BS7671 IET Wiring Regulations.</P>
                  <P>It is intended to complete the Electrical inspection and testing throughout all NHS Highland properties, in line with a ‘rolling program’, but the technical requirements associated with the works will be common throughout and are defined within the tender documents.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Quality</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>70</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>30</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">60</DURATION>
               <RENEWAL/>
               <RENEWAL_DESCR>
                  <P>Up to a further 12 months.</P>
               </RENEWAL_DESCR>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>The Authority shall treat as ineligible and shall not select any bidder on any of the grounds set out in 1.18 - 1.71 of the ESPD. The bidder uses the ESPD as a self-declaration that they have not breached any of the mandatory and discretionary exclusion grounds, or satisfactory self-cleansing measures and that they meet the relevant selection criteria.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>Award shall be subject to a satisfactory financial evaluation having been carried out by NHS Highland based on their Economic and Financial Standing ESPD response and credit check.</P>
               <P>In addition where a supplier is recommended for award, they will also be requested to provide one of the following for financial evaluation purposes:</P>
               <P>(a) A copy of your audited accounts or equivalent for the most recent 2 years, along with details of any significant changes since the last year end. An additional question has been provided below to enable you to upload your second set of accounts.</P>
               <P>Or.</P>
               <P>(b) A statement of your organisation's turnover; profit and cash flow for the most recent full year of trading or where a full year trading has not been completed the same information for the period applicable. NOTE if this information is not available in an audited format please provide an end of period balance sheet or make the response specified in option (c) below.</P>
               <P>Or.</P>
               <P>(c) If you are unable to provide the information requested above, please provide additional information and documentation that will give the Authority the assurance that you are capable of carrying out any subsequent awarded contract. For example, a statement of your organisation's cash flow forecast for the current year and a letter from your bank outlining the current cash and credit position or other alternative means of demonstrating financial standing.</P>
               <P>For example provide a statement explaining why the organisation was not in net profit after tax in either of the reported financial years.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>It is a requirement of this contract that bidders hold, or can commit to obtain prior to the commencement of any subsequently awarded contract, the types and levels of insurance indicated below:</P>
               <P>Employer’s (Compulsory) Liability Insurance = 5 000 000 GBP</P>
               <P>Public Liability Insurance = 5 000 000 GBP</P>
               <P>http://www.hse.gov.uk/pubns/hse40.pdf</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>Bidders will be required to provide examples that demonstrate that they have the relevant experience to deliver the services/supplies as described in II.2.4 of this Contract Notice.</P>
               <P>Bidders will be required to confirm details of the technicians or technical bodies who they can call upon, demonstrating their suitability and experience.</P>
               <P>Bidders will be required to confirm that they have (or have access to) the relevant supply chain management and tracking systems used by them to deliver the types of requirements detailed in II.2.4 in the OJEU Contract Notice or the relevant section of the Site Notice.</P>
               <P>Bidders will be required to demonstrate that they have (or have access to) the relevant tools, plant or technical equipment to deliver the types of requirements detailed in II.2.4 in this Contract Notice.</P>
               <P>Bidders will be required to confirm that they will employ environmental management measures that meet the following requirements:</P>
               <P>The Bidder must hold a UKAS (or equivalent) accredited independent third party certificate of compliance with BS EN ISO 14001 (or equivalent) or a valid EMAS (or equivalent) certificate, or documented policies and procedures of the appropriate level.</P>
               <P>Bidders will be required to confirm their average annual manpower for the last three years.</P>
               <P>Bidders will be required to confirm their and the number of managerial staff for the last three years.</P>
               <P>Bidders will be required to confirm whether they intend to subcontract and, if so, for what proportion of the contract.</P>
               <P>Bidders will be required to confirm that they have the required quality control institute certificates (or from agencies of recognised competence) confirming that products meet the following technical specifications or standards:</P>
               <P>The bidder must hold a UKAS (or equivalent) accredited independent third party certificate of compliance in accordance with BS EN ISO 9001 (or equivalent),or documented policies and procedures of the appropriate level.</P>
               <P>The bidder must hold a UKAS (or equivalent), accredited independent third party certificate of compliance in accordance with BS OHSAS 18001 (or equivalent) or have, within the last 12 months, successfully met the assessment requirements of a construction-related scheme in registered membership of the Safety Schemes in Procurement (SSIP) forum.</P>
               <P>Suppliers shall have an equality and diversity policy that complies with the Equality Act 2010 and explicitly refers to sexual orientation and provide details of any breaches of equality and human rights legislation.</P>
               <P>Suppliers shall have a business continuity and enable disaster recovery plan which shall include the scope, validation, risk treatment and leadership in these areas.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-05-25</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DATE_TENDER_VALID>2018-08-23</DATE_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-05-25</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <EORDERING/>
            <EINVOICING/>
            <EPAYMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The buyer is using PCS-Tender to conduct this ITT exercise. The Project code is 10339. For more information see: http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/info/InfoCentre.aspx?ID=2343</P>
               <P>(SC Ref:540401).</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>NHS Highland</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Assynt House, Beechwood Park</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Inverness</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>IV2 3BW</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1463706274</PHONE>
               <URL>http://www.nhshighland.scot.nhs.uk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-24</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
