<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="106991-2018" EDITION="2018049"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-104903-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180420</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>49</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180310</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 049-106991</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:106991-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UA"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="42000000">Industrial machinery</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="42160000">Boiler installations</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180306</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180420 11:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>BR505</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Ukraine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - Udskiftning af fjernvarmerør</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>die Ukraine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - Austausch von Fernwärmerohren</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Ukraine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Replacement of district heating pipes</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Ucrania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Sustitución de tuberías de calefacción urbana</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Ukraina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Kaukolämpöputkien uusiminen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Ukraine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Remplacement des conduites de chauffage du district</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Ουκρανία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - Αντικατάσταση των σωλήνων τηλεθέρμανσης</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Ucraina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - Sostituzione delle tubature di teleriscaldamento</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Oekraïne</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - Vervanging van leidingen voor stadsverwarming</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Ucrânia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Substituição das tubagens de aquecimento do distrito</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Ukraina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Byte av fjärrvärmeledningar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Ukrajina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Výměna potrubí dálkového vytápění</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Ukraina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Piirkonna küttetorude väljavahetamine</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Ukrajna</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Távfűtési hálózat csövek cseréje</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Ukraina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - Rajono šildymo vamzdžių keitimas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Ukraina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - Centralizētās siltumapgādes cauruļu nomaiņa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>l-Ukraina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - It-tibdil ta' pajpijiet ta' tisħin tad-distrett</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Ukraina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Wymiana instalacji ciepłowniczej</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Ukrajina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Výmena potrubí diaľkového vykurovania</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Ukrajina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Zamenjava cevi za daljinsko ogrevanje</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Úcráin, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Athsholáthar na bpíobán téimh cheantair</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Украйна</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - Подмяна на тръбопроводи за централно отопление</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Ucraina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Înlocuirea conductelor de încălzire urbană</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Ukrajina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ternopil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Zamjena cijevi sustava za gradsko grijanje</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - Udskiftning af fjernvarmerør (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - Austausch von Fernwärmerohren (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Replacement of district heating pipes (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Sustitución de tuberías de calefacción urbana (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Kaukolämpöputkien uusiminen (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Remplacement des conduites de chauffage du district (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - Αντικατάσταση των σωλήνων τηλεθέρμανσης (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - Sostituzione delle tubature di teleriscaldamento (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - Vervanging van leidingen voor stadsverwarming (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Substituição das tubagens de aquecimento do distrito (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Byte av fjärrvärmeledningar (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Výměna potrubí dálkového vytápění (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Piirkonna küttetorude väljavahetamine (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Távfűtési hálózat csövek cseréje (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - Rajono šildymo vamzdžių keitimas (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - Centralizētās siltumapgādes cauruļu nomaiņa (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - It-tibdil ta' pajpijiet ta' tisħin tad-distrett (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Wymiana instalacji ciepłowniczej (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Výmena potrubí diaľkového vykurovania (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Zamenjava cevi za daljinsko ogrevanje (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Athsholáthar na bpíobán téimh cheantair (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - Подмяна на тръбопроводи за централно отопление (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Înlocuirea conductelor de încălzire urbană (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Zamjena cijevi sustava za gradsko grijanje (UA-Ternopil)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Ternopil District Heating Modernisation Project</P><P>Country: Ukraine</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 9017-IFT-42524</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 06.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 20.4.2018 at 11:00 local (Kyiv) time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 4.9.2014 and latest updated on 6.3.2018.</P><P>The Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo” of the Ternopil City Council hereinafter referred to as “the Employer” intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Ternopil District Heating Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following Contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— replacement of district heating pipes (installation of pre-insulated pipes), approx. 1 100 m.</P><P>The Employer wishes to replace some sections of the existing district heating networks in some areas in the city of Ternopol with new pre-insulated pipelines. The quantity is estimated to be approximately 1 100 m of transmission pipeline plus fittings, valves and other accessories as per Part 2: Requirements. of the Tender Document. The pre-insulated pipes shall confirm to the requirements of the European standards EN 253 and EN 448 and of the Ukrainian standards DSTU 34-204-88-002-98 and DSTU B V.2.5-31:2007 or equivalent, while PUR foam insulation shall meet requirements of EN 253:2009 or equivalent.</P><P>A 2-pipe laying approach is envisaged. The sections to be rehabilitated include underground installation parts. The works are based on the Employer’s design. The Contractor is expected to provide supply of pipes and all necessary fittings and materials with subsequent installation, reconstruction of several existing heat chambers, inspection, testing, pre-commissioning and commissioning of the abovementioned pipelines.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a Contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>a) participation as contractor or management contractor in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods / technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, Employer’s Requirements;</P><P>(b) the Tenderer shall have successful experience as contractor or management contractor in the execution of at least 3 (three) completed contracts, each with a value of at least 1 000 000 EUR (one million), of a nature, complexity and completion schedule comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. In addition, the following specific experience: replacement of district heating transmission pipeline routes, including dismounting of old networks, with preinsulated pipes of at least 630 × 8/800 mm diameter and at least 1000 m length of 2-pipes laying completed during a single non-heating season;</P><P>(c) the audited balance sheets for the last 3 years shall be submitted and must demonstrate the soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position, showing long-term profitability. The Tenderer has long-term profitability with positive average annual operating profit in the last 3 years. Where necessary, the Purchaser will make inquiries with the tenderer's bankers,</P><P>(d) the average annual turnover over the last three years is not less than 3 000 000 EUR (five million) or equivalent,</P><P>(e) the Tenderer must have financial capability to meet plant, materials and works supply cash flow for the contract for a period of 3 (three) months, estimated as minimum 600 000 EUR (six hundred thousand) or equivalent taking into account the Tenderer’s commitments on other contracts,</P><P>(f) historical non-performance. A consistent history of awards against the Tenderer or any partner of a joint venture or consortium may result in rejection of the tender,</P><P>(g) the tenderer shall provide CVs of suitably qualified personnel and ensure their availability to fill the following positions:</P><P>— Project Manager (at least 15 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Design Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Construction Manager (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>— Commissioning and Tests Officer (at least 10 years of total experience and 5 years of experience in similar works),</P><P>(h) joint ventures or consortiums must satisfy the following minimum qualification requirements:</P><P>— the leading partner shall meet not less than 60 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— the other partners shall meet not less than 30 % of all the qualifying criteria for turnover and financial position specified above,</P><P>— Joint Ventures and Consortiums must satisfy collectively the criteria related to personnel, average annual turnover and financial position specified above;</P><P>(i) the Tenderer and its personnel shall have and be able to demonstrate to the Employer all the required construction licenses and permits stipulated by the legislation of Ukraine prior to contract signature. All such licenses and permits shall remain valid for the whole period of the contract.</P><P>The qualification requirements are further detailed in the Tender Documents.</P><P>The contract is planned to be completed in non-heating period 2018.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a nonrefundable fee of 200 EUR for foreign Tenderers and equivalent of the mentioned sum in Ukrainian Hryvnia (UAH) at National Bank rate of the payment day for Ukrainian tenderers. This fee includes expenses for duplication, delivery via registered express courier and communication services (VAT inclusive and exclusive of Bank commission and other fees, which shall be paid by the tenderer). The method of payment will be direct deposit to any of the specified account numbers for respective currency:</P><P>for payments in EUR:</P><P>Account # 26007000021432/978 (EUR)</P><P>Beneficiary’s bank: State Export Import Bank of Ukraine</P><P>Bank’s address: Kyiv, Ukraine</P><P>Swift: EXBS UA UXTER</P><P>Correspondent bank: Deutsche Bank AG</P><P>Frankfurt am Main, Germany</P><P>Swift: DEUTDEFF</P><P>Correspondent account: 9498767 10</P><P>Beneficiary: Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</P><P>For payments in UAH:</P><P>Комунальне підприємство теплових мереж “Тернопiльміськтеплокомуненерго” Тернопiльської міської ради</P><P>ЄДРПОУ 14034534</P><P>Р/р 26007000021432/980 АТ «Укрексімбанк»</P><P>Код банку (МФО): 322313</P><P>Адреса: 46008,м. Тернопiль, вул. Шептицького,21</P><P>It is necessary to state in the payment document:</P><P>— the name of the payer,</P><P>— name of the Beneficiary (Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”), and</P><P>— details of payment: TernopilDH/Pipelines/03.</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail. The tenderer can also collect the documents at the Employer’s office upon direct payment to the Purchaser’s cashier.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of 25 000 EUR (twenty five thousand) or equivalent in Ukrainian Hryvnia at the rate of the National Bank of Ukraine on the date of the Tender Security issue and must be delivered to the address below on or before 11:00 am, 20.4.2018, when they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 11:00 am on 20.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP and R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Contact person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Tetyana Sahat</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Deputy Director, Purchasing Entity: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Communal Enterprise “Ternopilmiskteplokomunenergo”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> , Address 16, Franka Street,</BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ternopil</TOWN><BLK_BTX> 46001, UKRAINE, Tel: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+380 50 339 5997</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+380 352 25 25 39</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sahattanya@ukr.net</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>pta-teplo@tr.ukrtel.net</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>