<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="036195-2018" EDITION="2018018"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-021228-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20190115</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>18</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180126</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 018-036195</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:036195-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>ES</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="PY"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71356200">Technical assistance services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180115</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="1">External aid and European Development Fund</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="Z">Not specified</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>AP301</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Teknisk bistand til styrkelsen af de lovgivningsmæssige, institutionelle og sanitære rammer for bæredygtig animalsk produktion og dets diversificering</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Technische Unterstützung zur Stärkung des rechtlichen, institutionellen und sanitären Rahmens einer nachhaltigen Viehzucht und ihrer Diversifizierung</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Technical assistance for strengthening the regulatory, institutional and sanitary framework of sustainable livestock production and its diversification</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Asistencia técnica para el fortalecimiento del marco normativo, institucional y sanitario de la producción pecuaria sustentable y su diversificación</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tekninen tuki kestävää karjankasvatustuotantoa ja sen monipuolistamista koskevan sääntelykehyksen ja institutionaalisen ja terveysasioita koskevan kehyksen vahvistamiseksi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Assistance technique pour le renforcement d’un cadre règlementaire, institutionnel et sanitaire d’un élevage de bétail durable et sa diversification</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Παραγουάη</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ασουνθιόν</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Παροχή τεχνικής βοήθειας για την ενίσχυση του κανονιστικού, θεσμικού και υγειονομικού πλαισίου της βιώσιμης κτηνοτροφικής παραγωγής και της διαφοροποίησής της</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Assistenza tecnica per il rafforzamento del quadro normativo, istituzionale e sanitario della produzione animale sostenibile e diversificata</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Technische bijstand ter versterking van het regelgevende, institutionele en sanitaire kader voor duurzame veeteelt en voor de diversificatie ervan</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Paraguai</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Assunção</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Assistência técnica para o reforço do quadro regulamentar, institucional e sanitário da produção de gado sustentável e a sua diversificação</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tekniskt stöd för att stärka de regleringsmässiga, institutionella och sanitära ramverken för hållbar animalieproduktion och dess diversifiering</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Technická pomoc pro posílení regulačního, institucionálního a hygienického rámce udržitelné produkce hospodářských zvířat a její diverzifikace</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tehniline abi jätkusuutliku loomakasvatuse ja selle mitmekesistamise normatiivse, institutsioonilise ja sanitaarse raamistiku tugevdamiseks</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Szakmai segítségnyújtás a fenntartható állattenyésztés és diverzifikálása szabályozási, intézményi és egészségügyi keretrendszerének megerősítéséhez</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Paragvajus</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunsjonas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Techninė pagalba stiprinant reguliavimo, institucinę ir sanitarinę tvarios gyvulininkystės produkcijos ir jos įvairinimo struktūrą</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Paragvaja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunsjona</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tehniskā palīdzība ilgtspējīgas lopkopības tiesiskā, institucionālā un sanitārā regulējuma stiprināšanai un nozares dažādošanai</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Paragwaj</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Għajnuna teknika għat-tisħiħ tal-qafas regolatorju, istituzzjonali u sanitarju tal-produzzjoni sostenibbli tal-bhejjem u d-diversifikazzjoni tagħha</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Paragwaj</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Wsparcie techniczne na potrzeby wzmocnienia ram prawnych, instytucjonalnych i sanitarnych na rzecz zrównoważonej produkcji żywego inwentarza i jego zróżnicowania</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Paraguaj</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Odborná pomoc na posilnenie regulačného, inštitucionálneho a sanitárneho rámca udržateľnej živočíšnej výroby a jej diverzifikácie</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Paragvaj</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tehnična pomoč pri krepitvi regulativnega, institucionalnega in sanitarnega okvira za trajnostno živinorejo in njeno diverzifikacijo</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Paragua</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Cúnamh teicniúil chun an creat rialála, institiúideach agus sláintíochta maidir le táirgeadh beostoic inbhuanaithe agus a éagsúlú a neartú</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Парагвай</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Асунсион</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Техническа помощ за подсилване на регулаторната, институционалната и здравната рамка на устойчивото животновъдство и неговото многообразие</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Paraguay</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Asistență tehnică pentru consolidarea cadrului normativ, instituțional și sanitar al producției durabile de origine animală și diversificarea acesteia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Paragvaj</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Asunción</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tehnička pomoć za jačanje regulatornog, institucijskog i sanitarnog okvira održive proizvodnje stoke i njezinu diversifikaciju</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Ministeriet for landbrug og husdyrhold i Republikken Paraguay</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Ministerium für Landwirtschaft und Viehzucht der Republik Paraguay</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">Ministry of Agriculture and Livestock of the Republic of Paraguay</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">Ministerio de Agricultura y Ganadería de la República del Paraguay</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Paraguayn tasavallan maataloudesta ja karjankasvatuksesta vastaava ministeriö</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Ministry of Agriculture and Livestock of the Republic of Paraguay</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Υπουργείο Γεωργίας και Κτηνοτροφίας της Δημοκρατίας της Παραγουάης</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Ministero dell'Agricoltura e dell'allevamento della Repubblica del Paraguay</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Ministerie van Landbouw en Veeteelt van de Republiek Paraguay</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">Ministério da Agricultura e do Gado da República do Paraguai</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Ministeriet för jordbruk och boskap i republiken Paraguay</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Ministerstvo zemědělství a hospodářských zvířat Paraguayské republiky</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Paraguay Vabariigi Põllumajandus- ja karjakasvatusministeerium</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">A Paraguayi Köztársaság Mezőgazdasági és Állattenyésztési Minisztériuma</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Paragvajaus Respublikos Žemės ūkio ir gyvulininkystės ministerija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Paragvajas Republikas Lauksaimniecības un lopkopības ministrija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">Il-Ministeru tal-Agrikoltura u l-Bhejjem tar-Repubblika tal-Paragwaj</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Ministerstwo Rolnictwa i Żywego Inwentarza Republiki Paragwaju</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Ministerstvo poľnohospodárstva a živočíšnej výroby Paraguajskej republiky</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Ministrstvo za poljedelstvo in živinorejo Republike Paragvaj</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">Aireacht Talmhaíocht agus Beostoic Phoblacht Pharagua</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Министерството на земеделието и животновъдството на република Парагвай</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Ministerul Agriculturii și Creșterii Animalelor din Republica Paraguay</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Ministarstvo poljoprivrede i stočarstva Republike Paragvaj</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Teknisk bistand til styrkelsen af de lovgivningsmæssige, institutionelle og sanitære rammer for bæredygtig animalsk produktion og dets diversificering</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Forhåndsmeddelelse vedrørende tjenesteydelser</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udbudsreference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Begrænset.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmets navn</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fremme af diversificeret og bæredygtig animalsk produktion</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministeriet for landbrug og husdyrhold i Republikken Paraguay</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontraktens art</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Honorarbaseret kontrakt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivelse af kontrakten</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kontraktens genstand indebærer støtten og styrkelsen af de lovgivningsmæssige og institutionelle rammer for bæredygtig animalsk produktion og dens diversificering, med aktionslinjer, der sigter på at forstærke de institutionelle kapaciteter i den offentlige sektor og give den private sektor nationale sektorpolitikker, lovgivning og tjenester, der er gunstige for dens udvikling, herunder sager, der relaterer til bæredygtig animalsk produktion i politikker og national lovgivning.</P><P>Den skal endvidere indebære forstærkning af de sanitære rammer for ikke-traditionelle husdyrsektorer (komælk, fjerkræ og deres biprodukter, svinekød, får, geder, akvakultur, biavl), med aktionslinjer, der sigter på at styrke eller udvide den nationale kvalitets- og sanitetsinfrastrukturs omfang inden for disse husdyrsektorer, herunder dens kapacitet for kontrolimplementering og sporbarhed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vejledende budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Den forventede dato for offentliggørelse af bekendtgørelsen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Februar 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yderligere oplysninger</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ikke relevant.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Retsgrundlag (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 236/2014 af 11.3.2014 om fælles regler og procedurer for gennemførelse af instrumenterne til finansiering af Unionens optræden udadtil og Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EF) nr. 1905/2006 af 18.12.2006 om oprettelse af et instrument til finansiering af udviklingssamarbejde, jf. bilag A2 til den praktiske vejledning.</P><P>Vær opmærksom på, at efter Det Forenede Kongeriges udtræden af EU vil reglerne om adgang til EU's udbudsprocedurer for økonomiske aktører, der er etableret i tredjelande, gælde for ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige, alt afhængigt af resultatet af forhandlingerne. I tilfælde af, at en sådan adgang ikke dækkes under retlige bestemmelser, der er gældende ved kontrakttildelingen, vil ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige kunne blive udelukket fra udbudsproceduren.</P><P>(1) Angiv venligst enhver specificitet, der kan have indflydelse på reglerne for deltagelse (såsom geografiske eller tematiske eller lang/kort-sigtede).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Bemærkninger:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Der skal være en periode på mindst 30 kalenderdage mellem offentliggørelsen af denne forhåndsmeddelelse og offentliggørelsen af den tilsvarende udbudsbekendtgørelse.</P><P>Der bør ikke fremsendes ansøgninger eller anmodninger om oplysninger på nuværende tidspunkt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Technische Unterstützung zur Stärkung des rechtlichen, institutionellen und sanitären Rahmens einer nachhaltigen Viehzucht und ihrer Diversifizierung</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vorinformation für einen Dienstleistungsauftrag</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verfahren</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nichtoffen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmbezeichnung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Förderung einer diversifizierten und nachhaltigen Viehzucht</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanzierung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Öffentlicher Auftraggeber</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministerium für Landwirtschaft und Viehzucht der Republik Paraguay</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Art des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Auf Honorarbasis.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Das Thema dieses Vertrages beinhaltet die Unterstützung und Stärkung des rechtlichen und institutionellen Rahmens für eine nachhaltige Viehwirtschaft und ihre Diversifizierung mit Aktionsplänen, deren Ziel es ist, die institutionellen Fähigkeiten des öffentlichen Sektors zu verstärken und für den privaten Sektor nationale Sektorpolitiken, Gesetzgebungen und Dienstleistungen zu schaffen, die förderlich für seine Entwicklung sind, dies umfasst Aspekte betreffend die Viehwirtschaft in Politikbereichen und nationaler Gesetzgebung.</P><P>Zudem muss er die Stärkung des sanitären Rahmens für nicht traditionelle Viehwirtschaftssektoren beinhalten (Kuhmilch, Geflügel und seine Nebenerzeugnisse, Schwein, Schafe, Ziegen, Aquakultur, Apikultur) mit Aktionsplänen, deren Ziel es ist, den Umfang der nationalen Qualitäts- und sanitären Infrastruktur für diese Viehzuchtsektoren zu stärken und zu erweitern, einschließlich ihrer Leistungsfähigkeit bezüglich der Anwendungskontrolle und Rückverfolgbarkeit.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veranschlagtes Budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Voraussichtlicher Zeitplan für die Veröffentlichung der Auftragsbekanntmachung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Februar 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zusätzliche Informationen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nicht zutreffend.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsgrundlage (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verordnung (EU) Nr. 236/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Festlegung gemeinsamer Vorschriften und Verfahren für die Anwendung der Instrumente der Union für die Finanzierung des auswärtigen Handelns und Verordnung (EG) Nr. 1905/2006 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 18.12.2006 zur Schaffung eines Finanzierungsinstruments für die Entwicklungszusammenarbeit; siehe Anhang A2 des „Handbuch“.</P><P>Es gilt zu beachten, dass für Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich nach dem Austritt des Vereinigten Königreichs aus der EU in Abhängigkeit des Ausgangs der Verhandlungen die Bestimmungen über den Zugang zu Beschaffungsverfahren der EU für in Drittländern ansässige Wirtschaftsteilnehmer gelten werden. Falls dieser Zugang gemäß den bei Auftragsvergabe geltenden Bestimmung nicht gewährt wird, können Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich vom Beschaffungsverfahren ausgeschlossen werden.</P><P>(1) Bitte geben Sie alle Besonderheiten an, die sich auf die Beteiligungsregeln auswirken können (z. B. geografisch oder thematisch, langfristig oder kurzfristig).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Hinweise:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Zwischen der Veröffentlichung der vorliegenden Vorinformation und der Veröffentlichung der zugehörigen Auftragsbekanntmachung müssen mindestens 30 Kalendertage liegen.</P><P>Derzeit ist von der Einreichung von Bewerbungen oder weiteren Anfragen abzusehen.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Technical assistance for strengthening the regulatory, institutional and sanitary framework of sustainable livestock production and its diversification</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Prior information notice for services</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publication reference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programme name</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Promotion of a Diversified and Sustainable Livestock Production</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financing</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contracting Authority</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministry of Agriculture and Livestock of the Republic of Paraguay</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature of contract</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fee-based contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contract description</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The subject of this contract entails supporting and strengthening the regulatory and institutional framework for a sustainable livestock production and its diversification, with lines of action aimed at reinforcing the institutional capacities of the public sector and providing the private sector with national sectoral policies, legislation and services favourable for its development, including matters related to sustainable livestock production in policies and national legislation.</P><P>Furthermore, it must include the reinforcement of the sanitary framework for non-traditional livestock sectors (cow milk, poultry and its by-products, pork, sheep, goats, aquaculture, apiculture), with lines of action aimed at strengthening or broadening the scope of the national quality and sanitary infrastructure for these livestock sectors, including its capacity for control implementation and traceability.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicative budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date of publication envisaged for the contract notice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>February 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Additional information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>N/A.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal basis(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulation (EU) No 236/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 laying down common rules and procedures for the implementation of the Union's instruments for financing external action, and Regulation (EC) No 1905/2006 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 18.12.2006 establishing a financing instrument for development cooperation; see Annex A2 to the Practical Guide.</P><P>Please be aware that after the United Kingdom's withdrawal from the EU, the rules of access to EU procurement procedures of economic operators established in third countries will apply to candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom depending on the outcome of the negotiations. In the event such access is not covered under legal provisions in force at the award of the contract, the candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom may be omitted from the procurement procedure.</P><P>(1) Please indicate any particular feature that may have an impact on the participation rules (for instance, geographical or thematic, long term or short term).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Notes:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>There must be a minimum period of 30 calendar days between publication of this prior information notice and publication of the corresponding contract notice.</P><P>No application or request for information may be sent at this stage.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Asistencia técnica para el fortalecimiento del marco normativo, institucional y sanitario de la producción pecuaria sustentable y su diversificación</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anuncio de Información Previa de Servicios</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referencia de publicación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedimiento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restringido.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Título del programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Promoción de una Producción Pecuaria Diversificada y Sustentable</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de Contratación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministerio de Agricultura y Ganadería de la República del Paraguay</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, PARAGUAY. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naturaleza del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Basado en honorarios.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>La prestación tendrá a su cargo el apoyo y el fortalecimiento del marco normativo e institucional para la producción pecuaria sustentable y su diversificación con líneas de acción que apunten a fortalecer capacidades institucionales del sector público, proporcionar al sector privado políticas sectoriales nacionales, legislación y servicios favorables para su desarrollo, incluyendo cuestiones de producción pecuaria sustentable en las políticas y legislación nacional.</P><P>También, deberá contemplar el fortalecimiento del marco sanitario para los sectores pecuarios no tradicionales (leche bovina, aves y derivados, porcinos, ovinos, caprinos, acuicultura, apicultura) con líneas de acción que fortalezcan o amplíen el alcance de la infraestructura nacional de calidad y sanidad a estos sectores pecuarios, incluyendo la capacidad de ejecución del control y la trazabilidad.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Presupuesto indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Calendario de publicación previsto del anuncio de contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Febrero 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información adicional</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>N/A.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fundamento jurídico (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Reglamento (UE) nº 236/2014 del Parlamento y del Consejo, de 11 de marzo de 2014, por el que se establecen normas y procedimientos de ejecución comunes de los instrumentos de la Unión para la financiación de la acción exterior y el Reglamento (CE) n1 1905/2006 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, del 18 de diciembre de 2006, por el que se establece un Instrumento de Financiación de la Cooperación al Desarrollo — Véase el anexo A2 de la Guía Práctica.</P><P>Téngase en cuenta que después de la retirada del Reino Unido de la UE, las reglas de acceso a los procedimientos de contratación de la UE de operadores económicos establecidos en países terceros se aplicarán a candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido dependiendo del resultado de las negociaciones.. En caso de que tal acceso no esté contemplado por disposiciones legales que se hallen vigentes en el momento de la adjudicación del contrato, los candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido podrían ser rechazados del procedimiento de contratación.</P><P>(1) Indíquese cualquier particularidad que pueda incidir en las normas de participación (por ejemplo, geográfica o temática, o a largo o corto plazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observaciones:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Debe transcurrir un plazo mínimo de 30 días naturales entre la publicación del presente anuncio de información previa y la publicación del anuncio de contrato correspondiente.</P><P>No debe enviarse ninguna candidatura ni solicitud de información en la presente fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Tekninen tuki kestävää karjankasvatustuotantoa ja sen monipuolistamista koskevan sääntelykehyksen ja institutionaalisen ja terveysasioita koskevan kehyksen vahvistamiseksi</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Palveluja koskeva ennakkotietoilmoitus</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen viite</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menettely</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rajoitettu menettely.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ohjelman nimi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kestävän ja monipuolisen karjankasvatustuotannon edistäminen</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahoitus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Paraguayn tasavallan maataloudesta ja karjankasvatuksesta vastaava ministeriö</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuslaji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Palkkiopohjainen sopimus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuksen kuvaus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tämän sopimuksen aihe käsittelee kestävää karjankasvatustuotantoa ja sen monipuolistamista koskevan sääntelykehyksen ja institutionaalisen kehyksen tukemista ja vahvistamista. Tähän liittyvillä toimintalinjoilla pyritään vahvistamaan julkisen sektorin institutionaalisia valmiuksia ja takaamaan yksityiselle sektorille kansalliset alakohtaiset politiikat, lainsäädäntö ja palvelut, jotka edistävät yksityisen sektorin kehittämistä, mukaan lukien aiheet, jotka liittyvät kestävään karjankasvatustuotantoon politiikoissa ja kansallisessa lainsäädännössä.</P><P>Lisäksi sopimukseen on sisällyttävä muiden kuin perinteisten karjankasvatusalojen (lehmänmaito, siipikarja ja sen sivutuotteet, sianliha, lampaat, vuohet, vesiviljely, mehiläistalous) terveysasioita koskevan kehyksen vahvistaminen. Tähän liittyvillä toimintalinjoilla pyritään vahvistamaan tai laajentamaan kansallista laatuinfrastruktuuria ja terveysasioihin liittyvää infrastruktuuria kyseisillä karjankasvatusaloilla, sekä vahvistamaan alan valmiuksia valvonnan toteuttamisen ja jäljitettävyyden osalta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Alustava budjetti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintailmoituksen ennakoitu julkaisemisajankohta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Helmikuu 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisätiedot</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ei saatavilla.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oikeusperusta(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 236/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, unionin ulkoisen toiminnan rahoitusvälineiden täytäntöönpanoa koskevista yhteisistä säännöistä ja menettelyistä sekä Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EY) N:o 1905/2006, annettu 18.12.2006, kehitysyhteistyön rahoitusvälineen perustamisesta – katso EU:n ulkoisten toimien yhteydessä toteutettavia sopimusmenettelyjä koskevan käytännön oppaan liite A2.</P><P>On syytä ottaa huomioon, että Yhdistyneen kuningaskunnan EU:sta irtautumisen jälkeen kolmansiin maihin sijoittautuneisiin talouden toimijoihin sovellettavia EU:n hankintamenettelyihin osallistumista koskevia sääntöjä sovelletaan Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin oleviin hakijoihin tai tarjoajiin neuvottelujen lopputuloksesta riippuen. Mikäli sopimuksenteon hetkellä voimassa olevassa lainsäädännössä ei anneta lupaa tällaiseen osallistumiseen, Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin olevat hakijat tai tarjoajat voidaan hylätä hankintamenettelystä.</P><P>(1) Mainitse seikat, joilla voi olla vaikutusta osallistumissääntöihin (kuten esimerkiksi maantieteellinen tai aihepiirikohtainen tai pitkä/lyhyt kesto).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Huom.</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Tämän ennakkotietoilmoituksen ja vastaavan hankintailmoituksen julkaisemisen välillä on oltava vähintään 30 kalenteripäivää.</P><P>Hakemuksia tai lisätietopyyntöjä ei pidä lähettää tässä vaiheessa.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Assistance technique pour le renforcement d’un cadre règlementaire, institutionnel et sanitaire d’un élevage de bétail durable et sa diversification</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avis de pré-information relatif à un marché de services</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Référence de la publication</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restreinte.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nom du programme</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Promotion de l’élevage d’un bétail diversifié et durable</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financement</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pouvoir adjudicateur</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministry of Agriculture and Livestock of the Republic of Paraguay</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>À prix unitaires.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L’objet de ce marché comprend le soutien et le renforcement du cadre règlementaire et institutionnel pour un élevage de bétail durable et sa diversification, parallèlement à une action destinée au renforcement des capacités institutionnelles du secteur public et offrant au secteur privé des politiques nationales sectorielles, une législation et des services favorables à son développement, y compris les questions liées à l’élevage du bétail dans les politiques et la législation nationale.</P><P>Par ailleurs, il doit inclure le renforcement du cadre sanitaire des secteurs non traditionnels du bétail (lait de vache, volaille et ses produits dérivés, porc, moutons, chèvres, aquaculture, apiculture), avec des conduites destinées à renforcer ou élargir l’étendue de la qualité nationale et de l’infrastructure sanitaire pour ses secteurs de bétail, y compris sa capacité pour le contrôle de la mise en œuvre et de la traçabilité.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Budget indicatif</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date envisagée de publication de l'avis de marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Février 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Renseignements complémentaires</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sans objet</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base juridique (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Règlement (UE) n° 236/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 fixant des règles et des modalités communes pour la mise en œuvre des instruments de l'Union pour le financement de l'action extérieure et Règlement (CE) n° 1905/2006 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 18.12.2006 portant établissement d'un instrument de financement de la coopération au développement ; voir annexe A2 du « Guide pratique ».</P><P>Il convient de noter qu'à la suite du retrait du Royaume-Uni de l'UE, les règles d'accès aux procédures de passation marchés de l'UE pour les opérateurs économiques établis dans des pays tiers s'appliqueront aux candidats ou aux soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni, en fonction du résultat des négociations. Si les dispositions légales en vigueur au moment de l'attribution du contrat ne prévoient pas un tel accès, les candidats ou les soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni pourraient être exclus de la procédure d'appel d'offres.</P><P>(1) Veuillez indiquer toute caractéristique particulière pouvant avoir un impact sur les règles de participation (par exemple, géographique ou thématique, long terme ou court terme).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarques :</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Un délai minimal de 30 jours calendaires doit être respecté entre la publication du présent avis de pré-information et celle de l'avis de marché correspondant.</P><P>Aucune candidature ni demande de renseignements complémentaires ne sera envoyée à ce stade de la procédure.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Ασουνθιόν: Παροχή τεχνικής βοήθειας για την ενίσχυση του κανονιστικού, θεσμικού και υγειονομικού πλαισίου της βιώσιμης κτηνοτροφικής παραγωγής και της διαφοροποίησής της</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Προκαταρκτική ανακοίνωση για υπηρεσίες</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Παραγουάη</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αριθ. αναφοράς της δημοσίευσης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Διαδικασία</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κλειστή.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ονομασία του προγράμματος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Προώθηση διαφοροποιημένης και βιώσιμης κτηνοτροφικής παραγωγής</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Χρηματοδότηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα αρχή</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Υπουργείο Γεωργίας και Κτηνοτροφίας της Δημοκρατίας της Παραγουάης</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ασουνθιόν</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Παραγουάη. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τύπος σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Βάσει αμοιβής.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Περιγραφή της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Το αντικείμενο της παρούσας σύμβασης συνίσταται στην υποστήριξη και την ενίσχυση του κανονιστικού και θεσμικού πλαισίου για τη βιώσιμη κτηνοτροφική παραγωγή και τη διαφοροποίησή της, με άξονες παρέμβασης που στοχεύουν στην ενίσχυση των θεσμικών ικανοτήτων του δημόσιου τομέα και την παροχή στον ιδιωτικό τομέα εθνικών τομεακών πολιτικών, νομοθεσίας και υπηρεσιών που ευνοούν την ανάπτυξή του, συμπεριλαμβάνοντας ζητήματα που σχετίζονται με τη βιώσιμη κτηνοτροφική παραγωγή σε πολιτικές και στην εθνική νομοθεσία.</P><P>Επιπλέον, πρέπει να συμπεριλαμβάνει την ενίσχυση του υγειονομικού πλαισίου για τους τομείς της μη παραδοσιακής κτηνοτροφίας (γάλα αγελάδας, πουλερικά και τα υπό-προϊόντα τους, χοιρινό κρέας, αιγοπρόβατα, υδατοκαλλιέργεια, μελισσοκομία), με άξονες παρέμβασης που στόχο έχουν την ενίσχυση ή τη διεύρυνση του πεδίου εφαρμογής των εθνικών υγειονομικών υποδομών και των υποδομών ποιότητας για τους εν λόγω τομείς της κτηνοτροφίας, όπως η ικανότητα υλοποίησης ελέγχων και η ανιχνευσιμότητα.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ενδεικτικός προϋπολογισμός</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης της προκήρυξης σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Φεβρουάριος 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Άνευ αντικειμένου.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Νομική βάση(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κανονισμός 236/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τον καθορισμό κοινών κανόνων και διαδικασιών για την εφαρμογή των μηχανισμών χρηματοδότησης της εξωτερικής δράσης της Ένωσης και κανονισμός (ΕΚ) αριθ. 1905/2006 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 18.12.2006, για τη θέσπιση μηχανισμού χρηματοδότησης της αναπτυξιακής συνεργασίας, βλέπε παράρτημα A2 του πρακτικού οδηγού.</P><P>Πρέπει να ληφθεί υπόψη ότι μετά την αποχώρηση του Ηνωμένου Βασιλείου από την ΕΕ, οι κανόνες πρόσβασης σε διαδικασίες διαγωνισμού της ΕΕ για οικονομικούς φορείς που είναι εγκατεστημένοι σε τρίτες χώρες θα ισχύουν για τους υποψήφιους ή προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο ανάλογα με το αποτέλεσμα των διαπραγματεύσεων. Σε περίπτωση που η πρόσβαση αυτή δεν καλύπτεται από νομικές διατάξεις που ίσχυαν κατά το χρόνο ανάθεσης της σύμβασης, οι υποψήφιοι ή οι προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο ενδέχεται να απορριφθούν από τη διαδικασία σύναψης συμβάσεων.</P><P>(1) Παρακαλείσθε να αναφέρετε οποιαδήποτε ιδιαιτερότητα που ενδέχεται να έχει αντίκτυπο στους κανόνες συμμετοχής (όπως, γεωγραφική ή θεματική, σε μακροπρόθεσμο ή βραχυπρόθεσμο επίπεδο).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Σημείωση:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Μεταξύ της δημοσίευσης της παρούσας προκαταρκτικής ανακοίνωσης και της δημοσίευσης της αντίστοιχης προκήρυξης σύμβασης, θα πρέπει να παρεμβληθεί χρονικό διάστημα τουλάχιστον 30 ημερολογιακών ημερών.</P><P>Κατά το παρόν στάδιο δεν πρέπει να αποστέλλονται υποψηφιότητες ή αιτήσεις για πληροφορίες.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Assistenza tecnica per il rafforzamento del quadro normativo, istituzionale e sanitario della produzione animale sostenibile e diversificata</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avviso di preinformazione per servizi</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Riferimento della pubblicazione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nome del programma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Promozione di una produzione animale diversificata e sostenibile</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanziamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Amministrazione aggiudicatrice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministero dell'Agricoltura e dell'allevamento della Repubblica del Paraguay</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contratto in base a tariffa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L'oggetto del presente appalto consiste nel sostegno e nel rafforzamento del quadro normativo e istituzionale per una produzione animale sostenibile e diversificata, con linee d'azione volte a rafforzare le capacità istituzionali del settore pubblico e fornire al settore privato politiche, legislazione e servizi nazionali settoriali favorevoli al suo sviluppo, comprese le questioni relative alla produzione animale sostenibile nelle politiche e nella legislazione nazionali.</P><P>Inoltre, esso deve includere il rafforzamento del quadro sanitario per i settori non tradizionali dell'allevamento (latte di mucca, pollame e derivati, suini, ovini, caprini, acquacoltura, apicoltura), con linee d'azione volte a rafforzare o ampliare la portata della qualità nazionale e dell'infrastruttura sanitaria per tali settori dell'allevamento, compresa la capacità di attuazione e tracciabilità del controllo.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Importo indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista per la pubblicazione del bando di gara</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Febbraio 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informazioni complementari</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Non applicabile</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base giuridica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regolamento (UE) n. 236/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che stabilisce norme e procedure comuni per l'attuazione degli strumenti per il finanziamento dell'azione esterna dell'Unione e regolamento (CE) n. 1905/2006 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, del 18.12.2006, che istituisce uno strumento per il finanziamento della cooperazione allo sviluppo; cfr. allegato A2 alla "Guida pratica".</P><P>Si prega di notare che, dopo il ritiro del Regno Unito dall'UE, ai candidati o agli offerenti provenienti dal Regno Unito si applicheranno le regole di accesso alle procedure di appalto dell'UE per gli operatori economici stabiliti nei paesi terzi, in funzione dell'esito delle negoziazioni. Nel caso in cui tale accesso non sia previsto dalle disposizioni giuridiche vigenti al momento dell'aggiudicazione del contratto, i candidati o gli offerenti del Regno Unito potranno essere esclusi dalla procedura di gara.</P><P>(1) Si prega di indicare qualsiasi caratteristica particolare che possa avere un impatto sulle regole di partecipazione (ad esempio, geografica o tematica, a lungo o a breve termine).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Osservazioni:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Dovrà intercorrere un periodo di almeno 30 giorni di calendario tra la pubblicazione del presente avviso di preinformazione e quella del bando di gara corrispondente.</P><P>Si prega di non inviare candidature o richieste di ulteriori informazioni in questa fase della procedura.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Technische bijstand ter versterking van het regelgevende, institutionele en sanitaire kader voor duurzame veeteelt en voor de diversificatie ervan</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vooraankondiging voor diensten</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referentie van de bekendmaking:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet-openbaar.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naam van het programma:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bevordering van een gediversifieerde en duurzame veeteelt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiering:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministerie van Landbouw en Veeteelt van de Republiek Paraguay</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aard van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Opdracht op basis van vergoeding.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschrijving van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Het voorwerp van onderhavige opdracht is het ondersteunen en versterken van het regelgevende en institutionele kader voor een duurzame veeteelt en voor de diversificatie ervan, via actielijnen die gericht zijn op het versterken van de institutionele capaciteiten van de overheidssector, alsook op het verstrekken van nationale sectorale beleidslijnen en wetgeving voor de private sector en de verlening van diensten die bevorderlijk zijn voor de ontwikkeling ervan. Daarbij moeten kwesties worden behandeld die verband houden met duurzame veeteelt in beleidslijnen en nationale wetgeving.</P><P>Bovendien moet het de versterking omvatten van het sanitaire kader voor niet-traditionele veeteeltsectoren (koemelk, pluimvee en bijproducten daarvan, varkens, schapen, geiten, aquacultuur, bijenteelt), via actielijnen die gericht zijn op het versterken of verbreden van de omvang van de nationale kwaliteits- en sanitaire infrastructuur voor deze veeteeltsectoren, alsook van de capaciteit ervan voor de tenuitvoerlegging van controles en met betrekking tot traceerbaarheid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicatieve begroting:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beoogde datum van bekendmaking van de aankondiging van opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Februari 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nadere inlichtingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>N.v.t.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Juridische basis (1):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verordening (EU) nr. 236/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van gemeenschappelijke voorschriften en procedures voor de tenuitvoerlegging van de instrumenten van de Unie ter financiering van extern optreden en Verordening (EG) nr. 1905/2006 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 18.12.2006 tot invoering van een financieringsinstrument voor ontwikkelingssamenwerking; zie bijlage A2 bij de „Praktische gids”.</P><P>Gelieve op te merken dat, na de uitstap van het Verenigd Koninkrijk uit de EU en afhankelijk van het resultaat van de onderhandelingen, de regels voor toegang tot EU-aanbestedingsprocedures voor ondernemers die gevestigd zijn in derde landen van toepassing zullen zijn op gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk. Indien dergelijke toegang niet is voorzien door de geldende wettelijke bepalingen op het tijdstip van de gunning van de opdracht, kunnen gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk worden geweigerd voor de aanbestedingsprocedure.</P><P>(1) Vermeld elke specificiteit die een effect kan hebben op de deelnameregels (zoals geografische of thematische specificiteiten op korte of lange termijn).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Noot:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>er moet een minimumtermijn van 30 kalenderdagen liggen tussen de bekendmaking van deze vooraankondiging en de bekendmaking van de overeenstemmende aankondiging van een opdracht.</P><P>In dit stadium mogen er geen aanvragen of verzoeken om nadere inlichtingen worden verzonden.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Assunção: Assistência técnica para o reforço do quadro regulamentar, institucional e sanitário da produção de gado sustentável e a sua diversificação</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anúncio de informação prévia relativo a um contrato de serviços</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguai</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referência da publicação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Limitado.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nome do programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Promoção de uma produção de gado diversificada e sustentável</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministério da Agricultura e do Gado da República do Paraguai</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Assunção</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguai. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natureza do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Baseado em honorários.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O objeto do presente contrato prevê o apoio e o reforço do quadro regulamentar e institucional para uma produção de gado sustentável e a sua diversificação, com linhas de ação destinadas a reforçar as capacidades institucionais do setor público e fornecer ao setor privado políticas setoriais nacionais, legislação e serviços que favoreçam o seu desenvolvimento, incluindo assuntos relativos à produção de gado sustentável em políticas e legislação nacional.</P><P>Além disso, deve incluir o reforço do quadro sanitário para os setores de gado não tradicionais (leite de vaca, aves e os seus subprodutos, suíno, ovino, caprino, aquicultura, apicultura), com linhas de ação destinadas a reforçar e ampliar o âmbito da qualidade nacional e das infraestruturas sanitárias para estes setores do gado, incluindo a sua capacidade para controlar a implementação e a rastreabilidade.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orçamento indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data de publicação prevista do anúncio de concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fevereiro de 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Outras informações</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>N/A.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base jurídica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulamento (UE) n.º 236/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que estabelece regras e procedimentos comuns para a execução dos instrumentos da União de financiamento da ação externa e Regulamento (CE) n.º 1905/2006 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 18.12.2006, que cria um instrumento de financiamento da cooperação para o desenvolvimento; ver o anexo A2 do «Guia Prático».</P><P>Importa notar que após a saída do Reino Unido da UE, as regras de acesso aos procedimentos de adjudicação de contratos da UE de operadores económicos estabelecidos em países terceiros aplicar-se-ão aos candidatos ou proponentes provenientes do Reino Unido consoante o resultado das negociações. Caso tal acesso não esteja previsto pelas disposições legais em vigor na adjudicação do contrato, os candidatos ou proponentes do Reino Unido poderão ser excluídos do processo de adjudicação.</P><P>(1) Indique qualquer característica específica que possa ter um impacto sobre as regras de participação (por exemplo, geográfico ou temático, de longo ou curto prazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observações:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deverá ser respeitado um prazo mínimo de 30 dias de calendário entre a publicação do presente anúncio de informação prévia e a publicação do anúncio de concurso correspondente.</P><P>Não devem ser enviadas candidaturas ou efetuados pedidos de informação nesta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Tekniskt stöd för att stärka de regleringsmässiga, institutionella och sanitära ramverken för hållbar animalieproduktion och dess diversifiering</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Förhandsmeddelande om tjänster</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publikationsreferens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Förfarande</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Selektivt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmets benämning</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Främjande av diversifierad och hållbar animalieproduktion</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministeriet för jordbruk och boskap i republiken Paraguay</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Typ av kontrakt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Arvodesbaserat kontrakt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivning av kontraktet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kontraktet har som syfte att stödja och stärka det regleringsmässiga och institutionella ramverket för en hållbar animalieproduktion och dess diversifiering, med handlingslinjer som syftar till att stärka den offentliga sektorns institutionella kapacitet samt tillhandahålla nationell sektorspolitik till den privata sektorn, lagstiftning och tjänster som främjar dess utveckling, inklusive frågor som rör hållbar animalieproduktion inom policyer och nationella lagstiftning.</P><P>Dessutom måste det innehålla stöd för det sanitära ramverket för den icke-traditionella boskapssektorn (komjölk, fjäderfä och dess biprodukter, fläsk, får, getter, vattenbruk, biodling), med handlingslinjer som syftar till att stärka och bredda omfattningen av den nationella infrastrukturen för kvalitet och sanitet inom dessa boskapssektorer, inklusive kapacitet för kontrollerad implementering och spårbarhet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Preliminär budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerat datum för offentliggörande av meddelandet om upphandling</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Februari 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kompletterande information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Inte tillämpligt</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rättslig grund(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 236/2014 av den 11.3.2014 om fastställande av gemensamma bestämmelser och förfaranden för genomförandet av unionens instrument för finansiering av yttre åtgärder och Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EG) nr 1905/2006 av den 18.12.2006 om upprättande av ett finansieringsinstrument för utvecklingssamarbete – se bilaga 2 till den praktiska handledningen.</P><P>Observera att efter Storbritanniens utträde ur EU kommer reglerna om tillgång till EU:s upphandlingsförfaranden för ekonomiska aktörer etablerade i tredjeländer att tillämpas på sökande eller anbudsgivare från Storbritannien beroende på resultatet av förhandlingarna. Om sådan tillgång inte tillhandahålls av rättsliga bestämmelser som gäller vid tidpunkten för kontraktstilldelningen kan sökande eller anbudsgivare från Storbritannien komma att uteslutas från upphandlingsförfarandet.</P><P>(1) Ange om det finns något som kan påverka reglerna för deltagande (såsom geografiskt läge, tema eller tid på lång eller kort sikt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observera:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>En period på minst 30 kalenderdagar ska förflyta mellan publiceringen av detta förhandsmeddelande och publiceringen av motsvarande meddelande om upphandling.</P><P>Inga ansökningar eller beställningar av information ska skickas i detta skede.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Technická pomoc pro posílení regulačního, institucionálního a hygienického rámce udržitelné produkce hospodářských zvířat a její diverzifikace</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Oznámení předběžných informací o službách</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenční číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užší.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Název programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Propagace diverzifikované a udržitelné produkce hospodářských zvířat</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financování</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veřejný zadavatel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministerstvo zemědělství a hospodářských zvířat Paraguayské republiky</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Povaha zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Placená zakázka.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popis zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Předmětem této zakázky je podpora a posílení regulačního a institucionálního rámce pro udržitelnou produkci hospodářských zvířat a její diverzifikaci, přičemž bude činnost zaměřena na posílení institucionálních kapacit veřejného sektoru a poskytování vnitrostátních sektorových politik, legislativy a služeb příznivých pro vývoj soukromého sektoru, včetně záležitostí souvisejících s udržitelnou produkcí hospodářských zvířat v politikách a vnitrostátní legislativě.</P><P>Dále musí zahrnovat posílení hygienického rámce pro netradiční sektory hospodářských zvířat (kravské mléko, drůbež a její vedlejší produkty, vepřové, ovčí a kozí produkty, akvakultura, včelařské výrobky), přičemž bude činnost zaměřena na posílení a zvětšení rozsahu vnitrostátní kvality a hygienické infrastruktury pro tyto sektory hospodářských zvířat, včetně schopnosti řídit zavádění a sledovatelnost.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Směrný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plánované datum uveřejnění oznámení o zakázce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Únor 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Další informace</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>nejsou.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právní základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 236/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se stanoví společná pravidla a postupy pro provádění nástrojů Unie pro financování vnější činnosti, a nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (ES) č. 1905/2006 ze dne 18. prosince 2006, kterým se zřizuje finanční nástroj pro rozvojovou spolupráci; viz příloha č. A2 praktického průvodce.</P><P>Připomínáme, že po vystoupení Spojeného království z EU se na zájemce nebo uchazeče ze Spojeného království, v závislosti od výsledku jednání, budou uplatňovat pravidla přístupu k postupům výběrového řízení EU ze strany hospodářských subjektů se sídlem ve třetích zemích. V případě, že takový přístup není zabezpečen právními předpisy platnými v době zadání zakázky, mohli by být uchazeči nebo účastníci ze Spojeného království vyloučeni z výběrového řízení.</P><P>(1) Uveďte prosím jakýkoli konkrétní prvek, který může mít vliv na pravidla účasti (např. geografický nebo tematický, dlouhodobý nebo krátkodobý).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Mezi zveřejněním těchto předběžných informací o zakázce a zveřejněním odpovídajícího oznámení o zakázce musí uplynout minimálně 30 kalendářních dnů.</P><P>V této fázi nesmí být zasílány žádné přihlášky ani žádosti o informace.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Tehniline abi jätkusuutliku loomakasvatuse ja selle mitmekesistamise normatiivse, institutsioonilise ja sanitaarse raamistiku tugevdamiseks</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Teenuste eelteade</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaldamise viide</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menetlus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Piiratud.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmi nimetus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mitmekesise ja jätkusuutliku loomakasvatuse edendamine</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahastamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaliku sektori hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Paraguay Vabariigi Põllumajandus- ja karjakasvatusministeerium</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu laad</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tasupõhine leping.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kõnealuse lepingu eesmärk hõlmab jätkusuutliku loomakasvatuse ja selle mitmekesistamist toetava ja tugevdava reguleeriva ja institutsioonilise raamistiku toetamist, seades tegevuse eesmärgiks avaliku sektori institutsioonilise suutlikkuse tugevdamise ja erasektorile arenguks soodsate riiklike valdkondlike poliitikate, õigusaktide ja teenuste tagamise, sh poliitikates ja siseriiklikes õigusaktides jätkusuutliku loomakasvatusega seotud küsimustes.</P><P>Ühtlasi peaks see hõlmama ebatraditsiooniliste loomakasvatussektorite (piimakarjakasvatus, linnukasvatus ja selle vahesaadused, seakasvatus, lambakasvatus, kitsekasvatus, vesiviljelus, mesindus) sanitaarse raamistiku tugevdamist, tegevustega, mille eesmärgiks oleks riikliku kvaliteedi ja sanitaarse infrastruktuuri raamistiku tugevdamine või laiendamine neile loomakasvatussektoritele, sh kontrollisuutlikkus ja jälgitavus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Soovituslik eelarve</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hanketeate avaldamise ettenähtud kuupäev</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Veebruar 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisateave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Puudub.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Õiguslik alus(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11. märtsi 2014. aasta määrus (EL) nr 236/2014, milles sätestatakse liidu välistegevuse rahastamisvahendite rakendamise ühised eeskirjad ja menetlused, ning Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 18. detsembri 2006. aasta määrus (EÜ) nr 1905/2006, millega luuakse arengukoostöö rahastamisvahend (vt praktilise juhendi lisa A2).</P><P>Palume tähele panna, et olenevalt läbirääkimiste tulemustest kohaldatakse pärast Ühendkuningriigi EList lahkumist Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaatidele või pakkujatele kolmandates riikides asutatud ettevõtjatele kehtivaid ELi hankemenetlustele juurepääsu käsitlevaid eeskirju. Juhul, kui selline juurdepääs ei ole hõlmatud lepingu sõlmimise ajal kehtivate õiguslike sätetega, võidakse Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaadid või pakkujad hankemenetlusest kõrvale jätta.</P><P>(1) Märkige kõik erijooned, mis võivad mõjutada osalemise tingimusi (näiteks geograafilised erijooned, valdkond, lühike või pikk tähtaeg).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Märkused</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Eelteate ja vastava hanketeate avaldamise vahele peab jääma vähemalt 30 kalendripäeva.</P><P>Taotlusi ega teabenõudeid ei või selles etapis veel saata.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Szakmai segítségnyújtás a fenntartható állattenyésztés és diverzifikálása szabályozási, intézményi és egészségügyi keretrendszerének megerősítéséhez</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Szolgáltatásokra irányuló előzetes tájékoztató hirdetmény</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A közzététel hivatkozási száma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Eljárás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Meghívásos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A program neve</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A diverzifikált és fenntartható állattenyésztés támogatása</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanszírozás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>A Paraguayi Köztársaság Mezőgazdasági és Állattenyésztési Minisztériuma</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés típusa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Díjalapú szerződés.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés meghatározása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A szerződés tárgya magában foglalja a fenntartható állattenyésztés és diverzifikálása szabályozási és intézményi keretrendszerének támogatását és megerősítését olyan tevékenységi irányvonalak mentén, melyek célja az állami szektor intézményi felkészültségének megerősítése és a magánszektor fejlődéséhez szükséges nemzeti ágazati szakpolitikák, jogszabályok és szolgáltatások biztosítása, a szakpolitikákba és nemzeti jogszabályrendszerbe belefoglalva a fenntartható állattenyésztéssel kapcsolatos témákat is.</P><P>Továbbá magában kell foglalnia az egészségügyi keretrendszer megerősítését is a nem hagyományos állattenyésztési ágazatok (tehéntej, baromfi és melléktermékei, sertés, juh, kecske, akvakultúra, méhészet) esetén, olyan tevékenységi irányvonalak mentén, melyek célja a nemzeti minőségbiztosítási és egészségügyi infrastruktúra hatókörének erősítése és kiszélesítése ezen állattenyésztési ágazatokban, beleértve a végrehajtás ellenőrzésére és a nyomonkövethetőség biztosítására való felkészültséget.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Várható költségvetés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlati felhívás közzétételének várható időpontja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018. február</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>További információk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>n.a.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Jogalap(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A külső tevékenységek finanszírozására vonatkozó uniós eszközök végrehajtására vonatkozó közös szabályok és eljárások megállapításáról szóló 11.3.2014 keltezésű 236/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet, valamint a fejlesztési együttműködés finanszírozási eszközének létrehozásáról szóló, 18.12.2006 keltezésű 1905/2006/EK európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet; lásd a Gyakorlati útmutató A2 mellékletét.</P><P>Figyelembe kell venni, hogy az Egyesült Királyságnak az EU-ból való kilépése után az Egyesült Királyságból származó jelentkezőkre vagy ajánlattevőkre – a tárgyalások kimenetelétől függően – az EU közbeszerzési eljárásaihoz való hozzáférés tekintetében a harmadik országok gazdasági szereplői számára érvényes szabályok vonatkoznak. Amennyiben a részvételről nem rendelkezik a szerződés odaítélésének időpontjában hatályban lévő jogszabály, az Egyesült Királyságból származó ajánlattevők vagy jelentkezők kizárhatók a közbeszerzési eljárásból.</P><P>(1) Kérjük, jelezzen bármely olyan sajátosságot, amely hatással lehet a részvételi szabályokra (például földrajzi, tematikus vagy hosszú/rövid távú sajátosság).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Megjegyzések:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Legalább 30 naptári napnak kell eltelnie az előzetes összesített hirdetmény megjelenése és a vonatkozó ajánlati felhívás közzététele között.</P><P>Ezen időszak alatt jelentkezések benyújtásának, illetve információkérésnek nincs helye.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunsjonas: Techninė pagalba stiprinant reguliavimo, institucinę ir sanitarinę tvarios gyvulininkystės produkcijos ir jos įvairinimo struktūrą</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paslaugų išankstinis informacinis skelbimas</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paragvajus</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nuoroda į publikaciją</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ribotas konkursas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programos pavadinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Įvairios ir tvarios gyvulininkystės produkcijos skatinimas</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansavimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Perkančioji organizacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Paragvajaus Respublikos Žemės ūkio ir gyvulininkystės ministerija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunsjonas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paragvajus. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties pobūdis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mokama sutartis.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties apibūdinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Šios sutarties objektas – remti ir stiprinti reguliavimo ir institucinę tvarios gyvulininkystės produkcijos bei jos įvairovės struktūrą, kai tam tikri veiksmai skirti viešojo sektoriaus instituciniams pajėgumams sustiprinti ir nacionalinei sektoriaus politikai, įstatymams bei paslaugoms, palankioms jos plėtrai, įskaitant politikose bei nacionaliniuose įstatymuose esantiems tvarios gyvulininkystės produkcijos klausimams, privačiam sektoriui pristatyti.</P><P>Be to, joje turi būti remiama netradicinių gyvulininkystės sektorių (karvės pieno, paukštienos ir jos produktų, kiaulienos, avienos, ožienos, akvakultūros, bitininkystės) sanitarinė struktūra, kai tam tikrais veiksmais siekiama sustiprinti ar praplėsti nacionalinės kokybės ir sanitarinės infrastruktūros apimtį šiems gyvulininkystės sektoriams, įskaitant jos pajėgumus įgyvendinti kontrolę ir atsekamumą.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatomas biudžetas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatyta skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo data</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018 m. vasario mėn.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildoma informacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nėra.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teisinis pagrindas (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2014 m. kovo 11 d. Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 236/2014, kuriuo nustatomos bendros Sąjungos išorės veiksmų finansavimo priemonių įgyvendinimo taisyklės ir procedūros, ir 2006 m. gruodžio 18 d. Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (EB) Nr. 1905/2006, nustatantis vystomojo bendradarbiavimo finansinę priemonę; žr. „Praktinio vadovo“ A2 priedą.</P><P>Prašome atkreipti dėmesį, kad Jungtinei Karalystei pasitraukus iš ES, ekonominės veiklos vykdytojų, įsikūrusių trečiosiose šalyse, prieigos prie ES pirkimo procedūrų taisyklės bus taikomos kandidatams ar konkurso dalyviams iš Jungtinės Karalystės, priklausomai nuo derybų rezultato. Jeigu tokia prieiga nebus suteikta galiojančiomis teisinėmis nuostatomis, kandidatai arba konkurso dalyviai iš Jungtinės Karalystės gali būti pašalinti iš pirkimo procedūros.</P><P>(1) Nurodykite visas konkrečias ypatybes, kurios gali daryti įtaką dalyvavimo taisyklėms (pavyzdžiui, geografinės, teminės, ilgalaikės ar trumpalaikės).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Pastabos:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Nuo šios išankstinės informacijos apie numatomą sutartį paskelbimo iki atitinkamo skelbimo dėl pirkimo publikavimo turi praeiti mažiausiai 30 kalendorinių dienų.</P><P>Šiuo etapu negalima siųsti paraiškų ar kreiptis dėl informacijos.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunsjona: Tehniskā palīdzība ilgtspējīgas lopkopības tiesiskā, institucionālā un sanitārā regulējuma stiprināšanai un nozares dažādošanai</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Iepriekšējs informatīvs paziņojums par pakalpojumu līgumu</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paragvaja</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsauce uz publikāciju</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Slēgta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmas nosaukums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Diversificētas un ilgtspējīgas lopkopības veicināšana</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansējums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Paragvajas Republikas Lauksaimniecības un lopkopības ministrija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunsjona</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paragvaja </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma veids</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Līgums, kura pamatā ir samaksa par pakalpojumiem</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Šā līguma priekšmets ir atbalsts ilgtspējīgas lopkopības tiesiskā un institucionālā regulējuma stiprināšanai un nozares dažādošanai; darbībām jābūt vērstām uz publiskā sektora institucionālo spēju stiprināšanu un tādas valsts sektora politikas, tiesību aktu un pakalpojumu nodrošināšanu privātajam sektoram, kas veicinātu tā attīstību, tostarp jautājumos, kas attiecas uz ilgtspējīgu lopkopību politikā un valsts tiesību aktos.</P><P>Turklāt darbībām jāiekļauj sanitārā regulējuma īstenošana netradicionālās lopkopības nozarēs (govs piena ražošana, mājputnu audzēšana un to blakusproduktu ražošana, cūku, aitu un kazu audzēšana, akvakultūra, biškopība); darbībām jābūt vērstām uz valsts kvalitātes un sanitārās infrastruktūras stiprināšanu vai paplašināšanu šīm lopkopības nozarēm, tostarp attiecībā uz kontroles un izsekojamības nodrošināšanas spējām.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Provizoriskais budžets</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paziņojuma par līgumu paredzamais publicēšanas datums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018. gada februāris</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildu informācija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nav</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tiesiskais pamats(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes 11.3.2014 Regula (ES) Nr. 236/2014, ar ko paredz kopīgus noteikumus un procedūras, lai īstenotu Savienības instrumentus ārējās darbības finansēšanai, un Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes 18.12.2006 Regula (EK) Nr. 1905/2006, ar ko izveido finanšu instrumentu sadarbībai attīstības jomā; skatīt “Praktiskās rokasgrāmatas” A2 pielikumu.</P><P>Lūdzam ņemt vērā, ka pēc Apvienotās Karalistes izstāšanās no ES uz kandidātiem un pretendentiem no Apvienotās Karalistes atkarībā no sarunu iznākuma attieksies noteikumi par trešo valstu uzņēmēju tiesībām piedalīties ES iepirkuma procedūrās. Ja līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas brīdī spēkā esošajās tiesību normās šāda piekļuve nebūs paredzēta, kandidāti vai pretendenti no Apvienotās Karalistes var tikt izslēgti no iepirkuma procedūras.</P><P>(1) Lūdzam norādīt visus specifiskos iemeslus (piemēram, ģeogrāfiskus, tematiskus, īstermiņa vai ilgtermiņa), kas var ietekmēt dalības noteikumus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Piezīmes</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Starp šā iepriekšējā informatīvā paziņojuma un attiecīgā paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datumiem jāpaiet vismaz 30 kalendārajām dienām.</P><P>Šajā posmā nekādus pieteikumus vai informācijas pieprasījumus nesūtīt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Għajnuna teknika għat-tisħiħ tal-qafas regolatorju, istituzzjonali u sanitarju tal-produzzjoni sostenibbli tal-bhejjem u d-diversifikazzjoni tagħha</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel għal servizzi</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>il-Paragwaj</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-proċedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-isem tal-programm</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-promozzjoni ta' Produzzjoni tal-Bhejjem Diversifikata u Sostenibbli</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-iffinanzjar</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Il-Ministeru tal-Agrikoltura u l-Bhejjem tar-Repubblika tal-Paragwaj</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>il-Paragwaj. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-tip ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kuntratt ibbażat fuq ħlas ta' miżata.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-deskrizzjoni tal-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Is-suġġett ta' dan il-kuntratt jinvolvi l-appoġġ u t-tisħiħ tal-qafas regolatorju u istituzzjonali għal produzzjoni sostenibbli tal-bhejjem u d-diversifikazzjoni tagħha, b'linji ta' azzjoni mmirati lejn ir-rinfurzar tal-ħiliet istituzzjonali tas-settur pubbliku u l-provvista tas-settur privat b'politiki, leġiżlazzjoni u servizzi settorjali nazzjonali favorevoli għall-iżvilupp tiegħu, inklużi kwistjonijiet relatati mal-produzzjoni sostenibbli tal-bhejjem f'politiki u l-leġiżlazzjoni nazzjonali.</P><P>Barra minn hekk, irid jinkludi r-rinfurzar tal-qafas sanitarju għal setturi tal-bhejjem mhux tradizzjonali (il-ħalib tal-baqar, it-tjur u l-prodotti sekondarji tagħhom, il-majjal, in-nagħaġ, il-mogħoż, l-akkwakultura, l-apikultura), b'linji ta' azzjoni mmirati lejn it-tisħiħ jew it-twessigħ tal-ambitu tal-infrastruttura tal-kwalitá u sanitarja nazzjonali għal dawn is-setturi tal-bhejjem, inklużi l-ħila tagħha għall-implimentazzjoni tal-kontroll u t-traċċabilità.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-baġit indikattiv</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-data tal-pubblikazzjoni maħsuba għall-avviż dwar il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>fi Frar tal-2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif addizzjonali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mhux applikabbli.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-bażi legali(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 236/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi regoli u proċeduri komuni għall-implimentazzjoni tal-istrumenti tal-Unjoni għall-finanzjament tal-azzjoni esterna, u r-Regolament (KE) Nru 1905/2006 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tat-18 ta' Diċembru 2006, li jistabbilixxi strument ta' finanzjament tal-koperazzjoni għall-iżvilupp; ara Anness A2 tal-Gwida Prattika.</P><P>Jekk jogħġbok kun af li wara l-irtirar tar-Renju Unit mill-UE, ir-regoli tal-aċċess għall-proċeduri ta' ksib tal-UE ta' operaturi ekonomiċi mwaqqfa f'pajjiżi terzi se japplikaw għall-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit skont ir-riżultat tan-negozjati. F'każ li tali aċċess ma jkunx kopert skont id-dispożizzjonijiet legali fis-seħħ fl-għoti tal-kuntratt, il-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit jistgħu jitwarrbu mill-proċedura tal-ksib.</P><P>(1) Jekk jogħġbok indika kwalunkwe karatteristika partikolari li jista' jkollha impatt fuq ir-regoli tal-parteċipazzjoni (pereżempju, dik ġeografika jew tematika, fit-tul jew fuq żmien qasir).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Noti:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Irid ikun hemm perijodu ta' mill-inqas 30 jum kalendarju bejn il-pubblikazzjoni ta' dan l-avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel u l-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt li għandu x'jaqsam miegħu.</P><P>M'għandhomx jintbagħtu applikazzjonijiet jew talbiet għal tagħrif f'dan l-istadju.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Wsparcie techniczne na potrzeby wzmocnienia ram prawnych, instytucjonalnych i sanitarnych na rzecz zrównoważonej produkcji żywego inwentarza i jego zróżnicowania</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Wstępne ogłoszenie informacyjne — zamówienie na usługi</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paragwaj</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numer referencyjny publikacji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograniczona.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nazwa programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Promocja zróżnicowanej i zrównoważonej produkcji żywego inwentarza</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansowanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Instytucja zamawiająca</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministerstwo Rolnictwa i Żywego Inwentarza Republiki Paragwaju</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paragwaj. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rodzaj zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Zamówienie według stawek jednostkowych.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Przedmiotem zamówienia są usługi wsparcia oraz wzmocnienie ram prawnych i instytucjonalnych w zakresie zrównoważonej produkcji żywego inwentarza oraz jego zróżnicowania. Działania w zakresie zamówienia mają na celu poprawienie wydajności instytucjonalnej sektora publicznego i zapewnienie sektorowi prywatnemu krajowych polityk sektorowych, przepisów i usług, które sprzyjać będą jego rozwojowi, w tym sprawom związanym ze zrównoważoną produkcją żywego inwentarza w ramach polityk i przepisów krajowych.</P><P>Co więcej, usługi muszą obejmować poprawienie jakości ram sanitarnych dla nietradycyjnych sektorów żywego inwentarza (mleko krowie, drób i jego produkty pochodne, wieprzowina, owce, kozy, akwakultura, pszczelarstwo), a działania będą miały na celu wzmocnienie lub poszerzenie zakresu jakości na skalę kraju i infrastruktury sanitarnej dla tych sektorów żywego inwentarza, w tym jego zdolność w zakresie wdrażania środków kontroli i śledzenia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orientacyjny budżet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planowana data publikacji ogłoszenia o zamówieniu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Luty 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacje dodatkowe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>nd.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Podstawa prawna(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 236/2014 z dnia 11.3.2014 ustanawiające wspólne zasady i procedury wdrażania unijnych instrumentów na rzecz finansowania działań zewnętrznych i rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (WE) nr 1905/2006 z dnia 18.12.2006 ustanawiające instrument finansowania współpracy na rzecz rozwoju; zob. załącznik A2 do „Praktycznego przewodnika”.</P><P>należy mieć świadomość, że po wystąpieniu Zjednoczonego Królestwa z UE brytyjscy kandydaci i oferenci będą podlegać zasadom dostępu do unijnych procedur udzielania zamówień podmiotom gospodarczym w państwach trzecich w zależności od wyniku negocjacji. W sytuacji, gdy przepisy prawa obowiązujące w chwili udzielenia zamówienia nie będą przewidywać takiego dostępu, kandydaci lub oferenci ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa mogą zostać ominięci w postępowaniu o udzielenie zamówienia.</P><P>(1) Proszę wskazać jakiekolwiek szczególne warunki, które mogą mieć wpływ na zasady uczestnictwa (na przykład geograficzne lub tematyczne, długo- lub krótkoterminowe).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Uwagi:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Między publikacją niniejszego wstępnego ogłoszenia informacyjnego a publikacją odpowiedniego ogłoszenia o zamówieniu musi upłynąć co najmniej 30 dni kalendarzowych.</P><P>Na tym etapie nie należy przesyłać wniosków ani zapytań o informacje.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Odborná pomoc na posilnenie regulačného, inštitucionálneho a sanitárneho rámca udržateľnej živočíšnej výroby a jej diverzifikácie</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Predbežné oznámenie o verejnom obstarávaní služieb</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguaj</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčné číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Konanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užšia súťaž.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Názov programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Podpora diverzifikovanej a udržateľnej živočíšnej výroby</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zdroj financovania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verejný obstarávateľ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministerstvo poľnohospodárstva a živočíšnej výroby Paraguajskej republiky</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguaj. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Charakter verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Odplatná zmluva.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Predmetom tohto obstarávania je podpora a posilnenie regulačného a inštitucionálneho rámca pre udržateľnú živočíšnu výrobu a jej diverzifikáciu s líniami činností zameranými na posilnenie inštitucionálnych kapacít verejného sektora a poskytnutie súkromnému sektoru vnútroštátnych odvetvových politiky, právnych predpisov a služieb priaznivých pre jeho rozvoj vrátane záležitostí súvisiacich s udržateľnou živočíšnou výrobou v politikách a vnútroštátnych právnych predpisoch.</P><P>Okrem toho musí zahŕňať posilnenie sanitárneho rámca pre netradičné odvetvia živočíšnej výroby (kravské mlieko, hydina a jej vedľajšie produkty, ošípané, ovce, kozy, akvakultúra, včelárstvo) s líniami činností zameranými na posilnenie alebo rozšírenie rozsahu vnútroštátnej kvalitatívnej a sanitárnej infraštruktúry pre tieto odvetvia živočíšnej výroby vrátane jej kapacity na vykonávanie kontroly a vysledovateľnosti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predbežný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dátum plánovaného zverejnenia vyhlásenia verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Február 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatočné informácie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Neuplatniteľné.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právny základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 236/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovujú spoločné pravidlá a postupy pre vykonávanie nástrojov Únie na financovanie vonkajšej činnosti, a nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (ES) č. 1905/2006 z 18.12.2006, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj financovania rozvojovej spolupráce; pozri prílohu A2 k Praktickej príručke.</P><P>Pripomíname, že po vystúpení Spojeného kráľovstva z EÚ sa na záujemcov alebo uchádzačov zo Spojeného kráľovstva, v závislosti od výsledku rokovaní, budú uplatňovať pravidlá prístupu k postupom obstarávania EÚ zo strany hospodárskych subjektov so sídlom v tretích krajinách. V prípade, že takýto prístup sa nezabezpečí ustanoveniami platnými v čase pridelenia zákazky, záujemcovia alebo uchádzači zo Spojného kráľovstva môžu byť vylúčení z obstarávacieho konania.</P><P>(1) Uveďte všetky špecifiká, ktoré by mohli mať vplyv na pravidlá účasti (napríklad geografické alebo tematické, dlhodobé alebo krátkodobé).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Medzi uverejnením predbežného oznámenia a uverejnením príslušného oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania musí uplynúť minimálne 30 kalendárnych dní.</P><P>V tomto období sa nesmú zasielať žiadne prihlášky ani žiadosti o informácie.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Tehnična pomoč pri krepitvi regulativnega, institucionalnega in sanitarnega okvira za trajnostno živinorejo in njeno diverzifikacijo</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Predhodno informativno obvestilo o naročilu storitev</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paragvaj</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčna številka objave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postopek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Omejeni.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Spodbujanje raznolike in trajnostne živinoreje</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministrstvo za poljedelstvo in živinorejo Republike Paragvaj</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paragvaj. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vrsta naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Naročilo na podlagi plačila.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Namen naročila je podpreti in okrepiti regulativni in institucionalni okvira za trajnostno živinorejo in njeno diverzifikacijo, in sicer z usmerjenimi ukrepi, ki bodo okrepili institucionalne zmogljivosti javnega sektorja ter zasebnemu sektorju zagotovili nacionalne sektorske politike, zakonodajo in storitve, ki bodo spodbujale njegov razvoj, vključno z vprašanji v zvezi s trajnostno živinorejo v politikah in nacionalni zakonodaji.</P><P>Poleg tega mora vključevati tudi krepitev sanitarnega okvira za netradicionalne živinorejske sektorje (kravje mleko, perutninarstvo in stranski proizvodi, prašičereja, ovčereja, kozjereja, ribogojstvo in čebelarstvo), in sicer z usmerjenimi ukrepi, ki bodo okrepili ali razširili razpon nacionalne infrastrukture za zagotavljanje kakovosti in zdravja v teh živinorejskih sektorjih, vključno s sposobnostjo izvajanja nadzora in sledljivostjo.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Okvirni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predvideni datum objave obvestila o naročilu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Februar 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ni navedeno.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravna podlaga(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uredba (EU) št. 236/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o določitvi skupnih pravil in postopkov za izvajanje instrumentov Unije za financiranje zunanjega delovanja in Uredba (ES) št. 1905/2006 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 18.12.2006 o vzpostavitvi instrumenta za financiranje razvojnega sodelovanja; glejte Prilogo A2 k Praktičnemu vodniku.</P><P>Upoštevajte, da se bodo po izstopu Združenega kraljestva iz EU pravila za dostop do razpisnih postopkov EU s strani gospodarskih subjektov, ustanovljenih v tretjih državah, za kandidate ali ponudnike iz Združenega kraljestva uporabljala v skladu z rezultati pogajanj. V primeru, da v času oddaje naročila veljavne pravne določbe ne zagotavljajo tovrstnega dostopa, se lahko kandidatom ali ponudnikom iz Združenega kraljestva sodelovanje v razpisnem postopku zavrne.</P><P>(1) Prosimo, navedite kakršno koli posebnost, ki bi lahko vplivala na pravila sodelovanja (na primer geografsko ali tematsko, dolgoročno ali kratkoročno).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opombe:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Med objavo tega predhodnega informativnega obvestila in objavo ustreznega obvestila o naročilu mora preteči najmanj 30 koledarskih dni.</P><P>V tej fazi ne pošiljajte prijav ali zahtevkov za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Cúnamh teicniúil chun an creat rialála, institiúideach agus sláintíochta maidir le táirgeadh beostoic inbhuanaithe agus a éagsúlú a neartú</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Fógra réamhaisnéise le haghaidh seirbhísí</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paragua</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nós imeachta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Teoranta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ainm an chláir</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Táirgeadh Beostoic Inbhuanaithe agus Éagsúlaithe a chur chun cinn</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Maoiniú</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás Conarthach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Aireacht Talmhaíocht agus Beostoic Phoblacht Pharagua</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paragua. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cineál an chonartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Conradh táillebhunaithe.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ar an gconradh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cuimsítear in ábhar an chonartha seo an creat rialála agus institiúideach maidir le táirgeadh beostoic inbhuanaithe agus a éagsúlú a neartú agus tacú leis, agus tá na modhanna oibre dírithe ar chumais institiúideacha na hearnála poiblí a neartú agus beartais náisiúnta earnála, reachtaíocht agus seirbhísí is fabhrach dá fhorbairt a chur ar fáil don earnáil phríobháideach, lena n-áirítear cúrsaí a bhaineann le táirgeadh beostoic inbhuanaithe i mbeartais agus sa reachtaíocht náisiúnta.</P><P>Lena chois sin, ní mór neartú an chreata sláintíochta le haghaidh earnálacha beostoic neamhthráidisiúnta (bainne bó, éanlaith chlóis agus a seachtháirgí, muiceoil, caoirigh, gadhair, talmhaíocht, beachadóireacht) bheith san áireamh leis, agus beidh na modhanna oibre dírithe ar leathnú raon feidhme na cáilíochta náisiúnta agus an chreat sláintíochta a neartú do na hearnálacha beostoic sin, lena n-áirítear a chumas le haghaidh cur chun feidhme a rialú agus le haghaidh inrianaitheachta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buiséad táscach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>An dáta foilsithe atá beartaithe don fhógra conartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Feabhra 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis bhreise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ní bhaineann le hábhar.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bunús dlí (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rialachán AE Uimh. 236/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 ina leagtar síos rialacha agus nósanna imeachta comhchoiteanna le haghaidh chur chun feidhme ionstraimí an Aontais chun an ghníomhaíocht sheachtrach a mhaoiniú agus Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 1905/2006 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 18.12.2006, lena mbunaítear ionstraim mhaoinithe maidir le comhar um fhorbairt; féach Iarscríbhinn A2 den Treoir Phraiticiúil.</P><P>Tabhair faoi deara go gcuirfear na rialacha um rochtain ar nósanna imeachta AE oibreoirí eacnamaíocha atá bunaithe i dtríú tíortha i bhfeidhm ar thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe (RA) tar éis don RA tarraingt siar ón AE, ag brath ar thorthaí na hidirbheartaíochta. I gcás nach bhfuil rochtain dá leithéid cumhdaithe faoi na forálacha dlíthiúla a bheidh i bhfeidhm nuair a dhámhfar an conradh, d'fhéadfaí diúltú d’iarrthóirí nó do thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe ón nós imeachta soláthair.</P><P>(1) Tabhair le fios aon ghné faoi leith a bhféadfadh tionchar a imirt ar na rialacha rannpháirtíochta (cuir i gcás, gné thíreolaíoch nó théamach, gné fhadtéarmach nó ghearrthéarmach).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Nótaí:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Ní mór tréimhse 30 lá féilire ar a laghad a bheith idir foilsiú an fhógra réamhaisnéise seo agus foilsiú an fhógra conartha chomhfhreagraigh.</P><P>Níor cheart aon iarratais ná iarrataí ar fhaisnéis a sheoladh faoi láthair.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Асунсион: Техническа помощ за подсилване на регулаторната, институционалната и здравната рамка на устойчивото животновъдство и неговото многообразие</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Обявление за предварителна информация за услуги</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Парагвай</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Референтен номер на публикация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Процедура</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ограничена.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Наименование на програмата</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Промотиране на разнообразно и устойчиво животновъдство</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Финансиране</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Министерството на земеделието и животновъдството на република Парагвай</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Асунсион</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Парагвай. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Вид на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Комисионна поръчка.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Описание на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Целта на тази поръчка включва подкрепа и подсилване на регулаторната и институционална рамка за устойчиво животновъдство и неговото разнообразяване, като насоките на действие целят да подсилят институционалните възможности на публичния сектор и да предоставят на частния сектор национални секторни политики, законодателство и услуги, благоприятни за развитието му, включително въпроси, свързани с устойчивото животновъдство, в политиките и националното законодателство.</P><P>Освен това, тя трябва да включва подсилването на здравната рамка за нетрадиционните животновъдски сектори (краве мляко, пилета и техните странични продукти, прасета, агнета, кози, аквакултури, пчелни продукти), с насоки на действие, целящи да подсилят или разширят обхвата на националното качество и здравната инфраструктура за тези животновъдски сектори, включително възможността й да контролира изпълнението и проследимостта.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Индикативен бюджет</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Предвидена дата за публикуване на обявлението за поръчка</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>февруари 2018 г.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Допълнителна информация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Няма</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Правно основание (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Регламент (ЕС) № 236/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за определяне на общи правила и процедури за изпълнението на инструментите на Съюза за финансиране на външната дейност и Регламент (ЕО) № 1905/2006 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 18.12.2006 г. за създаване на финансов инструмент за сътрудничество за развитие; вж. приложение А2 на Практическото ръководство.</P><P>Моля, имайте предвид, че след оттеглянето на Обединеното кралство от ЕС, правилата за достъп до процедури за обществени поръчки на ЕС за икономически оператори, установени в трети държави, ще се прилагат за кандидати или оференти от Обединеното кралство, в зависимост от резултата от преговорите. В случай че такъв достъп не е предвиден в действащите правни разпоредби, които са в сила по време на възлагането на поръчката, кандидатите или оферентите от Обединеното кралство могат да бъдат пропуснати в процедурата за обществена поръчка.</P><P>(1) Моля, посочете всяка конкретна особеност, която може да окаже въздействие върху правилата за участие (напр. географска или тематична, кратък или дълъг срок).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Забележки:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Трябва да има минимален период от 30 календарни дни между публикуването на това обявление за предварителна информация и публикуването на съответното обявление за поръчка.</P><P>На този етап не трябва да се изпращат никакви молби или искания за информация.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Asistență tehnică pentru consolidarea cadrului normativ, instituțional și sanitar al producției durabile de origine animală și diversificarea acesteia</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anunț de intenție privind un contract de achiziții publice de servicii</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paraguay</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referința publicației</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedură</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restrânsă.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titlul programului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Promovarea producției diversificate și durabile de origine animală</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanțare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea contractantă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministerul Agriculturii și Creșterii Animalelor din Republica Paraguay</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paraguay. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contract bazat pe onorarii.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Obiectul acestui contract implică susținerea și consolidarea cadrului normativ și instituțional pentru o producție durabilă de origine animală și diversificarea acesteia, cu acțiuni menite să consolideze capacitățile instituționale ale sectorului public și să ofere sectorului privat politicile, legislația și serviciile sectoriale naționale favorabile dezvoltării sale, inclusiv aspecte legate de producția durabilă de origine animală în cadrul politicilor și legislației naționale.</P><P>Mai mult, trebuie să includă consolidarea cadrului sanitar pentru sectoarele de creștere a animalelor netradiționale (lapte de vacă, păsări de curte și subproduse sale, carnea de porc, oaie, capre, acvacultură, apicultură), cu acțiuni menite să consolideze sau să extindă domeniul de aplicare a infrastructurii naționale de calitate și sanitare pentru aceste sectoare de creștere a animalelor, inclusiv capacitățile sale de implementare a controlului și de trasabilitate.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buget indicativ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data publicării prevăzute a anunțului de participare:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Februarie 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informații suplimentare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nu este cazul.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Temeiul juridic (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulamentul (UE) nr. 236/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de stabilire a normelor și procedurilor comune pentru punerea în aplicare a instrumentelor Uniunii pentru finanțarea acțiunii externe și Regulamentul (CE) nr. 1905/2006 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 18.12.2006 de stabilire a unui instrument de finanțare a cooperării pentru dezvoltare; a se vedea anexa A2 din Ghidul practic.</P><P>A se avea în vedere că, după retragerea Regatului Unit din UE, normele de acces al operatorilor economici stabiliți în țări terțe la procedurile de achiziții publice ale UE se vor aplica ofertanților sau candidaților din Regatul Unit în funcție de rezultatul negocierilor. În cazul în care acest acces nu este reglementat de dispozițiile juridice în vigoare la momentul atribuirii contractului, candidații sau ofertanții din Regatul Unit ar putea fi omiși din procedura de achiziții publice.</P><P>(1) Vă rugăm să indicați orice particularitate care ar putea avea un impact asupra regulilor de participare (de exemplu, geografică sau tematică, pe termen lung sau pe termen scurt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observații:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Trebuie respectată o perioadă de minimum 30 de zile calendaristice între publicarea prezentului anunț de intenție și publicarea anunțului de participare corespunzător.</P><P>În această etapă nu se acceptă candidaturi sau cereri de informații.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>PY-Asunción: Tehnička pomoć za jačanje regulatornog, institucijskog i sanitarnog okvira održive proizvodnje stoke i njezinu diversifikaciju</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Prethodna informacijska obavijest o uslugama</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paragvaj</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uputa na objavu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeaid/139378/IH/SER/PY</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postupak</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograničeni.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naziv programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Promoviranje diversificirane i održive proizvodnje stoke</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>LA/2016/039050</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ministarstvo poljoprivrede i stočarstva Republike Paragvaj</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Asunción</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Paragvaj. </BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Priroda ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Temeljen na naknadama.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Predmet ugovora obuhvaća podršku i jačanje regulatornog i institucijskog okvira za održivu proizvodnju stoke i njezinu diversifikaciju, s akcijama usmjerenim na jačanje institucionalnih kapaciteta javnog sektora te pružanje nacionalnih sektorskih politika, zakonodavstva i usluga povoljnih za razvoj javnog sektora, uključujući pitanja vezana uz održivu proizvodnju stoke u politikama i nacionalnom zakonodavstvu.</P><P>Nadalje, mora obuhvaćati jačanje sanitarnog okvira za netradicionalne stočarske sektore (kravlje mlijeko, perad i nusproizvodi, svinjetina, ovčetina, kozletina, akvakultura, pčelarski proizvodi), s akcijama usmjerenim na jačanje ili širenje opsega nacionalne kvalitete i sanitarne infrastrukture za ove stočarske sektore, uključujući sposobnost za provedbu kontrole i sljedivost.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indikativni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2 500 000,00 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum predviđene objave poziva na nadmetanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Veljača 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nije primjenjivo.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravni temelj(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uredba (EU) br. 236/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014 o utvrđivanju zajedničkih pravila i postupaka za provedbu instrumenata Unije za financiranje vanjskog djelovanja i Uredba (EZ) br. 1905/2006 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 18.12.2006 o uspostavljanju instrumenta financiranja za razvojnu suradnju; vidjeti Prilog A2 Praktičnom vodiču.</P><P>Napominjemo da će se nakon povlačenja Ujedinjene Kraljevine iz EU-a na natjecatelje ili ponuditelje iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine primjenjivati pravila pristupa postupcima nabave EU-a za gospodarske subjekte s poslovnim nastanom u trećim zemljama, ovisno o rezultatima pregovora. U slučaju da pristup nije omogućen putem pravnih odredbi koje su na snazi u vrijeme sklapanja ugovora, natjecatelji ili ponuditelji iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine mogu biti odbijeni iz postupka javne nabave.</P><P>(1) Navedite bilo koju posebnu značajku koja može utjecati na pravila o sudjelovanju (geografska ili tematska, dugoročna ili kratkoročna).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Napomene:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Između objave ove prethodne informacijske obavijesti i objave odgovarajućeg poziva na nadmetanje mora proći najmanje 30 kalendarskih dana.</P><P>U toj se fazi ne smiju slati prijave ili zahtjevi za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>