<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="066857-2018" EDITION="2018031"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-066900-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180322</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>31</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180214</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 031-066857</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:066857-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN DE FR</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="66151000">Financial market operational services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180209</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180322</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="Z">Not specified</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>OB302</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Tyskland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Offentliggjort bekendtgørelse om begrænset udbud 2690 med forudgående prækvalifikationsprocedure</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Deutschland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bekanntmachung beschränkte ausschreibung Nr. 2690 mit vorausgehender Präqualifikation</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Germany</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Published notice restricted invitation to tender 2690 with preceding pre-qualification procedure</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Alemania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Múnich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anuncio publicado licitación restringida 2690 con precedente procedimiento de precalificación</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Saksa</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Julkaistu ilmoitus rajoitetusta tarjouspyynnöstä 2690 (jota edeltää esikarsintamenettely)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Allemagne</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Avis d' appel à la concurrence restreint 2690 précédé d’une procédure de présélection</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Γερμανία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Μόναχο</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Δημοσιευθείσα προκήρυξη κλειστής πρόσκλησης υποβολής προσφορών αριθ. 2690 με προηγηθείσα διαδικασία προεπιλογής</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Germania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Monaco di Baviera</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Avviso pubblicato relativo al bando di gara ristretta 2690, preceduta da una procedura di prequalifica</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Duitsland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bekendmaking van aankondiging van niet-openbare uitnodiging tot inschrijving nr. 2690 met voorafgaande prekwalificatieprocedure</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Alemanha</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munique</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anúncio publicado de convite limitado a concurso 2690 com procedimento de pré-qualificação prévio</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Tyskland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Publicerat meddelande om selektiv anbudsinfordran nr 2690 med föregående förhandsförfarande</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Německo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Mnichov</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Zveřejnění oznámení o výzvě k účasti v užším nabídkovém řízení č. 2690 s předcházejícím řízením předběžné kvalifikace</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Saksamaa</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Avaldatud teade – piiratud hankemenetlus 2690, eelneva eelkvalifitseerimismenetlusega</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Németország</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Közzététel: 2690. számú meghívásos pályázati eljárás, megelőző előminősítési eljárással</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Vokietija, VFR</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Miunchenas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Paskelbtas pranešimas dėl kvietimo dalyvauti ribotame konkurse 2690 su išankstine atrankos procedūra</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Vācija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Minhene</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Publicētais paziņojums par uzaicinājumu uz slēgtu konkursu 2690 ar iepriekšēju priekšatlases procedūru</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Ġermanja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Avviż ippubblikat ta' stedina għall-offerti ristretta 2690 b'proċedura ta' prekwalifikazzjoni li tippreċedi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Niemcy</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Monachium</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Opublikowane ogłoszenie o ograniczonej procedurze przetargowej nr 2690 z uprzednią kwalifikacją wstępną</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Nemecko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Mníchov</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Uverejnené oznámenie o užšej výzve na predkladanie ponúk č. 2690 s predchádzajúcim konaním predbežného výberu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Nemčija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Objavljeno obvestilo: omejen javni razpis 2690 s predhodnim predkvalifikacijskim postopkom</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Ghearmáin, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Fógra foilsithe cuireadh srianta chun tairisceana 2690 le nós imeachta réamhcháilithe roimhe sin</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Гepмaния</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Мюнхен</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Публикувано обявление за ограничена покана за участие в търг 2690 с предходна процедура преди класирането</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Germania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Publicarea anunțului de invitare la licitație restrânsă 2690 anterior procedurii de pre-calificare</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Njemačka</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Objavljena obavijest o ograničenom pozivu za dostavu ponuda 2690 s prethodnim postupkom predkvalifikacije</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Patentorganisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Organisation européenne des brevets (OEB)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Offentliggjort bekendtgørelse om begrænset udbud 2690 med forudgående prækvalifikationsprocedure</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Bekanntmachung beschränkte ausschreibung Nr. 2690 mit vorausgehender Präqualifikation</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Auftraggeber:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Patentorganisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, handelnd durch das Europäische Patentamt mit Hauptsitz in D-80469 München, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, Postanschrift: EPA, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>München</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, DEUTSCHLAND.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Die Europäische Patentorganisation ist eine zwischenstaatliche Organisation, die durch das 1977 in Kraft getretene Europäische Patentübereinkommen gegründet wurde. Ihr gehören derzeit 38 Mitgliedstaaten an (Albanien, Belgien, Bulgarien, Dänemark, Deutschland, ehemalige jugoslawische Republik Mazedonien, Estland, Finnland, Frankreich, Griechenland, Irland, Island, Italien, Kroatien, Lettland, Liechtenstein, Litauen, Luxemburg, Malta, Monaco, Niederlande, Norwegen, Österreich, Polen, Portugal, Rumänien, San Marino, Schweden, Schweiz, Serbien, Slowakei, Slowenien, Spanien, Tschechische Republik, Türkei, Ungarn, Vereinigtes Königreich und Zypern). Ausführendes Organ der EPO ist das Europäische Patentamt, das die Recherche und Prüfung europäischer Patentanmeldungen und die Erteilung europäischer Patente zur Aufgabe hat. Es beschäftigt rund 6 700 Bedienstete am Hauptsitz des EPA in München, in einer Zweigstelle in Den Haag/Rijswijk (NL) und in zwei Dienststellen in Berlin und Wien. (Die Zahl der Mitgliedstaaten und der Bediensteten kann sich ändern.)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vergabeverfahren:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Beschränkte Ausschreibung im Leistungswettbewerb</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Gegenstand des Auftrags:</P><P>Dienstleistungen der Asset Manager für Investment-Fonds-Management.</P><P>b) Teilung in Lose:</P><P>Nicht zutreffend.</P><P>c) Erforderliche Sicherheiten und Bürgschaften:</P><P>„wird in den Ausschreibungsunterlagen definiert;“</P><P>d) Wichtigste Zahlungsbedingungen:</P><P>Innerhalb von 30 Tagen nach Abschluss und Abnahme der Arbeiten Wiederkehrende Kosten: monatlich im Nachhinein.</P><P>e) Rechtlich vorgeschriebene Qualifikationen:</P><P>Sofern zutreffend für professionelle Finanzdienstleistungen (siehe auch Pre-Auswahlkriterien unter Punkt 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Erfüllungsort und Leistungsfrist:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Erfüllungsort:</P><P>Lieferung bei Ihnen vor Ort, mit gelegentlichen Besprechungen an einer der EPA-Standorte.</P><P>b) Vertragslaufzeit oder Ausführungsfrist:</P><P>Der Vertrag hat eine Laufzeit von drei Jahren ab Vertragsunterzeichnung.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Änderungsvorschläge:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Änderungsvorschläge, die sich in einer erheblichen Einschränkung der Rechte und Sicherheiten der EPO niederschlagen würden, sind nicht zulässig.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vorauswahl und Ausschreibungsverfahren:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Letzter Tag der Frist für die Beantwortung der Vorauswahlfragen (s. Nr. 11 dieser Bekanntmachung):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14.00 Uhr (MEZ)</P><P>Bei Interesse an der Teilnahme an diesem Ausschreibungsverfahren beantworten Sie bitte die Vorauswahlfragen unter Nr. 11 (Sonstige Angaben) und übermitteln Sie Ihre Antwort an die unter Nr. 6 e) angegebene E-Mail-Adresse.</P><P>Laden Sie außerdem die folgenden Fragebogen herunter: http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Folgen Sie den Anweisungen auf dem Deckblatt, füllen Sie das entsprechende Dokument aus, unterzeichnen Sie diese und senden Sie sie wie folgt an das EPA:</P><P>Scannen Sie den ausgefüllten und unterzeichneten Fragebogen und schicken Sie sie bis zum vorstehend genannten Datum an die unter Nr. 6 e) angegebene E-Mail-Adresse und Postanschrift.</P><P>Da die Antworten auf die Vorauswahlfragen eventuell einer Klarstellung bedürfen, würde es das EPA begrüßen, wenn Interessenten ihre Fragen zu die Vorauswahlfragen bis 21.2.2018; 12:00 (MEZ) übermitteln, damit die nachfolgenden Fristen eingehalten werden.</P><P>b) Versand der Verdingungsunterlagen:</P><P>Die Verdingungsunterlagen werden nur an bis zu 15 potenzielle Anbieter verschickt. Die potenziellen Anbieter werden auf Basis eine Evaluierung der Antworten auf die Vorauswahlfragen durchgeführt. Dieser Vorauswahl basiert auf:</P><P>Kriterien gemäß Punkt 11: 50 %</P><P>Weitere Information gemäß Fragebogen: 50 %</P><P>Der Versand der Verdingungsunterlagen an die ausgewählten Teilnehmer ist für den 1.3.2018 geplant.</P><P>c) Annahmeschluss für Rückfragen bei der EPO:</P><P>— Vorläufig geplant für 9.3.18. Das genaue Datum wird den geeigneten Teilnehmern mit dem Versand der Verdingungsunterlagen mitgeteilt,</P><P>— Rückfragen sind schriftlich oder per E-Mail einzureichen.</P><P>d) Annahmeschluss für Angebote/Zahl der einzureichenden Ausfertigungen:</P><P>— Vorläufig geplant für 22.3.18. Das genaue Datum wird den geeigneten Teilnehmern mit dem Versand der Verdingungsunterlagen mitgeteilt,</P><P>— Angebote sind in einer Originalausfertigung mit Preisangaben (Angebotsformblatt und Begleitunterlagen) sowie einer Ausfertigung ohne Preisangaben einzureichen, Letztere als durchsuchbare PDF-Datei auf einem Datenträger.</P><P>e) Anschrift, an die Rückfragen, Antworten auf die Vorauswahlfragen und das Angebot zu richten sind:</P><P>Europäisches Patentamt, (2690 Selection), Zentrale Beschaffung München, Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1, 80469 München, E-Mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Bitte reichen Sie Ihr Angebot nur per Post und nicht per Fax oder per E-Mail ein. Per Fax oder per E-Mail eingereichte Angebote werden ausgeschlossen.</P><P>f) Sprache oder Sprachen, in denen Rückfragen, Vorauswahlfragen und das Angebot abzufassen sind:</P><P>Englisch,</P><P>Die Verdingungsunterlagen sind nur auf Englisch erhältlich.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsform einer Bietergemeinschaft:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Reichen mehrere Bieter ein gemeinsames Angebot ein, so haften sie gesamtschuldnerisch für die Erfüllung der vertraglichen Verpflichtungen. Zusammen mit dem Angebot ist eine entsprechende von allen Mitgliedern der Bietergemeinschaft unterzeichnete Erklärung einzureichen, in der ein Vertreter bestimmt ist, der bevollmächtigt ist, für alle Mitglieder zu handeln.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kriterien für die Beurteilung der zur Auftragsausführung erforderlichen Fachkunde, Leistungsfähigkeit und Zuverlässigkeit des Bieters:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Angebote von Bietern, die nicht die unter Nr. 11 genannten Auswahlkriterien erfüllen und/oder deren finanzielle und professionelle Zuverlässigkeit aufgrund ihrer Verhältnisse ernstlich infrage steht (s. Artikel 2 der Allgemeinen Ausschreibungsbedingungen, abrufbar unter www.epo.org), sind von der Auftragsvergabe ausgeschlossen.</P><P>Die zur Auftragsausführung erforderliche Fachkunde, Leistungsfähigkeit und Zuverlässigkeit des Bieters wird auf der Grundlage der Angaben und Nachweise beurteilt, die in Beantwortung des Fragebogens in Anhang 1 der Allgemeinen Ausschreibungsbedingungen und zusätzlicher Fragebögen zu den Verdingungsunterlagen erbracht werden.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bindefrist:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sechs Monate ab dem Annahmeschluss für Angebote, der mit dem Versand der Verdingungsunterlagen mitgeteilt wird.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kriterien für die Zuschlagserteilung:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kriterien für die Zuschlagserteilung:</P><P>Der Zuschlag wird dem Bieter erteilt, der am besten in der Lage ist, die Anforderungen des EPA zu erfüllen. Ausschlaggebend sind dabei:</P><P>Finanzielle Aspekte: 30 %</P><P>Technische Aspekte: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sonstige Angaben:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bieter, die sich für die Teilnahme an dieser Ausschreibung interessieren, übermitteln ihre Antworten auf die nachstehenden Fragen in Tabellenform sowie die erforderlichen Nachweise bis zum unter Nr. 6 a) genannten Datum an die unter Nr. 6 e) angegebene E-Mail-Adresse.</P><P>Vorauswahlfragen</P><P>Wirtschaftliche und finanzielle Kapazität des Bieters</P><P>1. Bestätigen Sie bitte, dass Sie ein Gesamtvermögen von mindestens 100 Milliarden EUR verwalten, davon mindestens 10 Milliarden EUR in Multi-Asset-Strategien;</P><P>2. Bestätigen Sie bitte, dass Sie nachweislich über mindestens fünf Jahre Erfahrung mit Multi-Asset-Strategien verfügen;</P><P>3. Erklären Sie, dass Ihr Unternehmen nicht insolvent ist oder abgewickelt wird, die gewerbliche Tätigkeit nicht eingestellt oder ausgesetzt hat, nicht einer gerichtlichen Verwaltung unterstellt ist, keine Vereinbarungen mit Gläubigern getroffen hat bzw. sich nicht in einer ähnlichen Lage befindet;</P><P>4. Bestätigen Sie, dass die EPO über eine externe Quelle eine Bonitätsprüfung Ihres Unternehmens durchführen darf;</P><P>5. Nennen Sie die Kontaktdaten und Namen der Mitarbeiter, die befugt sind, im Namen Ihres Unternehmens zu unterzeichnen, und fügen Sie einen aktuellen Auszug aus dem Handelsregister oder einem ähnlichen Verzeichnis für Ihr Unternehmen bei (ggf. ergänzt durch weitere Informationen). Falls das Register keine entsprechenden konkreten Angaben enthält, ist für eine Bevollmächtigung zu sorgen;</P><P>Wirtschaftliche und professionelle Kapazität des Bieters</P><P>6. Bestätigen Sie bitte, dass Sie in der Lage sind, die Mehrheit der Anlagekategorien im Rahmen der Multi-Asset-Strategie aktiv zu verwalten;</P><P>7. Bestätigen Sie bitte, dass Sie Ihre Multi-Asset-Strategie mit einer deutschen KVG als Subsegment einer Master-KVG, d. h. auf einem getrennt geführten Konto implementieren können;</P><P>8. Bestätigen Sie bitte, dass Sie in der Lage sind, ein Mandat mit Zugang zu einem breiten Spektrum von Renditetreibern umzusetzen (mindestens Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Bestätigen Sie bitte, dass Sie Marktanteile in Multi-Asset-Strategien vor allem durch nicht derivative (Cash-) Instrumente erwerben können;</P><P>9. Reichen Sie mindestens drei Referenzen/schriftliche Kundenberichte von früheren Kunden ein, für die Sie die vorstehend genannten Leistungen in Europa erbracht haben. Es sollte die folgende Struktur verwendet werden:</P><P>— Allgemeine Angaben:</P><P>Name der Organisation/Land - Standorte/Wirtschaftszweig;</P><P>— Einzelheiten:</P><P>Beschreibung der Leistungen und wichtigste technische Einzelheiten des Umfanges / Zeitraum der Leistung</P><P>Beachten Sie Nr. 6 b) und c) bezüglich der auf die Vorauswahlphase folgenden Schritte.</P><P>Derzeit wird davon ausgegangen, dass der Zuschlag im Juni 2018 erteilt wird.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munich: Published notice restricted invitation to tender 2690 with preceding pre-qualification procedure</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Múnich: Anuncio publicado licitación restringida 2690 con precedente procedimiento de precalificación</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Julkaistu ilmoitus rajoitetusta tarjouspyynnöstä 2690 (jota edeltää esikarsintamenettely)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munich: Avis d' appel à la concurrence restreint 2690 précédé d’une procédure de présélection</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autorité responsable du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>L'</BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Organisation européenne des brevets (OEB)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, agissant par l'intermédiaire de l'Office européen des brevets; sise: Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich; adresse postale: OEB, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ALLEMAGNE.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>L'Organisation européenne des brevets est une organisation intergouvernementale créée conformément à la Convention sur le brevet européen qui est entrée en vigueur en 1977. Elle compte actuellement 38 Etats membres (l'Albanie, l’Allemagne, l’Autriche, la Belgique, la Bulgarie, Chypre, la Croatie, le Danemark, l’Espagne, l'Estonie, l'ex-République yougoslave de Macédoine, la Finlande, la France, la Grèce, la Hongrie, l’Irlande, l’Islande, l’Italie, la Lettonie, le Liechtenstein, la Lituanie, le Luxembourg, Malte, Monaco, la Norvège, les Pays-Bas, la Pologne, le Portugal, la Roumanie, le Royaume-Uni, Saint-Marin, la Serbie, la Slovaquie, la Slovénie, la Suède, la Suisse, la République tchèque et la Turquie). L'organe exécutif de l'OEB est l'Office européen des brevets, qui est chargé de la recherche et de l'examen concernant les demandes de brevet européen et de la délivrance de brevets européens. Il emploie environ 6700 agents en poste à son siège à Munich, dans son département à La Haye/Rijswijk (NL) et dans ses agences à Berlin et à Vienne (le nombre d'Etats membres et d'agents indiqués peut changer).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Mode de passation du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Appel d'offres restreint avec attribution discrétionnaire</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Objet du marché:</P><P>Fourniture de Services d’Asset Manager pour la gestion de fonds d’investissement</P><P>b) Partage en lots:</P><P>Sans objet.</P><P>c) Dépôts et garanties exigés:</P><P>«seront définis dans les documents d’appel d’offres»</P><P>d) Principales conditions relatives au paiement:</P><P>Dans un délai de 30 jours après la réalisation et l'acceptation.</P><P>Charges récurrentes: paiements mensuels à terme échu</P><P>e) Qualifications exigées par la loi:</P><P>Le cas échéant pour la fourniture de services financiers professionnels (voir aussi les critères de présélection au point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lieu et période d'exécution:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Lieu où le marché doit être exécuté:</P><P>Livraison dans vos locaux, avec des réunions occasionnelles à l’un des sites de l’OEB.</P><P>b) Durée du contrat ou délai de livraison ou d'exécution des prestations:</P><P>Le contrat aura une durée de 3 ans à compter de la signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variantes:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les propositions de variantes susceptibles de réduire de façon significative les droits et garanties de l'OEB ne sont pas autorisées.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure de présélection et d'appel d'offres:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Date limite de réponse aux questions de présélection (voir le point 11 du présent Avis):</P><P>Le 28.2.2018 à 14:00 heures (HEC)</P><P>Les parties intéressées peuvent faire part de leur intérêt à participer à la procédure d'appel d'offres en répondant par e-mail aux questions de présélection telles que décrites au point 11 (Autres informations) à l'adresse électronique indiquée au point 6e du présent Avis.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Suivre les instructions sur la page de couverture, compléter et signer les copies du document résultant et l’envoyer à l’OEB:</P><P>Scanner le complété et signé et envoyer par email ce scan à l’adresse mail et l’adresse postale de L’OEB indiquée sous le point 6e du présent avis à la date mentionnée ci-dessus</P><P>Comme une clarification des réponses aux questions de pré-sélection peut être nécessaire, l'OEB apprécierait si les parties intéressées soumettent leurs questions aux questions de présélection avant le 21.2.2018 à 12:00 heures (HEC) afin de respecter les échéanciers suivants.</P><P>b) Envoi du cahier des charges:</P><P>Le cahier des charges ne sera communiqué qu’aux quinze candidats éligibles. Les candidats éligibles seront sélectionnés selon l’évaluation des réponses du questionnaire. Les présélections seront mesurées sur les bases de:</P><P>Critère du point 11: 50 %</P><P>Autres informations détaillées dans le questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>La diffusion du cahier des charges est prévue pour le 1.3.2018</P><P>c) Date limite de réception par l'OEB des demandes de précisions:</P><P>— Provisoirement prévue pour fin 9.3.2018. La date exacte sera communiquée aux candidats éligibles lors de l'envoi du cahier des charges,</P><P>— Les questions doivent parvenir par lettre ou par courrier électronique.</P><P>d) Date limite de dépôt des offres - nombre d'exemplaires à envoyer à l'Office:</P><P>— Provisoirement prévue pour fin 21.3.2018. La date exacte sera communiquée aux candidats éligibles lors de l'envoi du cahier des charges,</P><P>— L'offre doit comprendre d'une part un exemplaire original avec indication de prix (formulaire d'offre ‘offer form’ et documents à l'appui), d'autre part une copie sur support de données (sous forme de fichier PDF recherchable et sans indication de prix).</P><P>e) Adresse à laquelle doivent être envoyées les demandes de précisions, de réponse aux questions de présélection et les offres:</P><P>Office européen des brevets</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Service central des achats</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>Adresse électronique: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Les offres doivent être soumises uniquement par courrier, et non par télécopie ou par courrier électronique. Les offres envoyées par télécopie ou par courrier électronique ne seront pas prises en considération.</P><P>f) Langue ou langues dans lesquelles les demandes de précisions, réponse aux questions de présélection et les offres doivent être rédigées:</P><P>Anglais.</P><P>Le cahier des charges n’est disponible qu'en anglais.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Forme légale du groupement, en cas d'offre soumise en commun:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Si des candidats soumettent une offre en commun, ils doivent être conjointement et solidairement responsables de l'exécution des obligations découlant du contrat. Une déclaration à cet effet, dûment signée par tous les membres du groupement et désignant un représentant autorisé à agir pour le compte de tous les membres, doit accompagner l'offre.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critères visant à évaluer les compétences, les capacités et la fiabilité des candidats pour pouvoir exécuter le marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Seront éliminées les offres émanant de candidats qui ne satisfont pas aux critères de sélection énoncés dans le point 11 de cet avis et/ou dont la situation suscite des doutes sérieux quant à leur fiabilité du point de vue financier et professionnel (cf. article 2 des Conditions générales relatives aux appels à la concurrence, qui figurent à l'adresse www.epo.org).</P><P>Les compétences, les capacités et la fiabilité des candidats pour pouvoir exécuter le marché seront évaluées sur la base des informations et pièces justificatives soumises en réponse au questionnaire de l'annexe 1 aux Conditions générales relatives aux appels à la concurrence, et en réponse à tout questionnaire supplémentaire inclus dans le cahier des charges.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Durée obligatoire de validité des offres:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 mois à compter de la date finale de dépôt des offres, qui sera indiquée lors de l'envoi du cahier des charges.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critères d'attribution du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les critères d'attribution et leurs pondérations sont les suivants:</P><P>Aspects financiers: 30 %</P><P>Aspects techniques: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autres informations:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Si les parties sont intéressées pour participer à cet appel d'offres, elles doivent envoyer leurs réponses en anglais aux questions ci-dessous sous forme de tableau, accompagnées des preuves demandées, ainsi à l'adresse électronique mentionnée au point 6e du présent Avis dans l'avis mentionné au point 6a:</P><P>Questions de présélection</P><P>Capacité financière et économique du candidat</P><P>1. Veuillez confirmer que vous appliquez des stratégies à actifs multiples depuis au moins 5 ans;</P><P>2. Veuillez confirmer que votre entreprise n'est pas en situation de faillite, de liquidation, de cessation ou de suspension d'activités, n'est pas sous concordat judiciaire, n'a pas conclu d'accords avec des créanciers et ne se trouve dans aucune situation analogue;</P><P>3. Veuillez confirmer que l'OEB peut effectuer un contrôle de solvabilité dans votre entreprise par l'intermédiaire d'une source externe;</P><P>4. Veuillez fournir les coordonnées et les noms du ou des représentants autorisé(s) à signer au nom de votre entreprise, ainsi qu'un extrait récent du registre du commerce ou d'un registre similaire (si besoin accompagné d'informations supplémentaires). Si ces informations ne sont pas concrètement précisées dans le registre, veuillez prendre vos dispositions pour une procuration.</P><P>Aptitude professionnelle et technique du candidat:</P><P>5. Veuillez confirmer que vous avez la capacité de gérer de façon active la plupart des catégories d’actifs dans le cadre de la stratégie à actifs multiples;</P><P>6. Veuillez confirmer que vous pouvez mettre en œuvre votre stratégie à actifs multiples avec une société allemande de type KVG, sous la forme d’un sous-segment d’une Master-KVG, c’est-à-dire d’un compte distinct;</P><P>7. Veuillez confirmer que vous pouvez exécuter un mandat impliquant l’accès à un large éventail de facteurs de rendement économique (au moins actions mondiales, obligations mondiales et crédit mondial). Veuillez confirmer que vous pouvez gagner en visibilité commerciale dans le cadre des stratégies à actifs multiples au moyen d’instruments (de trésorerie) non dérivés;</P><P>8. Veuillez produire au moins 3 références/témoignages écrits d'anciens clients auxquels le candidat a fourni les services susvisés sur plusieurs sites en Europe au moins. Il convient de suivre le modèle suivant:</P><P>— Informations générales:</P><P>Nom de l'organisation/Pays d'implantation/Secteur d'activité;</P><P>— Informations détaillées:</P><P>Descriptions des services et principaux détails techniques de la solution / Période de prestation des services</P><P>Veuillez tenir compte des points 6 b) et 6 c) pour le suivi de ce qui précède.</P><P>Le marché devrait être attribué au juin 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Μόναχο: Δημοσιευθείσα προκήρυξη κλειστής πρόσκλησης υποβολής προσφορών αριθ. 2690 με προηγηθείσα διαδικασία προεπιλογής</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Monaco di Baviera: Avviso pubblicato relativo al bando di gara ristretta 2690, preceduta da una procedura di prequalifica</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Bekendmaking van aankondiging van niet-openbare uitnodiging tot inschrijving nr. 2690 met voorafgaande prekwalificatieprocedure</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munique: Anúncio publicado de convite limitado a concurso 2690 com procedimento de pré-qualificação prévio</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Publicerat meddelande om selektiv anbudsinfordran nr 2690 med föregående förhandsförfarande</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Mnichov: Zveřejnění oznámení o výzvě k účasti v užším nabídkovém řízení č. 2690 s předcházejícím řízením předběžné kvalifikace</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Avaldatud teade – piiratud hankemenetlus 2690, eelneva eelkvalifitseerimismenetlusega</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Közzététel: 2690. számú meghívásos pályázati eljárás, megelőző előminősítési eljárással</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Miunchenas: Paskelbtas pranešimas dėl kvietimo dalyvauti ribotame konkurse 2690 su išankstine atrankos procedūra</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Minhene: Publicētais paziņojums par uzaicinājumu uz slēgtu konkursu 2690 ar iepriekšēju priekšatlases procedūru</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munich: Avviż ippubblikat ta' stedina għall-offerti ristretta 2690 b'proċedura ta' prekwalifikazzjoni li tippreċedi</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Monachium: Opublikowane ogłoszenie o ograniczonej procedurze przetargowej nr 2690 z uprzednią kwalifikacją wstępną</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Mníchov: Uverejnené oznámenie o užšej výzve na predkladanie ponúk č. 2690 s predchádzajúcim konaním predbežného výberu</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Objavljeno obvestilo: omejen javni razpis 2690 s predhodnim predkvalifikacijskim postopkom</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Fógra foilsithe cuireadh srianta chun tairisceana 2690 le nós imeachta réamhcháilithe roimhe sin</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Мюнхен: Публикувано обявление за ограничена покана за участие в търг 2690 с предходна процедура преди класирането</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Publicarea anunțului de invitare la licitație restrânsă 2690 anterior procedurii de pre-calificare</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Objavljena obavijest o ograničenom pozivu za dostavu ponuda 2690 s prethodnim postupkom predkvalifikacije</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member States and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Asset Manager Services for Investment Funds Management</P><P>b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>Recurring charges: monthly in arrears</P><P>e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional financial services (see also preselection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall have a 3-year duration from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this published notice):</P><P>28.2.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the pre-selection questions as described under point 11 (Other Information) to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/ADDF6A07F2C4194EC125822F005080DD?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire and relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address and the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this published notice by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the pre-selection questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the pre-selection questions by latest 21.2.2018, 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 15 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be measured based on:</P><P>Criteria under point 11: 50 %</P><P>Other information detailed in the questionnaire: 50 %</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 1.3.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 9.3.2018. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or e-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids /number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 22.3.2018. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European Patent Office</P><P>(2690 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire &amp; procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfill the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the general conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to up to three bidders whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 30 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 70 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions below in a table format, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this published notice within the notice mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection questions</P><P>Economic and financial capacity of the bidder</P><P>1— Please confirm that you have at least a track record of 5 years in multi-asset-strategies;</P><P>2— Please confirm that your company is not bankrupt or being wound up, has ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or has entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations;</P><P>3— Please confirm that the EPO may run a solvency check on your company via an external source;</P><P>4— Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5— Please confirm that you have the ability to actively manage the majority of asset classes within a multi-asset-strategy;</P><P>6— Please confirm that you can implement your multi-asset-strategy with a German KVG as a sub-segment of a Master-KVG, i.e. as a segregated account;</P><P>7— Please confirm that you have the ability to implement a mandate with access to a broad range of economic return drivers (at least Global Equity, Global Bonds, Global Credit). Please confirm that you can gain market exposure in multi-asset-strategy primarily through non-derivative (cash) instruments;</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references /written customer testimonials from previous customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name /Country locations /Business sector:</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided /Service period</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this published notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>