<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="067683-2018"
            EDITION="2018031">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-070223-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20190213</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>31</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180214</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 031-067683</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:067683-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>https://www.delta-esourcing.com</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="80650000">Training and simulation in aircrafts, missiles and spacecrafts</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKC">NORTH EAST (ENGLAND)</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKC">NORTH EAST (ENGLAND)</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180213</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C01</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Бристол</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Тренировка и симулация със самолети, ракети и космически кораби</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Školení a simulace v oblasti letadel, raket a kosmických lodí</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Uddannelse og simulering — luftfartøjer, missiler og rumfartøjer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Schulung und Simulation für Luftfahrzeuge, Raketen und Raumfahrzeuge</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Μπρίστολ</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Επιμόρφωση και προσομοίωση σε αεροσκάφη, πυραύλους και διαστημόπλοια</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Training and simulation in aircrafts, missiles and spacecrafts</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Formación y simulación en materia de aeronaves, misiles y naves espaciales</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sõjaväe õhusõidukite, rakettide ja kosmosesõidukite alane koolitus ja simulatsioonid</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ilma-aluksiin, ohjuksiin ja avaruusaluksiin liittyvä koulutus ja simulointi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Formation et simulation dans le domaines des aéronefs, des missiles et des spationefs militaires</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Briostó</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Training and simulation in aircrafts, missiles and spacecrafts</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Izobrazba i simulacija u području letjelica, raketa i svemirskih letjelica</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Repülőgépekkel, rakétákkal és űrhajókkal kapcsolatos képzés és szimulációs gyakorlat</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Formazione e simulazione in materia di velivoli militari, missili e velivoli spaziali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristolis</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Mokymo naudotis karo orlaiviais, raketomis, erdvėlaiviais ir imitavimo paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristole</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Mācības un simulācija gaisa kuģu, raķešu un kosmosa kuģu jomā</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Taħriġ u simulazzjoni fl-ajruplani, il-missilli u l-vetturi spazjali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Opleiding en simulatie met lucht- en ruimtevaartuigen en raketten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Szkolenie i symulacja w zakresie samolotów, rakiet (pocisków rakietowych) i statków kosmicznych</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Formação e simulação em aeronaves, mísseis e naves espaciais militares</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Formare profesională şi simulare în domeniul aeronavelor militare, al proiectilelor şi al navelor spaţiale</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Školenia a simulácie v oblasti lietadiel, rakiet a vesmírnych lodí</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usposabljanje in simulacije na zrakoplovih, raketah in vesoljskih plovilih</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Utbildning och simulering: luftfartyg, robotar och rymdfarkoster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Ministry of Defence, Air Support, C&amp;C</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F01_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F01" LG="EN">
         <NOTICE TYPE="PRI_ONLY"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, Air Support, C&amp;C</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Building 1300, #7001, MOD Abbeywood</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bristol</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>BS34 8JH</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>John Harris</CONTACT_POINT>
               <E_MAIL>john.harris172@mod.gov.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKC"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://www.delta-esourcing.com</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="MINISTRY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Fixed-wing Light Aircraft Training System</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="80650000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>All the information contained within this prior information note does not constitute, and should not be construed as, any commitment by the Ministry of Defence (MOD) to proceed with any aspect of this activity beyond the industry day, to be held on 28.2.2018 at RAF College Cranwell. All further activity is strictly subject to further internal MOD approvals. The training solution must provide fully-aerobatic, light flying training aircraft, sufficiently robust to withstand intensive use; flying hours (a total of circa 36 000 hrs per year); aircraft engineering, operations and Motor Transportation (MT) support at 15 operating locations, dispersed throughout the UK and Northern Ireland.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <LOT_DIVISION>
               <LOT_COMBINING_CONTRACT_RIGHT>
                  <P>This is an option that the authority is currently considering.</P>
               </LOT_COMBINING_CONTRACT_RIGHT>
            </LOT_DIVISION>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <TITLE>
                  <P>Fixed-wing Light Aircraft Training System</P>
               </TITLE>
               <LOT_NO>Lot 1 North, Lot 2 Midlands, Lot 3 South</LOT_NO>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="80650000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKC"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>North East (England).</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The training solution must provide fully-aerobatic, light flying training aircraft, sufficiently robust to withstand intensive use; flying hours (a total of circa 36 000 hours per year); aircraft engineering, operations and Motor Transportation (MT) support at 15 operating locations, dispersed throughout the UK and Northern Ireland. Additional requirements will include: Instructor pilot provision (2 sites): Air Traffic Provision (1 site); and limited Soft Facilities Management (3 sites). There is no synthetic flying requirement and theoretical training is required only in support of the respective single service flying Ggading Syllabi for the Royal Navy and Army elements of the task. Contract duration will be 10 years with possible scope for a further 3 option years.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>To help us develop the requirement we will be holding an Industry Day on Wednesday 28.2.2018 at RAF College Cranwell. Start time TBA. Any suppliers who feel they are capable of delivering the training, as briefly described, are welcome to attend. If you are wishing to attend please contact John Harris.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>2018-05-31</DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The Authority reserves the right to amend any condition related to security of information to reflect any changes in national law or government policy. If any contract documents are accompanied by instructions on safeguarding classified information (e.g. a Security Aspects Letter), the Authority reserves the right to amend the terms of these instructions to reflect any changes in national law or government policy, whether in respect of the applicable protective marking scheme, specific protective markings given, the aspects to which any protective marking applies, or otherwise. The link below to the Gov.uk website provides information on the Government Security Classification.</P>
               <P>https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/government-security-classifications</P>
               <P>Advertising Regime OJEU:- This contract opportunity is published in the Official Journal of the European Union (OJEU),the MoD Defence Contracts Bulletin and www.contracts.mod.uk.</P>
               <P>Suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P>
               <P>The information and/or documents for this opportunity are available on http://www.contracts.mod.uk</P>
               <P>You must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password. Please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P>
               <P>Suppliers must log in, go to your Response Manager and add the following access code: 69TZ96GB48.</P>
               <P>Please ensure you follow any instruction provided to you here.</P>
               <P>The deadline for submitting your response(s) is detailed within this contract notice, you will also have visibility of the deadline date, once you have added the Access code via DCO as the opening and closing date is visible within the opportunity.</P>
               <P>Please ensure that you allow yourself plenty of time when responding to this opportunity prior to the closing date and time, especially if you have been asked to upload documents.</P>
               <P>If you experience any difficulties please refer to the online Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ&#x92;s) or the User Guides or contact the MOD DCO Helpdesk by emailing support@contracts.mod.uk or Telephone 0800 282 324.</P>
               <P>GO Reference: GO-2018213-DCB-11900383.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-13</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F01_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
