<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="045244-2018"
            EDITION="2018021">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-044325-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180321</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>21</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180131</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 021-045244</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:045244-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.vegvesen.no</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="63712200">Highway operation services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45233139">Highway maintenance work</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="50230000">Repair, maintenance and associated services related to roads and other equipment</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="NO053">Møre og Romsdal</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="NO053">Møre og Romsdal</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180129</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180321 15:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="B">European Economic Area (EEA), with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="1">Lowest price</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>03C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>03</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Норвегия</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги, свързани с експлоатация на пътната мрежа</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Norsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Provozování dálnic</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Norge</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Drift af hovedveje</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Norwegen</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Betrieb von Straßen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Νορβηγία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες λειτουργίας αυτοκινητοδρόμων</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Norway</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Highway operation services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Noruega</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de explotación de autopistas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Norra</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Maantee käitamisteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Norja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Teiden käyttöön liittyvät palvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Norvège</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services d'exploitation des autoroutes</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Iorua, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Highway operation services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Norveška</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge upravljanja autocestama</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Norvégia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Autópálya-üzemeltetési szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Norvegia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di gestione autostradale</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Norvegija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Greitkelių eksploatavimo paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Norvēģija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Automaģistrāļu ekspluatācijas pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>in-Norveġja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi operazzjoni f’toroq arterjali ewlenija</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Noorwegen</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Beheer van wegen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Norwegia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi w zakresie eksploatacji autostrad</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Noruega</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de exploração de auto-estradas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Norvegia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de exploatare a autostrăzilor</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Nórsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Prevádzkovanie diaľnic</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Norveška</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Obratovanje daljinskih cest</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Norge</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Molde</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Drift av allmän väg</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Statens vegvesen Region midt</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>af1b4e02-dc09-489a-a40b-e9a9a3f1aea5</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Statens vegvesen Region midt</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>971 032 081</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>Postboks 2525</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Molde</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>6404</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
               <E_MAIL>firmapost-midt@vegvesen.no</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="NO053"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.vegvesen.no</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://eu.eu-supply.com/ctm/Company/CompanyInformation/Index/249176</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY_ADDITIONAL>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Møre og Romsdal fylkeskommune</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>944138779</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>Postboks 2500</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Molde</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>6404</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
               <E_MAIL>post@mrfylke.no</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="NO053"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.mrfylke.no</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY_ADDITIONAL>
            <JOINT_PROCUREMENT_INVOLVED/>
            <DOCUMENT_RESTRICTED/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://www.vegvesen.no/s/anbud/RegMidt/2018/1503_Indre_Romsdal/1503_vodjak.html</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=198763&amp;B=VEGVESEN</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="MINISTRY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Operational Contract 1503 Indre Romsdal 2018 — 2023.</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>17/92505</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="63712200"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The assignment comprises operational and maintenance assignments on the road network with functional responsibility for some of the assignments. Statens vegvesen Region midt [the Norwegian Public Roads Administration Central Region] wants tender offers from contractors with the professional, technical and economical basis necessary for fulfilment of the contract. Furthermore, experience is required from equivalent works, for the execution of the above named contract work in accordance with the tender documentation. Refer to the supplementary provisions in the pre-qualification documentation.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45233139"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="50230000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="NO053"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Indre Romsdal.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The assignment comprises operational and maintenance assignments with functional responsibility for some of the assignments on national roads, national foot and bicycle paths, county roads and county foot and bicycle paths with associated side installations, side areas, equipment and installations in Rauma, Vestnes and Nesset, part of Nordal, part of Ørskog and part of Lesja municipalities in accordance with list of roads given in chapter D2-V and D2-S20.</P>
                  <P>The work will be settled by round sum for round sum processes, in accordance with amounts and unit prices for other processes such as daywork in accordance with the hourly rates for crew and machines.</P>
                  <P>The contract period is from 2018-09-01 to 2023-08-31 for all off the described assignments.</P>
                  <P>The Builder has an option to extend the contract for 12 months, from 1.9.2023 to 31.8.2024.</P>
                  <P>The road network included in the contract (including arms and ramps) consists of:</P>
                  <P>A total of 453 750 km road of which:</P>
                  <P>— 117 638 km national roads,</P>
                  <P>— 12 938 km national foot/bicycle paths,</P>
                  <P>— 309 837 km county road in Møre og Romsdal,</P>
                  <P>— 13 785 km county foot/bicycle paths in Møre og Romsdal.</P>
                  <P>The traffic on the road network varies from approx. ADT 50 to approx. ADT 7 500 and an annual traffic growth of approx. 1.5 % is anticipated.</P>
                  <P>The assignment mainly consists of routine operational assignments and minor maintenance assignments on the road network. The assignment also consists of inspecting and registering, planning the activity, stand-by for winter operations and general traffic flow, documentation, reporting to the builder, information to the public and handling other assignments that are necessary for the operation and maintenance of the road network.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PRICE/>
               <DATE_START>2018-09-01</DATE_START>
               <DATE_END>2023-08-31</DATE_END>
               <RENEWAL/>
               <RENEWAL_DESCR>
                  <P>The Contracting Authority has the option to extend the contract for 12 months.</P>
               </RENEWAL_DESCR>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Tenderers shall be a legally established company. Documentation: Company Registration Certificate from the Register of Business enterprises. Foreign tenderers can submit an equivalent certificate in accordance with the legislation in the tenderer's country of establishment.</P>
               <P>In the tender offer, tenderers shall present a tax and VAT certificate issued by a competent body in the tenderer's home country or the country where the tenderer is established, which shows that the tenderer has fulfilled their obligations for the payment of taxes, duties and social security obligations.</P>
               <P>Norwegian tenderers can order the certificate via the Norwegian Tax Authority's website, www.skatteetaten.no</P>
               <P>The certificate must not be more than 6 months from the tender deadline.</P>
               <P>The tenderer shall have a well functioning quality assurance system for the delivery, based on ISO 9001:2015 or equivalent, with relevance for equivalent transport projects. The system shall be subject to periodic review.</P>
               <P>Documentation requirement:</P>
               <P>1. Certificate showing that the tenderer fulfils the requirements in ISO 9001:2015 or equivalent certification based on relevant European standard series, which are certified by accredited bodies or equivalent certificates issued by bodies in other EEA countries.</P>
               <P>2. Other documentation of equivalent quality assurance measures will be accepted if due to no fault of their own, the tenderer does not have the possibility to obtain such certificates with the deadline. This requires that the tenderer documents that these measures are equivalent to the requested quality assurance standards. Tenderers shall justify why they cannot obtain such certificates by the deadline and the reason for this.</P>
               <P>3. Documentation of audits for recent years, with confirmation from the person/persons who have carried out the audits.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>1. The tenderer's Annual Financial Statements, Annual Report and audit report for the last 3 years and recent information (quarterly accounts) which is of significance to the tenderer's fiscal figures. The form in Chapter E2 Point 4 shall be completed.</P>
               <P>2. If relevant; a brief statement on information on the economic conditions or losses that are not documented other places and that are required to be documented in accordance with Norwegian and/or international accounting standards.</P>
               <P>3. If relevant; an overview of any newly performed, ongoing or impending tax or public reviews of the tenderer’s business.</P>
               <P>If the tenderer has valid reasons for not being able to provide the documentation requested by the Contracting Authority, the tenderer can document his economic and financial capacity by presenting any other document that is relevant to the fiscal figures/economy and that the Contracting Authority deems suitable. The tenderer shall substantiate why he can’t present the documentation required by the Contracting Authority.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Tenderers shall have good economic and financial capacity to fulfil the contract and shall fulfil the following requirements:</P>
               <P>— tenderers must have positive equity,</P>
               <P>— the tenderer's average annual turnover for the last three years shall be at least NOK 20 000 000. per annum.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>A list of up to 5 but no less than 3 contracts that the tenderer has carried out or is carrying out in the last 5 years, calculated from the tender deadline. The list shall, cf. the form included in Chapter E, include the following for each of the contracts:</P>
               <P>— name of the recipient (Contracting Authority).</P>
               <P>— description of what the contract work included, including its relevance for the qualification requirements, points 1 and 2,</P>
               <P>— what work was carried out by the tenderer himself and what work was carried out by subsuppliers (contract facilitators),</P>
               <P>— the date of the assignment,</P>
               <P>— the value of the contract,</P>
               <P>— reference person/contact person at the contracting authority with contact information (telephone number and email address) and a statement of the person’s role at the contracting authority during the contract. The tenderer is responsible for ensuring that the reference person is available and will provide a reference.</P>
               <P>The builder’s experience is documented through the list described under the minimum requirement.</P>
               <P>1. Description of the tenderer's system for ensuring SHA.</P>
               <P>2. Table of contents of the system.</P>
               <P>3. Documentation of audits for recent years, with confirmation from the person/persons who have carried out the audits.</P>
               <P>Overview of the H1 value for the tenderer and central contract facilitators in the last three years. By “the tenderer and key contract facilitators” we mean the tenderer themself, all parties in any working partnerships, as well as any organisations on which the tenderer relies for fulfilment of the qualification requirements.</P>
               <P>1. If the H1-value is higher than 10, an account shall be given of the developing trend of the H1-value and possibly the F-value, which will express the severity of any high H1-value. Furthermore, a report shall be enclosed with the tender offer, regarding whether improvement measures are implemented and if so, also documentation on the effect of these measures.</P>
               <P>Certificate as documentation that the tenderer fulfils the requirements in the EU scheme for Environmental Management and Environmental Audit (EMAS) or other recognised environmental management systems in the decree (EF) nº 1221/2009 article 45 or other environmental management standards based on relevant European or international standards from accredited organs, e.g. ISO 14001, or equivalent certificates issued by organs in other EEA countries.</P>
               <P>2. Other documentation of equivalent environmental management measures will be accepted if the tenderer, through no fault of their own, does not have the possibility to obtain such certificates by the deadline. This requires that the tenderer documents that these measures are equivalent to the requested environmental management systems or standards. Tenderers shall justify why they cannot obtain such certificates by the deadline and the reason for this.</P>
               <P>3. Documentation of audits for recent years, with confirmation from the person/persons who have carried out the audits.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Tenderers must have sufficient experience of a relevant nature and degree of difficulty from the following works:</P>
               <P>1. The main disciplines included in the assignment include: operation and maintenance of roads.</P>
               <P>2. The following sub-assignments are of significant importance for the contract work:</P>
               <P>— winter operations,</P>
               <P>— clearing traffic areas/traffic objects,</P>
               <P>— construction notification and traffic management.</P>
               <P>The Norwegian Public Roads Administrations’ and other Builders’ experiences with the tenderer will be assessed. The tenderer is required to be able to refer to references to relevant contracts that the tenderer has carried out in a satisfactory manner.</P>
               <P>Conditions which will be evaluated are related to, a:</P>
               <P>— documentation of completed quality,</P>
               <P>— fulfilment of contracts,</P>
               <P>— compliance with provisions and procedures for HSE,</P>
               <P>— compliance with provisions for wages and working conditions,</P>
               <P>— observance of deadlines,</P>
               <P>— follow up during the warranty/claims period,</P>
               <P>— use of apprentices.</P>
               <P>The tenderer shall have a system that shows that he works proactively to ensure safety, health and working environment (SHA), with relevance for equivalent works as those comprised in this competition. The system shall be subject to periodic review.</P>
               <P>Tenderers and their central contract facilitators should have an average H1 value lower than 10 for the last 3 years.</P>
               <P>If the H1-value is higher than 10, an account shall be given of the developing trend of the H1-value and possibly the F-value, which will express the severity of any high H1-value.</P>
               <P>If the tenderer is a working partnership (supplier consortium), the requirements apply for each of the participants.</P>
               <P>The tenderer shall have a good and well functioning environmental management system, based on ISO 14001 (2015), EMAS (EU Eco-Management and Audit Scheme for environmental management) or equivalent. The system shall be subject to periodic review.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-03-21</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>15:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NO"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DATE_TENDER_VALID>2018-06-01</DATE_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-03-21</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>15:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Tenderer opening will be electronic in the Tender Implementation Tool. Therefore the opening of tenders will not be public.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <EINVOICING/>
            <EPAYMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>A tender conference will take place 15.2.2018, 10:00 at St. Carolus, Bjørnstjerne Bjørnsons veg 6, 6404 Molde.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Statens vegvesen Region midt</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Postboks 2525</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Molde</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>6404</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
               <E_MAIL>firmapost-midt@vegvesen.no</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.vegvesen.no</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-01-29</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
