<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="082967-2018"
            EDITION="2018038">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-086007-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20190222</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>38</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180223</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 038-082967</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:082967-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.scotland.gov.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="30162000">Smart cards</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="66000000">Financial and insurance services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="30160000">Magnetic cards</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="30161000">Credit cards</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="30163000">Charge cards</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UK">UNITED KINGDOM</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKM">SCOTLAND</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">2500000</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180222</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="N">National or federal Agency/Office</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="8">Other</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C01</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Единбург</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Смарткарти</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Karty smart</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Smartkort</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Chipkarten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Εδιμβούργο</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Έξυπνες κάρτες</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Smart cards</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edimburgo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tarjetas inteligentes</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kiipkaardid</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Toimikortit</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Édimbourg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Cartes à puce</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Dún Éideann</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Smart cards</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pametne kartice</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Csipkártyák</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edimburgo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Carte intelligenti</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Intelektinės kortelės</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburga</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Viedkartes</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinbugh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Karti smart</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Smartcards</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edynburg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Karty "inteligentne"</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edimburgo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Cartões inteligentes</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Carduri inteligente</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Smart (inteligentné) karty</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pametne kartice</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Aktiva kort</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Scottish Government</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>8fa4d17c-a1db-4c2f-a3e7-edada4927409</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F01_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F01" LG="EN">
         <NOTICE TYPE="PRI_ONLY"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Scottish Government</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Victoria Quay, Leith</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Edinburgh</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>EH6 6QQ</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Ian Whitelaw</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+44 1312445522</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>ian.whitelaw@gov.scot</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.scotland.gov.uk</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/search/Search_AuthProfile.aspx?ID=AA10482</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CENTRAL_PURCHASING/>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="NATIONAL_AGENCY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>Social Security</CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Best Start Food Payment</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="30162000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>This Prior Information Notice (PIN) relates to the following services contract, namely:</P>
               <P>1. Best Start Food Payment:</P>
               <P>It is intended that the Contract Notice for this contract shall be issued on 4.5.2018.</P>
               <P>Further information on the scope of services Social Security Directorate (SSD) wish to procure shall be provided by way of a forthcoming information day, to be held in Glasgow at 12:30 on 7.3.2018.</P>
               <P>The intention of the information day is to enable potential operators both to better understand the scope of services required by Social Security Directorate, and to enable SSD to better understand the current market and future development of such systems, such that a productive procurement competition can be achieved.</P>
               <P>To register interest in the Supplier information day please contact Ian Whitelaw (ian.whitelaw@gov.scot).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">2500000</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30162000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="66000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30160000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30161000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30163000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UK"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Scottish Government (SG) is seeking to deliver a Smartcard/Digital Payment Card solution that will enable the distribution of monetary benefits to support the purchase of healthy foods for low income families. The power to deliver this scheme has been devolved to Scotland through the Scotland Act (2016) and the scheme is being integrated with the delivery of wider social security benefits also being devolved.</P>
                  <P>Currently, UK Government and Department of Health administer Healthy Start Vouchers to low-income pregnant women and families with children up to the age of four to receive paper vouchers up to the value of GBP 3.1 per week. In the child’s first year of life 2 paper vouchers per week are issued. The vouchers can be used to purchase plain cow’s milk, infant formula milk, plain fresh or frozen fruit and vegetables from supermarkets and grocers who have registered to accept them.</P>
                  <P>SG will make a number of changes to the existing scheme and, in particular, is looking to move away from the paper voucher currently in place by introducing a more widely accepted Smartcard/Digital Payment Card solution. This change is expected to improve the customer experience by increasing flexibility of use and removing the stigma associated with paper vouchers, while significantly reducing the administrative burden on both retailers and the Scottish Government.</P>
                  <P>Requirements:</P>
                  <P>It is expected that the card will remain the property of Scottish Government and that the supplier will be able to provide a solution that meets the requirements outlined below, but recognise that the list below is not exclusive or exhaustive at this stage.</P>
                  <P>Card Design &amp; Functionality:</P>
                  <P>— a PIN secured payment card using widely accepted technology to ensure as wide a range of retailers as possible can accept these,</P>
                  <P>— the card must be free at the point of use for both recipients and retailers,</P>
                  <P>— the card must be blocked for use within non-food category retailers, for example off-licences, tobacconists, vaping outlets, clothing shops etc…. In addition, the card should be blocked for use at tobacco and alcohol kiosks within larger grocery stores,</P>
                  <P>— the ability to have a bespoke card design on both sides, including relevant branding and specific information about what the card can be used to purchase.</P>
                  <P>Volumes:</P>
                  <P>— the issue of circa 23 000 cards to existing recipients in a phased manner (3-6 month period),</P>
                  <P>— the issue of around 5 000 cards per year to new applicants,</P>
                  <P>— transfer of circa GBP 442 000 total value per month between 23 000 individual cards.</P>
                  <P>Customer Service &amp; Administration:</P>
                  <P>— the ability for users to check the card balance at an ATM and through an online portal (which can be linked to through SG/Social Security Agency websites),</P>
                  <P>— the ability to put a “stop” on lost or stolen cards, issue a replacement card and transfer any remaining balance to the new card,</P>
                  <P>— a dedicated free helpline to report lost or stolen cards (this is expected to be around 750 lost/stolen cards per year) and/or problems with use, which can transfer calls to the Social Security Agency (if the query relates to eligibility, value received onto card or applications). As a minimum, the help-line should be open between 9:00 and 17:00 Monday to Friday excepting Bank Holidays. Tenderers may wish to provide an automated service outside these hours,</P>
                  <P>— notification system for monthly payments (ie sending a text message to recipients confirm the amount being loaded every month),</P>
                  <P>— a system to identify cards that have been unused for a period of 3 months and notify the social security agency of this in order for action to be taken (customer contact and/or putting a stop to new payments).</P>
                  <P>Data &amp; Security:</P>
                  <P>— a secure system to store necessary recipient data and accept monthly data transfer from the Social Security Agency on amounts to be transferred onto individual cards.</P>
                  <P>Contract Duration:</P>
                  <P>Contract duration: 30 months plus up to a maximum of 12 month extension.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>2018-05-04</DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The More Powers Implementation Procurement Team will conduct the proposed procurement process on behalf of the Scottish Ministers. In the event of a contract award, the contract(s) will be entered into between the Scottish Ministers and the successful tenderer(s).</P>
               <P>More Powers Implementation Procurement Team will manage this process in an open and transparent manner to maximise the possible benefits. Participation or non-participation at this event will not preclude suppliers or advantage/disadvantage any supplier's ability to participate in any future procurement activity.</P>
               <P>Direct or indirect canvassing of any More Powers Implementation Procurement Team or Social Security Directorate official concerning this requirement, or any attempt to procure information from any More Powers Implementation Procurement Team/Social Security Directorate official concerning this PIN outside of the formal process described in this document may result in the disqualification of the supplier from consideration of any future procurement activity.</P>
               <P>No information contained in this document or in any communication made between More Powers Implementation Procurement Team and any supplier in connection with this shall be relied upon as constituting a contract, agreement or representation that any contract shall be offered in accordance with this PIN. Social Security Directorate and the Scottish Ministers shall have no liability for any costs however incurred by those attending the information day, attendance at subsequent meetings, or involvement in the procurement competition.</P>
               <P>The estimated total value in Section II.1.5 is the total value for this contract.</P>
               <P>A Request for Information (RFI) is attached to this notice. All potential bidders are invited to complete this and return it to Ian Whitelaw (ian.whitelaw@gov.scot).</P>
               <P>Note: To register your interest in this notice and obtain any additional information please visit the Public Contracts Scotland website at http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/Search/Search_Switch.aspx?ID=532099</P>
               <P>(SC Ref:532099).</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-22</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F01_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
