<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="083124-2018"
            EDITION="2018038">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-085170-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180325</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>38</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180223</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 038-083124</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:083124-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="FI"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.businessfinland.fi</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://hanki.tarjouspalvelu.fi/hanki</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79000000">Business services: law, marketing, consulting, recruitment, printing and security</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="FIZ">EXTRA-REGIO NUTS 1</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="FI">SUOMI / FINLAND</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="EUR">290000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180222</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180325 16:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="8">Other</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="F">Economic and financial affairs</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Финлaндия</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Хелзинки</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Бизнес услуги: право, маркетинг, консултиране, набиране на персонал, печат и охрана</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Finsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinky</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Obchodní služby: právní, marketingové, poradenské služby, nábor zaměstnanců, tiskařské a bezpečnostní služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Finland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Forretningstjenesteydelser: forskrifter, markedsføring, rådgivning, rekruttering, trykning og sikkerhed</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Finnland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dienstleistungen für Unternehmen: Recht, Marketing, Consulting, Einstellungen, Druck und Sicherheit</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Φινλανδία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ελσίνκι</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Επιχειρηματικές υπηρεσίες: νομικές, μάρκετινγκ, παροχής συμβουλών, πρόσληψης, εκτύπωσης και ασφάλειας</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Finland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Business services: law, marketing, consulting, recruitment, printing and security</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Finlandia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios a empresas: legislación, mercadotecnia, asesoría, selección de personal, imprenta y seguridad</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Soome</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsingi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Õigus-, turundus-, nõustamis-, värbamis-, trüki- ja turvaalased kommertsteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Suomi</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Liike-elämän palvelut: laki, markkinointi, neuvonta, työhönotto, painatus ja turvallisuus</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Finlande</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services aux entreprises: droit, marketing, conseil, recrutement, impression et sécurité</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Fhionlainn, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Heilsincí</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Business services: law, marketing, consulting, recruitment, printing and security</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Finska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Poslovne usluge: pravo, marketing, savjetovanje, zapošljavanje, tiskanje i sigurnost</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Finnország</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Üzleti szolgáltatások: jog, marketing, tanácsadás, munkaerő-felvétel, nyomtatás és biztonság</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Finlandia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi per le imprese: servizi giuridici, di marketing, di consulenza, di reclutamento, di stampa e di sicurezza</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Suomija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinkis</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Verslo paslaugos: teisinės, rinkodaros, konsultavimo, įdarbinimo, spausdinimo ir apsaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Somija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Uzņēmējdarbības pakalpojumi: tiesības, tirgzinība, konsultēšana, darbinieku vervēšana, iespiešana un drošība</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>il-Finlandja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ħelsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' negozju: Liġi, kummerċjalizzazzjoni, konsulenza, reklutaġġ, stampar u sigurtà</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Finland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zakelijke dienstverlening: juridisch, marketing, consulting, drukkerij en beveiliging</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Finlandia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi biznesowe: prawnicze, marketingowe, konsultingowe, rekrutacji, drukowania i zabezpieczania</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Finlândia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsínquia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços a empresas: direito, comercialização, consultoria, recrutamento, impressão e segurança</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Finlanda</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii pentru întreprinderi: drept, marketing, consultanţă, recrutare, tipărire şi securitate</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Fínsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Podnikateľské služby: právo, marketing, konzultácie, nábor pracovníkov, tlačiarenské a bezpečnostné služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Finska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsinki</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Poslovne storitve: pravo, trženje, svetovanje, zaposlovanje, tiskanje in varnost</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Finland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Helsingfors</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Företagstjänster: lagstiftning, marknadsföring, rådgivning, rekrytering, tryckning och säkerhet</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Business Finland Oy</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Business Finland Oy</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>2725690-3</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>PO BOX 358</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Helsinki</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>00181</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="FI"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Juho Partanen</CONTACT_POINT>
               <E_MAIL>kilpailutus@businessfinland.fi</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="FI"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.businessfinland.fi</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://hanki.tarjouspalvelu.fi/hanki</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://hanki.tarjouspalvelu.fi/hanki?id=174755&amp;tpk=1243e23b-3570-4769-a666-d7ca97dcd517</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE_OTHER>state owned company</CA_TYPE_OTHER>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="ECONOMIC_AND_FINANCIAL_AFFAIRS"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Adviser in Russia — Arctic Maritime &amp; Offshore from Finland Growth Program</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>9/27/2018</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79000000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Business Finland is looking for an adviser based in Russia for the year 2018 to work with the Business Finland’s Arctic Maritime &amp; Offshore from Finland — Growth Program and its Finnish member companies. The elected person will act as a local business adviser for the Growth Program and its Finnish member companies, bringing new business leads and helping Finnish member companies to win business in Russia with end customers (see below for definitions of key concepts). The Growth Program will focus in 2018 on 20 shipbuilding countries in Europe, Asia, North America and Latin America. The success of the Growth Program is measured by increase of new export business done by the Finnish member companies in the target markets and investments done by foreign companies into Finland in the related field. The adviser's position implies a full commitment for the duration of the assignment.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">290000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="FIZ"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Russia.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Definitions of key concepts:</P>
                  <P>“Growth Program”: refers to Business Finland’s Arctic Maritime &amp; Offshore from Finland — Growth Program.</P>
                  <P>“Finnish Enterprise”: refers to Finnish companies that are members of the Growth Program. There are about 355 Finnish Enterprises participating the Growth Program.</P>
                  <P>“Scope”: refers to business segment that the Growth Program is focusing and Finnish Enterprises are offering to their end customers either directly or via partners. In this document the scope consists of arctic fleet owners, shipbuilding, offshore building, port and shipyard building technologies and services; ship and rig building engineering and design, software and big data products and services for maritime, port, shipyard and offshore use.</P>
                  <P>“End Customers or Seller”: refers to companies that could have business benefit from working with Finnish Enterprise(s) by procuring or reselling either complete or partial scope of products and services and therefore be able to improve their or their customers’ operational efficiency, create new products and service and new business models.</P>
                  <P>“Target Market”: refers to Target Market of the Growth Program that is been addressed in this document. The target market is Russia.</P>
                  <P>Description of procured services:</P>
                  <P>The adviser based in the Target Market for Growth Program will provide following services:</P>
                  <P>a) the adviser will be responsible for communication with the Finnish Enterprises in the program;</P>
                  <P>b) the adviser shall map out the offering, needs, experience and expectations of the Finnish Enterprises in the program, regarding Target Market;</P>
                  <P>c) the adviser shall map out the needs, challenges and coming projects of end customers in the Target Market and other related stakeholders such as potential partners;</P>
                  <P>d) the adviser shall map out the present status of the market developments in The Target Market and what business opportunities it offers to Finnish Enterprises;</P>
                  <P>e) the adviser shall find business opportunities and business leads for the group of Finnish Enterprises and provide generic support in further processing of the business leads towards closing of the deal;</P>
                  <P>f) the adviser shall keep the Growth Program Director/Manager and the Finnish Enterprises informed about the key developments and news related to the scope in The Target Market with help of a newsletter or other suitable means on regular basis, with at least on monthly basis;</P>
                  <P>g) the adviser shall give generic advice and consultation to the Finnish enterprises;</P>
                  <P>h) the adviser is responsible to marketing and introducing the service of Finnish enterprises to the end customers, partners and other stakeholders in the Target Market;</P>
                  <P>i) the adviser shall find out if there is a need of common offering what Finnish Enterprises could offer together for the Target Market customers;</P>
                  <P>j) the adviser seeks and promotes actively the Scope to the Target Market companies to generate interest for those to invest in Finland. As requested and agreed separately, either leads and/or participates trade delegations to Finland;</P>
                  <P>k) the adviser reports on monthly basis the activities performed to Business Finland Growth Program Director/Manager. This includes brief on the tasks performed and especially on the business opportunities and leads generated and their progress (company matches made, names, brief status);</P>
                  <P>l) the adviser shall arrange Finnish companies' trade missions and business delegation trips to the Target Market including meeting and event arrangements. The result of this work shall be a strong pipeline of potential End Customers and business leads for the Finnish Enterprises. Business Finland will define, lead and guide the actions taken in market area. The details and scope of the activities in the market area will be commonly agreed and clarified on a program plan.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Quality/Named adviser's experience</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>70</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Price</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>30</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>Quality 70/Price 30</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">48</DURATION>
               <RENEWAL/>
               <RENEWAL_DESCR>
                  <P>The contract is open-ended and planned to enter into force in 4.2018 (estimated target) both Business Finland and service provider are entitled to terminate the contract without cause by giving 3 months prior written notice.</P>
               </RENEWAL_DESCR>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI/>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-03-25</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>16:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">4</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-03-26</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>08:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>Helsinki.</P>
               </PLACE>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <EINVOICING/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Markkinaoikeus</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Radanrakentajantie 5</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Helsinki</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>00520</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="FI"/>
               <PHONE>+358 295643300</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>markkinaoikeus@oikeus.fi</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+358 295643314</FAX>
               <URL>http://www.oikeus.fi/markkinaoikeus</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-22</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
