<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="173036-2018"
            EDITION="2018077">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-175807-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180518</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>77</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180420</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 077-173036</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:173036-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>https://fiskeridir.no/</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=209639&amp;B=DFO</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="60651000">Hire of vessels with crew</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="60653000">Hire of boats with crew</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="NO">NORGE</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="NO">NORGE</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180418</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180518 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="N">National or federal Agency/Office</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="B">European Economic Area (EEA), with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>03C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>03</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Норвегия</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги по даване под наем на плавателни съдове с екипаж</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Norsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pronájem plavidel s posádkou</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Norge</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Udlejning af skibe med besætning</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Norwegen</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Vermietung von Wasserfahrzeugen mit Besatzung</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Νορβηγία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ενοικίαση σκαφών με πλήρωμα</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Norway</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Hire of vessels with crew</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Noruega</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Alquiler de embarcaciones con tripulación</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Norra</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laevaperega veesõidukite rent</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Norja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Alusten vuokraus miehistön kanssa</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Norvège</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Location de vaisseaux avec équipage</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Iorua, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Hire of vessels with crew</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Norveška</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Iznajmljivanje plovila s posadom</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Norvégia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Vízi jármű kölcsönzése személyzettel</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Norvegia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Noleggio di imbarcazioni con equipaggio</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Norvegija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laivų su įgula nuoma</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Norvēģija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kuģu ar apkalpi noma</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>in-Norveġja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kiri ta’ dgħajjes bl-ekwipaġġ tagħhom</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Noorwegen</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Verhuur van vaartuigen met bemanning</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Norwegia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Wynajem jednostek pływających wraz z załogą</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Noruega</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Aluguer de embarcações, com tripulação</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Norvegia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Închiriere de nave cu echipaj</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Nórsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Prenájom plavidiel s posádkou</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Norveška</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dajanje plovil s posadko v najem</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Norge</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bergen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Uthyrning av fartyg med besättning</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Fiskeridirektoratet</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>5df01114-f3f0-422c-b3ad-9a0ca1d00e58</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Fiskeridirektoratet</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>971 203 420</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>Strandgaten 229</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bergen</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>5004</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Erik Myrmel</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+47 99168997</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>erik.myrmel@fiskeridir.no</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="NO"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://fiskeridir.no/</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://eu.eu-supply.com/ctm/Company/CompanyInformation/Index/340237</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=209639&amp;B=DFO</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=209639&amp;B=DFO</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="NATIONAL_AGENCY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Hire of shrimp trawls — Selection of spawn from fish in a shrimp trawl in the Barents Sea</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Saksnummer: 18/5574</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="60651000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The vessel shall be hired with the intention of being in operation in the period approx. 15.9.2018 — approx. 29.9.2018. The contract shall be valid for 14 days, with an option for a 4 day extension, from an agreed start-up date. The Directorate of Fisheries will pay a fixed day rate as the hire price in accordance with the contract with the tenderer. Other expenses are to be covered by the tenderer.</P>
               <P>The Directorate of Fisheries’ representatives on board during the period the vessel is leased, will have command of the vessel. The crew shall follow instructions and carry out mission and work assignments as directed by the mission leader or persons whom he gives authority to.</P>
               <P>The vessel’s owners (possibly a representative of the shipping company) are at all times responsible for the vessel operating in line with the applicable regulations or the guidelines that the mission leader gives.</P>
               <P>A specified contract will be signed with the tenderers who sign a contract.</P>
               <P>More detailed requirements for the services are in Annex 1 the contracting authority´s requirement specifications.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="60653000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="NO"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Intermingling of spawn from cod, haddock, Norway haddock, Greenland halibut and shrimp spawn in shrimp catches is, and has been a problem for shrimp fishing north of N 62<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> for many years. For periods of the year, large parts of the most important shrimp trawl fishing grounds have been closed. The sorting grate that is used in shrimp fishing, with 19 mm holes functions well, but the selection abilities of the grate for fish spawn under 18 cm is limited and so too many of the smallest fish spawn end up in the trawl bag.</P>
                  <P>The trials shall be carried out in a commercial shrimp fishing ground in the Fish Protection zone by Svalbard during almost ordinary fishing. The vessel that shall be used must be equipped with and rigged for fishing with a double trawl mounted on 2 identical trawlers with identical set-ups. Different devices shall be tested in the trawl, in combination with the ordinary sorting grate. There will be some shorter trawl draws than what is usual in ordinary shrimp fishing. Each trial series shall consist of at least 8 trawl draws, which shall be made within the same shrimp fishing ground. There will be a need to use collection bags and to assemble underwater cameras on and off. The trials will delay or influence the ordinary fishing for a maximum of approx. four hours per day (15 % of the time). The catches from the 2 trawls and the collection bags must be kept separate and the total catches of shrimps (and by-catches) from each trawl must be obtained for each trawl draw. The catches must be sorted and measurements shall be made of the lengths from both catches in the trawl sacks and in the collection bags. The vessel must have room for at least 4 persons in addition to the ordinary crew. The mission will last for 14 days, with an option for a 2 day extension.</P>
                  <P>The vessel shall be hired with the intention of being in operation in the period approx. 15.9.2018 — approx. 2909.2018. The contract shall be valid for 14 days, with an option for a 4 day extension, from an agreed start-up date. The Directorate of Fisheries will pay a fixed day rate as the hire price in accordance with the contract with the tenderer. Other expenses are to be covered by the tenderer.</P>
                  <P>The Directorate of Fisheries’ representatives on board during the period the vessel is leased, will have command of the vessel. The crew shall follow instructions and carry out mission and work assignments as directed by the mission leader or persons whom he gives authority to.</P>
                  <P>The vessel’s owners (possibly a representative of the shipping company) are at all times responsible for the vessel operating in line with the applicable regulations or the guidelines that the mission leader gives.</P>
                  <P>A specified contract will be signed with the tenderers who sign a contract.</P>
                  <P>More detailed requirements for the services are in Annex 1 the contracting authority´s requirement specifications.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <DURATION TYPE="DAY">14</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>The mission will last for 14 days, with an option for a 4 day extension.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Requirement:</P>
               <P>The tenderer must have their affairs in order with respect to the payment of tax, employer contribution and value added tax (VAT).</P>
               <P>Documentation requirement:</P>
               <P>Tenderers must attach a tax certificate, not older than 6 months, cf. FOA § 7-2 (2).</P>
               <P>— Norwegian tenderers can order a tax certificate via form RF-1316 in Altinn.</P>
               <P>— Foreign tenderers must submit equivalent certificates from their own country that show that they have an arrangement for the payment of taxes and duties.</P>
               <P>If the authorities in the relevant country do not issue these certificates, the tenderer should submit a statement which states that all taxes and duties have been paid. The statement shall be approved and signed by the tenderer's Financial Director/ person responsible for finance.</P>
               <P>Requirement:</P>
               <P>The tenderer shall be a legally established company.</P>
               <P>Documentation requirement:</P>
               <P>Norwegian tenderers must present a Company Registration Certificate.</P>
               <P>Foreign tenderers must present confirmation that the tenderer is registered in a company register or trade register, in accordance with the legislation in the country where the tenderer is established or registered.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>Requirement:</P>
               <P>The tenderer shall have sufficient financial strength to comply with the contractual obligations.</P>
               <P>Documentation requirement:</P>
               <P>The tenderer's Annual Financial Statements including notes with the Board's and auditor's reports from the last two years.</P>
               <P>If the annual accounts for the previous year have not been completed, the provisional annual accounts must be enclosed for the previous year.</P>
               <P>Newly started companies must document the financial strength to fulfil the contract in another way.</P>
               <P>Tenderers can choose to rely on other companies’ capacity to fulfil the requirement for the tenderer's economic and financial position. If so, the tenderer must document the resources in the company he will rely on and that these resources will be available (cf. the commitment statement in Annex C).</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>Requirement:</P>
               <P>The tenderer must have adequate implementation ability.</P>
               <P>Documentation requirement:</P>
               <P>A short, general description of the company shall be given, including:</P>
               <P>— An account of the company’s business concept and core competencies related to the scope of the delivery.</P>
               <P>— An overview of the company’s history, organisation and ownership, as well as a description of the current business activities.</P>
               <P>— Description of how the service provider is organised for the execution of this contract.</P>
               <P>— A concise description of the overall quality assurance system that the supplier will apply in carrying out this contract must be given.</P>
               <P>The tenderer may choose to rely on other companies’ capacity to meet the technical and professional qualification requirements.</P>
               <P>The tenderer must, in such an event, substantiate that the resources of the companies on which he will rely and prove that he will have the requisite resources from these companies at his disposal during the contract period, by, for example presenting a declaration of commitment (Annex A), guarantee, co-operation agreement or similar. In addition equivalent documentation on the technical and professional qualifications of the companies that will be used must be enclosed.</P>
               <P>This applies regardless of the legal nature of the connection between the companies, i.e. that the supporting companies can either be the tenderer's parent company, another company in the same group, a collaborating partner etc.</P>
               <P>Requirement:</P>
               <P>Tenderers shall have relevant experience from similar contracts.</P>
               <P>Documentation requirement:</P>
               <P>Description of the tenderer's three most relevant contracts during the last 3 years.</P>
               <P>The description must include:</P>
               <P>— A brief description of the assignment.</P>
               <P>— Time of execution.</P>
               <P>— Scope of the assignment in monetary amount.</P>
               <P>— Name, and telephone number of the reference person at the Contracting Authority.</P>
               <P>The Contracting Authority must have the possibility to contact the contact persons who are listed.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-05-18</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="NO"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DATE_TENDER_VALID>2018-07-16</DATE_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-05-18</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Fiskeridirektoratet</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Pb 185, Sentrum</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bergen</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>5804</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="NO"/>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-18</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
