<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="058022-2018" EDITION="2018027"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-053318-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180222</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>27</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180208</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 027-058022</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:058022-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79416000">Public relations services</ORIGINAL_CPV><REF_NOTICE><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 022-045294</NO_DOC_OJS></REF_NOTICE></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180202</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="2">Additional information</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="1">External aid and European Development Fund</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="Z">Not specified</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>AP3EA</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Synlighed og kommunikationsstøtte til EU-ernærings og -uddannelsesprogrammer i Den Demokratiske Folkerepublik Laos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Visibilitäts- und Kommunikationsunterstützung für die Lebensmittel- und Bildungsprogramme der EU in der Demokratischen Volksrepublik Laos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussels</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Visibility and Communications Support to EU Nutrition and Education Programmes in Lao PDR</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Visibilidad y apoyo en materia de comunicación a favor de los programas de nutrición y educación de la UE en la República Democrática Popular de Laos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Näkyvyyden ja viestinnän tuki EU:n ravitsemus- ja koulutusohjelmille Laosin demokraattisessa kansantasavallassa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Belgique</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Soutien à la visibilité et aux communications relatives aux programmes de l'UE portant sur l'éducation et la nutrition au bénéfice de la RPD du Laos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Βέλγιο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Στήριξη των δραστηριοτήτων προβολής και επικοινωνίας για τα προγράμματα διατροφής και εκπαίδευσης της ΕΕ στη Λαϊκή Δημοκρατία του Λάος</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Belgio</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Visibilità e sostegno delle comunicazioni ai programmi di nutrizione e istruzione dell'UE nella Repubblica democratica popolare del Laos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>België</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ondersteuning inzake zichtbaarheid en communicatie voor de voedsel- en onderwijsprogramma's van de EU in de Democratische Volksrepubliek Laos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Apoio nos domínios de visibilidade e comunicações a favor dos programas de nutrição e educação da UE na República Democrática Popular Lao</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Stöd för synlighet och kommunikation till EU:s närings- och utbildningsprogram i demokratiska folkrepubliken Laos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Belgie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Podpora zviditelnění a komunikační podpora pro programy EU zaměřené na výživu a vzdělávání v Laoské lidově demokratické republice</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Märgatavus- ja teabevahetuse tugi ELi toitlustus- ja haridusprogrammidele Laose Demokraatlikus Rahvavabariigis</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüsszel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Az uniós táplálkozási és oktatási programok láthatósági és kommunikációs támogatása a Laoszi Népi Demokratikus Köztársaságban</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Briuselis</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Matomumo ir komunikacijos parama ES mitybos ir švietimo programoms Laoso Liaudies Demokratinėje Respublikoje</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Beļģija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brisele</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Atpazīstamības un komunikācijas atbalsts ES uztura un izglītības programmām Laosas TDR</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Belġju</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussell</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Appoġġ fil-Viżibilità u l-Komunikazzjoni lill-Programmi tal-UE għan-Nutrizzjoni u l-Edukazzjoni f'Lao PDR</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruksela</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Wsparcie widoczności i komunikacji na rzecz unijnych programów dotyczących edukacji i żywienia w Laotańskiej Republice Ludowo-Demokratycznej</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Belgicko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Podpora viditeľnosti a komunikácie pre výživové a vzdelávacie programy EÚ v Laoskej ľudovodemokratickej republike</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselj</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Podpora na področju prepoznavnosti in komuniciranja v zvezi s programi EU za prehrano in izobraževanje v Laoški ljudski demokratični republiki</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Bheilg, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tacaíocht Infheictheachta agus Cumarsáide do Chláir Chothaitheach agus Oideachais AE i nDaon-Phoblacht Dhaonlathach Laos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бeлгия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Брюксел</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Подкрепа за действията по популяризиране и комуникация във връзка с програмите на ЕС в областта на храненето и образованието в Лаоска народнодемократична република</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Vizibilitate și sprijin privind comunicațiile în cadrul programelor UE de nutriție și educație în Republica Populară Democrată Laos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Vidljivost i komunikacijska podrška programima na području prehrane i obrazovanja EU-a u Narodnoj Demokratskoj Republici Laos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den Europæiske Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">La Unión Europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan unioni</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Union européenne</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Η Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Unione europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europese Unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">União Europeia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska unionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Liit</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Európai Unió</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos Sąjunga</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Savienība</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">L-Unjoni Ewropea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Unia Europejska</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európska únia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska unija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An tAontas Eorpach</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейски съюз</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Uniunea Europeană</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska unija</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Synlighed og kommunikationsstøtte til EU-ernærings og -uddannelsesprogrammer i Den Demokratiske Folkerepublik Laos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Berigtigelse nr. 1 til vejledende forhåndsmeddelelse om tjenesteydelser</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Udbudsreference: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement til Den Europæiske Unions Tidende, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den Europæiske Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, repræsenteret ved Europa-Kommissionen, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>I stedet for:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Retsgrundlag</P><P>Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 233/2014 om oprettelse af et instrument til finansiering af udviklingssamarbejde for perioden 2014-2020</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Læses:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Retsgrundlag</P><P>Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 2014 af 11.3.2014 om fælles regler og procedurer for gennemførelse af instrumenterne til finansiering af Unionens optræden udadtil og Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 233/2014 om oprettelse af et instrument til finansiering af udviklingssamarbejde for perioden 2014-2020 — se bilag No236 i den praktiske vejledning.</P><P>Vær opmærksom på, at efter Det Forenede Kongeriges udtræden af EU vil reglerne om adgang til EU's udbudsprocedurer for økonomiske aktører, der er etableret i tredjelande, gælde for ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige, alt afhængigt af resultatet af forhandlingerne. Hvis en sådan adgang ikke gives ved retlige bestemmelser, der er gældende på tidspunktet for kontrakttildelingen, vil ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige kunne blive udelukket fra udbudsproceduren.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alle andre bestemmelser og betingelser i udbudsbekendtgørelsen forbliver uændrede. Ovenstående ændringer og/eller berigtigelser vil være at betragte som en integreret del af udbudsbekendtgørelsen.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: Visibilitäts- und Kommunikationsunterstützung für die Lebensmittel- und Bildungsprogramme der EU in der Demokratischen Volksrepublik Laos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Berichtigung Nr. 1 zur Vorinformation für eine Dienstleistung</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement zum Amtsblatt der Europäischen Union, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertreten durch die Europäische Kommission, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Anstatt:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Rechtsgrundlage</P><P>Verordnung (EU) Nr. 233/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates zur Schaffung eines Finanzierungsinstruments für die Entwicklungszusammenarbeit für den Zeitraum 2014 - 2020.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>muss es heißen:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Rechtsgrundlage</P><P>Verordnung (EU) Nr. 236/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Festlegung gemeinsamer Vorschriften und Verfahren für die Anwendung der Instrumente der Union für die Finanzierung des auswärtigen Handelns und Verordnung (EU) Nr. 233/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Schaffung eines Finanzierungsinstruments für die Entwicklungszusammenarbeit für den Zeitraum 2014-2020 (siehe Anhang A2 des „Handbuch“).</P><P>Es gilt zu beachten, dass für Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich nach dem Austritt des Vereinigten Königreichs aus der EU in Abhängigkeit des Ausgangs der Verhandlungen die Bestimmungen über den Zugang zu Beschaffungsverfahren der EU für in Drittländern ansässige Wirtschaftsteilnehmer gelten werden. Falls dieser Zugang gemäß den bei Auftragsvergabe geltenden Bestimmung nicht gewährt wird, können Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich vom Beschaffungsverfahren ausgeschlossen werden.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alle anderen Daten und Bedingungen der Auftragsbekanntmachung bleiben unverändert. Die oben genannten Änderungen und/oder Berichtigungen der Auftragsbekanntmachung sind integraler Bestandteil derselben.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussels: Visibility and Communications Support to EU Nutrition and Education Programmes in Lao PDR</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Corrigendum no.1 to the Service prior information notice</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Publication Ref: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement to the Official Journal of the European Union, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, represented by the European Commission, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussels</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Instead of:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Legal basis</P><P>Regulation (EU) N<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> 233/2014 of the European parliament and of the Council establishing a financing instrument for development cooperation for the period 2014-2020</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Read:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Legal basis</P><P>Regulation (EU) N<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> 236/2014 of the European parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 laying down common rules and procedures for the implementation of the Union's instruments for financing external action and Regulation (EU) N<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> 233/2014 of the European parliament and of the Council establishing a financing instrument for development cooperation for the period 2014-2020 — See Annex A2 of the practical guide.</P><P>Please be aware that after the United Kingdom's withdrawal from the EU, the rules of access to EU procurement procedures of economic operators established in third countries will apply to candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom depending on the outcome of negotiations. In case such access is not provided by legal provisions in force at the time of contract award, candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom could be rejected from the procurement procedure.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>All other terms and conditions of the contract notice remain unchanged. The above alterations and /or corrections to the contract notice are integral part of the contract notice.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselas: Visibilidad y apoyo en materia de comunicación a favor de los programas de nutrición y educación de la UE en la República Democrática Popular de Laos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rectificativo no 1 del anuncio de previsión de contrato de servicios</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referencia de publicación: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplemento al Diario Oficial de la Unión Europea, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>La Unión Europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada por la Comisión Europea, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>En lugar de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Fundamento jurídico</P><P>Reglamento (UE) n.º 233/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, por el que se establece un Instrumento de Financiación de la Cooperación al Desarrollo para el período 2014-2020</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Léase:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Fundamento jurídico</P><P>Reglamento (UE) n.o 236/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establecen normas y procedimientos de ejecución comunes de los instrumentos de la Unión para la financiación de la acción exterior, y Reglamento (UE) n.o 233/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establece un Instrumento de Financiación de la Cooperación al Desarrollo para el período 2014-2020; véase el anexo A2 de la «Guía Práctica».</P><P>Téngase en cuenta que tras la salida del Reino Unido de la Unión Europea, las normas de acceso a los procedimientos de contratación pública de la Unión Europea de los operadores económicos establecidos en terceros países se aplicarán a candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido en función del resultado de las negociaciones. En caso de que dicho acceso no se prevea en disposiciones legales en vigor, los candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido podrán ser excluidos del proceso de contratación.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>El resto de términos y condiciones del presente anuncio de contrato permanecen sin cambios. Las presentes modificaciones o correcciones del anuncio de contrato forman parte integral del mismo.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: Näkyvyyden ja viestinnän tuki EU:n ravitsemus- ja koulutusohjelmille Laosin demokraattisessa kansantasavallassa</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Palveluja koskevaa ennakkotietoilmoitusta koskeva oikaisuilmoitus nro 1</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ilmoituksen viite: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Euroopan unionin virallisen lehden täydennysosa, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan unioni</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, jota edustaa Euroopan komissio, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Oikaistava tieto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Oikeusperusta</P><P>Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 233/2014 kehitysyhteistyön rahoitusvälineen perustamisesta kaudelle 2014-2020–2020.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Oikaisu:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Oikeusperusta</P><P>Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) n:o 236/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, unionin ulkoisen toiminnan rahoitusvälineiden täytäntöönpanoa koskevista yhteisistä säännöistä ja menettelyistä sekä Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) n:o 233/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, kehitysyhteistyön rahoitusvälineen perustamisesta kaudelle 2014–2020 (katso PRAG-oppaan liite A2).</P><P>On syytä ottaa huomioon, että Yhdistyneen kuningaskunnan EU:sta irtautumisen jälkeen kolmansiin maihin sijoittautuneisiin talouden toimijoihin sovellettavia EU:n hankintamenettelyihin osallistumista koskevia sääntöjä sovelletaan Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin oleviin hakijoihin tai tarjoajiin neuvottelujen lopputuloksesta riippuen. Mikäli sopimuksenteon hetkellä voimassa olevassa lainsäädännössä ei anneta lupaa tällaiseen osallistumiseen, Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin olevat hakijat tai tarjoajat voidaan hylätä hankintamenettelystä.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Kaikki muut hankintailmoituksen kohdat ja ehdot pysyvät muuttumattomina. Hankintailmoitukseen edellä tehdyt muutokset ja/tai korjaukset ovat olennainen osa hankintailmoitusta.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Soutien à la visibilité et aux communications relatives aux programmes de l'UE portant sur l'éducation et la nutrition au bénéfice de la RPD du Laos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rectificatif no 1 à l'avis de préinformation relatif à un marché de services</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Référence de la publication : EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplément au Journal officiel de l'Union européenne, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Union européenne</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, représentée par la Commission européenne </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgique.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Au lieu de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Base juridique</P><P>Règlement (UE) n<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> 233/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil instituant un instrument de financement de la coopération au développement pour la période 2014-2020</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Lire:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Base juridique</P><P>Règlement (UE) no 2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 énonçant des règles et des modalités communes pour la mise en œuvre des instruments de l'Union pour le financement de l'action extérieure et règlement (UE) no 233/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 instituant un instrument de financement de la coopération au développement pour la période 2014-2020 — voir annexe No236 du «Guide pratique».</P><P>Il convient de noter qu'à la suite du retrait du Royaume-Uni de l'UE, les règles d'accès aux procédures de marché de l'UE pour les opérateurs économiques établis dans des pays tiers s'appliqueront aux candidats ou aux soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni, en fonction du résultat des négociations. Si les dispositions légales en vigueur au moment de l'attribution du contrat ne prévoient pas un tel accès, les candidats ou les soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni pourraient être exclus de la procédure d'appel d'offres.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Toutes les autres conditions générales de l'avis de marché demeurent inchangés. Les modifications et/ou corrections ci-dessus font intégralement partie de l'avis de marché.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Βρυξέλλες: Στήριξη των δραστηριοτήτων προβολής και επικοινωνίας για τα προγράμματα διατροφής και εκπαίδευσης της ΕΕ στη Λαϊκή Δημοκρατία του Λάος</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Διορθωτικό Αριθ. 1 στην προκαταρκτική ανακοίνωση για σύμβαση υπηρεσιών</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Αριθ. αναφοράς της δημοσίευσης: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Συμπλήρωμα στην Επίσημη Εφημερίδα της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Η Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, εκπροσωπούμενη από την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Βέλγιο.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Αντί:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Νομική βάση</P><P>Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 233/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου της 11.3.2014 για τη θέσπιση μηχανισμού χρηματοδότησης της αναπτυξιακής συνεργασίας για την περίοδο 2014-2020</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Διάβαζε:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Νομική βάση</P><P>2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τον καθορισμό κοινών κανόνων και διαδικασιών για την εφαρμογή των μηχανισμών χρηματοδότησης της εξωτερικής δράσης της Ένωσης και κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 233/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, περί μηχανισμού χρηματοδότησης της αναπτυξιακής συνεργασίας την περίοδο 2014–2020 — βλέπε παράρτημα No236 του «Πρακτικού οδηγού».</P><P>Πρέπει να ληφθεί υπόψη ότι μετά την αποχώρηση του Ηνωμένου Βασιλείου από την ΕΕ, οι κανόνες πρόσβασης σε διαδικασίες διαγωνισμού της ΕΕ για οικονομικούς φορείς που είναι εγκατεστημένοι σε τρίτες χώρες θα ισχύουν για τους υποψήφιους ή προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο ανάλογα με το αποτέλεσμα των διαπραγματεύσεων. Σε περίπτωση που η πρόσβαση αυτή δεν παρέχεται από νομικές διατάξεις που ίσχυαν κατά το χρόνο ανάθεσης της σύμβασης, οι υποψήφιοι ή οι προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο θα μπορούσαν να απορριφθούν από τη διαδικασία διαγωνισμού.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Όλοι οι λοιποί όροι και προϋποθέσεις της προκήρυξης σύμβασης παραμένουν αμετάβλητοι. Οι ανωτέρω τροποποιήσεις ή/και διορθώσεις στην προκήρυξη σύμβασης αποτελούν αναπόσπαστο τμήμα της προκήρυξης σύμβασης.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Visibilità e sostegno delle comunicazioni ai programmi di nutrizione e istruzione dell'UE nella Repubblica democratica popolare del Laos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rettifica n. 1 all'avviso di preinformazione relativo a servizi</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rif. della pubblicazione: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplemento alla Gazzetta ufficiale dell'Unione europea, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unione europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, rappresentata dalla Commissione europea, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgio.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>anziché:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Base giuridica</P><P>Regolamento (UE) n. 233/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, che istituisce uno strumento per il finanziamento della cooperazione allo sviluppo per il periodo 2014-2020.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>leggi:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Base giuridica</P><P>Regolamento (UE) n. 236/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che stabilisce norme e procedure comuni per l'attuazione degli strumenti per il finanziamento dell'azione esterna dell'Unione e regolamento (UE) n. 233/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che istituisce uno strumento per il finanziamento della cooperazione allo sviluppo per il periodo 2014–2020 — cfr. allegato A2 della «Guida pratica».</P><P>Si prega di notare che, dopo il ritiro del Regno Unito dall'UE, ai candidati o agli offerenti provenienti dal Regno Unito si applicheranno le regole di accesso alle procedure di appalto dell'UE per gli operatori economici stabiliti nei paesi terzi, in funzione dell'esito delle negoziazioni. Qualora tale accesso non fosse previsto dalle disposizioni giuridiche vigenti al momento dell'aggiudicazione del contratto, i candidati o gli offerenti del Regno Unito potranno essere esclusi dalla procedura di gara.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Tutte le altre condizioni del bando di gara rimangono immutate. Le summenzionate modifiche e/o correzioni al bando di gara sono parte integrante del bando di gara.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussel: Ondersteuning inzake zichtbaarheid en communicatie voor de voedsel- en onderwijsprogramma's van de EU in de Democratische Volksrepubliek Laos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rectificatie nr. 1 op de vooraankondiging voor diensten</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referentie van de bekendmaking: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement op het Publicatieblad van de Europese Unie, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europese Unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertegenwoordigd door de Europese Commissie, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, België.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>In plaats van:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Juridische basis:</P><P>Verordening (EG) nr. 233/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad tot vaststelling van een financieringsinstrument voor ontwikkelingssamenwerking voor de periode 2014-2020.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Te lezen:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Juridische basis:</P><P>Verordening (EU) nr. 236/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van gemeenschappelijke voorschriften en procedures voor de tenuitvoerlegging van de instrumenten van de Unie ter financiering van extern optreden en Verordening (EU) nr. 233/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van een financieringsinstrument voor ontwikkelingssamenwerking voor de periode 2014-2020 — Zie bijlage A2 bij de „Praktische gids”.</P><P>Gelieve op te merken dat, na de uitstap van het Verenigd Koninkrijk uit de EU en afhankelijk van het resultaat van de onderhandelingen, de regels voor toegang tot EU-aanbestedingsprocedures voor ondernemers die gevestigd zijn in derde landen van toepassing zullen zijn op gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk. Indien dergelijke toegang niet is voorzien door de geldende wettelijke bepalingen op het tijdstip van de gunning van de opdracht, kunnen gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk worden geweigerd voor de aanbestedingsprocedure.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alle andere voorwaarden van de aankondiging van opdracht blijven ongewijzigd. De hiervoor vermelde wijzigingen en/of correcties aan de aankondiging van opdracht maken integraal deel uit van de aankondiging van opdracht.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelas: Apoio nos domínios de visibilidade e comunicações a favor dos programas de nutrição e educação da UE na República Democrática Popular Lao</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Retificativo n.o 1 ao anúncio de pré-informação relativo a um contrato de serviços</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referência da publicação: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplemento do Jornal Oficial da União Europeia, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>União Europeia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada pela Comissão Europeia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Em vez de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Base jurídica</P><P>Regulamento (UE) n.<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> 233/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, que institui um instrumento de financiamento da cooperação para o desenvolvimento para o período de 2014-2020.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Ler:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Base jurídica</P><P>Regulamento (UE) n.o 236/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que estabelece regras e procedimentos comuns para a execução dos instrumentos da União de financiamento da ação externa e Regulamento (UE) n.o 233/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que cria um instrumento de financiamento da cooperação para o desenvolvimento para o período 2014-2020 — Ver anexo A2 do «Guia Prático».</P><P>Importa notar que após a saída do Reino Unido da UE, as regras de acesso aos procedimentos de adjudicação de contratos da UE de operadores económicos estabelecidos em países terceiros aplicar-se-ão aos candidatos ou proponentes provenientes do Reino Unido consoante o resultado das negociações. Caso tal acesso não esteja previsto pelas disposições legais em vigor, os candidatos ou proponentes do Reino Unido poderão ser excluídos do concurso.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Todos os restantes pontos e condições do anúncio de concurso permanecem inalterados. As modificações e/ou correções supramencionadas ao anúncio de concurso são parte integrante do mesmo.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: Stöd för synlighet och kommunikation till EU:s närings- och utbildningsprogram i demokratiska folkrepubliken Laos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rättelse nr 1 av förhandsmeddelandet om tjänster</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Publikationsreferens: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Tillägg till Europeiska unionens officiella tidning, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska unionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representerad av Europeiska kommissionen, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>I stället för:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Rättslig grund</P><P>Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 233/2014 om upprättande av ett finansieringsinstrument för utvecklingssamarbete för perioden 2014-2020</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Skall det stå:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Rättslig grund</P><P>Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 236/2014 av den 11 mars 2014 om fastställande av gemensamma bestämmelser och förfaranden för genomförandet av unionens instrument för finansiering av yttre åtgärder och Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 233/2014 av den 11 mars 2014 om upprättande av ett finansieringsinstrument för utvecklingssamarbete för perioden 2014–2020 – Se bilaga A2 till den praktiska handledningen.</P><P>Observera att efter Storbritanniens utträde ur EU kommer reglerna om tillgång till EU:s upphandlingsförfaranden för ekonomiska aktörer etablerade i tredjeländer att tillämpas på sökande eller anbudsgivare från Storbritannien beroende på resultatet av förhandlingarna. Om sådan tillgång inte tillhandahålls av rättsliga bestämmelser som gäller vid tidpunkten för kontraktstilldelningen kan sökande eller anbudsgivare från Förenade kungariket komma att uteslutas från upphandlingsförfarandet.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alla andra villkor i meddelandet om upphandling förblir oförändrade. Ovannämnda ändringar och/eller rättelser av meddelandet om upphandling utgör en integrerad del av meddelandet om upphandling.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: Podpora zviditelnění a komunikační podpora pro programy EU zaměřené na výživu a vzdělávání v Laoské lidově demokratické republice</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Oprava č. 1 oznámení předběžných informací o službách</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenční číslo: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatek k Úřednímu věstníku Evropské unie, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastoupená Evropskou komisí, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgie.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Namísto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Právní základ</P><P>Nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 233/2014, kterým se zřizuje finanční nástroj pro rozvojovou spolupráci pro období 2014-2020</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Čtěte:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Právní základ</P><P>Nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 2014 ze dne 11.3.2014, kterým se stanoví společná pravidla a postupy pro provádění nástrojů Unie pro financování vnější činnosti a nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady č. 233/2014 ze dne 11.3.2014, kterým se zřizuje finanční nástroj pro rozvojovou spolupráci pro období let 2014–2020 – viz příloha No236 „Praktického průvodce“.</P><P>Připomínáme, že po vystoupení Spojeného království z EU se na zájemce nebo uchazeče ze Spojeného království, v závislosti od výsledku jednání, budou uplatňovat pravidla přístupu k postupům výběrového řízení EU ze strany hospodářských subjektů se sídlem ve třetích zemích. V případě, že takový přístup není zabezpečen právními předpisy platnými v době zadání zakázky, mohli by být uchazeči nebo účastníci ze Spojeného království vyloučeni z výběrového řízení.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Další smluvní podmínky oznámení o zakázce zůstávají beze změn. Výše uvedené úpravy a/nebo opravy oznámení o zakázce jsou nedílnou součástí oznámení o zakázce.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: Märgatavus- ja teabevahetuse tugi ELi toitlustus- ja haridusprogrammidele Laose Demokraatlikus Rahvavabariigis</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Teenuste eelteate parandus nr 1</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avaldamise viide: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Euroopa Liidu Teataja täiendus, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Liit</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, keda esindab Euroopa Komisjon, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Enne:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Õiguslik alus</P><P>Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu määrus (EL) nr 233/2014, millega luuakse arengukoostöö rahastamisvahend aastateks 2014-2020.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Uus versioon:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Õiguslik alus</P><P>Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 236/2014, milles sätestatakse liidu välistegevuse rahastamisvahendite rakendamise ühised eeskirjad ja menetlused, ning Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 233/2014, millega luuakse arengukoostöö rahastamisvahend aastateks 2014–2020 (vt praktilise juhendi lisa A2).</P><P>Võtke teadmiseks, et olenevalt läbirääkimiste tulemustest kohaldatakse pärast Ühendkuningriigi EList lahkumist Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaatidele või pakkujatele kolmandates riikides asutatud ettevõtjatele kehtivaid ELi hankemenetlustele juurepääsu käsitlevaid eeskirju. Juhul, kui selline juurdepääs ei ole tagatud lepingu sõlmimise ajal kehtivate õiguslike sätete kaudu, võidakse Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaadid või pakkujad hankemenetlusest kõrvale jätta.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Kõik muud hanketeate tingimused jäävad muutmata. Hanketeate eespool nimetatud muudatused ja/või parandused on hanketeate lahutamatu osa.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüsszel: Az uniós táplálkozási és oktatási programok láthatósági és kommunikációs támogatása a Laoszi Népi Demokratikus Köztársaságban</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>A szolgáltatásra irányuló előzetes összesített hirdetmény 1. számú helyesbítése</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Közzétételi hivatkozás: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Kiegészítés az Európai Unió Hivatalos Lapjához, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európai Unió</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, amelyet az Európai Bizottság képvisel, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüsszel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>A következő helyett:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Jogalap</P><P>A 2014-2020-ig szóló fejlesztési együttműködés finanszírozási eszközének létrehozásáról szóló 233/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Helyesen:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Jogalap</P><P>A külső tevékenységek finanszírozására vonatkozó uniós eszközök végrehajtására vonatkozó közös szabályok és eljárások megállapításáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű 236/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet, valamint a 2014-2020-as időszakra szóló fejlesztési együttműködési finanszírozási eszköz létrehozásáról szóló 233/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet – Lásd a gyakorlati útmutató A2 mellékletét.</P><P>Figyelembe kell venni, hogy az Egyesült Királyságnak az EU-ból való kilépése után az Egyesült Királyságból származó jelentkezőkre vagy ajánlattevőkre – a tárgyalások kimenetelétől függően – az EU közbeszerzési eljárásaihoz való hozzáférés tekintetében a harmadik országok gazdasági szereplői számára érvényes szabályok vonatkoznak. Amennyiben az ilyen eljárásokban való részvételről nem rendelkezik a szerződés odaítélésének időpontjában hatályban lévő jogszabály, az Egyesült Királyságban székhellyel rendelkező jelentkezőket, illetve ajánlattevőket kizárhatják a közbeszerzési eljárásból.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Az ajánlati felhívás többi feltétele változatlan marad. Az ajánlati felhívás fenti módosításai és/vagy javításai annak szerves részét képezik.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Briuselis: Matomumo ir komunikacijos parama ES mitybos ir švietimo programoms Laoso Liaudies Demokratinėje Respublikoje</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paslaugų išankstinio informacinio skelbimo klaidų ištaisymas Nr. 1</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Nuoroda į publikaciją: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Europos Bendrijos Oficialiojo Leidinio priedas, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos Sąjunga</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, atstovaujama Europos Komisijos, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Briuselis</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Vietoj:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Teisinis pagrindas</P><P>11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 233/2014, kuriuo nustatoma vystomojo bendradarbiavimo finansavimo priemonė 2014-2020 m. laikotarpiui</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Turi būti:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Teisinis pagrindas</P><P>11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 236/2014, kuriuo nustatomos bendros Sąjungos išorės veiksmų finansavimo priemonių įgyvendinimo taisyklės ir procedūros, Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 233/2014, kuriuo nustatoma vystomojo bendradarbiavimo finansavimo priemonė 2014–2020 m. laikotarpiui (žr. Praktinio vadovo A2 priedą).</P><P>Prašome atkreipti dėmesį, kad Jungtinei Karalystei pasitraukus iš ES, ekonominės veiklos vykdytojų, įsikūrusių trečiosiose šalyse, prieigos prie ES pirkimo procedūrų taisyklės bus taikomos kandidatams ar konkurso dalyviams iš Jungtinės Karalystės, priklausomai nuo derybų rezultato. Jeigu tokia prieiga nebus suteikta galiojančiomis teisinėmis nuostatomis, kandidatai arba konkurso dalyviai iš Jungtinės Karalystės gali būti pašalinti iš pirkimo procedūros.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Visos kitos skelbimo apie pirkimą nuostatos ir sąlygos lieka nepakeistos. Pirmiau išvardyti skelbimo apie pirkimą pakeitimai ir (arba) pataisymai yra neatskiriama skelbimo apie pirkimą dalis.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brisele: Atpazīstamības un komunikācijas atbalsts ES uztura un izglītības programmām Laosas TDR</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Iepriekšējā informatīvā paziņojuma par pakalpojumu līgumu labojums Nr. 1</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Atsauce uz publikāciju: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Eiropas Savienības Oficiālā Vēstneša pielikums, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Savienība</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ko pārstāv Eiropas Komisija, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brisele</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Beļģija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Šī teksta vietā:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Tiesiskais pamats</P><P>Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 233/2014, ar ko izveido finanšu instrumentu sadarbībai attīstības jomā 2014-2020 gadam.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Jābūt:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Tiesiskais pamats</P><P>Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes 11.3.2014 Regula (ES) Nr. 236/2014, ar ko paredz kopīgus noteikumus un procedūras, lai īstenotu Savienības instrumentus ārējās darbības finansēšanai, un Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes 11.3.2014 Regula (ES) Nr. 233/2014, ar ko izveido finanšu instrumentu sadarbībai attīstības jomā 2014.–2020. gadam — Skatīt Praktiskās rokasgrāmatas A2. pielikumu.</P><P>Lūdzam ņemt vērā, ka pēc Apvienotās Karalistes izstāšanās no ES uz kandidātiem un pretendentiem no Apvienotās Karalistes atkarībā no sarunu iznākuma attieksies noteikumi par trešo valstu uzņēmēju tiesībām piedalīties ES iepirkuma procedūrās. Ja līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas brīdī spēkā esošajās tiesību normās šāda piekļuve nebūs paredzēta, kandidāti vai pretendenti no Apvienotās Karalistes var tikt izslēgti no iepirkuma procedūras.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Visi pārējie paziņojuma par līgumu noteikumi un nosacījumi paliek nemainīgi. Iepriekš minētās izmaiņas un/vai labojumi paziņojumā par līgumu ir neatņemama paziņojuma par līgumu daļa.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussell: Appoġġ fil-Viżibilità u l-Komunikazzjoni lill-Programmi tal-UE għan-Nutrizzjoni u l-Edukazzjoni f'Lao PDR</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tiswija Nru 1 għall-avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel dwar servizz</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement tal-Gurnal Ufficjali ta’ l-Unjoni Ewropea’, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>L-Unjoni Ewropea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, irrappreżentata mill-Kummissjoni Ewropea, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussell</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Belġju.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Minflok:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Il-bażi legali</P><P>Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 233/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill li jistabbilixxi strument ta' finanzjament tal-kooperazzjoni għall-iżvilupp għall-perjodu 2014-2020.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Aqra:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Il-bażi legali</P><P>Ir-Regolament Nru 236/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi regoli u proċeduri komuni għall-implimentazzjoni tal-istrumenti tal-Unjoni għall-finanzjament tal-azzjoni esterna u r-Regolament (UE) Nru 233/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi strument ta' finanzjament tal-kooperazzjoni għall-iżvilupp għall-perjodu 2014-2020 — Ara l-Anness A2 tal-gwida prattika.</P><P>Jekk jogħġbok kun af li wara l-irtirar tar-Renju Unit mill-UE, ir-regoli tal-aċċess għall-proċeduri ta' ksib tal-UE ta' operaturi ekonomiċi mwaqqfa f'pajjiżi terzi se japplikaw għall-kandidati jew dawk li jitgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit skont ir-riżultat tan-negozjati. F'każ li tali aċċess mhux ipprovdut minn dispożizzjonijiet legali fis-seħħ fil-ħin tal-għoti tal-kuntratt, il-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit jistgħu jitwarrbu mill-proċedura tal-ksib.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>It-termini u l-kundizzjonijiet l-oħrajn kollha tal-avviż ta' kuntratt jibqgħu ma jinbidlux. It-tibdiliet u/jew it-tiswijiet ta' hawn fuq għall-avviż ta' kuntratt huma parti integrali mill-avviż tal-kuntratt.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruksela: Wsparcie widoczności i komunikacji na rzecz unijnych programów dotyczących edukacji i żywienia w Laotańskiej Republice Ludowo-Demokratycznej</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sprostowanie nr 1 wstępnego ogłoszenia informacyjnego o zamówieniu na usługi</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Numer referencyjny publikacji: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplement do Dziennika Urzędowego Unii Europejskiej, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unia Europejska</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentowana przez Komisję Europejską, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruksela</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Zamiast:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Podstawa prawna</P><P>Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (WE) nr 233/2014 ustanawiające Instrument Finansowania Współpracy na rzecz Rozwoju na lata 2014-2020.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Powinno być:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Podstawa prawna</P><P>Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 236/2014 z dnia 11 marca 2014 r. ustanawiające wspólne zasady i procedury wdrażania unijnych instrumentów na rzecz finansowania działań zewnętrznych oraz rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 233/2014 z dnia 11 marca 2014 r. ustanawiające Instrument Finansowania Współpracy na rzecz Rozwoju na lata 2014-2020 – zob. Załącznik A2 Praktycznego przewodnika</P><P>Należy mieć świadomość, że po wystąpieniu Zjednoczonego Królestwa z UE brytyjscy kandydaci i oferenci będą podlegać zasadom dostępu do unijnych procedur udzielania zamówień podmiotom gospodarczym w państwach trzecich w zależności od wyniku negocjacji. W sytuacji gdy przepisy prawa obowiązujące w chwili udzielenia zamówienia nie będą przewidywać takiego dostępu, kandydaci lub oferenci ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa mogą zostać wykluczeni z postępowania o udzielenie zamówienia.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Pozostałe warunki wymienione w ogłoszeniu o zamówieniu nie ulegają zmianie. Powyższe zmiany i/lub poprawki ogłoszenia o zamówieniu stanowią jego integralną część.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: Podpora viditeľnosti a komunikácie pre výživové a vzdelávacie programy EÚ v Laoskej ľudovodemokratickej republike</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Korigendum č. 1 k predbežnému oznámeniu o obstarávaní služieb</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenčné číslo: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Príloha k Úradnému vestníku Európskej únie, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európska únia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastúpená Európskou komisiou, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgicko.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Namiesto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Právny základ</P><P>Nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 233/2014, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj financovania rozvojovej spolupráce na obdobie rokov 2014–2020.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Viď:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Právny základ</P><P>Nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 236/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovujú spoločné pravidlá a postupy pre vykonávanie nástrojov Únie na financovanie vonkajšej činnosti, a nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 233/2014, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj financovania rozvojovej spolupráce na obdobie 2014 – 2020 – pozri prílohu A2 v Praktickej príručke.</P><P>Pripomíname, že po vystúpení Spojeného kráľovstva z EÚ sa na záujemcov alebo uchádzačov zo Spojeného kráľovstva, v závislosti od výsledku rokovaní, budú uplatňovať pravidlá prístupu k postupom obstarávania EÚ zo strany hospodárskych subjektov so sídlom v tretích krajinách. V prípade, že takýto prístup sa nezabezpečí ustanoveniami platnými v čase pridelenia zákazky, záujemcovia alebo uchádzači zo Spojeného kráľovstva by mohli byť vylúčení z obstarávacieho konania.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Všetky ostatné body a podmienky oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania zostanú nezmenené. Vyššie uvedené zmeny a/alebo úpravy v oznámení o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania tvoria neoddeliteľnú súčasť oznámenia.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselj: Podpora na področju prepoznavnosti in komuniciranja v zvezi s programi EU za prehrano in izobraževanje v Laoški ljudski demokratični republiki</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Popravek št. 1 predhodnega informativnega obvestila o naročilu storitev</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenčna številka dokumenta: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatek k Uradnemu listu Evropske unije, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ki jo zastopa Evropska komisija, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselj</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Namesto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Pravna podlaga</P><P>Uredba (EU) št. 233/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta o vzpostavitvi instrumenta za financiranje razvojnega sodelovanja za obdobje 2014-2020</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Beri:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Pravna podlaga</P><P>Uredba (EU) št. 236/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o določitvi skupnih pravil in postopkov za izvajanje instrumentov Unije za financiranje zunanjega delovanja in Uredba (EU) št. 233/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o vzpostavitvi instrumenta za financiranje razvojnega sodelovanja za obdobje 2014–2020 — Glej Prilogo A2 k Praktičnemu vodniku.</P><P>Upoštevajte, da se bodo po izstopu Združenega kraljestva iz EU pravila za dostop do razpisnih postopkov EU s strani gospodarskih subjektov, ustanovljenih v tretjih državah, za kandidate ali ponudnike iz Združenega kraljestva uporabljala v skladu z rezultati pogajanj. V primeru, da v času oddaje naročila veljavne pravne določbe ne zagotavljajo tovrstnega dostopa, se lahko kandidatom ali ponudnikom iz Združenega kraljestva sodelovanje v razpisnem postopku zavrne.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Vsi ostali formalni pogoji obvestila o naročilu ostanejo nespremenjeni. Zgornje spremembe in/ali popravki obvestila o naročilu so sestavni del obvestila o naročilu.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-An Bhruiséil: Tacaíocht Infheictheachta agus Cumarsáide do Chláir Chothaitheach agus Oideachais AE i nDaon-Phoblacht Dhaonlathach Laos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ceartúchán uimh.1 leis an bhfógra réamhaisnéise seirbhíse</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Forlíonaidh d'Iris Oifigiúil an Aontais Eorpaigh, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An tAontas Eorpach</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, arna ionadú ag an gCoimisiún Eorpach, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Bheilg.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Seachas:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Bunús dlí</P><P>Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 233/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle, lena mbunaítear ionstraim mhaoinithe le haghaidh comhair um fhorbairt don tréimhse 2014-2020</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Léigh:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Bunús dlí</P><P>Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 236/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 ina leagtar síos rialacha agus nósanna imeachta comhchoiteanna chun ionstraimí an Aontais a chur chun feidhme maidir le gníomhaíocht sheachtrach a mhaoiniú agus Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 233/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle lena mbunaítear ionstraim mhaoinithe maidir le comhar um fhorbairt don tréimhse idir na blianta 2014–2020 — féach Iarscríbhinn A2 leis an treoir phraiticiúil.</P><P>Tabhair faoi deara go gcuirfear na rialacha um rochtain ar nósanna imeachta soláthair an AE ag oibreoirí eacnamaíocha atá bunaithe i dtríú tíortha i bhfeidhm ar iarrthóirí nó ar thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe tar éis di tarraingt siar ón AE, ag brath ar thorthaí na n-idirbheartaíochtaí. Sa chás nach gcuirfear a leithéid de rochtain ar fáil trí fhorálacha dlíthiúla a bheidh i bhfeidhm an tráth a dhámhfar an conradh, d'fhéadfaí tairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe a dhiúltú ón nós imeachta soláthair.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Níl athrú ar bith thairis sin ar théarmaí ná ar choinníollacha an fhógra chonartha. Is dlúthchuid den fhógra conartha iad na hathruithe nó na ceartúcháin thuas leis an bhfógra conartha.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Брюксел: Подкрепа за действията по популяризиране и комуникация във връзка с програмите на ЕС в областта на храненето и образованието в Лаоска народнодемократична република</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Поправка № 1 на предварително информационно обявление за услуги</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Референтен № на публикация: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Приложение към Официален вестник на Европейския съюз, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейски съюз</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, представляван от Европейската комисия, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Брюксел</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Белгия.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Вместо:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Правно основание</P><P>Регламент (ЕС) № 233/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета за създаване на финансов инструмент за сътрудничество за развитие за периода 2014—2020 г.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Да се чете:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Правно основание</P><P>Регламент (ЕС) № 2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за определяне на общи правила и процедури за изпълнението на инструментите на Съюза за финансиране на външната дейност и Регламент (ЕС) № 233/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета за създаване на финансов инструмент за сътрудничество за развитие за периода 2014–2020 г. – вижте приложение А2 на Практическото ръководство.</P><P>Моля, имайте предвид, че след оттеглянето на Обединеното кралство от ЕС, правилата за достъп до процедури за обществени поръчки на ЕС за икономически оператори, установени в трети държави, ще се прилагат за кандидати или оференти от Обединеното кралство, в зависимост от резултата от преговорите. В случай че такъв достъп не е предвиден в действащите правни разпоредби, които са в сила по време на възлагането на поръчката, кандидатите или оферентите от Обединеното кралство могат да бъдат отхвърлени от процедурата за обществена поръчка.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Всички други срокове и условия на обявлението за поръчка остават непроменени. Горепосочените промени и/или поправки към обявлението за поръчка са неразделна част от него.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Vizibilitate și sprijin privind comunicațiile în cadrul programelor UE de nutriție și educație în Republica Populară Democrată Laos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Erata nr. 1 la anunțul de intenție privind un contract de achiziții publice de servicii</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referința publicației: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplimentul Jurnalului Oficial al Uniunii Europene, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Uniunea Europeană</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentată de Comisia Europeană, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>În loc de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Temeiul juridic</P><P>Regulamentul (UE) nr. 233/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului de instituire a unui instrument de finanțare a cooperării pentru dezvoltare în perioada 2014-2020.</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>A se citi:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Temeiul juridic</P><P>Regulamentul (UE) nr. 236/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de stabilire a normelor și procedurilor comune pentru punerea în aplicare a instrumentelor Uniunii pentru finanțarea acțiunii externe și Regulamentul (UE) nr. 233/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului de instituire a unui instrument de finanțare a cooperării pentru dezvoltare în perioada 2014-2020 – a se vedea anexa 2 la „Ghidul Practic”.</P><P>A se avea în vedere că, după retragerea Marii Britanii din UE, normele de acces al operatorilor economici stabiliți în țări terțe la procedurile de achiziții publice ale UE se vor aplica ofertanților sau candidaților din Marea Britanie în funcție de rezultatul negocierilor. În cazul în care accesul nu este prevăzut de dispozițiile juridice în vigoare la momentul atribuirii contractului, candidații sau ofertanții din Marea Britanie ar putea fi respinși de la procedura de achiziții publice.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Toți ceilalți termeni și toate celelalte condiții din anunțul de participare rămân neschimbate. Modificările și/sau rectificările de mai sus aduse anunțului de participare fac parte integrantă din acesta.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Vidljivost i komunikacijska podrška programima na području prehrane i obrazovanja EU-a u Narodnoj Demokratskoj Republici Laos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ispravak br. 1 prethodne informacijske obavijesti o uslugama</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Uputa na objavu: EuropeAid/139467/DH/SER/LA</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatak Službenom listu Europske unije, 1.2.2018, 2018/S 022-045294)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, koju predstavlja Europska komisija, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Umjesto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Pravni temelj</P><P>Uredba (EU) br. 233/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća o uspostavi Instrumenta financiranja za razvojnu suradnju za razdoblje 2014-2020</P><P>[...]</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Glasi:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>11. Pravni temelj</P><P>Uredba (EU) br. 236/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014 o utvrđivanju zajedničkih pravila i postupaka za provedbu instrumenata Unije za financiranje vanjskog djelovanja i Uredba (EU) br. 233/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014 o uspostavi Instrumenta financiranja za razvojnu suradnju za razdoblje 2014.–2020. — Vidjeti Prilog A2 Praktičnom vodiču.</P><P>Napominjemo da će se nakon povlačenja Ujedinjene Kraljevine iz EU-a na natjecatelje ili ponuditelje iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine primjenjivati pravila pristupa postupcima nabave EU-a za gospodarske subjekte s poslovnim nastanom u trećim zemljama, ovisno o rezultatima pregovora. U slučaju da pristup nije omogućen putem pravnih odredbi koje su na snazi u vrijeme sklapanja ugovora, natjecatelji ili ponuditelji iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine mogu biti odbijeni iz postupka javne nabave.</P><P>[...]</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Svi ostali uvjeti poziva na nadmetanje ostaju nepromijenjeni. Prethodno navedene izmjene i/ili ispravci poziva na nadmetanje čine sastavni dio poziva na nadmetanje.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>