<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="034846-2018"
            EDITION="2018017">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-035170-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20190123</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>17</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180125</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 017-034846</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:034846-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>https://www.gov.uk/government/organisations/department-for-international-development</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="75211200">Foreign economic-aid-related services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKM95">South Lanarkshire</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKM95">South Lanarkshire</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">16000000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180123</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="8">Other</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C01</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги, свързани с външноикономическа помощ</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Služby související se zahraniční hospodářskou pomocí</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tjenester vedrørende økonomisk hjælp til udlandet</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Wirtschaftshilfe an das Ausland</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες που σχετίζονται με θέματα εξωτερικής οικονομικής βοήθειας</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Foreign economic-aid-related services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios relacionados con la ayuda económica exterior</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Välismaise majandusabi teenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kansainväliseen talousapuun liittyvät palvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services liés à l'aide économique aux pays étrangers</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Foreign economic-aid-related services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge povezane s vanjskom ekonomskom pomoći</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Külföldi gazdasági segítséggel kapcsolatos szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi connessi agli aiuti economici destinati a paesi terzi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Paslaugos, susijusios su užsienio ekonomine pagalba</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ar ārējo ekonomisko palīdzību saistītie pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' l-għajnuna ekonomika barranija</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Diensten in verband met economische hulp aan het buitenland</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi związane ze świadczeniem pomocy gospodarczej dla zagranicy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços relacionados com a ajuda económica aos outros países</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de ajutor economic extern</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Služby súvisiace so zahraničnou hospodárskou pomocou</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve gospodarske pomoči tujini</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>East Kilbride</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tjänster för ekonomiskt bistånd till utlandet</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Department for International Development</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F01_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F01" LG="EN">
         <NOTICE TYPE="PRI_ONLY"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Department for International Development</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Abercrombie House, Eaglesham Road</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>East Kilbride</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>G758EA</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Susan Lynch</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+44 1355843620</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>S-Lynch@dfid.gov.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM95"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://www.gov.uk/government/organisations/department-for-international-development</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://www.gov.uk/government/organisations/department-for-international-development/about/procurement</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="MINISTRY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>International Aid</CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>PO 8180, Forest Governance, Markets and Climate (FGMC) programme</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>8180</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="75211200"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The Forest Governance, Markets, and Climate (FGMC) programme aims at governance and market reforms that reduce the illegal use of forest resources and benefit poor people who depend on forests for their livelihoods.</P>
               <P>It supports global efforts to tackle deforestation, in particular by tackling illegal logging in developing timber-producing countries and the trade in illegally-produced timber products.</P>
               <P>It applies lessons from the timber trade to other commodities that impact forests and people who depend on forests for their livelihoods.</P>
               <P>It is part of a coordinated endeavor with the EU and is aligned with global efforts involving Norway, China, Japan, the USA, and developing forest countries in Africa, Asia, and Latin America.</P>
               <P>FGMC is a 10-year programme (2011-2021) with this requirement running from 2018-2021 and focussing on completing reforms, consolidating gains, and communicating lessons to drive change at both national and international levels.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">16000000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="75211200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM95"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Services may be delivered in Liberia, Ghana, Guyana, Democratic Republic of Congo, Gabon, China, Myanmar, Indonesia, and one other country in either Africa or East Asia..</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The intended procurement route is still to be determined and will be discussed further at the Early Market Engagement (EME) event. A DFID Standard Services contract(s) will be awarded.</P>
                  <P>DFID intends to hold an Early Market Engagement (EME) event on Friday the 2nd February 2018 at 13:30 at DFID's Headquarters at 22 Whitehall, London SW1A 2EG. There will be a facility to dial in remotely to this event.</P>
                  <P>During the EME representatives from DFID will:</P>
                  <P>1) Present further details on the requirements,</P>
                  <P>2) Provide an update on the procurement process, and,</P>
                  <P>3) Provide an opportunity for attendees to ask questions and contribute to the planned procurement approach.</P>
                  <P>In addition, there will be an opportunity during the event for networking. An attendance list will be circulated after the event.</P>
                  <P>In order to register your attendance, you must register your interest on the DFID Supplier Portal (https://supplierportal.dfid.gov.uk/selfservice/) and complete the details requested in the Survey Monkey link that will be available on the DFID Supplier Portal. Due to limited capacity, attendance is restricted to 2 representatives per organization. Places will be reserved on a first come first served basis and when capacity is reached the Survey Monkey will be closed and no further registration will be accepted. You must register by 12:00 (Noon- BST) on Wednesday the 31st January 2018. Please note that only Companies that pre-register will have security clearance to attend the event.</P>
                  <P>The ‘Dialogue/ Clarification’ function on the DFID Supplier Portal will be the main communication channel moving forward. We are happy to receive questions, comments, and suggestions in advance, which we will respond to at the event, and we will not disclose the source of these when responding.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>2018-04-06</DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>This PIN Notice and EME cover the full DFID Forest Governance, Market, and Climate (FGMC) Programme and will provide information on the 6 individual requirements which will be operational as soon as feasible and will run through until 2021. The start and end points for specific contracts will vary depending on the scope of work and timing of when detailed TORs and specifications can be provided.</P>
               <P>Suppliers will be sought to deliver the following services:</P>
               <P>1) Provision of a team of experts to support the management and monitoring of FGMC. A supplier will provide technical expertise to assist DFID in monitoring the programme, especially projects in the 6 focal countries, and manage approximately 20 accountable grants (with likely value of £40m). A contract value of up to £2.5 million, to be deployed as soon as possible, and by September if feasible.</P>
               <P>NOTE: The existing contract is under review and may be extended. Should this happen DFID will not look to contract a new supplier to support the management of FGMC.</P>
               <P>2) Facilitation of multi-stakeholder processes in up to 6 countries (including Guyana, Liberia, Ghana and the Republic of Congo). The supplier will deploy experts to be based in each country and to work with national stakeholders across government, the private sector and civil society to support stakeholder-driven dynamic policy, legal and VPA reform processes. 3 years contract, up to £6 million to be deployed as soon as possible, and by September 2018 if feasible.</P>
               <P>3) Support to build capacity and create demand for governance reforms as framed by the Liberia VPA. The supplier will build technical capacity of Liberian stakeholders (notably from the private sector, communities, and CSOs) to comply with laws and regulations governing forest production. It will support negotiations between national stakeholders to establish norms and regulations for the informal sector that mainly supplies the domestic market, thereby reducing levels of illegal logging. Up to £6m over 3 years, starting in September 2018.</P>
               <P>4) Support to further the UK-China partnership that seeks to tackle illegal logging, to develop sustainable business standards and foster dialogue and responsible investments in developing countries. The focus in developing countries will be to work jointly in Guyana, Myanmar, Gabon, Rep of Congo (country selection still to be determined). Up to £2m over 3 years, starting in January 2019.</P>
               <P>5) Technical assistance and support to stakeholders in Guyana to implement the VPA and the legal and governance reforms and system upgrades required to ensure full legal compliance and to meet international market expectations. Detailed TORs will only be developed once the VPA negotiations are concluded (in January 2018) identifying capacity development needs. Up to £3m over 2 years starting in January 2019 if feasible.</P>
               <P>6) Independent research to understand the results and impacts of the FGMC programme. Details of the monitoring required will be framed on an annual basis to generate independent information on the influence and results of the programme. A team of experts with governance, economics and forest expertise would be required with detailed knowledge of political economy of the sector in West and Central Africa, the Mekong and Indonesia. It may include final evaluation. Up to £1 million over 2 years, to start by December 2018.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-01-23</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F01_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
