<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="086563-2018" EDITION="2018040"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-084192-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180322</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>40</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180227</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 040-086563</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:086563-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="MD"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45233120">Road construction works</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71520000">Construction supervision services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180221</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180322 17:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="Z">Not specified</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>BR605</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - Vejsektorprogram III i Moldova</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Moldau</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - Programm III für den Straßensektor der Republik Moldau</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Moldova Road Sector Program III</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Moldavia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Programa III relativo al sector viario de Moldavia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Moldovan tiealaa koskeva ohjelma III</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Moldavie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Programme III relatif au secteur routier en Moldavie</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Μολδαβία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Κισινάου</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - Πρόγραμμα III για τον οδικό τομέα στη Μολδαβία</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - Programma III relativo al settore stradale in Moldova</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Moldavië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - Programma III voor de wegensector in Moldavië</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Moldávia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Programa relativo ao setor rodoviário da Moldávia III</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Moldavien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Program III för vägsektorn i Moldavien</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Moldavsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kišiněv</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Program silničního sektoru v Moldavsku III</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chişinău</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Moldova maanteesektori III programm</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Moldovai közúti ágazati program III.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Moldavija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kišiniovas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - Moldovos kelių sektoriaus programa III</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kišiņeva</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - III Moldovas ceļu nozares programma</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - It-III Programm tas-Settur tat-Toroq fil-Moldova</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Mołdawia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kiszyniów</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Program dotyczący sektora dróg w Mołdawii III</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Moldavsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kišiňov</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Program cestného sektora v Moldavsku III</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Moldavija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Program cestnega sektorja v Moldaviji III</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Mholdóiv, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Clár Earnála Bóithre III don Mholdóiv</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Молдова</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Кишинев</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - Програма за пътния сектор на МолдоваMoldova Road Sector Program III</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Programul III privind sectorul rutier din Moldova</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kišinjev</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Program u području cestovnog sektora III. u Moldovi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">State Road Administration</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - Vejsektorprogram III i Moldova (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - Programm III für den Straßensektor der Republik Moldau (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Moldova Road Sector Program III (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Programa III relativo al sector viario de Moldavia (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Moldovan tiealaa koskeva ohjelma III (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Programme III relatif au secteur routier en Moldavie (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - Πρόγραμμα III για τον οδικό τομέα στη Μολδαβία (MD-Κισινάου)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - Programma III relativo al settore stradale in Moldova (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - Programma III voor de wegensector in Moldavië (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Programa relativo ao setor rodoviário da Moldávia III (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Program III för vägsektorn i Moldavien (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Program silničního sektoru v Moldavsku III (MD-Kišiněv)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Moldova maanteesektori III programm (MD-Chişinău)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Moldovai közúti ágazati program III. (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - Moldovos kelių sektoriaus programa III (MD-Kišiniovas)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - III Moldovas ceļu nozares programma (MD-Kišiņeva)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - It-III Programm tas-Settur tat-Toroq fil-Moldova (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Program dotyczący sektora dróg w Mołdawii III (MD-Kiszyniów)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Program cestného sektora v Moldavsku III (MD-Kišiňov)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Program cestnega sektorja v Moldaviji III (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Clár Earnála Bóithre III don Mholdóiv (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - Програма за пътния сектор на МолдоваMoldova Road Sector Program III (MD-Кишинев)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Programul III privind sectorul rutier din Moldova (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Program u području cestovnog sektora III. u Moldovi (MD-Kišinjev)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>“REHABILITATION OF M3 CHISINAU-GIURGIULESTI ROAD, KM 96+800 - KM 171+290 AND KM 179+650-KM 190+750”</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPERVISION OF CIVIL WORKS UNDER THE CONTRACT:</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: Moldova Road Sector Program III</P><P>Country: Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 21.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 22.3.2018, at 17:00 (local time)</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the general procurement notice nº 8857-GPN-41442 for this project which was updated in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s web-site on 20.10.2017 and in the Supplement to the Official Journal of European Union (OJ/S) on 25.10.2017.</P><P>The government of the Republic of Moldova intends using the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of the Moldova Road Sector Program where the construction supervision services are required.</P><P>The objective of the construction supervision services is to supervise the execution of the works and administer the contract through efficient and effective expertise, resulting in the issue of a taking-over certificate and a performance certificate for the following works contracts within the budget and time defined in the project procurement plan.</P><P>The M3 Road provides the shortest road connection between Chişinau, the capital, and Giurgiuleşti and its nearby port in the south giving access to the Danube River and the Black Sea. The M3 Road is part of a larger Trans - European Road, the E577.</P><P>The rehabilitation works under this contract comprises three sections of M3 Road. The first section commences from Municipality of Comrat at km 96 + 800 to km 151 + 200 at Ciumai village. The second section commences from km 151 + 200 to km 171 + 290. The third section of M3 Road runs further from the km 179 + 650 to km 190 + 750. The first section includes works for the completion of earthworks, asphalt works, road markings, signs, sidewalks, bridges, drainage facilities, minor intersections, roundabout, shoulders, bus stops, guardrails, landscaping, external lightening and removal of underground communication cable.</P><P>The length of second section is about 20,1 km from Ciumai village to Vulcăneşti town. The existing road is mainly a 2-lane single carriageway paved road. The 3rd section measures 11,1 km and runs from south of Vulcanesti to the beginning of Slobozia Mare new designed bypass.</P><P>The employer invites expressions of interest from suitably qualified firms who are interested in providing such assistance to the employer to facilitate the timely and effective implementation of the project by advising the employer on the administration of the EBRD funded Contracts with due diligence and by carrying out the duties of the engineer assigned to him in the contracts which will be a re-measurement unit rate contract based on FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction, MDB Harmonized edition, 2010. The consultant shall exercise the authority attributable to the engineer, as specified in or necessarily implied from the contracts, to ensure timely, satisfactory completion of the works in accordance with the contracts.</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: The assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and last about 52 months, which includes 1 month for pre-commencement activities, 36 months of works supervision, 12 months covering defects notification period and 3 months for the performance certificate issue and other closing activities.</P><P>In order to successfully implement the assignment, it is envisaged that the Consultant’s team will consist of the following experts:</P><P>— 1 (one) team leader/ engineer’s representative,</P><P>— 1 (one) resident engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer/ quality assurance engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor / contract specialist,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge engineer,</P><P>— Short-term experts.</P><P>Also, the consultant shall envisage the group of following technical support staff:</P><P>— 1 (one) materials engineer,</P><P>— 1 (one) quantity surveyor,</P><P>— 1 (one) environmental and social expert,</P><P>— 1 (one) road inspector,</P><P>— 1 (one) bridge inspector,</P><P>— 2 (two) land surveyors,</P><P>— 2 (two) laboratory assistants,</P><P>— 1 (one) designer’s representative.</P><P>Funding source: EBRD.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan/grant shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the client’s country prohibitions, if such prohibitions are confirmed as acceptable by the Bank.</P><P>In order to determine the capability and experience of consulting firms seeking to be shortlisted, the information submitted with the expression of interest shall include the following:</P><P>1. Company profile:</P><P>— company profile, core business, staffing levels and technical capacity, annual turnover,</P><P>— details of firm's/association's/joint venture's standard quality policies, procedures and.</P><P>Practices;</P><P>— name, qualifications and relevant experience of firm's director or manager who will assume overall responsibility for the firm’s, association’s or joint venture’s team coordination, management and output,</P><P>— specific details of firm’s/association’s/join venture’s procedures to ensure quality of its performance over the life of this assignment including management coordination and role of each firm.</P><P>2. Company Experience:</P><P>Provide evidence of the successful completion of 10 projects (Taking-Over Certificate is considered completion) under FIDIC conditions of Contract during the past 5 years.</P><P>Specific Project Data to be provided should include the following details:</P><P>— project title, and narrative description of the project,</P><P>— contractual role of the firm,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by the firm,</P><P>— type of FIDIC contract used for works subject to the supervision,</P><P>— name of firm's senior staff (Project Coordinator, Team Leader/ Engineer’s Representative) involved and functions performed,</P><P>— number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by the firm,</P><P>— the presence of any lead or affiliate companies and their respective roles,</P><P>— detailed description of the actual services provided by associate companies; Number of staff and number of person-months of professional staff provided by affiliate companies,</P><P>— location, and start and completion dates,</P><P>— works contract value,</P><P>— supervision Contract Value,</P><P>— name of the Client and funding source, with which procurement rules, e.g. IFIs’, were applied,</P><P>— details of the works supervised including the following aspects:</P><P>—— supervision of the works in accordance with FIDIC,</P><P>—— review / approval of Construction Drawings,</P><P>—— preparation of variations, analysis of claims in accordance with conditions of contract,</P><P>—— contract administration (correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, document control / contract records, reporting to Employer and Funding agencies),</P><P>—— environmental / Social monitoring and reporting,</P><P>—— concrete bridge construction,</P><P>—— bridge rehabilitation,</P><P>—— drainage structures (culverts / ditches),</P><P>—— earthworks construction,</P><P>—— cold in place asphalt recycling,</P><P>—— cement stabilised pavement construction,</P><P>—— asphalt mix design and construction (binder, SMA),</P><P>—— roadside furniture (signs, safety fencing and road marking),</P><P>—— relocation of utilities (gas /water /electrical /communications).</P><P>In case more than 10 project references will be provided, only 10 most relevant to the assignment in the client’s view will be taken into consideration during evaluation.</P><P>The information on the company’s profile shall be submitted in accordance with Table 1 and the information on company’s experience in accordance with Table 2 of the attached Annex 1.</P><P>The expression of interest is to be in English language and should not exceed 50 pages.</P><P>Evaluation criteria of EOIs:</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile</P><P>Weighting: 10 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — core business and years of experience</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: company profile: — technical and administrative capacity</P><P>Weighting: 5 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience</P><P>Weighting: 90 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the</P><P>Assignment</P><P>Weighting: 75 %</P><P>Criteria — Sub criteria: experience: — experience of consultant specific to the NIS</P><P>Region</P><P>Weighting: 15 %</P><P>Procurement procedure: Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) dated November, 2017. The consultants will be selected under “Quality and Cost-Based Selection” (QCBS).</P><P>A shortlist of qualified firms will be prepared on the response to this invitation, after which the short-listed firms will be invited to submit their proposals.</P><P>If the consultant has been found by a judicial process or other official enquiry to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices as defined in the EBRD PP&amp;R, details of the basis for the outcome of such process or enquiry shall be provided with the expression of interest.</P><P>The employer reserves the right not to shortlist consulting firms that have been found to have engaged in any of the prohibited practices regardless of the results of the valuation of the expressions of interest.</P><P>Interested consultants may obtain further information at the address below during office hours from 8:00 to 17:00 (local time).</P><P>Expressions of interest must be delivered to the Client in an envelope marked "EXPRESSION OF INTEREST for Moldova Road Sector Program: supervision of civil works on M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti Road, km 96 + 800 - km 171 + 290 and km 179 + 650 - km 190 + 750”, to the address mentioned below by 22.3.2018 at 17:00 (local time) in hard copy: 1 original and 1 copy, and 1 electronic copy on CD-ROM or memory stick. Please note that submission of expressions of interest that do not comply with these requirements may be rejected.</P><P>Expressions of interest received after this time and date may be returned unopened.</P><P>Consultants should be aware that distance and customs formalities may require longer than expected delivery time.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Executing Agency/Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>. Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Ms. Diana Lupu</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, Chief of the Procurement Section, Office 401, Bucuriei str. 12A, MD 2004, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Republic of MOLDOVA, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>procurement@asd.md</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX>, Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>www.asd.md</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>