<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="076364-2018"
            EDITION="2018035">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-077524-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180321</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>35</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180220</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 035-076364</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:076364-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.transport.gov.scot</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79212000">Auditing services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79212200">Internal audit services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79212300">Statutory audit services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="90714000">Environmental auditing</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKM">SCOTLAND</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKM82">Glasgow City</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">500000</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180216</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180321 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="N">National or federal Agency/Office</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="8">Other</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Глазгоу</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Одиторски услуги</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Provádění revizí</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Revisionsvirksomhed</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Betriebsprüfung</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Γλασκώβη</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες διαχειριστικού ελέγχου</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Auditing services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de auditoría</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Auditeerimisteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Auditointi- ja tarkastuspalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services d'audit</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glaschú</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Auditing services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Revizorske usluge</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Könyvvizsgálói szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di verifica contabile</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Audito paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glāsgova</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Revīzijas pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' l-awditjar</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Auditdiensten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi audytu</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de auditoria</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de auditare</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Audítorské služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Revizorske storitve</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Revision</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Transport Scotland</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>b656abae-c6a3-40e6-86db-9fa840300520</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Transport Scotland</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Buchanan House, 58 Port Dundas Road</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Glasgow</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>G4 0HF</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Alasdair Sim</CONTACT_POINT>
               <E_MAIL>Alasdair.Sim@transport.gov.scot</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM82"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.transport.gov.scot</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/search/Search_AuthProfile.aspx?ID=AA00099</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CENTRAL_PURCHASING/>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="NATIONAL_AGENCY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>Transport</CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Single supplier framework agreement for Management Systems Audit Services</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>TS/MTRIPS/SER/2018/07</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79212000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Transport Scotland has a requirement for suitably qualified and experienced consultants capable of providing independent auditing services relating to management systems on works and services contracts of varying size and complexity. These services will support the procurement, development, construction, commissioning, operational and delivery stages of trunk road projects across Scotland.</P>
               <P>Transport Scotland on behalf of the Scottish Ministers wish to progress a procurement competition to provide Scottish Ministers with confidence that contractors and consultants are operating compliant management systems on our projects, and to support continuous improvements.</P>
               <P>It is anticipated that these services will be predominantly in relation to Scotland’s trunk road network, but could extend to the railways and other parts of the transport system.</P>
               <P>Further information on Transport Scotland can be accessed through our website at: www.transport.gov.scot.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">500000</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79212000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79212200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79212300"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="90714000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Scotland wide, Glasgow.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Transport Scotland on behalf of the Scottish Ministers wish to progress a procurement competition for the services of a suitably experienced audit organisation to provide the following services:</P>
                  <P>a) Provide suitably experienced and qualified personnel to support the Employer and provide services in relation to the audit of the management systems of contractors and consultants for works and services contracts;</P>
                  <P>b) propose an audit schedule and a reporting schedule which will deliver comprehensive auditing of contractor’s and consultant’s management systems;</P>
                  <P>c) undertake focused audits on particular sections management systems on a 3-monthly basis for contractors and a 6-monthly basis for consultants;</P>
                  <P>d) attend the offices, construction sites or other locations within the UK at which the contractor’s and consultant’s management systems are in use in order to undertake the audits;</P>
                  <P>e) auditing of the following management systems:</P>
                  <P>a. BS EN ISO 9001:2008 (quality management systems);</P>
                  <P>b. BS EN ISO 14001:2004 (environmental management systems);</P>
                  <P>c. OHSAS 18001 (occupational health and safety management systems);</P>
                  <P>d. the particular requirements of the contract under which the contractor or consultant is appointed;</P>
                  <P>f) undertake audits of fair work practices and/or ethical practice processes and policy implementation to monitor compliance with particular commitments to community benefits or sustainable practices outlined in the contract under which the contractor or consultant is appointed;</P>
                  <P>g) undertake on-going monitoring of any non-conformances identified by the audit process, and audit corrective actions implemented by contractors and consultants to rectify such non-conformances;</P>
                  <P>h) provide reporting of audit activities to Transport Scotland;</P>
                  <P>i) provide audits on projects ranging in value up to approximately GBP 3 000 000 000;</P>
                  <P>j) attend meetings at Transport Scotland’s main office in Buchanan House, Glasgow or site offices as and when may be required, and</P>
                  <P>k) undertake other miscellaneous/ad-hoc related activities such as: running/facilitating quality or management systems workshops, seminars etc...</P>
                  <P>Auditing of contractors or consultants will also include the auditing of companies or organisations that have been appointed by the contractor or consultant who are operating under the contractor’s or consultant’s management systems, whether directly or indirectly.</P>
                  <P>The auditing organisation/ key personnel may also be required to attend offices, construction sites or other locations within the UK at which the contractor’s and consultant’s management systems are in operation.</P>
                  <P>The auditing organisation shall be required to regularly report on the performance of the services which shall include the following:</P>
                  <P>(i) Monthly briefing notes;</P>
                  <P>(ii) Audit reports;</P>
                  <P>(iii) Quarterly reports;</P>
                  <P>(iv) Annual reports;</P>
                  <P>(v) Financial estimates;</P>
                  <P>(vi) Inception reports;</P>
                  <P>(vii) Status reports;</P>
                  <P>(viii) Any other ad-hoc reports on relevant topics relating to the performance of the services.</P>
                  <P>The Framework participant will be procured through a competitive tender procedure, in accordance with the restricted procedure as provided for in the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015. The Framework Agreement will be for a period of 4 years. Contracts called off the framework will be of varying length depending on individual project requirements. This contract will not be divided into lots as this would make the service unreasonably complex to administer in that manner given the anticipated forward workload since services will be of a repetitive nature.</P>
                  <P>To be considered for this Contract, Economic Operators are required to complete the European Single Procurement Document (ESPD) in accordance with this Contract Notice. Economic Operators shall be evaluated in accordance with the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015, on the basis of information they have provided within the ESPD.</P>
                  <P>The ESPD can be downloaded via the Public Contracts Scotland portal (www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk).</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>The tenderers approach to execution of the Services; management procedures and quality systems and policies, personnel. Further information will be included in the tender documents.</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_COST>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Final tenders will be assessed against evaluation criteria to determine the most economically advantageous submission. Further information will be included in the tender documents.</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_COST>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">500000</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">48</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>5</NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>These economic operators shall be who have:</P>
                  <P>(i) submitted a compliant submission, comprising the completed ESPD;</P>
                  <P>(ii) satisfied the relevant selection criteria under the exclusion grounds;</P>
                  <P>(iii) (a) Minimum Standards of Eligibility — provided evidence of working on specified types of projects over a specified value; and</P>
                  <P>(b) Technical or Professional Ability — provided evidence demonstrating an acceptable level of technical or professional ability; and</P>
                  <P>(c) Human Resources – possess the necessary human resources, qualified appropriately to perform the requirement.</P>
                  <P>(iv) has in place quality, environmental and health and safety management systems and appropriate sustainability measures attributing significantly to the requirement;</P>
                  <P>(v) satisfied minimum standards of economic and financial standing;</P>
                  <P>(vi) achieved the first, second, third, fourth or fifth highest combined weighted scores in respect of technical or professional ability calculated in accordance with the responses to Statements (c);(d) and (e) (refer to Section III.1.3).</P>
                  <P>However, if an economic operator has not submitted a compliant submission as described in (i) above, failed in respect of either (ii), (iii), (iv) or (v) above, then that Economic Operator shall be excluded from the ranking of scores described in (vi) as above.</P>
                  <P>Economic operators shall be required to self-certify their adherence to the above selection criteria via the ESPD (Question Ref. 5.1). Suppliers shall be required to submit appropriate means of proof at a later stage as stated in Regulation 60 of the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015.</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Economic operators may be excluded from this competition if they are in any of the situations referred to in regulation 58 of the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Economic Operators must be enrolled in the relevant professional or trade registers kept in the member state of its establishment (as described in Schedule 5 of the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015) (i.e. registered under Companies House). Economic operators should provide details under Question Ref. 4A.1.</P>
               <P>Accreditation.</P>
               <P>Economic Operators or their appropriate subcontractors must be appropriately accredited/registered with an applicable and relevant body (i.e. UKAS, BSi, IRCA etc) to provide the audit services outlined in this Contract Notice. Economic Operators should provide details of their certifications/ accreditations/ registrations under Question Ref. 4C.6. Subsequently, under ESPD, Question Ref 4D.1 Economic Operators are required to confirm their compliance and be able to provide the appropriate certification.</P>
               <P>Qualifications and Experience.</P>
               <P>It is a requirement that staff employed under the Contract shall have minimum levels of experience, education and professional qualifications. In particular, the Consultant shall have staff who are Chartered professionals (or equivalent) with relevant experience to undertake Audits of Management Systems. This should be coupled with relevant experience of Auditing Management Systems on construction/ civil engineering and highway construction projects.</P>
               <P>Sub-contracting.</P>
               <P>Under ESPD, Question Ref 4C.10: Bidders will be required to confirm whether they intend to subcontract and, if so, for what proportion of the contract.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>Economic Operators shall be required to satisfy minimum standards of economic and financial standing. To determine these standards, Economic Operators shall:</P>
               <P>a) in response to ESPD, Question Ref 4B.1.1 provide the specified annual turnover for the last 2 years of trading, or for the period which is available if trading for less than 2 years;</P>
               <P>b) in response to ESPD Question Ref 4B.4 provide the name, value and/or range of Nine financial criteria for the last 2 years of trading, or for the period which is available if trading for less than 2 years; and</P>
               <P>c) in response to ESPD Question Ref 4B.5.1 confirm they already have or can commit to obtain, prior to commencement of the contract the required levels of insurance.</P>
               <P>In addition to the information requested under (a) and (b), Economic Operators are required to provide a link/ copies of the associated annual accounts as filed at Companies House (or equivalent if not a UK registered company) for the last 2 years of trading, or for the period which is available if less than 2 years.</P>
               <P>This information has been requested to enable Transport Scotland to perform their own assessment and confirm the financial ratios submitted. Ultimately, ensuring the correct score is allocated, and to ensure no misinterpretation. Where there exist differences in ratios, between those provided and those calculated by Transport Scotland, clarification will be sought.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Economic operators shall be required to satisfy minimum standards of economic and financial standing. These are described below:</P>
               <P>Evaluation Criteria Ratios (Question Ref. 4B.4).</P>
               <P>The financial information received under ESPD, Question Ref. 4B.4 shall be evaluated and scored out of 50 by allocating a score against nine individual economic and financial standing evaluation criteria, namely:</P>
               <P>1. Acid Test Ratio;</P>
               <P>2. Cash Interest Cover Ratio;</P>
               <P>3. Return on Capital Employed;</P>
               <P>4. Operating Profit Ratio;</P>
               <P>5. Net Worth;</P>
               <P>6. Gearing;</P>
               <P>7. Annual Contract Value to Turnover;</P>
               <P>8. Filed Accounts;</P>
               <P>9. Audit Report</P>
               <P>The individual scores shall be weighted, with the most recent (“Year 1”) financial statements weighted at 67 percent and the previous (“Year 2”) statements being weighted at 33 percent, to form an aggregated score for each of the 9 criteria over the 2 years.</P>
               <P>The maximum cumulative score resulting from the summation of the 9 economic and financial standing aggregated scores shall be 50 marks. A submission shall be marked as a FAIL and will not be considered further if the score achieved by a Single Economic Operator or a Group of Economic Operators is less than 50 percent of the available marks. The scoring mechanism can be downloaded via the Public Contracts Scotland portal (www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk).</P>
               <P>Where the submission has been submitted by a Group of Economic Operators, the information submitted by each Group Member will be evaluated in the proportion of the percentage shareholdings or percentage equity/interest of each Group Member and a score determined for such Group of Economic Operators on that basis.</P>
               <P>Insurance (Question Ref. 4B.5).</P>
               <P>In response to Question Ref. 4B.5.1 Economic Operators must confirm they already have or can commit to obtain, prior to the commencement, the following levels of insurance:</P>
               <P>Employer's (Compulsory) Liability Insurance = GBP 5 000 000.</P>
               <P>Public Liability Insurance = GBP 5 000 000.</P>
               <P>Professional Indemnity Insurance = GBP 1 000 000.</P>
               <P>In responding to Question Ref 4B.5.1 and 4B.5.2 of the ESPD, where the bidder ticks the box “No, and I cannot commit to obtain it” they shall be marked as FAIL and shall be excluded from this procurement competition.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>ESPD: Question Ref. 4C.1.2 – Using the tables provided, Economic Operators shall be required to insert suitable responses to Statements (a) to (g) set out below, demonstrating that they have the required minimum standards of eligibility and technical and professional ability. Answers to these statements shall be provided by single economic operators and by groups of economic operators (group members should not respond individually). A “group of economic operators” is defined as an unincorporated consortium or joint venture.</P>
               <P>Response to Statement (a) shall be assessed on the basis of PASS or FAIL. Economic Operators who fail to satisfy these minimum standards (either they answer ‘No’ or fail to provide an acceptable answer) shall be excluded from the procurement competition.</P>
               <P>Statement (b) is not scored but is required to be completed.</P>
               <P>The responses to Statements (c), (d) and (e) shall be assessed on the basis of a score with a minimum threshold, using the following scoring mechanism:</P>
               <P>— Nil or inadequate response. Fails to demonstrate previous experience/capacity/capability relevant to this criterion (0-2 Unacceptable),</P>
               <P>— Response is partially relevant but generally poor. The response shows some elements of relevance to the criterion but contains insufficient/limited detail or explanation to demonstrate previous relevant experience/capability/capacity (3-4 Weak),</P>
               <P>— Response is relevant and acceptable. The response demonstrates broad previous experience, knowledge and skills/capacity/capability but may lack in some aspects of similarity e.g. previous experience, knowledge or skills may not be of a similar nature (5-6 Acceptable),</P>
               <P>— Response is relevant and good. The response is sufficiently detailed to demonstrate a good amount of experience, knowledge or skills/capacity/capability relevant to providing similar services to similar clients (7-8 Good),</P>
               <P>— Response is completely relevant and excellent overall. The response is comprehensive, unambiguous and demonstrates thorough experience, knowledge or skills/capacity/capability relevant to providing similar services to similar clients (9-10 Excellent).</P>
               <P>An ESPD submission shall be marked as FAIL and will not be considered further if the score achieved for any statement is less than or equal to 2. Where a response is greater than 2 it shall be weighted in order to calculate a score out of 100 for the 3 statements.</P>
               <P>Under ESPD, Question Ref. 4C6.1 Economic Operators shall be required to insert suitable responses to Statement (f) demonstrating that their employees have the requisite experience, educational and professional qualifications to perform the Framework Agreement.</P>
               <P>The response to statement (g) shall be assessed on the basis of PASS or FAIL. Economic Operators who fail to provide suitable practices, procedures or policies supporting Transport Scotland’s sustainable procurement duty, equality duty or fair work practice policies that satisfy these minimum standards will not be considered further in this procurement competition.</P>
               <P>Under ESPD, Question Ref. 4C.7 Economic Operators shall be required to insert suitable responses to Statements (h), (i) and (j) demonstrating that they have in place an appropriate quality, environmental and health and safety management systems. Economic Operators should specify their recognised accredited system or own non-accredited system, which shall ultimately be adopted upon conclusion of the Framework Agreement and in the event of a call-off contract. Subsequently, under ESPD Question Ref 4D.1 Economic Operators are required to confirm their compliance and be able to provide the appropriate certification.</P>
               <P>The responses to Statements (h), (i) and (j) shall each be assessed on the basis of PASS or FAIL. Economic Operators who obtain a FAIL in either of their responses shall not be considered further in this procurement competition.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Statement (a) — Within the last 3 years, have you provided audit services for management systems in respect of a civil engineering project with a construction cost of at least GBP 100 000 000  in 2018 prices exclusive of VAT? If yes, please provide details.</P>
               <P>Statement (b) – Provide information on no more than 4 “reference projects” which reflect similar works in terms of scope, size and/ or complexity to the Framework Agreement, predominantly carried out within the last 6 years detailing your role and the scope of the services performed.</P>
               <P>Statement (c) – communication and engagement (Weighting 30 %) –provide details of approach to working with and interfacing with key stakeholders involved. The response should provide evidence of the approaches to audit methodology, liaison, follow up and evidence of the development of mutual value and benefits achieved as a result. (max. 500 words).</P>
               <P>Statement (d) – Management and reporting(weighting 40 %) – Describe your approach, using the reference projects, of the development, installation and operation of management audit systems on civil engineering construction projects detailing the analysis and auditing methods used to identify problems and gaps including evidence of audit methodology and method for producing and monitoring corrective actions. (max. 500 words).</P>
               <P>Statement (e) – performance management and development (weighting 30 %) – Describe your approach, referring to the reference projects detailed above, to delivering improvements to managements systems and audit procedures to achieve cost and/or efficiency saving and Value For Money (VFM) for the client. Your response should include details of the methodology of how improvements are sought and identified; and evidence of how the development of improvements has achieved cost and/or efficiency savings. (max 500 words).</P>
               <P>Statement (f) – It is a requirement of the contract that the staff employed under the Framework Agreement shall have minimum levels of experience, education and professional qualifications. Economic Operators should provide no more than 5 CVs (Maximum length 1 single sided sheet of A4 for each CV) to demonstrate staff with the requisite capability to deliver the Framework Agreement. The minimum educational and professional qualifications include: Professional staff – chartered status (or equivalent) of a relevant professional organisation; Graduate staff – Degree (or equivalent) in a relevant subject from a relevant degree-awarding body; and Technical Staff – Appropriately qualified to contribute to the provision of services.</P>
               <P>Statement (g) – Fair work and equality practices - Describe your approach to equality and fair work practices for workers (including any agency or sub-contractor workers) engaged in the delivery of this contract. (max 500 words).</P>
               <P>Statement (h) – Quality Management System. This may be European Foundation Quality Model (EFQM) or equivalent; BS EN ISO 9001:2015 (Quality Management Systems); other accredited management system; or own non-accredited management system.</P>
               <P>Statement (i) - Health and Safety Management System. This may be BS OHSAS 18001:2007 (Occupational Health and Safety Management Systems) and associated standards; other accredited management system; or own non-accredited management system.</P>
               <P>Statement (j) – Environmental Management System. This may be BS EN ISO 14001:2015 (Environmental Management Systems); other accredited management systems; or own non-accredited management system.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>It is the Employer’s policy to measure the performance of each Consultant on a regular basis.</P>
               <P>In the event that the Consultant’s performance falls below a satisfactory level, the Consultant will be invited to determine a means of rectifying the situation. Repeated or continual service failures shall result in suspension or termination of the contract. Further details will be contained in the tender documents.</P>
               <P>It is a requirement of the contract that the staff employed under the Framework Agreement shall have minimum levels of experience, education and professional qualifications. These should be provided for under ESPD, Question Ref. 4C6.1 in response to Statement (f) above.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_RESTRICTED/>
            <FRAMEWORK>
               <SINGLE_OPERATOR/>
            </FRAMEWORK>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-03-21</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>2018-04-09</DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">3</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Transport Scotland will conduct the proposed procurement process for the Framework Agreement on behalf of the Scottish Ministers. In the event of the conclusion of the Framework Agreement, it is the intention that the Framework Agreement will be entered into between the Scottish Ministers and the most economically advantageous tenderers.</P>
               <P>Each selected Economic Operator shall be invited to submit a Tender on the same contract terms.</P>
               <P>The Framework Agreement will be based on an NEC4 Framework and professional services contract with bespoke amendments.</P>
               <P>These amendments may arise from three basic considerations:</P>
               <P>(i) amendments to reflect the Scottish Ministers' particular requirements and risk allocation for this agreement;</P>
               <P>(ii) amendments to reflect Scots law; and</P>
               <P>(iii) presentational changes to make the Framework Agreement more user friendly.</P>
               <P>Each Economic Operator shall submit four paper copies (one marked “Original” and three marked COPY 1, 2 or 3 as relevant) together with one USB Flash drive/ USB data storage device of the completed ESPD, in a sealed package to arrive by no later than 12 noon GMT on 21.3.2018 to the following addressee and address:</P>
               <P>Procurement support manager.</P>
               <P>Transport Scotland.</P>
               <P>Buchanan House.</P>
               <P>58 Port Dundas Road</P>
               <P>Glasgow.</P>
               <P>G4 0HF.</P>
               <P>United Kingdom.</P>
               <P>The Scottish Ministers shall not evaluate any submissions received past the specified deadline, unless the delay is caused by a situation out with the control of the Economic Operator, the determination of which shall be at the sole discretion of the Scottish Ministers. Compliance with achieving the specified deadline is the sole responsibility of the Economic Operator.</P>
               <P>Economic Operators which alter their composition after making a submission will be the subject of re-evaluation.</P>
               <P>Any request by Economic Operators for clarification of any part of the documentation shall be made to the following email address: Alasdair.Sim@transport.gov.scot. The deadline to submit questions relating to the submission via the Public Contracts Scotland portal is 12:00 GMT on 15.3.2018.</P>
               <P>Neither Transport Scotland nor the Scottish Ministers shall be responsible in any way to Economic Operators as a result of any delay or failure in answering any request for clarification or any decision not to answer a request for clarification (either in full or in part). Absence of a response from Transport Scotland or the Scottish Ministers shall not entitle Economic Operators to qualify their submission.</P>
               <P>The Scottish Ministers reserve the right not to conclude any Framework Agreement as a result of the procurement process initiated by this notice and to make whatever changes the Scottish Ministers deem appropriate to the content, process, timing and structure of the procurement process.</P>
               <P>Transport Scotland and the Scottish Ministers shall have no liability for any costs howsoever incurred by those participating in the competition.</P>
               <P>Economic Operators should be aware that all information submitted to the Scottish Minister may need to be disclosed and/or published by the Scottish Ministers in compliance with the Freedom of Information (Scotland) Act 2002.</P>
               <P>Note: To register your interest in this notice and obtain any additional information please visit the Public Contracts Scotland Web Site at http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/Search/Search_Switch.aspx?ID=531044.</P>
               <P>A sub-contract clause has been included in this contract. For more information see: http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/info/InfoCentre.aspx?ID=2363.</P>
               <P>Community benefits are included in this requirement. For more information see: http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/info/InfoCentre.aspx?ID=2361.</P>
               <P>A summary of the expected community benefits has been provided as follows:</P>
               <P>Further information will be in the tender documents.</P>
               <P>(SC Ref:531044).</P>
               <P>Download the ESPD document here: http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/ESPD/ESPD_Download.aspx?id=531044.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Transport Scotland</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Buchanan House, 58 Port Dundas Road</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Glasgow</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>G4 0HF</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1412727100</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>TS_Procurement_mailbox@gov.scot</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+44 1412727272</FAX>
               <URL>http://www.transport.gov.scot</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>An Economic Operator that suffers, or risks suffering, loss or damage attributed to a breach of duty under the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015 may bring proceedings in the Sheriff Court or the Court of Session.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-16</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
