<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="138823-2018" EDITION="2018063"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-137308-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180708</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>63</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180330</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 063-138823</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138823-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="EG"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="34927000">Toll equipment</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45200000">Works for complete or part construction and civil engineering work</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180326</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180708 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="3">Submission for one or more lots</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>BR505</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Egypten</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - Indkøb af 6 togsæt og 2 lokomotiver til Kairo-områdets metro nr. 2 — Shubra el Kheima til el Monib, inklusive reservedele og vedligeholdelse</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Ägypten</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - Beschaffung von 6 Zugsets und 2 Lokomotiven für die U-Bahn-Linie Nr. 2 von Kairo Shubra el Kheima nach el Monib einschließlich Ersatzteilen und Wartung</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Egypt</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Cairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Procurement of 6 Train Sets and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No. 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Egipto</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>El Cairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Adquisición de 6 ramas de tren y 2 locomotoras para el metro del Gran Cairo, línea N.º 2 Shubra el Kheima a el Monib, con piezas de recambio y mantenimiento</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Egypti</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - 6 junakokonaisuuden ja 2 veturin hankinta Suur-Kairon metrolinjaa nro 2 varten (Shubra el Kheima – el Monib), mukaan luettuina varaosat ja ylläpito</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Égypte</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Le Caire</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Approvisionnement de 6 rames de trains et de 2 locomotives pour la ligne de métro numéro 2 du grand Caire allant de Shimura el Kheima jusqu'à El Monib avec des pièces de rechange et de la maintenance</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Αίγυπτος</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Κάιρο</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - Σύναψη σύμβασης για την προμήθεια 6 συρμών και 2 μηχανών για τη γραμμή του μετρό αριθ. 2 της ευρύτερης περιοχής του Καΐρου, Shubra el Kheima - el Monib, με ανταλλακτικά και συντήρηση</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Egitto</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Il Cairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - Fornitura di 6 set di treni e 2 locomotive per la linea n. 2 della metro dell’area metropolitana del Cairo da Shubra el Kheima a El Monib inclusi i pezzi di ricambio e la manutenzione</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Egypte</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Caïro</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - Aanbesteding van 6 treinstellen en 2 locomotieven voor metrolijn nr. 2 in Groot-Caïro van Shubra el Kheima tot el Monib, evenals reserveonderdelen en onderhoud</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Egito</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Cairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Aprovisionamento de 6 composições ferroviárias e 2 locomotivas para a linha n.º 2 do metropolitano do Grande Cairo, de Shubra el Kheima a el Monib com peças de reposição e manutenção</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Egypten</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Upphandling av 6 tågset och 2 lokomotiv till tunnelbanelinjen Greater Cairo nr 2 från Shubra El Kheima till El Monib, inklusive reservdelar och underhåll</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Egypt</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Káhira</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Nákup 6 vlakových souprav a 2 lokomotiv pro linku metra ve Velké Káhiře č. 2 Shubra el Kheima do el Monib a náhradních dílů včetně údržby</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Egiptus</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - 6 rongikoosseisu ja 2 veduri hankimine Suur-Kairo metrooliinile nr 2 Shubra el Aheimast el Monibi koos varuosade ja hooldusega</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Egyiptom</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kairó</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - 6 vonatszerelvény és 2 mozdony beszerzése a nagy-kairói metró 2-es vonala számára Shubra el Kheima és El Mounib között pótalkatrészekkel és karbantartással</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Egiptas</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kairas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - 6 traukinio sąstatų ir 2 lokomotyvų, skirtų Didžiojo Kairo 2-ajai metro linijai Šubra al Cheima–el Monib, įskaitant atsargines dalis ir techninę priežiūrą, pirkimas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Ēģipte</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kaira</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - 6 vilciena sastāvu un 2 lokomotīvju iepirkums Kairas aglomerācijas metro līnijai Nr. 2 no Shubra el Kheima līdz el Monib kopā ar rezerves daļām un uzturēšanu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>l-Eġittu</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Il-Kajr</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - Il-ksib ta' 6 Settijiet tal-Ferrovija u 2 Lokomottivi għall-Greater Cairo Metro Line Nru. 2 minn Shubra el Kheima għal el Monib b'partijiet tal-bdil u manutenzjoni</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Egipt</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kair</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Nabycie 6 składów pociągów i 2 lokomotyw wraz z częściami zamiennymi i serwisem naprawczym na potrzeby linii metra nr 2 z Szubra al-Chajma do el Monib w Wielkim Kairze</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Egypt</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Káhira</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Obstaranie 6 vlakových súprav a 2 lokomotív s náhradnými dielmi a údržbou pre trasu č. 2 metra metropolitnej oblasti Veľká Káhira z Shubra El Kheima do El Monib</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Egipt</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Naročilo 6 vlakovnih kompozicij in 2 lokomotiv za linijo št. 2 (Shubra el Kheima–el Monib) podzemne železnice širšega območja Kaira, vključno z nadomestnimi deli in vzdrževanjem</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Éigipt, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Caireo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - 6 sheit traenach agus 2 inneall traenach a sholáthar do Mheitreo Chaireo Mhóir Líne 2 Shubra el Kheima go dtí el Monib le páirteanna spártha agus cothabháil</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Египет</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Кайро</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - Обществена поръчка за 6 комплекта влакове и 2 локомотива за Greater Cairo Metro Line № 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib с резервни части и поддръжка</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Egipt</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Cairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Achiziționarea a 6 seturi de tren și a 2 locomotive pentru linia de metrou nr. 2 Greater Cairo Shubra el Kheima către el Monib cu piese de schimb și întreținere</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Egipat</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kairo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Nabava 6 kompozicija i 2 lokomotive za liniju br. 2 podzemne željeznice u širem području Kaira, Shubra el Kheima do el Monib, s rezervnim dijelovima i održavanjem</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">National Authority for Tunnels</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - Indkøb af 6 togsæt og 2 lokomotiver til Kairo-områdets metro nr. 2 — Shubra el Kheima til el Monib, inklusive reservedele og vedligeholdelse (EG-Kairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - Beschaffung von 6 Zugsets und 2 Lokomotiven für die U-Bahn-Linie Nr. 2 von Kairo Shubra el Kheima nach el Monib einschließlich Ersatzteilen und Wartung (EG-Kairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Procurement of 6 Train Sets and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No. 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance (EG-Cairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Adquisición de 6 ramas de tren y 2 locomotoras para el metro del Gran Cairo, línea N.º 2 Shubra el Kheima a el Monib, con piezas de recambio y mantenimiento (EG-El Cairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - 6 junakokonaisuuden ja 2 veturin hankinta Suur-Kairon metrolinjaa nro 2 varten (Shubra el Kheima – el Monib), mukaan luettuina varaosat ja ylläpito (EG-Kairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Approvisionnement de 6 rames de trains et de 2 locomotives pour la ligne de métro numéro 2 du grand Caire allant de Shimura el Kheima jusqu'à El Monib avec des pièces de rechange et de la maintenance (EG-Le Caire)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - Σύναψη σύμβασης για την προμήθεια 6 συρμών και 2 μηχανών για τη γραμμή του μετρό αριθ. 2 της ευρύτερης περιοχής του Καΐρου, Shubra el Kheima - el Monib, με ανταλλακτικά και συντήρηση (EG-Κάιρο)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - Fornitura di 6 set di treni e 2 locomotive per la linea n. 2 della metro dell’area metropolitana del Cairo da Shubra el Kheima a El Monib inclusi i pezzi di ricambio e la manutenzione (EG-Il Cairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - Aanbesteding van 6 treinstellen en 2 locomotieven voor metrolijn nr. 2 in Groot-Caïro van Shubra el Kheima tot el Monib, evenals reserveonderdelen en onderhoud (EG-Caïro)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Aprovisionamento de 6 composições ferroviárias e 2 locomotivas para a linha n.º 2 do metropolitano do Grande Cairo, de Shubra el Kheima a el Monib com peças de reposição e manutenção (EG-Cairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Upphandling av 6 tågset och 2 lokomotiv till tunnelbanelinjen Greater Cairo nr 2 från Shubra El Kheima till El Monib, inklusive reservdelar och underhåll (EG-Kairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Nákup 6 vlakových souprav a 2 lokomotiv pro linku metra ve Velké Káhiře č. 2 Shubra el Kheima do el Monib a náhradních dílů včetně údržby (EG-Káhira)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - 6 rongikoosseisu ja 2 veduri hankimine Suur-Kairo metrooliinile nr 2 Shubra el Aheimast el Monibi koos varuosade ja hooldusega (EG-Kairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - 6 vonatszerelvény és 2 mozdony beszerzése a nagy-kairói metró 2-es vonala számára Shubra el Kheima és El Mounib között pótalkatrészekkel és karbantartással (EG-Kairó)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - 6 traukinio sąstatų ir 2 lokomotyvų, skirtų Didžiojo Kairo 2-ajai metro linijai Šubra al Cheima–el Monib, įskaitant atsargines dalis ir techninę priežiūrą, pirkimas (EG-Kairas)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - 6 vilciena sastāvu un 2 lokomotīvju iepirkums Kairas aglomerācijas metro līnijai Nr. 2 no Shubra el Kheima līdz el Monib kopā ar rezerves daļām un uzturēšanu (EG-Kaira)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - Il-ksib ta' 6 Settijiet tal-Ferrovija u 2 Lokomottivi għall-Greater Cairo Metro Line Nru. 2 minn Shubra el Kheima għal el Monib b'partijiet tal-bdil u manutenzjoni (EG-Il-Kajr)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Nabycie 6 składów pociągów i 2 lokomotyw wraz z częściami zamiennymi i serwisem naprawczym na potrzeby linii metra nr 2 z Szubra al-Chajma do el Monib w Wielkim Kairze (EG-Kair)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Obstaranie 6 vlakových súprav a 2 lokomotív s náhradnými dielmi a údržbou pre trasu č. 2 metra metropolitnej oblasti Veľká Káhira z Shubra El Kheima do El Monib (EG-Káhira)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Naročilo 6 vlakovnih kompozicij in 2 lokomotiv za linijo št. 2 (Shubra el Kheima–el Monib) podzemne železnice širšega območja Kaira, vključno z nadomestnimi deli in vzdrževanjem (EG-Kairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - 6 sheit traenach agus 2 inneall traenach a sholáthar do Mheitreo Chaireo Mhóir Líne 2 Shubra el Kheima go dtí el Monib le páirteanna spártha agus cothabháil (EG-Caireo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - Обществена поръчка за 6 комплекта влакове и 2 локомотива за Greater Cairo Metro Line № 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib с резервни части и поддръжка (EG-Кайро)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Achiziționarea a 6 seturi de tren și a 2 locomotive pentru linia de metrou nr. 2 Greater Cairo Shubra el Kheima către el Monib cu piese de schimb și întreținere (EG-Cairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Nabava 6 kompozicija i 2 lokomotive za liniju br. 2 podzemne željeznice u širem području Kaira, Shubra el Kheima do el Monib, s rezervnim dijelovima i održavanjem (EG-Kairo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9034-IFT-46875</P><P>Project name: Cairo Metro</P><P>Country: Egypt</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46875</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tender</P><P>Issue date: 26.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was ublished on the EBRD website, procurement notices 11.6.2015 on the EBRD web site, procurement opportunities (www.ebrd.com) nº 7932-GPN-46875 (project nº 46875) and updated on 22.3.2018. This invitation for tenders is published on EBRD web site (www.ebrd.com) and the website of the National Authority for Tunnels (NAT) (www.nat.org.eg).</P><P>The Government of Egypt represented by the Ministry of International Cooperation has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) towards the cost of Cairo Metro – Procurement of 6 Trains and 2 Locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line No.2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with Spare Parts and Maintenance. The executing agency for this project is the National Authority for Tunnels.</P><P>The national authority for tunnels now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following lots:</P><P>— Lot nº1 - Supply of 6 train sets with it’s on board equipment for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance, and</P><P>— Lot nº 2 - Supply of 2 locomotives for Greater Cairo Metro Line nº 2 Shubra el Kheima to el Monib with spare parts and maintenance.</P><P>Scope of work under the contracts to be funded by the proceeds of the EBRD loan and includes: manufacturing, delivery and commissioning of 6 train sets (8 coaches per train set) or 2 diesel locomotives, as applicable, supply of spare parts together with trains or locomotives for the first 10 years of their operation (including 2 years defects notification period) as well as training of the purchaser’s staff and provision of maintenance services during the defect notification period. Scope of work also includes provisions of maintenance services for the supplied trains or locomotives, as the case may be, within 8 years of their operation upon completion of the defects notification period. The contact for these services will be signed with and financed by the national authority for tunnels. More detailed information is provided in the tender document.</P><P>It is expected that the contracts with successful tenderers will be signed in IV quarter of 2018. Estimated delivery period for train sets is 25th – 27th months and for locomotives - 14th – 17th months after the contracts effective dates.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or both lots. Each lot must be priced separately.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of the loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>— Sound financial position of the tenderer and its long-term profitability. The average annual turnover over the last 5 years (2013 – 2017) shall not be less than:</P><P>Lot nº 1 EUR 120 000 000 (One hundred twenty million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 10 000 000 (Ten million)</P><P>— Access to or availability of liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means other than any contractual advance payments in the amount not less than:</P><P>(i) The following cash-flow requirement equivalent to:</P><P>Lot nº 1. EUR 25 000 000 (Twenty five million)</P><P>Lot nº 2 EUR 2 000 000 (Two million)</P><P>(ii) The overall cash flow requirements for this contract and other current commitments of the tenderer.</P><P>— For Lot nº1. Proven successful experience as supplier within the last 10 years in at least 3 contracts for supply of passenger trains that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed contract, each with a value of at least EUR 55 000 000 (Fifty-five million euro). For the above or other contracts executed during this period, a minimum experience in the following key activities is required:</P><P>(i) successful experience in supply of at least 40 metro cars per year within not less than two consecutive years over the last 5 years,</P><P>(ii) successful experience in supply of spare parts for the supplied trains in the amounts adequate for the period of at least 5 years.</P><P>— Lot nº 2. Proven successful experience as supplier in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years for supply of similar locomotives that has been successfully completed with a value of not less than 3 000 000 (Three million) EUR. The above or other contracts executed during this period shall include supply of at least 4 diesel locomotives and spare parts in the amounts adequate for at least 5 years of their operation,</P><P>— Manufacturers of trains shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of passenger trains at least over the last 10 years, including air conditioned /ventilated metro trains for the countries with similar climate, (ii) proven successful experience in supply minimum 200 metro cars in countries other than the country of manufacture within the last 8 years (offered metro cars shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) and (iii) manufacturing capacities to produce 6 trains (8 coaches per train) under the contract in question within the planned period of time,</P><P>— Manufacturers of diesel locomotives shall have: (i) proven successful experience in manufacturing of diesel locomotives at least over the last 10 years (offered locomotives shall be proven in service for a period of not less than 3 years, including in the countries with similar climate) (ii) manufacturing capacities to produce 2 locomotives under the contract in question within the planned period of time, and</P><P>— Other criteria named in the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 1 000 EUR or equivalent in Egyptian pounds at the exchange rate established by the Central Bank of Egypt for the date of payment. The payment shall be made in a form of Bank cheque to be provided at the address below, or by transfer to the following bank account of the Employer:</P><P>For the interested tenderers to purchase the complete set of tender documents, the payment should be a bank check for National Authority for Tunnels (NAT), or otherwise it could be by a bank transfer to national authority for tunnels</P><P>Account nº: 4/082/17918/8</P><P>Central Bank of Egypt.</P><P>Swift code: CBEGEGCXXXXX.</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security in the amount equivalent to:</P><P>Lot № 1 EUR 1 700 000 (One million seven hundred thousand)</P><P>Lot № 2 EUR 100 000 (One hundred thousand).</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before at 8.7.2018, 12:00 noon Cairo time which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policiesand-</P><P>Rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and also inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>National Authority for Tunnels</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Maj. Gen. Eng. Tarek G.E. Galal, Ramses Building, Ramses Square, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Cairo</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, P.O. Box 466, Egypt, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>202 (257-42968/69/70)</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Facsimile number: </BLK_BTX><FAX>202 (2574 2950)</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Electronic mail address: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>chairman@NAT.org.eg</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P/></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>