<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="138810-2018" EDITION="2018063"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-126163-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180413</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>63</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180330</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 063-138810</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:138810-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="MT"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="70332000">Non-residential property services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180319</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180409</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="Z">Not specified</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>AG302</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bekendtgørelse om ejendomsprospektering til imødekommelse af Det Europæiske Asylstøttekontors behov for kontorarealer</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bekanntmachung der Suche nach Immobilien zur Deckung des Bedarfs des Europäischen Unterstützungsbüros für Asylfragen an Büroflächen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Property prospecting notice to meet office space requirements of the European Asylum Support Office</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anuncio de prospección de inmuebles a fin de satisfacer las necesidades de la Oficina Europea de Apoyo al Asilo en cuanto a espacio de oficinas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ilmoitus kiinteistöjen kartoittamisesta Euroopan turvapaikka-asioiden tukiviraston toimistotilatarpeiden täyttämiseksi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Malte</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Avis de prospection d'immeubles pour combler les besoins du bureau européen d’appui en matière d’asile</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Μάλτα</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Προκήρυξη κτηματομεσιτικής έρευνας για την κάλυψη των αναγκών της Ευρωπαϊκής Υπηρεσίας Υποστήριξης για το Άσυλο</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Indagine immobiliare volta a sovvenire alle esigenze dell’Ufficio europeo di sostegno per l’asilo</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Aankondiging van een onderzoek van de vastgoedmarkt om te voldoen aan de behoeften van het Europees Ondersteuningsbureau voor asielzaken inzake kantoorruimte</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anúncio de prospeção de imóveis para suprir as necessidades em matéria de espaços de escritórios do Gabinete Europeu de Apoio em matéria de Asilo</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Meddelande om sökande efter fastigheter för att tillgodose behovet av kontorsytor för Europeiska stödkontoret för asylfrågor</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Oznámení o vyhledávání nemovitosti, která bude splňovat požadavky na kancelářské prostory Evropského podpůrného úřadu pro otázky azylu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Euroopa Varjupaigaküsimuste Tugiameti vajatava büroopinna leidmiseks kinnisvaraturu uurimise teade</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Málta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>A brüsszeli ingatlanpiac felmérésére irányuló felhívás az Európai Menekültügyi Támogatási Hivatal irodaterület-igényeinek kielégítése céljából</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Skelbimas apie nuosavybės rinkos tyrimą, siekiant atitikti Europos prieglobsčio paramos biuro reikalavimus</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Paziņojums par īpašuma izpēti, lai izpildītu ar Eiropas Patvēruma atbalsta biroja telpām saistītās prasības</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Avviż dwar tiftix għall-proprjetà biex jintlaħqu l-ħtiġijiet marbuta mal-ispazju għall-uffiċċji tal-Uffiċċju Ewropew ta' Appoġġ fil-qasam tal-Asil</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ogłoszenie o rozpoznaniu rynku nieruchomości w celu zaspokojenia potrzeb Europejskiego Urzędu Wsparcia w dziedzinie Azylu w zakresie powierzchni biurowych</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Oznámenie o vyhľadávaní nehnuteľností na splnenie požiadaviek na kancelárske priestory pre Európsky podporný úrad pre azyl</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Obvestilo o iskanju nepremičnin za izpolnitev zahtev glede pisarniškega prostora Evropskega azilnega podpornega urada</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Málta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Fógra um chuardach réadmhaoine chun freastal ar riachtanais spás don Oifig Tacaíochta Eorpach do Chúrsaí Tearmainn</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Малта</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Обявление за проучване за недвижими имоти, отговарящи на изискванията на Европейска служба за подкрепа в областта на убежището</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anunț de prospectare a pieței imobiliare pentru îndeplinirea cerințelor Biroului European de Sprijin pentru Azil</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Malta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Valletta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Obavijest o predviđanjima za nekretnine radi ispunjavanja zahtjeva za uredskim prostorijama Europskog potpornog ureda za azil</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Det Europæiske Asylstøttekontor</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäisches Unterstützungsbüro für Asylfragen (EASO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Asylum Support Office</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">Oficina Europea de Apoyo al Asilo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan turvapaikka-asioiden tukivirasto (EASO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Bureau européen d'appui en matière d'asile</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Ευρωπαϊκή Υπηρεσία Υποστήριξης για το Άσυλο</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Ufficio europeo di sostegno per l'asilo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europees Ondersteuningsbureau voor asielzaken</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">Gabinete Europeu de Apoio em Matéria de Asilo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska stödkontoret för asylfrågor</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropský podpůrný úřad pro otázky azylu</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Varjupaigaküsimuste Tugiamet</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Európai Menekültügyi Támogatási Hivatal (EASO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos prieglobsčio paramos biuras</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Patvēruma atbalsta birojs</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">L-Uffiċċju Ewropew ta' Appoġġ fil-qasam tal-Asil</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Europejski Urząd Wsparcia w dziedzinie Azylu</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európsky podporný úrad pre azyl</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropski azilni podporni urad</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">Oifig Eorpach um Thacaíocht don Chóras Tearmainn</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейска служба за подкрепа в областта на убежището</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Biroul European de Sprijin pentru Azil</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europski potporni ured za azil</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Bekendtgørelse om ejendomsprospektering til imødekommelse af Det Europæiske Asylstøttekontors behov for kontorarealer</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ansvarlige EU-agentur</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Det Europæiske Asylstøttekontor</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Søgningens genstand:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Det Europæiske Asylstøttekontor (EASO) leverer støtte til Cypern inden for rammerne af aftalen om en særlig støtteplan, indgået med regeringen for Cypern. Agenturet anvender inden for rammerne af denne plan sine medarbejdere samt eksperter og tolke til at levere støtte til specifikke foranstaltninger. EASO ønsker, med henblik på at sørge for tilstrækkelig arbejdsplads til sine medarbejdere, eksperter og tolke, at lease faciliteter/kontorarealer i overensstemmelse med nedenstående minimumskrav, samt tilhørende rengøringstjenester.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivelse af kontrakten og den anvendte procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Minimumskrav</P><P>EASO ønsker at leje kontorarealer i de lokaler, der huser den cypriotiske asyltjeneste, på adressen 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Cypern, eller i en tilstødende bygning.</P><P>Lokalerne skal være tilgængelige for EASO's medarbejdere, eksperter og tolke fra kl. 7:00-22:00, alle ugens dage.</P><P>Agenturet ønsker et omtrentligt etageareal over gadeplan til faciliteter/kontorer på mindst 250 m{^&gt;2&lt;^} og højst 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Faciliteterne/kontorarealerne skal være egnede til at rumme følgende:</P><P>— 7 kontorer/samtalerum — skal anvendes som samtalerum — med plads til 3-4 personer ad gangen,</P><P>— 1 kontor til tolke — skal anvendes som møde/ventelokale til tolke og derudover til tolke, som har behov for at arbejde i enrum (i forbindelse med oversættelser, telefonsamtaler med ansøgere osv.) — med plads til 6-8 personer ad gangen,</P><P>— 1 driftskontor — skal anvendes som kontor for EASO's koordinator og driftsassistent(er) og have tilstrækkelig plads til aflåselige arkivskabe med henblik på filstyring (filer om planlagte sager, filer, der venter på meningstilkendegivelser osv.) — med plads til 3 personer ad gangen og med et tilpas stort kontorareal til at kunne rumme både arkivskabe og arbejdsstationer,</P><P>— 1 køkken med passende faciliteter (køkkenbord, skabe, vask),</P><P>— 2 badeværelser/toiletter — 1 til personalet og 1 til ansøgerne,</P><P>— 1 lokale til flere forskellige formål — skal om nødvendigt også bruges til printerrum, mødelokale, venteområde for ansøgere i en pause eller efter behov — med plads til mindst 15-16 personer ad gangen,</P><P>— 1 lagerrum.</P><P>Kontorerne skal have tilstrækkelig plads til at kunne udstyres med arbejdsstationer, hvor det er påkrævet (møbler og IKT-udstyr).</P><P>Hvis faste sikkerhedsvagter ikke bliver til rådighed/tilbudt, har EASO lov til at have sine egne sikkerhedsvagter og installere de nødvendige sikkerhedskontrolsystemer. Hvis der desuden ikke er en receptionstjeneste til rådighed, har EASO lov til at have sit eget receptionspersonale og etablere passende faciliteter med de nødvendige møbler og former for udstyr. Til det formål skal kontrahenten gøre det nødvendige areal tilgængeligt på gade-/indgangsplan, ud over de påkrævede kontorarealer anført ovenfor.</P><P>Hele bygningen skal omfattes af et integreret branddetektionssystem (røg- og varmedetektorer, brandvægge). Der skal være en særlig nødudgang til evakuering af folk på hver etage.</P><P>Elforsyning og elstik, rindende varmt og koldt vand, opvarmnings-/afkølings-/aircondition-faciliteter, kloaktilslutninger skal alt sammen være etableret og forbundet med de kommunale/offentlige forsyningsværker.</P><P>I tilfælde af, at EASO har behov for at udføre strukturelle tilpasninger, skal kontrahenten stille den nødvendige baggrundsdokumentation til rådighed med henblik på at erhverve de nødvendige tilladelser til bygge- og anlægsarbejderne og eventuelt accept fra alle ejere af bygningen.</P><P>EASO har efter aftale med kontrahenten lov til for egen regning at foretage ikke-strukturelle tilpasninger i form af installation af elementer i eller småforbedringer af lokalerne.</P><P>Kontrahenten er ansvarlig for at tegne og opretholde en bygningsforsikring, som skal dække basale skader som brand, tyveri, oversvømmelse og lignende skader, i hele lejeperioden.</P><P>Kontrahenten er ansvarlig for at løse eventuelle problemer, der måtte opstå vedrørende alle tekniske tjenester, herunder elforsyning, vandforsyning, kloakering, bortskaffelse af affald og ventilation, samt for øjeblikkeligt at reparere/rette op på relaterede skader, der ikke kan tilskrives EASO.</P><P>Rengøringstjenester skal leveres som følger:</P><P>Opgaver, der skal udføres dagligt:</P><P>— tømning af papirkurve, eventuelt udskiftning af tilhørende plasticaffaldsposer og bortskaffelse af affald til de kommunale affaldscontainere,</P><P>— afstøvning samt aftørring med våd klud af alle eksponerede overflader,</P><P>— rengøring og fejning af gulve og vægfliser,</P><P>— rengøring, fejning og desinficering af badeværelser, herunder toiletter, håndvaske/vaskekummer, opfyldning af toiletpapir, papirservietter og andre nødvendige artikler,</P><P>— rengøring, fejning og desinficering af køkkenet, herunder køkkenvask og alle overflader, opfyldning af papirservietter og andre nødvendige artikler.</P><P>Opgaver, der skal udføres 1 gang om måneden:</P><P>— grundig rengøring og desinficering af toiletterne,</P><P>— afstøvning og rengøring af varme-/køleenheder,</P><P>— rengøring af alt glas på indvendige døre og/eller skillevægge.</P><P>Opgaver, der skal udføres 1 gang hver 3. (tredje) måned:</P><P>— rengøring af alle vinduer og alt glas på yderdøre (hvis relevant),</P><P>— rengøring af gardiner og persienner (hvis relevant).</P><P>3.2 Tidsfrister</P><P>Lokalerne skal være til rådighed i april 2018.</P><P>3.3 Procedure</P><P>Denne prospekteringsprocedure afsluttes med prækvalifikation af op til 3 ansøgere, hvis lokaler kan dække behovene. EASO kan opfordre den eller de prækvalificerede ansøgere til at indgå i forhandlinger i en efterfølgende særskilt fase af proceduren. De detaljerede tekniske specifikationer vil blive sendt til den eller de prækvalificerede ansøgere. Den eller de ansøgere, der opfordres til at deltage, vil blive informeret om det obligatoriske indhold i</P><P>forslagene, og om hvilke dokumenter der skal fremlægges. Hver prækvalificeret ansøger skal samtidig med indsendelse af sit forslag garantere følgende:</P><P>— at vedkommendes forslag vil forblive gyldigt indtil underskrivelse af kontrakt,</P><P>— at alle dokumenter vedrørende lokalerne vil blive fremlagt inden de frister, der er fastlagt af EASO.</P><P>Denne bekendtgørelse er ikke på nogen måde bindende for EASO, hvad angår kontrakttildelingsprocedurer. EASO forbeholder sig ret til, til hver en tid forud for underskrivelsen af en kontrakt, at indstille eller annullere denne procedure, uden at ansøgerne har krav på kompensation. Forud for eller i løbet af forhandlingsfasen underskriver EASO ingen eksklusivitetskontrakter eller lignende klausuler til fordel for en ansøger.</P><P>3.4 Kontrakttype</P><P>Lejeaftalens samlede maksimale varighed er 10 (ti) måneder, med mulighed for forlængelse 3 gange med yderligere 12 måneder pr. gang, til en samlet varighed på 3 år og 10 måneder.</P><P>Lejeaftalen skal dække lejeomkostningerne og de tilhørende rengøringstjenester. EASO er berettiget til at annullere lejeaftalen og de tilhørende rengøringstjenester med 1 måneds forudgående varsel.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Krav vedrørende anmodninger om deltagelse i proceduren med forhandling</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Indhold</P><P>Oplysningerne indeholdt i anmodningen om deltagelse skal indgives ved hjælp af følgende skemaer:</P><P>1) Identifikations- og erklæringsskema behørigt dateret og underskrevet (med angivelse af oplysninger om ansøgeren; oplysninger om ejeren — hvis der er tale om to forskellige personer; den fuldstændige adresse på lokalerne; bekræftelse på levering af de tjenesteydelser, der opfylder minimumskravene). Skemaet er tilgængeligt på: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/</P><P>Indkøb</P><P>2) Beskrivelse af overfladearealer; tegninger (gulve, facader, tværsnit) og planer, der omfatter en standardoversigtstegning (i tvivlstilfælde kan der blive anmodet om tegninger i skalaen 1:50 eller 1:100 eller 1:200);</P><P>4.2 Indsendelse af anmodninger om deltagelse i proceduren med forhandling</P><P>Anmodninger om deltagelse i udbudsproceduren med forhandling skal sammen med de påkrævede oplysninger i henhold til punkt 4.1 sendes pr. e-mail til contracts@easo.europa.eu senest 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vurdering af forslag i anden fase (procedure med forhandling):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Forslag modtaget fra de prækvalificerede ansøgere, der ikke er i overensstemmelse med og/eller ikke er beliggende inden for det søgte område og/eller ikke har det søgte etageareal, som anført i punkt 3 i denne bekendtgørelse, vil ikke blive taget i betragtning. Udbydere af udelukkede lokaler vil blive behørigt informeret.</P><P>Gyldige forslag vil blive vurderet på grundlag af kvalitets- og priskriterier efter følgende vægtninger:</P><P>— pris (40 %),</P><P>— kvalitet (60 %).</P><P>Buddets kvalitet (Q) vil blive bestemt på grundlag af følgende elementer (100 point):</P><P>— Fysisk nærhed i forhold til bygningen, der huser den cypriotiske asyltjeneste (jf. første afsnit i punkt 3.1): 55 point (mindstekrav: 35),</P><P>— Pladsfordeling i lokalerne — fordelingen af kontorareal, venteområde og muligheden for udvidelse af kontorerne bliver evalueret: 30 point (mindstekrav: 18),</P><P>— Sikkerheds- og beskyttelsesforanstaltninger i lokalerne (ud over minimumskravene anført i punkt II.) — tilstedeværelsen af fysiske sikkerhedstjenester (vagter), installerede ildslukkere, nødudgange og evakueringsplaner m.v. vil blive evalueret: 15 point (mindstekrav: 7).</P><P>Indplacering af tilbuddene baseres på det endelige resultat (F) i overensstemmelse med følgende formel:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontakter og yderligere oplysninger:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ansøgerne får besked om eventuel prækvalifikation, eller om det er besluttet ikke at opfordre dem til at deltage i proceduren med forhandling. Enhver kontakt mellem ansøgerne og EASO er forbudt, undtagen i tilfælde af et behov for præciseringer vedrørende bekendtgørelsen om ejendomsprospektering. Anmodninger om præcisering skal fremsættes skriftligt til contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Bekanntmachung der Suche nach Immobilien zur Deckung des Bedarfs des Europäischen Unterstützungsbüros für Asylfragen an Büroflächen</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Leiter der EU-Agentur</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäisches Unterstützungsbüro für Asylfragen (EASO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Gegenstand der Suche:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Das Europäische Unterstützungsbüro für Asylfragen (EASO) bietet Zypern Unterstützung im Rahmen eines Speziellen Unterstützungsplans (Special Support Plan), der mit der Regierung von Zypern unterzeichnet wurde, an. Im Rahmen dieses Plans setzt die Agentur ihr Personal sowie seine Experten und Dolmetscher ein, um Unterstützung für spezifische Maßnahmen bereitzustellen. Um den Arbeitsraum für das Personal, die Experten und Dolmetscher sicherzustellen, möchte die EASO Räumlichkeiten/Büroflächen sowie zusätzliche Reinigungsdienste gemäß den unten angegebenen Mindestanforderungen anmieten.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags und des anwendbaren Verfahrens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Mindestanforderungen</P><P>Die EASO möchte Büroflächen in den vom zyprischen Asyldienst (Cypriot Asylum Service) belegten Räumlichkeiten in 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Zypern oder einem benachbarten Gebäude anmieten.</P><P>Die Räumlichkeiten sollen für das Personal, die Experten und Dolmetscher der EASO an allen Wochentagen von 7:00 bis 22:00 zugänglich sein.</P><P>Die Agentur benötigt überirdische Räumlichkeiten/Büroflächen von mindestens 250 bis maximal 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Die Räumlichkeiten/Büroflächen sollten zur Unterbringung von Folgendem geeignet sein:</P><P>- 7 Büros/Räume für Gespräche - die als Gesprächsräume zu nutzen sind - zur gleichzeitigen Unterbringung von 3-4 Personen,</P><P>- 1 Büro für Dolmetscher - das als Besprechungs-/Warteraum für Dolmetscher und, falls erforderlich, auch von getrennt arbeitenden Dolmetschern zu nutzen ist (Übersetzungen, Anrufe von Bewerbern, usw.) - zur gleichzeitigen Unterbringung von 6-8 Personen,</P><P>- 1 operatives Büro - das als Büro für den EASO-Koordinator und Betriebsassistent(en) zu nutzen ist und ausreichend Bürofläche für Aktenregale zur Aktenverwaltung bietet (Akten von geplanten Fällen, Akten, die auf eine Stellungnahme warten, usw.) - zur gleichzeitigen Unterbringung von 3 Personen und zusätzlich zu den Arbeitsplätzen mit ausreichend Bürofläche für Aktenregale,</P><P>- 1 Küche mit den entsprechenden Einrichtungen (Theke, Schränke, Spüle),</P><P>- 2 Waschräume/Toiletten - 1 für Personal und 1 für Bewerber,</P><P>- 1 Mehrzweckraum - der auch als Druckerraum, Besprechungsraum, Wartebereich für Bewerber in der Pause oder wie erforderlich genutzt wird - um mindestens 15-16 Personen gleichzeitig unterzubringen,</P><P>- 1 Lagerraum.</P><P>Die Büros müssen ausreichend Fläche aufweisen, um, wo erforderlich, mit Arbeitsplätzen (Möbeln und IKT-Ausrüstung) ausgestattet zu werden.</P><P>Falls nicht ständig Sicherheitspersonal verfügbar ist/angeboten wird, ist es der EASO erlaubt, ihr eigenes Sicherheitspersonal einzusetzen und die erforderlichen Sicherheitskontrollsysteme anzubringen. Darüber hinaus ist es der EASO für den Fall, dass kein Empfangsdienst zur Verfügung steht, erlaubt, ihr eigenes Empfangspersonal und angemessene Räumlichkeiten mit den erforderlichen Möbeln und Ausrüstungen einzusetzen. Zu diesem Zweck soll der Auftragnehmer zusätzlich zu den oben aufgeführten Büroflächen die erforderlichen Flächen im Erdgeschoss/Eingang zugänglich machen.</P><P>Das gesamte Gebäude ist durch ein integriertes Rauchmeldesystem (Rauch- und Wärmemelder, Brandmeldezentralen) geschützt sein. Auf jeder Etage sind spezielle Notausgänge erforderlich.</P><P>Stromversorgung und -anschlüsse, Warm- und Kaltwasserversorgung, Heizung/Kühlung/Klimaanlage, Abwasseranschlüsse müssen vorhanden und an die Gemeinde-/öffentlichen Dienstleistungen angeschlossen sein.</P><P>Falls die EASO strukturelle Anpassungen vornehmen muss, müssen die erforderlichen unterstützenden Dokumente für den Erhalt der erforderlichen Baugenehmigungen und das Einverständnis aller Gebäudebesitzer, falls erforderlich, seitens des Auftragnehmers zugänglich gemacht werden.</P><P>Der EASO ist es in Übereinstimmung mit dem Auftragnehmer auf eigene Kosten erlaubt, nicht-strukturelle Anpassungen vorzunehmen, um Elemente anzubringen oder für kleine Verbesserung in den Räumlichkeiten zu sorgen.</P><P>Der Auftragnehmer ist für die Gebäudeversicherung zuständig, um grundsätzliche Schäden wie Brand, Diebstahl, Wasserüberlauf und ähnliche Schäden während der Laufzeit der Vermietung abzudecken.</P><P>Der Auftragnehmer ist für die Behebung von Problemen zuständig, die in Verbindung mit allen technischen Diensten einschließlich Stromversorgung, Abwasser, Abfallentsorgung und Belüftung entstehen, sowie für sofortige Reparaturen der damit verbundenen Schäden, die nicht der EASO zugeschrieben werden können.</P><P>Die Reinigungsdienste sind wie folgt bereitzustellen:</P><P>Aufgaben, die täglich auszuführen sind:</P><P>- Leeren der Abfalleimer,falls erforderlich Austausch von Kunststoffauskleidungen und Entsorgung von Abfällen in den Gemeindebehältern,</P><P>- Staubwischen und Feuchtwischen aller exponierten Oberflächen,</P><P>- Reinigen und Fegen aller Böden und Wandfliesen,</P><P>- Reinigen, Fegen und Desinfizieren aller Wachräume einschließlich Toiletten, Spülen/Waschbecken, Bereitstellen von Toilettenpapier, Papierhandtüchern und sonstigem erforderlichen Bedarf,</P><P>- Reinigen, Fegen und Desinfizieren der Küche einschließlich Spüle und aller Flächen, Anbringen von Papierhandtüchern und sonstigem erforderlichen Bedarf.</P><P>Aufgaben, die monatlich auszuführen sind:</P><P>- Gründliche Reinigung und Desinfektion der Toiletten,</P><P>- Staubwischen und Reinigung aller Heiz-/Kühlgeräte,</P><P>- Reinigung aller Glasflächen von Innentüren bzw. Trennwänden.</P><P>Aufgaben, die alle drei (3) Monate auszuführen sind:</P><P>- Reinigung aller Fenster und Glasflächen an Innentüren, falls vorhanden,</P><P>- Reinigung der Vorhänge und Jalousien, falls vorhanden.</P><P>3.2 Fristen</P><P>Die Räumlichkeiten sollten im April 2018 zur Verfügung stehen.</P><P>3.3 Verfahren</P><P>Dieses Suchverfahren endet mit der Vorauswahl von höchstens 3 Angeboten, deren Räumlichkeiten die Erfüllung der Bedürfnisse gewährleisten. Die EASO wird die vorausgewählte(n) Anbieter zur Aufnahme von Verhandlungen in einer weiteren, nachgelagerten Phase des vorliegenden Verfahrens einladen. Die detaillierten technischen Spezifikationen werden den vorausgewählten Anbieter(n) zugesandt. Der/die eingeladene(n) Anbieter wird über den erforderlichen Inhalt der bereitzustellenden</P><P>Angebote und Dokumente informiert. Mit der Einreichung des Angebots muss jeder Anbieter garantieren:</P><P>— das sein Angebots bis zur möglichen Vertragsunterzeichnung gültig ist,</P><P>— das alle Unterlagen zum Gebäude innerhalb der von der EASO festgesetzten Fristen eingereicht werden.</P><P>Die vorliegende Bekanntmachung begründet keinerlei Verpflichtung seitens der EASO im Hinblick auf die Auftragsvergabeverfahren. Die EASO behält sich bis zur Vertragsunterzeichnung das Recht vor, auf den vorliegenden Auftrag zu verzichten oder das Verfahren zu annullieren, ohne dass dadurch für die Anbieter ein Anspruch auf Entschädigung entsteht. Die EASO wird vor oder während der Verhandlungsphase weder einen Exklusivvertrag noch vergleichbare Klauseln zugunsten eines Anbieters unterzeichnen.</P><P>3.4 Art des Auftrags</P><P>Die maximale Gesamtlaufzeit des Mietvertrags entspricht zehn (10) Monaten mit der Möglichkeit der 3-maligen Verlängerung um eine zusätzliche Laufzeit von je 12 Monaten für eine Gesamtlaufzeit von 3 Jahren und 10 Monaten.</P><P>Der Mietvertrag deckt die Mietkosten und Nebenleistungen ab. Die EASO muss in der Lage sein, den Mietvertrag und die Nebenleistungen mit einer Kündigungsfrist von einem Monat zu kündigen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Anforderungen bezüglich des Antrags auf Teilnahme am Verhandlungsverfahren</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Inhalt</P><P>Die Informationen im Antrag auf Teilnahme müssen unter Verwendung der folgenden Formulare eingereicht werden:</P><P>1) Ordnungsgemäß datiertes und unterzeichnetes Kennblatt und Erklärung (einschließlich der Details des Anbieters; Details des Besitzers - falls anderslautend; vollständige Anschrift der Räumlichkeiten; Bestätigung, dass die geforderten Mindestdienstleistungen bereitgestellt werden). Das Formular ist verfügbar unter: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Beschreibung der Räumlichkeiten; Zeichnungen (Etagen, Fassaden, Schnittpläne) und Pläne, die ein Standard-Layout aufweisen (im Zweifelsfall können Zeichnungen im Maßstab 1/50 oder 1/100 oder 1/200 angefordert werden);</P><P>4.2 Einreichung von Anträgen auf Teilnahme am Verhandlungsverfahren</P><P>Anträge auf Teilname am Verhandlungsverfahren sind zusammen mit den in Punkt 4.1 geforderten Informationen bis zum 9.4.2018 per E-Mail an contracts@easo.europa.eu zu senden.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bewertung der Angebote in der zweiten Phase (Verhandlungsverfahren):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nicht konforme Vorschläge und/oder Vorschläge, die außerhalb des Suchbereichs liegen oder nicht der gewünschten Fläche entsprechen, der/die unter Ziffer 3 der vorliegenden Bekanntmachung genannt ist/sind, werden nicht berücksichtigt. Die ausgeschlossenen Anbieter von Gebäuden werden entsprechend in Kenntnis gesetzt.</P><P>Die zulässigen Vorschläge werden auf der Grundlage von Qualitäts- und Preiskriterien mit folgender Gewichtung geprüft:</P><P>— Preis (40 %),</P><P>— Qualität (60 %).</P><P>Die Qualität (Q) des Angebots wird auf der Grundlage folgender Punkte ermittelt (100 Punkte):</P><P>— Physische Nähe zum vom Cypriot Asylum Service belegten Gebäude (Ref. 3.1., erster Absatz): 55 Punkte (erforderliche Mindestanforderung: 35),</P><P>— Aufteilung der Flächen in den Räumlichkeiten - die Aufteilung der Bürofläche, des Wartebereichs und die Möglichkeit der Erweiterung der Büros wird bewertet: 30 Punkte (erforderliche Mindestanforderung: 18),</P><P>- Sicherheits- und Sicherungsmaßnahmen in den Räumlichkeiten (zusätzlich zu den unter Punkt II angegebenen Mindestanforderungen - die Anwesenheit von physischer Objektsicherung (Sicherheitskräfte), Anbringung von Feuerlöschern, Notausgängen und Evakuierungsplänen usw. wird bewertet: 15 Punkte (erforderliche Mindestanforderung: 7).</P><P>Ausgehend von einer nach der folgenden Formel berechneten Gesamtnote (F) wird eine Rangliste erstellt:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontaktaufnahme und weitere Informationen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Die Anbieter werden über ihre Vorauswahl oder dem Beschluss, nicht zu dem Verhandlungsverfahren eingeladen zu werden, informiert. Jeder Kontakt zwischen den Anbietern und der EASO ist verboten, es sei denn, eine Klarstellung bezüglich der Bekanntmachung der Immobiliensuche muss erteilt werden. Der Antrag für Klarstellung muss schriftlich an contracts@easo.europa.eu gerichtet werden.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Property prospecting notice to meet office space requirements of the European Asylum Support Office</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>EU Agency responsible</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Asylum Support Office</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, MALTA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Object of the search:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>European Asylum Support Office (EASO) provides support to Cyprus in the framework of a Special Support Plan signed with the Government of Cyprus. In the framework of the Plan, the Agency deploys its staff, as well as experts and interpreters, to provide support on specific measures. To ensure the working space for the staff, experts and interpreters, EASO is looking to lease facilities/office space in line with the minimum requirements below, and ancillary cleaning services.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract and the procedure to be applied</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Minimum requirements</P><P>EASO is looking to lease office space located in the premises occupied by the Cypriot Asylum Service at 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Cyprus or in an adjacent building.</P><P>The premises should be accessible to EASO staff, experts and interpreters from 7:00 until 22:00 on all days of the week.</P><P>The Agency requires an estimated above-ground facilities/office space of minimum 250 to maximum 320 m2.</P><P>The facilities/office space should be suitable to accommodate:</P><P>— 7 offices/interview rooms — to be used as interview rooms - to host 3-4 persons at a time,</P><P>— 1 office for interpreters — to be used as Meeting/waiting room for interpreters and also by interpreters to work separately, if needed (translations, calls with applicants, etc.) — to host 6-8 persons at a time,</P><P>— 1 operations office — to be used as an office for the EASO Coordinator and Operations Assistant(s) and have sufficient office space for file lockers for file management (files of scheduled cases, files waiting for opinions, etc.) — to host 3 persons at a time and provide sufficient office space for file lockers, in addition to the working stations,</P><P>— 1 kitchen with appropriate facilities (counter, cupboards, sink),</P><P>— 2 rest rooms/toilets — 1 for staff and 1 for applicants,</P><P>— 1 multipurpose room — to be used also as printer room, meeting room, waiting area for applicants during break or as necessary — to host minimum 15-16 persons at a time,</P><P>— 1 storage room.</P><P>The offices must have sufficient space to be equipped with workstations, where required (furniture and ICT equipment).</P><P>If permanent security guard(s) are not available/offered, EASO shall be permitted to have its own security guards and install the required security control systems. In addition, if a reception service is not available, EASO shall be permitted to have its own reception staff and to set up adequate facilities with the required furniture and equipment. To that end, the necessary space at ground/entrance level shall be made available by the Contractor, in addition to the required office space listed above.</P><P>The entire building shall be covered by an integrated fire detection system (smoke and heat detectors, fire panels). Dedicated evacuation exit on each floor is required.</P><P>Electrical supply and points, hot and cold water supply, heating/cooling/air conditioning, sewage connections shall be in place and connected to municipal/public services.</P><P>In the event that EASO needs to perform structural adaptations, the necessary supporting documents to acquire the required permits for construction works, and agreement of all building owners, when required, shall be made available by the Contractor.</P><P>EASO shall, in agreement with the Contractor, be allowed to make non-structural adaptations, at its own costs, in order to install items or make small improvements to the premises.</P><P>The Contractor shall be responsible for the buildings insurance, to cover basic damages such as fire, theft, water overflow and similar damages, throughout the duration of the lease.</P><P>The Contractor shall be responsible for resolving any problems that might come up in relation to all technical services, including power supply, water supply, sewage, waste disposal and ventilation, as well as for the immediate repair of related damages not attributable to EASO.</P><P>Cleaning services shall be provided as follows:</P><P>Tasks to be executed on a daily basis:</P><P>— Emptying of waste baskets, replacement of plastic liners, if needed, and removal of waste to the communal containers,</P><P>— Dusting and wet-wiping of all exposed surfaces,</P><P>— Cleaning and sweeping of floors and wall tiles,</P><P>— Cleaning, sweeping and disinfection of the rest rooms, including toilets, sinks/wash-basins, placing toilet paper, paper towels and other needed supplies,</P><P>— Cleaning, sweeping and disinfection of the kitchen, including sink and all surfaces, placing paper towels and other needed supplies.</P><P>Tasks to be executed once per month:</P><P>— Deep cleaning and disinfection of the toilets,</P><P>— Dusting and cleaning of heating/cooling units,</P><P>— Cleaning of all glass on internal doors and/or partitions.</P><P>Tasks to be executed once every three (3) months:</P><P>— Cleaning of all windows and glass on external doors, if any,</P><P>— Cleaning of curtains and blinds, if any.</P><P>3.2 Deadlines</P><P>The premises shall be available in April 2018.</P><P>3.3 Procedure</P><P>This prospecting procedure will be concluded with preselection of up to 3 applicants whose premises enable requirements to be met. EASO will invite the preselected applicant(s) to enter into negotiations in a subsequent phase distinct from this procedure. The detailed technical specifications will be sent to the preselected applicant(s). The invited applicant(s) will be informed of the required content of the</P><P>Proposals and the documents to be furnished. With the submission of the proposal, each preselected applicant shall guarantee:</P><P>— that his proposal shall remain valid until any contract is signed,</P><P>— that any document concerning the premises shall be provided within the deadlines stipulated by EASO.</P><P>This notice is not in any way binding on EASO as regards contract award procedures. EASO reserves the right, at any time prior to the signature of the contract, to renounce or cancel this procedure, without applicants being entitled to claim any compensation. Prior to, or during, the negotiation stage, EASO will not sign any exclusivity contracts or similar clauses in favour of an applicant.</P><P>3.4 Type of contract</P><P>The total maximum duration of the lease agreement will be ten (10) months, with the possibility to extend 3 times for an additional duration of 12 months/each for a total duration of 3 years 10 months.</P><P>The lease agreement shall cover the lease costs and the ancillary services. EASO shall be able to cancel the lease agreement and ancillary services with one month’s prior notice.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requirements relating to requests to participate in the negotiated procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Content</P><P>The information contained in the request to participate must be submitted using the following forms:</P><P>1) Identification and declaration form duly dated and signed (indicating the details of the applicant; details of the owner – if different; full address of the premises; confirmation that the minimum required services shall be provided). The form is available on: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/</P><P>Procurement</P><P>2) Description of the surface areas; drawings (floors, facades, cross-sections) and plans showing a standard layout (in case of doubt 1/50 or 1/100 or 1/200 scale drawings may be requested);</P><P>4.2 Submission of requests to participate in the negotiated procedure</P><P>Requests to participate, in the negotiated procedure, accompanied with the information required under point 4.1, must be sent by e-mail to contracts@easo.europa.eu by 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Assessment of proposals in the second phase (negotiated procedure):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals received from the preselected applicant(s) that are not compliant and/or do not observe the area of research and/or the surface area sought as mentioned in point 3 of this notice, will be discarded. Applicants of premises excluded will be duly informed.</P><P>Eligible proposals will be analysed on the basis of quality and price criteria in accordance with the following weightings:</P><P>— price (40 %),</P><P>— quality (60 %).</P><P>The tender's quality (Q) will be determined on the basis of the following elements (100 points):</P><P>— Physical proximity to the building occupied by the Cypriot Asylum Service (ref. 3.1., first paragraph): 55 points (minimum required: 35),</P><P>— Distribution of space in the premises - distribution of office space, waiting area and possibility of expansion of the offices will be evaluated: 30 points (minimum required: 18),</P><P>— Security and safety measures in the premises (in addition to the minimum requirements indicated in point II.) – the presence of physical security (guards), instalment of fire extinguishers, emergency exits and evacuation plans, etc. in place will be evaluated: 15 points (minimum required: 7).</P><P>The classification of the offers will be based on a final score (F) in accordance with the following formula:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contacts and additional information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Applicants will be informed of their preselection or the decision not to be invited for the negotiated procedure. Any contact between applicants and EASO is prohibited, except where clarification would need to be given regarding the property prospecting notice. The request for clarification shall be made in writing to contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Anuncio de prospección de inmuebles a fin de satisfacer las necesidades de la Oficina Europea de Apoyo al Asilo en cuanto a espacio de oficinas</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Agencia responsable de la UE</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Oficina Europea de Apoyo al Asilo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC bloque A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Objeto de la investigación:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>La Oficina Europea de Apoyo al Asilo (EASO) brinda apoyo a Chipre en el marco de un Plan de Apoyo Especial firmado con el Gobierno de Chipre. En el marco del Plan, la Agencia asigna a su personal, así como a expertos e intérpretes, para dar soporte en la aplicación de medidas específicas. Para garantizar el espacio de trabajo para el personal, los expertos y los intérpretes, EASO requiere alquilar instalaciones/espacios de oficinas de conformidad con los requisitos mínimos que se detallan a continuación, así como servicios auxiliares de limpieza.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción del contrato y procedimiento aplicable</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Requisitos mínimos</P><P>EASO requiere alquilar oficinas ubicadas en los locales ocupados por el Servicio de Asilo de Chipre, situado en 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Chipre, o en un edificio adyacente.</P><P>Las instalaciones deben permitir la entrada al personal, los expertos e intérpretes de la EASO desde las 7:00 horas hasta las 22:00 horas todos los días de la semana.</P><P>La Agencia requiere un espacio de oficinas/instalaciones sobre el suelo estimado de entre 250 y 320 m².</P><P>Las instalaciones/espacio de oficinas deben ser adecuadas para acoger:</P><P>— 7 oficinas/salas de entrevistas, para usarse como salas de entrevistas, con espacio para acoger de 3 a 4 personas simultáneamente,</P><P>— 1 oficina para intérpretes, para ser utilizada como sala de reuniones/sala de espera para intérpretes, así como para sala de trabajo en solitario para intérpretes, si se requiere (traducciones, llamadas con solicitantes, etc.) y que permita acoger de 6 a 8 personas simultáneamente,</P><P>— 1 oficina de operaciones, para ser utilizada como oficina para el Coordinador de EASO y asistente(s) de operaciones y que, simultáneamente, sirva para albergar armarios para la gestión de archivos (archivos de casos programados, archivos que esperan opiniones, etc.) y que permita acoger a 3 personas a la vez y sobre espacio suficiente para los armarios de archivos y las mesas de trabajo,</P><P>— 1 cocina con instalaciones apropiadas (encimera, armarios, fregadero),</P><P>— 2 salas de descanso/aseos, 1 para el personal y 1 para los solicitantes,</P><P>— 1 sala polivalente, para ser utilizada también como sala de impresoras, sala de reuniones, área de espera para los solicitantes durante los descansos o cuando se requiera y que permita acoger a un mínimo de 15-16 personas a la vez,</P><P>— 1 sala de almacenamiento.</P><P>Las oficinas deben tener espacio suficiente para poder albergar mesas de trabajo, en los casos en los que se requiera (muebles y equipos de TIC).</P><P>Si los guardias de seguridad permanentes no se encuentran disponibles, se le permitirá a la EASO tener sus propios guardias de seguridad e instalar los sistemas de control de seguridad requeridos. Además, si no se puede disponer de un servicio de recepción, se le permitirá a la EASO tener su propio personal de recepción y establecer las instalaciones adecuadas con el mobiliario y el equipo necesarios. Con ese fin, el contratista deberá poner a disposición el espacio que se requiera a nivel de calle, además del espacio de oficina mencionado anteriormente.</P><P>Todo el edificio quedará cubierto por un sistema integrado de detección de incendios (detectores de humo y calor y paneles contra incendios). Se requiere una salida de evacuación especial en cada piso.</P><P>Además, deberá contar con una correcta instalación de suministro eléctrico con sus correspondientes puntos de consumo, sistemas de agua fría y caliente, calefacción/refrigeración/aire acondicionado y de aguas residuales conectados a los servicios municipales/públicos.</P><P>En caso de que la EASO necesite realizar adaptaciones estructurales, el contratista deberá poner a disposición los documentos necesarios para adquirir los permisos requeridos para las obras de construcción y, en los casos en los que sea necesario, se deberá contar con el acuerdo de todos los propietarios del edificio.</P><P>La EASO, de acuerdo con el contratista, podrá realizar adaptaciones no estructurales, por sus propios medios, para instalar elementos o realizar pequeñas mejoras en las instalaciones.</P><P>El contratista deberá hacerse responsable del seguro de los edificios, a fin de cubrir daños básicos como incendio, robo, inundaciones y otros accidentes similares, a lo largo de la duración del alquiler.</P><P>El contratista deberá hacerse responsable de resolver cualquier problema que surja en relación con cualquiera de los servicios técnicos, como el suministro eléctrico, sistemas de agua, de eliminación de residuos y de ventilación, así como de la reparación inmediata de los daños relacionados no atribuibles a la EASO.</P><P>Los servicios de limpieza se proporcionarán de la siguiente manera:</P><P>Tareas para realizar diariamente:</P><P>— Vaciado de cubos de basura, sustitución de bolsas de plástico, si se requiere, y eliminación de residuos en los contenedores comunes,</P><P>— Limpieza y desempolvado de todas las superficies expuestas,</P><P>— Limpieza y barrido de suelos y azulejos de la pared,</P><P>— Limpieza, barrido y desinfección de los baños, incluidos inodoros, lavabos y pilas, restitución de papel higiénico, toallas de papel y otros suministros necesarios,</P><P>— Limpieza, barrido y desinfección de la cocina, incluido el fregadero y todas las superficies, restitución de toallas de papel y otros suministros necesarios.</P><P>Tareas para realizar una vez al mes:</P><P>— Limpieza profunda y desinfección de los baños,</P><P>— Polvo y limpieza de equipos de calefacción/refrigeración,</P><P>— Limpieza de los cristales de las puertas y/o particiones internas.</P><P>Tareas para realizar una vez cada tres (3) meses:</P><P>— Limpieza de todas las ventanas y cristales en puertas externas, de haberlas,</P><P>— Limpieza de cortinas y persianas, de haberlas.</P><P>3.2 Plazos</P><P>Las instalaciones estarán disponibles en abril de 2018.</P><P>3.3 Procedimiento</P><P>Este procedimiento de prospección concluirá con la preselección de hasta 3 solicitantes cuyas instalaciones permitan satisfacer las necesidades. La EASO podrá invitar al (a los) licitador(es) que haya(n) sido preseleccionado(s) a iniciar negociaciones en una fase posterior distinta del presente procedimiento. Se enviarán las especificaciones técnicas detalladas a los solicitantes preseleccionados. El (los) solicitante(s) invitado(s) serán informados del contenido requerido de</P><P>las propuestas y documentos a entregar. Con la presentación de la propuesta cada solicitante preseleccionado deberá garantizar:</P><P>— que su propuesta será válida hasta la eventual firma del contrato,</P><P>— la puesta a disposición de cualquier documento relacionado con las instalaciones en los plazos que indique la EASO.</P><P>La presente publicación no constituye, de forma alguna, un compromiso para la EASO en el ámbito de los procedimientos de adjudicación de contratos. La EASO se reserva el derecho, hasta la firma de un contrato, de renunciar al contrato o de anular el presente procedimiento sin que los candidatos puedan exigir indemnización alguna. La EASO no firmará, antes o durante la fase de negociación, ningún contrato de exclusividad ni ninguna cláusula similar en favor de un candidato.</P><P>3.4 Tipo de contrato</P><P>La duración máxima total del contrato de alquiler será de diez (10) meses, con la posibilidad de extenderse 3 veces con una duración adicional de 12 meses cada uno, por una duración total de 3 años y 10 meses.</P><P>El contrato de alquiler cubrirá los costes del alquiler y los servicios auxiliares. La EASO podrá cancelar el contrato de alquiler y los servicios auxiliares con un preaviso de un mes.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requisitos relacionados con las solicitudes de participación en el procedimiento negociado</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Contenido</P><P>La información contenida en la solicitud de participación debe enviarse mediante los siguientes formularios:</P><P>1) Formulario de identificación y declaración debidamente fechado y firmado (indicando los detalles del solicitante, detalles del propietario, si fuera diferente, dirección completa del local y confirmación de que se proporcionarán los servicios mínimos requeridos). El formulario se encuentra disponible en: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Descripción de las áreas de superficie; dibujos (suelos, fachadas, secciones transversales) y planos que muestren una disposición estándar (en caso de duda pueden solicitarse planos a escala 1/50, 1/100 o 1/200);</P><P>4.2 Presentación de solicitudes de participación en el procedimiento negociado</P><P>Las solicitudes de participación en el procedimiento negociado, junto con la información requerida en el punto 4.1, deberán enviarse por correo electrónico a contracts@easo.europa.eu antes del 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Evaluación de propuestas en la segunda fase (procedimiento negociado):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Las propuestas que se reciban de los solicitantes preseleccionados y que no sean conformes o que no respeten el perímetro de búsqueda o la superficie deseada, tal y como se indica en el punto 3 del presente anuncio, serán descartadas. Se informará debidamente a los solicitantes de instalaciones que hayan resultado excluidos.</P><P>Las propuestas admisibles se analizarán sobre la base de los criterios de calidad y de precio, de acuerdo con la ponderación siguiente:</P><P>— precio (40 %),</P><P>— calidad (60 %).</P><P>La calidad (Q) de la oferta se establecerá a partir de los elementos siguientes (100 puntos):</P><P>— La proximidad física al edificio ocupado por el Servicio de Asilo de Chipre (ref. 3.1., primer párrafo): 55 puntos (mínimo requerido: 35),</P><P>— Distribución del espacio en el local, se evaluará la distribución del espacio de oficinas, el área de espera y la posibilidad de ampliación de las oficinas: 30 puntos (mínimo requerido: 18),</P><P>— Medidas de seguridad en los locales (además de los requisitos mínimos indicados en el punto II.), se evaluará la presencia de seguridad física (guardias), instalación de extintores de incendios, salidas de emergencia y planes de evacuación, etc.: 15 puntos (mínimo requerido: 7).</P><P>La clasificación de las ofertas se basará en un puntaje final (F) de acuerdo con la siguiente fórmula:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contactos e información complementaria:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Se informará a los solicitantes de su preselección o de la decisión mediante la cual no se les invita al procedimiento negociado. Se prohíbe cualquier contacto entre los solicitantes y la EASO, excepto en los casos en los que se requieran aclaraciones en relación con el anuncio de prospección de inmuebles. La solicitud de aclaración se realizará por escrito a contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Ilmoitus kiinteistöjen kartoittamisesta Euroopan turvapaikka-asioiden tukiviraston toimistotilatarpeiden täyttämiseksi</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vastaava EU:n virasto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan turvapaikka-asioiden tukivirasto (EASO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kartoituksen kohde:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan turvapaikka-asioiden tukivirasto (EASO) toimittaa Kyprokselle tukea Kyproksen hallituksen kanssa allekirjoitetun erityisen tukisuunnitelman puitteissa. Suunnitelman puitteissa virasto sijoittaa henkilöstöään sekä asiantuntijoita ja tulkkeja tukemaan erityistoimenpiteitä. Henkilöstön, asiantuntijoiden ja tulkkien työtilan varmistamiseksi EASO pyrkii vuokraamaan tiloja/ toimistotiloja alla olevien vähimmäisvaatimusten mukaisesti ja täydentäviä siivouspalveluita.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuksen kuvaus ja sovellettava menettely</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1. Vähimmäisvaatimukset</P><P>EASO aikoo vuokrata toimistotilan, joka sijaitsee Kyproksen turvapaikkapalvelun tiloissa osoitteessa 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nikosia, Kypros tai viereisessä rakennuksessa.</P><P>EASOn henkilökunnalla, asiantuntijoilla ja tulkeilla on oltava pääsy rakennukseen kaikkina viikonpäivinä klo 7:00–22:00.</P><P>Virasto tarvitsee maanpinnan yläpuolella olevat tilat/toimistotilat, joiden pinta-ala on vähintään 250 neliömetriä ja enintään 320 neliömetriä.</P><P>Tiloihin/toimistotiloihin tulisi soveltua seuraaviksi käyttökohteiksi:</P><P>— 7 toimistoa/haastatteluhuonetta, joita käytetään haastatteluhuoneena, 3–4 henkilöä kerrallaan,</P><P>— 1 toimisto tulkeille, jota käytetään tulkkien kokous-/odotushuoneena sekä tulkkaustila, jossa tulkit voivat työskennellä tarvittaessa erikseen (käännökset, puhelut hakijoiden kanssa jne.), 6–8 henkilöä kerrallaan,</P><P>— 1 työhuone, jota käytetään EASOn koordinaattorin ja toiminta-avustajien toimistona, ja siinä on oltava riittävästi toimistotilaa arkistokaapeille asiakirjojen hallintaa varten (lähiaikoina esille tulevat asiakirjat, lausuntoja odottavat asiakirjat jne.), 3 henkilöä kerrallaan ja riittävästi toimistotilaa arkistokaapeille työpisteiden lisäksi,</P><P>— 1 keittiö tarvittavilla mukavuuksilla (työtaso, kaapit, tiskiallas),</P><P>— 2 saniteettitilat/wc, 1 henkilökunnalle ja 1 hakijoille,</P><P>— 1 monikäyttöhuone, jota käytetään tulostushuoneena, kokoushuoneena, hakijoiden odotusalueena tauon aikana tai tarpeen mukaan, vähintään 15–16 henkilöä kerrallaan,</P><P>— 1 varastotila.</P><P>Toimistoissa on oltava riittävästi tilaa työpisteille tarvittaessa (huonekalut ja tieto- ja viestintätekniset laitteet).</P><P>Jos pysyvää vartijaa ei ole saatavilla/tarjolla, EASOlla on oikeus tuoda omat vartijansa ja asentaa tarvittavat turvatarkastusjärjestelmät. Lisäksi, jos vastaanottopalvelua ei ole saatavilla, EASOlla on oikeus tuoda oma vastaanottohenkilöstö ja perustaa riittävät tilat tarvittavine kalusteineen ja laitteineen. Sopimusosapuolen on annettava tarvittava tila vastaanottoa varten pohjakerroksesta/ sisäänkäyntikerroksesta edellä mainitun toimistotilan lisäksi.</P><P>Koko rakennuksessa on oltava integroitu palonilmaisinjärjestelmä (savu- ja lämpöilmaisimet, palonvalvontapaneelit). Jokaisessa kerroksessa tulee olla hätäuloskäynti.</P><P>Sähkönsyöttö ja pistorasiat, kuuma ja kylmä vesi, lämmitys/jäähdytys/ilmastointi, jätevesiliitännät on asennettava ja kytkettävä kunnallisiin tai julkisiin palveluihin.</P><P>Mikäli EASOn on tehtävä rakenteellisia muutoksia, sopimusosapuoli toimittaa tarvittavat lisäasiakirjat vaadittavien rakennuslupien saamiseksi ja hankkii kaikkien rakennuksen omistajien suostumuksen tarvittaessa.</P><P>EASOn on voitava sopimusosapuolen luvalla tehdä muita kuin rakenteellisia muutoksia omalla kustannuksellaan asentaakseen laitteita tai tehdäkseen pieniä parannuksia toimitiloihin.</P><P>Sopimusosapuoli on vastuussa rakennusten vakuutuksesta, joka kattaa perusvahingot, kuten tulipalon, varkauden, vesivahingon ja muut samanlaiset vahingot koko vuokrasopimuksen kestoajan.</P><P>Sopimusosapuoli on vastuussa kaikkien mahdollisten ongelmien ratkaisemisesta, joita voi esiintyä esim. kaikkiin teknisiin palveluihin liittyen, mukaan lukien sähkön saanti, vesihuolto, viemäröinti, jätteiden hävitys ja ilmanvaihto. Lisäksi sopimusosapuoli on vastuussa kaikkien vahinkojen välittömästä korjaamisesta, jotka eivät ole EASOn aiheuttamia.</P><P>Siivouspalvelut toimitetaan seuraavasti:</P><P>Tehtävät, jotka suoritetaan päivittäin:</P><P>— roskakorien tyhjentäminen, tarvittaessa muovisten roskapussien vaihtaminen uusiin ja jätteiden poistaminen yhteissäiliöihin,</P><P>— kaikkien vapaiden pintojen pyyhkiminen pölyistä ja kostea pyyhintä,</P><P>— lattioiden lakaisu ja seinälaattojen puhdistaminen,</P><P>— saniteettitilojen irtoroskien poistaminen, puhdistaminen ja desinfiointi mukaan lukien wc-tilat, lavuaari/pesuallas, wc-paperin, paperipyyhkeiden ja muiden tarvikkeiden paikoilleen asettaminen,</P><P>— keittiön lakaisu, puhdistaminen ja desinfiointi mukaan lukien pesuallas ja kaikki pinnat, paperipyyhkeiden ja muiden tarvikkeiden paikoilleen asettaminen.</P><P>Tehtävät, jotka suoritetaan kuukausittain:</P><P>— wc-tilojen perusteellinen puhdistus ja desinfiointi,</P><P>— lämmitys-/jäähdytysyksiköiden pölynpoisto ja puhdistus,</P><P>— sisäovien ja/tai seinäkkeiden/tilanjakajien kaikkien lasipintojen puhdistus.</P><P>Tehtävät, jotka suoritetaan kerran kolmessa (3) kuukaudessa:</P><P>— kaikkien ikkunoiden ja ulko-ovien mahdollisten lasien puhdistus,</P><P>— mahdollisten verhojen ja pimennysverhojen puhdistus.</P><P>3.2 Määräaika</P><P>Toimitilojen on oltava käytettävissä huhtikuussa 2018.</P><P>3.3 Menettely</P><P>Tämän kartoitusmenettelyn lopuksi suoritetaan 3 sellaisen hakijan esivalinta, jonka toimitilojen avulla voidaan täyttää tarpeet. EASO voi kutsua esivalitut hakijat neuvotteluihin seuraavassa tästä menettelystä erillisessä vaiheessa. Yksityiskohtaiset tekniset eritelmät lähetetään esivalituille hakijoille. Esivalituille hakijoille ilmoitetaan ehdotusten tarvittavasta sisällöstä ja toimitettavista asiakirjoista.</P><P> Jättäessään ehdotuksen jokaisen hakijan tulee taata seuraavaa:</P><P>— ehdotus on voimassa mahdolliseen sopimusten allekirjoittamiseen saakka,</P><P>— kaikki toimitiloja koskevat asiakirjat toimitetaan EASOn asettamiin määräaikoihin mennessä.</P><P>Tämä ilmoitus ei sido yhteistä EASOa mitenkään sopimuksentekomenettelyjen suhteen. EASO varaa oikeuden keskeyttää tai peruuttaa tämä menettely koska tahansa ennen sopimuksen allekirjoittamista ilman, että hakijat ovat oikeutettuja mihinkään korvauksiin. Ennen neuvotteluvaihetta tai sen aikana EASO ei tee minkäänlaista yksinoikeussopimusta tai sovi mitään vastaavaa ehtoa yhdenkään hakijan kanssa.</P><P>3.4. Sopimuslaji</P><P>Vuokrasopimuksen kokonaiskestoaika on enintään 10 kuukautta, ja se voidaan uusia 3 kertaa 12 kuukaudeksi kerrallaan, joista kunkin enimmäiskesto on 3 vuotta 10 kuukautta.</P><P>Vuokrasopimuksen on katettava vuokrakustannukset ja lisäpalvelut. EASOn on voitava perua vuokrasopimus ja lisäpalvelut 1 kuukauden varoitusajalla.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Neuvottelumenettelyn osallistumishakemusta koskevat vaatimukset</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1. Sisältö</P><P>Osallistumishakemusten tiedot on toimitettava seuraavilla lomakkeilla:</P><P>1) asianmukaisesti päivätty ja allekirjoitettu tieto- ja vakuutuslomake (hakijan tiedot, omistajan tiedot, jos eri, toimitilojen täydellinen osoite, vahvistus siitä, että vähintään vaaditut palvelut toimitetaan). Lomake on saatavissa osoitteesta: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) käytettävissä olevien tilojen kuvaus, piirustuksia (kerrokset, julkisivut, poikkileikkaukset) ja suunnitelmia, joista ilmenevät standardiasettelut (epäselvissä tapauksissa voidaan pyytää pohjapiirustuksia mittakaavoissa 1:50 tai 1:100 tai 1:200);</P><P>4.2 Neuvottelumenettelyn osallistumishakemuksen toimittaminen</P><P>Neuvottelumenettelyn osallistumishakemus, liitteenä 4.1 kohdassa vaaditut tiedot, on lähetettävä 9.4.2018 mennessä sähköpostitse osoitteeseen: contracts@easo.europa.eu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ehdotusten arviointi toisessa vaiheessa (neuvottelumenettely):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Esivalittujen hakijoiden ehdotukset hylätään, jos ne eivät täytä vaatimuksia ja/tai jos niissä ei oteta haluttua aluetta ja/tai tarvittavia tiloja tämän ilmoituksen kohdassa 3 mainitun mukaisesti. Hakijoille, joiden ehdottamat toimitilat suljetaan pois arvioinnista, ilmoitetaan tästä asianmukaisesti.</P><P>Valintakelpoiset ehdotukset analysoidaan laatua ja hintaa koskevien perusteiden ja seuraavien painotusten mukaisesti:</P><P>— hinta (40 prosenttia),</P><P>— laatu (60 prosenttia).</P><P>Tarjouksen laatu (Q) määritetään seuraavien seikkojen perusteella (100 pistettä):</P><P>— fyysinen läheisyys Kyproksen turvapaikkapalvelun käytössä olevan rakennukseen (viite 3.1., 1 kohta):  55 pistettä (vaadittava vähimmäismäärä: 35), </P><P>— tilanjako toimitiloissa – toimistotilan, odotusalueen tilanjako ja toimistojen laajennusmahdollisuus arvioidaan: 30 pistettä (vaadittava vähimmäismäärä: 18), </P><P>— turvallisuus ja turvallisuustoimet toimitiloissa (II. kohdassa ilmoitettujen vähimmäisvaatimusten lisäksi) – fyysisen turvajärjestelmän (vartijat), palonsammuttimien asennusten, hätäuloskäyntien ja evakuointisuunnitelmien jne. olemassa olo arvioidaan: 15 pistettä (vaadittava vähimmäismäärä: 7). </P><P>Tarjousten luokittelu perustuu seuraavan kaavan mukaiseen lopulliseen pistemäärään (F):</P><P>F = (60% x Q) + (40% x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yhteystiedot ja lisätiedot:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Hakijoille ilmoitetaan, jos heidät esivalitaan tai jos heitä ei kutsuta neuvottelumenettelyyn. Yhteydenpito hakijan ja EASOn välillä in kielletty paitsi tilanteissa, joissa kiinteistöjen kartoitusilmoitusta on selvennettävä. Selvennyspyynnöt on annettava kirjallisesti osoitteeseen contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Avis de prospection d'immeubles pour combler les besoins du bureau européen d’appui en matière d’asile</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Responsable de l’agence de l’UE</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Bureau européen d'appui en matière d'asile</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, MALTE</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Objet de la recherche:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le Bureau européen d’appui en matière d’asile (EASO) fournit un appui pour Chypre dans le cadre d’un plan spécial de soutien signé avec le gouvernement de Chypre. Dans le cadre du plan, l’agence déploie son personnel, ainsi que des experts et des interprètes, pour apporter un soutien sur des mesures spécifiques. Afin de veiller à un espace de travail pour le personnel, experts et interprètes, l’EASO cherche à louer un espace d’installations/bureau conformément aux exigences minimales ci-dessous, et des services auxiliaires de nettoyage.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché et de la procédure applicable</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Exigences minimales</P><P>L’EASO cherche la location d’un espace de bureau situé dans les locaux occupés par le service d’asile chypriote au 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosie, Chypre ou dans un bâtiment adjacent.</P><P>Les locaux doivent être accessibles au personnel de l’EASO, aux experts et aux interprètes de 7h00 à 22h00 tous les jours de la semaine.</P><P>L’agence exige un espace d’installations/bureau en surface estimé entre 250 et 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>L’espace d’installations/bureau doit convenir à l’hébergement de :</P><P>— 7 salles de bureaux/d’entretien — seront utilisées comme salles d’entretien - pour recevoir 3-4 personnes en même temps,</P><P>— 1 bureau pour les interprètes — qui sera utilisé comme salle de réunion/d’attente pour les interprètes et également par les interprètes pour travailler séparément si besoin (traductions, appels des candidats, etc.) — pour recevoir 6-8 personnes simultanément,</P><P>— 1 bureau des opérations — utilisé comme bureau par le coordinateur et le(s) assistant(s) des opérations de l’EASO et ayant suffisamment d’espace pour le rangement et la gestion de dossiers (dossiers de cas programmés, des dossiers en attente d’opinions, etc.) — pour recevoir 3 personnes en même temps et offrir un espace de bureau suffisant pour les rangements, en plus des postes de travail,</P><P>— 1 cuisine avec le matériel nécessaire (comptoir, buffets, évier),</P><P>— 2 salles de repos/toilettes — 1 pour le personnel et 1 pour les candidats,</P><P>— 1 salle à usages multiples — à utiliser également comme salle d’impression, salle de réunion, salle d’attente pour les candidats lors des pauses ou selon les nécessités — pour recevoir simultanément 15-16 personnes au moins,</P><P>— 1 salle de stockage.</P><P>Les bureaux doivent avoir suffisamment d’espace pour équiper les postes de travail selon les besoins (meubles et équipements informatiques).</P><P>Si un/des gardien(s) de sécurité permanent(s) n’est/ne sont pas disponible(s)/proposé(s), l’EASO sera autorisé à disposer de ses propres gardiens de sécurité et installer les systèmes de contrôle de sécurité nécessaires. De plus, si un service de réception n’est pas disponible, l’EASO sera autorisé à avoir son propre personnel de réception et à mettre en place les installations appropriées avec les meubles et les équipements nécessaires. A cette fin, l’espace au sol/niveau d’entrée nécessaire doit être mis à disposition par le contractant, en plus de l’espace de bureau nécessaire cité plus haut.</P><P>L’ensemble du bâtiment doit être protégé par un système intégré de détection d’incendie (détecteurs de fumée et de chaleur, panneaux d’incendie). Une sortie d’évacuation dédiée à chaque étage est nécessaire.</P><P>Des points d’alimentation électrique, une alimentation en eau froide et chaude, climatisation et chauffage, des raccordements aux égouts doivent être en place et raccordés aux services municipaux/publics.</P><P>Dans le cas où l’EASO aura besoin d’effectuer des adaptations structurelles, les documents supports nécessaires pour acquérir les autorisations requises pour les travaux de constructions, et l’accord de tous les propriétaires des bâtiments, en cas de besoin, doivent être mises à dispositions par le contractant.</P><P>L’EASO doit, en commun accord avec le contractant, être autorisé à effectuer des adaptations non structurelles, à sa charge, afin d’installer des éléments pour faire de petites améliorations sur les locaux.</P><P>Le contractant prendra à sa charge l’assurance des bâtiments, pour la couverture des dommages de base comme l’incendie, le vol, des fuites d’eau et des dommages similaires, pendant toute la durée de la location.</P><P>Le contractant est tenu responsable de la résolution de tout problème pouvant apparaître concernant l’ensemble des services techniques, y compris l’alimentation électrique, l’alimentation en eau, l’évacuation des eaux usées, l’élimination des déchets et la ventilation, ainsi que toute réparation rapide des dommages non attribués à l’EASO.</P><P>Les services de nettoyage sont assurés comme suit :</P><P>Tâches à effectuer quotidiennement :</P><P>— Vidage des poubelles, remplacement des cuves intérieures plastiques, si nécessaire, et déplacement des déchets vers les bacs communaux,</P><P>— Dépoussiérage et essuyage humide de toutes les surfaces exposées,</P><P>— Nettoyage et balayage de tous les planchers et des carreaux sur les murs,</P><P>— Nettoyage, balayage et désinfection des salles de repos, y compris des toilettes, des éviers/lavabos, mise en place du papier hygiénique, des essuie-mains en papier et des autres fournitures nécessaires,</P><P>— Nettoyage, balayage et désinfection de la cuisine, y compris de l’évier et de toutes les surfaces, placement du papier hygiénique et des autres fournitures nécessaires.</P><P>Tâches à effectuer mensuellement :</P><P>— Nettoyage approfondi et désinfection des toilettes,</P><P>— Dépoussiérage et nettoyage et des appareils de chauffage/climatisation,</P><P>— Nettoyage de toutes les vitres sur les portes intérieurs et/ou des séparations.</P><P>Tâches à effectuer trimestriellement :</P><P>— Nettoyage de l’ensemble des fenêtres et des vitres sur les portes d’extérieur éventuellement,</P><P>— Nettoyages des rideaux et des stores, éventuellement.</P><P>3.2 Délais</P><P>Les locaux doivent être disponibles en avril 2018.</P><P>3.3 Procédure</P><P>La présente procédure de prospection sera clôturée par une présélection de 3 candidatures au maximum dont les locaux répondent aux besoins. L’EASO invitera le(s) proposant(s) ainsi présélectionné(s) à entamer des négociations dans une phase ultérieure distincte de la présente procédure. Les spécifications techniques détaillées seront envoyées au(x) candidat(s) présélectionné(s). Le(s) candidat(s) invité(s) sera/seront informé(s) du contenu nécessaire des</P><P>offres et des documents à présenter. Avec la présentation de l’offre, chaque candidat présélectionné doit garantir :</P><P>— la validité de son offre jusqu'à la signature éventuelle du contrat,</P><P>— la mise à disposition de tout document concernant les locaux dans les délais précisés par l’EASO.</P><P>La présente publication ne constitue en aucun cas un engagement pour l’EASO dans le cadre des procédures de passation de marchés. L’EASO se réserve le droit, jusqu'à la signature du contrat, de renoncer au marché ou d'annuler la présente procédure sans que les candidats puissent prétendre à une quelconque indemnisation. L’EASO ne signera, avant ou pendant la phase de négociations, aucun contrat d'exclusivité ni aucune clause similaire en faveur d'un candidat.</P><P>3.4 Type de contrat</P><P>La durée maximum de la convention de location sera de dix (10) mois, avec la possibilité de 3 reconductions pour une durée supplémentaire de 12 mois chacune pour une durée totale de 3 ans et 10 mois.</P><P>La convention de location doit couvrir les coûts de location et les services auxiliaires. L’EASO est habilité à annuler la convention de location et les services auxiliaires par un préavis d’un mois.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Les exigences concernant la demande de participation dans la procédure négociée</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Contenu</P><P>Les informations contenues dans la demande de participation doivent être présentées en utilisant les formulaires suivants :</P><P>1) Formulaire d’identification et de déclaration dûment daté et signé (indiquant les détails du candidat ; les détails du propriétaire - si différents, l’adresse complète des locaux ; la confirmation que les services minimum nécessaires doivent être fournis). Le formulaire est disponible à : https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Description des superficies des surfaces ; des plans (étages, façades, coupes en section) et des plans indiquant un schéma standard (en cas de doute, une échelle de 1/50, 1/100 ou 1/200 pour les plans sera exigée) ;</P><P>4.2 La présentation de la demande de participation à la procédure négociée</P><P>Les demandes de participation à la procédure négociée, accompagnées des informations exigées au point 4.1, doivent être envoyées par email à : contracts@easo.europa.eu le 9.4.2018 au plus tard.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L’évaluation des offres dans la deuxième phase (procédure négociée) :</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les offres des candidats présélectionnés non conformes et/ou ne respectant pas le périmètre de recherche et/ou la surface souhaitée tels que mentionnés au point 3 du présent avis seront écartées. Les candidats des locaux exclus en seront informés.</P><P>Les offres recevables seront analysées sur la base des critères de qualité et de prix, selon la pondération suivante:</P><P>— prix (40 %),</P><P>— qualité (60 %).</P><P>La qualité (Q) de l'offre sera établie sur la base des éléments suivants (100 points):</P><P>— La proximité physique au bâtiment occupé par le service d’asile chypriote (réf. 3.1., premier paragraphe) : 55 points (minimum requis : 35),</P><P>— Distribution de l’espace dans les locaux - la distribution de l’espace des bureaux, la salle d’attente et la possibilité d’une expansion des bureaux seront évaluées : 30 points (minimum requis : 18),</P><P>— Mesures de sureté et de sécurité dans les locaux (en plus des exigences minimum indiquées au point II.) - la présence de sécurité physique (gardes), l’installation d’extincteurs, les sorties de secours et les plans d’évacuation, etc. seront évalués : 15 points (minimum requis : 7).</P><P>Le classement des offres sera réalisé sur la base d'une note finale (F), selon la formule suivante :</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contacts et informations complémentaires:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les candidats seront informés de leur présélection ou de la décision de ne pas être invités pour la procédure négociée. Tout contact entre les candidats et l’EASO est interdit, sauf en cas de clarification à apporter concernant l’avis de prospection d'immeubles. La demande de clarification doit être présentée par écrit à : contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Προκήρυξη κτηματομεσιτικής έρευνας για την κάλυψη των αναγκών της Ευρωπαϊκής Υπηρεσίας Υποστήριξης για το Άσυλο</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αρμόδιος οργανισμός της ΕΕ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ευρωπαϊκή Υπηρεσία Υποστήριξης για το Άσυλο</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Μάλτα</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αντικείμενο της έρευνας:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Η Ευρωπαϊκή Υπηρεσία Υποστήριξης για το Άσυλο (EASO) παρέχει υποστήριξη στην Κύπρο στο πλαίσιο ενός ειδικού σχεδίου υποστήριξης που έχει υπογραφεί με την κυβέρνηση της Κύπρου. Στο πλαίσιο του σχεδίου, ο Οργανισμός διαθέτει το προσωπικό του, καθώς και εμπειρογνώμονες και διερμηνείς, προκειμένου να παράσχει στήριξη σε συγκεκριμένα μέτρα. Για να εξασφαλιστεί ο χώρος εργασίας για το προσωπικό, τους εμπειρογνώμονες και τους διερμηνείς, η EASO αναζητά εγκαταστάσεις/γραφεία προς ενοικίαση σύμφωνα με τις κατωτέρω ελάχιστες απαιτήσεις, καθώς και βοηθητικές υπηρεσίες καθαρισμού.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Περιγραφή της σύμβασης και της ισχύουσας διαδικασίας</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Ελάχιστες απαιτήσεις</P><P>Η EASO επιθυμεί να μισθώσει χώρους γραφείων που βρίσκονται στις εγκαταστάσεις που καταλαμβάνει η Κυπριακή Υπηρεσία Ασύλου στη Λεωφόρο Αρχιεπισκόπου Μακαρίου ΙΙΙ 70, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Κύπρος, ή σε ένα παρακείμενο κτίριο.</P><P>Οι χώροι θα πρέπει να είναι προσβάσιμοι από το προσωπικό, τους εμπειρογνώμονες και τους διερμηνείς της EASO από τις 7:00 έως τις 22:00 όλες τις ημέρες της εβδομάδας.</P><P>Ο Οργανισμός απαιτεί εκτιμώμενες εγκαταστάσεις/χώρους γραφείων άνω του εδάφους από 250 έως 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Οι εγκαταστάσεις/χώροι γραφείων πρέπει να είναι κατάλληλοι για να φιλοξενήσουν:</P><P>— 7 γραφεία/αίθουσες συνεντεύξεων — για χρήση ως αίθουσες συνεντεύξεων - για φιλοξενία 3-4 ατόμων τη φορά,</P><P>— 1 γραφείο διερμηνέων — για χρήση ως αίθουσα συσκέψεων/αναμονής για διερμηνείς αλλά και από διερμηνείς για να εργάζονται μεμονωμένα, εάν χρειάζεται (μεταφράσεις, κλήσεις με αιτούντες, κ.λπ.) — για φιλοξενία 6-8 ατόμων τη φορά,</P><P>— 1 γραφείο επιχειρήσεων — για χρήση ως γραφείο του συντονιστή και του βοηθού(βοηθών) λειτουργιών της EASO και διάθεση επαρκούς χώρου γραφείων για αρχειοθήκες για τη διαχείριση αρχείων (αρχεία προγραμματισμένων υποθέσεων, αρχεία με αναμονή απόψεων, κ.λπ.) — για φιλοξενία 3 προσώπων κάθε φορά και παροχή επαρκούς χώρου γραφείων για θυρίδες αρχείων, εκτός από τους σταθμούς εργασίας,</P><P>— 1 κουζίνα με κατάλληλο εξοπλισμό (πάγκος, ντουλάπια, νεροχύτης),</P><P>— 2 αποχωρητήρια/τουαλέτες — 1 για το προσωπικό και 1 για τους αιτούντες,</P><P>— 1 δωμάτιο πολλαπλών χρήσεων — για χρήση και ως αίθουσα εκτυπωτών, αίθουσα συνεδριάσεων, αίθουσα αναμονής για αιτούντες κατά τη διάρκεια κάποιας διακοπής ή ανάλογα με τις ανάγκες — για φιλοξενία τουλάχιστον 15-16 ατόμων τη φορά,</P><P>— 1 χώρος αποθήκευσης.</P><P>Τα γραφεία πρέπει να διαθέτουν επαρκή χώρο για να είναι εξοπλισμένα με σταθμούς εργασίας, όπου απαιτείται (έπιπλα και εξοπλισμός ΤΠΕ).</P><P>Εάν δεν διατίθενται/προσφέρονται φύλακες ασφαλείας, η EASO έχει το δικαίωμα να διαθέτει δικούς της φύλακες ασφαλείας και να εγκαθιστά τα απαιτούμενα συστήματα ελέγχου ασφαλείας. Επιπλέον, εάν δεν είναι διαθέσιμη υπηρεσία υποδοχής, η EASO θα έχει τη δυνατότητα να διαθέτει δικό της προσωπικό υποδοχής και να δημιουργεί κατάλληλες εγκαταστάσεις με τα απαιτούμενα έπιπλα και εξοπλισμό. Για το σκοπό αυτό, ο απαραίτητος χώρος στο επίπεδο εδάφους/εισόδου πρέπει να είναι διαθέσιμος από τον ανάδοχο, πέρα από τον απαιτούμενο χώρο γραφείων που αναφέρεται παραπάνω.</P><P>Το σύνολο του κτιρίου πρέπει να καλύπτεται από ένα ολοκληρωμένο σύστημα ανίχνευσης πυρκαγιάς (ανιχνευτές καπνού και θερμότητας, πυροσβεστικοί πίνακες). Απαιτείται ειδική έξοδος εκκένωσης σε κάθε όροφο.</P><P>Η παροχή ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος και σημείων ηλεκτρισμού, η παροχή ζεστού και κρύου νερού, η θέρμανση/ψύξη/κλιματισμός, οι συνδέσεις αποχέτευσης πρέπει να είναι συνδεδεμένες με δημοτικές/δημόσιες υπηρεσίες.</P><P>Σε περίπτωση που η EASO πρέπει να προβεί σε διαρθρωτικές προσαρμογές, τα αναγκαία δικαιολογητικά για την απόκτηση των απαιτούμενων αδειών για κατασκευαστικά έργα και τη συμφωνία όλων των ιδιοκτητών κτιρίων, εφόσον απαιτείται, θα τεθούν στη διάθεση του αναδόχου.</P><P>Η EASO, σε συμφωνία με τον ανάδοχο, μπορεί να πραγματοποιεί μη διαρθρωτικές προσαρμογές, με δικά της έξοδα, προκειμένου να εγκαταστήσει αντικείμενα ή να πραγματοποιήσει μικρές βελτιώσεις στις εγκαταστάσεις.</P><P>Ο ανάδοχος είναι υπεύθυνος για την ασφάλιση των κτιρίων, για την κάλυψη βασικών ζημιών όπως πυρκαγιά, κλοπή, πλημμύρα και παρόμοιες ζημιές, καθ' όλη τη διάρκεια της μίσθωσης.</P><P>Ο ανάδοχος είναι υπεύθυνος για την επίλυση τυχόν προβλημάτων που ενδέχεται να προκύψουν σε σχέση με όλες τις τεχνικές υπηρεσίες, συμπεριλαμβανομένης της τροφοδοσίας ρεύματος, νερού, της αποχέτευσης, της διάθεσης αποβλήτων και του αερισμού, καθώς και για την άμεση αποκατάσταση συναφών ζημιών που δεν αποδίδονται στην EASO.</P><P>Οι υπηρεσίες καθαρισμού παρέχονται ως εξής:</P><P>Εργασίες που πρέπει να εκτελούνται καθημερινά:</P><P>— Άδειασμα καλαθιών απορριμμάτων, αντικατάσταση πλαστικών εσωτερικών επενδύσεων, εάν χρειάζεται, και αφαίρεση απορριμμάτων από τους κοινόχρηστους κάδους,</P><P>— Ξεσκόνισμα και υγρό σκούπισμα όλων των εκτεθειμένων επιφανειών,</P><P>— Καθαρισμός και σκούπισμα δαπέδων και πλακιδίων τοίχου,</P><P>— Καθαρισμός, σκούπισμα και απολύμανση των χώρων ανάπαυσης, όπως τουαλέτες, νεροχύτες/νιπτήρες, τοποθέτηση χαρτιού υγείας, χαρτοπετσετών και άλλων απαραίτητων προμηθειών,</P><P>— Καθαρισμός, σκούπισμα και απολύμανση της κουζίνας, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του νεροχύτη και όλων των επιφανειών, τοποθέτηση χαρτοπετσετών και άλλων απαραίτητων προμηθειών.</P><P>Εργασίες που πρέπει να εκτελούνται μία φορά το μήνα:</P><P>— Βαθύς καθαρισμός και απολύμανση των τουαλετών,</P><P>— Ξεσκόνισμα και καθαρισμός μονάδων θέρμανσης/ψύξης,</P><P>— Καθαρισμός όλων των τζαμιών στις εσωτερικές πόρτες και/ή στα διαχωριστικά χώρων.</P><P>Εργασίες που πρέπει να εκτελούνται κάθε τρείς (3) μήνες:</P><P>— Καθαρισμός όλων των παραθύρων και των τζαμιών στις εξωτερικές πόρτες, εάν υπάρχουν,</P><P>— Καθαρισμός κουρτινών και περσίδων, εάν υπάρχουν.</P><P>3.2 Προθεσμίες</P><P>Οι χώροι θα είναι διαθέσιμοι τον Απρίλιο του 2018.</P><P>3.3 Διαδικασία</P><P>Η παρούσα διαδικασία κτηματομεσιτικής έρευνας θα ολοκληρωθεί με μια προεπιλογή 3 υποψηφίων των οποίων οι χώροι επιτρέπουν την ικανοποίηση των αναγκών. Η EASO θα καλέσει τον/τους προεπιλεγέντα/προεπιλεγέντες υποψήφιο/υποψήφιους, να πραγματοποιήσει/πραγματοποιήσουν διαπραγματεύσεις σε μεταγενέστερη φάση, διαφορετική από την παρούσα διαδικασία. Οι λεπτομερείς τεχνικές προδιαγραφές αποστέλλονται στους προεπιλεγέντες υποψήφιους. Οι υποψήφιοι που έχουν κληθεί θα ενημερωθούν για το απαιτούμενο περιεχόμενο των</P><P>προτάσεων και των εγγράφων που πρέπει να υποβληθούν. Με την υποβολή της πρότασης, κάθε προεπιλεγείς υποψήφιος εγγυάται:</P><P>— την ισχύ της πρότασής του έως την ενδεχόμενη υπογραφή της σύμβασης,</P><P>— τη διάθεση κάθε εγγράφου σχετικά με τις εγκαταστάσεις εντός των προθεσμιών που ορίζονται από την EASO.</P><P>Η παρούσα δημοσίευση δεν αποτελεί σε καμία περίπτωση δέσμευση για την EASO στο πλαίσιο των διαδικασιών σύναψης συμβάσεων. Η EASO επιφυλάσσεται του δικαιώματος, έως την υπογραφή της σύμβασης, να παραιτηθεί από τη σύμβαση ή να ακυρώσει την παρούσα διαδικασία, χωρίς οι υποβάλλοντες πρόταση να δικαιούνται να διεκδικήσουν οποιαδήποτε αποζημίωση. Η EASO δεν θα υπογράψει, πριν ή κατά τη διάρκεια της φάσης διαπραγματεύσεων, καμία σύμβαση αποκλειστικότητας ούτε παρόμοια ρήτρα υπέρ ενός υποβάλλοντα πρόταση.</P><P>3.4 Τύπος σύμβασης</P><P>Η συνολική μέγιστη διάρκεια της σύμβασης μίσθωσης θα είναι δέκα (10) μήνες, με δυνατότητα παράτασης 3 φορές για επιπλέον περίοδο 12 μηνών/έκαστη για συνολική διάρκεια 3 ετών και 10 μηνών.</P><P>Η σύμβαση μίσθωσης καλύπτει τα έξοδα μίσθωσης και τις βοηθητικές υπηρεσίες. Η EASO μπορεί να ακυρώσει τη σύμβαση μίσθωσης και τις βοηθητικές υπηρεσίες με προειδοποίηση ενός μηνός.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Απαιτήσεις σχετικά με τις αιτήσεις συμμετοχής στη διαδικασία με διαπραγμάτευση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Περιεχόμενο</P><P>Οι πληροφορίες που περιέχονται στην αίτηση συμμετοχής πρέπει να υποβάλλονται χρησιμοποιώντας τα ακόλουθα έντυπα:</P><P>1) Έντυπο ταυτοποίησης και δήλωσης δεόντως χρονολογημένο και υπογεγραμμένο (αναφέροντας τα στοιχεία του αιτούντος, τα στοιχεία του ιδιοκτήτη - εάν είναι διαφορετικά, πλήρης διεύθυνση των χώρων, επιβεβαίωση ότι παρέχονται οι ελάχιστες απαιτούμενες υπηρεσίες). Το έντυπο διατίθεται στη διεύθυνση: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Περιγραφή των επιφανειών, σχέδια (όροφοι, προσόψεις, διατομές) και σχέδια που παρουσιάζουν μια τυποποιημένη διάταξη (σε περίπτωση αμφιβολιών μπορούν να ζητηθούν σχέδια κλίμακας 1/50 ή 1/100 ή 1/200);</P><P>4.2 Υποβολή αιτήσεων συμμετοχής στη διαδικασία με διαπραγμάτευση</P><P>Οι αιτήσεις συμμετοχής, στη διαδικασία με διαπραγμάτευση, συνοδευόμενες από τις πληροφορίες που απαιτούνται στο σημείο 4.1, πρέπει να αποσταλούν μέσω ηλεκτρονικού ταχυδρομείου στη διεύθυνση contracts@easo.europa.eu έως τις 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αξιολόγηση των προτάσεων στη δεύτερη φάση (διαδικασία με διαπραγμάτευση):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Οι προτάσεις που υποβλήθηκαν από τους προεπιλεγέντες υποψηφίους που δεν συμμορφώνονται με ή/και δεν πληρούν τους όρους σχετικά με την ακτίνα έρευνας ή/και τη ζητούμενη επιφάνεια σύμφωνα με το σημείο 3 της παρούσας προκήρυξης θα απορριφθούν. Οι απορριφθέντες υποψήφιοι για χώρους θα ενημερωθούν σχετικά.</P><P>Οι αποδεκτές προτάσεις θα αναλυθούν με βάση τα κριτήρια ποιότητας και τιμής σύμφωνα με την ακόλουθη βαρύτητα:</P><P>— τιμή (40 %),</P><P>— ποιότητα (60 %).</P><P>Η ποιότητα (Q) της προσφοράς θα διαπιστωθεί με βάση τα ακόλουθα στοιχεία (100 βαθμοί):</P><P>— Φυσική εγγύτητα με το κτίριο που καταλαμβάνει η Κυπριακή Υπηρεσία Ασύλου (αναφ. 3.1., πρώτη παράγραφος): 55 βαθμοί (ελάχιστοι απαιτούμενοι: 35),</P><P>— Θα αξιολογηθεί η κατανομή χώρων στις εγκαταστάσεις - η κατανομή χώρων γραφείων, χώρου αναμονής και η δυνατότητα επέκτασης των γραφείων: 30 βαθμοί (ελάχιστοι απαιτούμενοι: 18),</P><P>— Μέτρα ασφαλείας και προστασίας στους χώρους (εκτός από τις ελάχιστες απαιτήσεις που αναφέρονται στο σημείο II) – θα αξιολογηθεί η ύπαρξη φυσικής ασφάλειας (φρουροί), η τοποθέτηση πυροσβεστήρων, οι έξοδοι έκτακτης ανάγκης και τα σχέδια εκκένωσης, κλπ.: 15 βαθμοί (ελάχιστοι απαιτούμενοι: 7).</P><P>Η κατάταξη των προσφορών θα πραγματοποιηθεί με βάση την τελική βαθμολογία (F) σύμφωνα με τον ακόλουθο τύπο:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Επικοινωνία και πρόσθετες πληροφορίες:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Οι υποψήφιοι θα ενημερωθούν για την προεπιλογή τους ή για την απόφαση να μην προσκληθούν για τη διαδικασία με διαπραγμάτευση. Οποιαδήποτε επαφή μεταξύ τωνυποψηφίων και της EASO απαγορεύεται, εκτός εάν χρειάζεται να δοθούν διευκρινίσεις σχετικά με την προκήρυξη κτηματομεσιτικής έρευνας. Το αίτημα για διευκρινίσεις υποβάλλεται γραπτώς στη διεύθυνση contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Indagine immobiliare volta a sovvenire alle esigenze dell’Ufficio europeo di sostegno per l’asilo</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Agenzia UE responsabile</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ufficio europeo di sostegno per l'asilo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oggetto dell'indagine:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L’Ufficio europeo di sostegno per l’asilo (EASO) fornisce sostegno a Cipro nell’ambito di un Piano speciale di assistenza sottoscritto con il governo di Cipro. Nell’attuazione di detto piano, l'Agenzia impiega il proprio personale, nonché esperti e interpreti, per fornire supporto su misure specifiche. Allo scopo di garantire lo spazio di lavoro per il personale, gli esperti e gli interpreti, l'EASO sta cercando di affittare strutture/spazi per uffici in linea con i requisiti minimi specificati qui di seguito, e i servizi accessori di pulizia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dell'appalto e della procedura da applicare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Requisiti minimi</P><P>L’EASO sta cercando di affittare spazi per uffici presso i locali occupati dal Servizio cipriota di asilo sito in 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Cipro o in un edificio adiacente.</P><P>I locali dovranno essere accessibili al personale, agli esperti e agli interpreti dell'EASO dalle 7:00 alle 22:00 tutti i giorni della settimana.</P><P>L'Agenzia richiede strutture/spazi per uffici fuori terra stimati in un minimo di 250 a un massimo di 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Le strutture/spazi per uffici dovranno essere idonei ad ospitare:</P><P>— 7 uffici/stanze per colloqui — da utilizzare come stanze per i colloqui — in grado di accogliere 3-4 persone alla volta,</P><P>— 1 ufficio per gli interpreti — da utilizzare come sala riunione o sala di attesa dagli interpreti e anche dagli interpreti per lavorare separatamente, se richiesto (traduzioni, conversazioni con i richiedenti, etc.) — in grado di accogliere 6-8 persone alla volta,</P><P>— 1 ufficio operativo — da utilizzare come ufficio per il coordinatore e gli assistenti operativi dell'EASO e disporre di uno spazio ufficio sufficiente per l’archivio dei file per la gestione dei fascicoli (file di casi programmati, file in attesa di pareri, ecc.) — in grado di accogliere 3 persone alla volta e di fornire sufficiente spazio di ufficio per gli armadietti per l’archiviazione, oltre alle postazioni di lavoro,</P><P>— 1 cucina con strutture adeguate (bancone, armadi, lavello),</P><P>— 2 servizi igienici — 1 per il personale e 1 per i richiedenti,</P><P>— 1 sala polivalente — da utilizzare anche come sala per le stampanti, sala riunioni, sala d'attesa per i richiedenti durante la pausa o secondo le esigenze — in grado di accogliere minimo 15-16 persone alla volta,</P><P>— 1 locale adibito a deposito.</P><P>Gli uffici dovranno disporre di spazio sufficiente per essere dotati di postazioni di lavoro, laddove richiesto (mobili e apparecchiature TIC).</P><P>Se non è disponibile/offerto un servizio di guardie di sicurezza permanenti, sarà consentito all'EASO di avere le proprie guardie di sicurezza e di installare i sistemi di controllo di sicurezza richiesti. Inoltre, nel caso in cui non sia disponibile un servizio di accoglienza, sarà consentito all'EASO di avere il proprio personale di accoglienza e di predisporre strutture adeguate con mobilio e le attrezzature richieste. A tal fine, il Contraente metterà a disposizione lo spazio necessario a livello di ingresso o al pian terreno, oltre agli spazi per uffici come sopra richiesti.</P><P>L'intero edificio dovrà essere coperto da un sistema integrato di rilevamento di incendi (rilevatori di fumo e calore, pannelli antincendio). È richiesta un'uscita di evacuazione dedicata su ciascun piano.</P><P>Alimentazione elettrica e punti di allacciameto elettrico, fornitura di acqua calda e fredda, riscaldamento/raffrescamento/climatizzazione, collegamenti alla rete fognaria devono essere installati e collegati ai servizi municipali/pubblici.</P><P>Nel caso in cui l'EASO debba eseguire adattamenti strutturali, il contraente dovrà mettere a disposizione i documenti giustificativi necessari per acquisire i permessi necessari per l’esecuzione dei lavori di costruzione e il consenso di tutti i proprietari dell’edificio, ove richiesto.</P><P>L'EASO, in accordo con il contraente, potrà eseguire adeguamenti non strutturali, a proprie spese, al fine di installare elementi o di apportare piccoli miglioramenti ai locali.</P><P>Il Contraente sarà responsabile per l'assicurazione degli edifici, per la copertura i danni di base come incendio, furto, trabocco dell’acqua e danni simili, per tutta la durata del contratto di locazione.</P><P>Il Contraente avrà la responsabile di risolvere gli eventuali problemi che potranno verificarsi riguardo tutti i servizi tecnici, inclusi l'alimentazione elettrica, l'approvvigionamento idrico, le fognature, lo smaltimento dei rifiuti e la ventilazione, nonché per la riparazione immediata dei relativi danni non imputabili all'EASO.</P><P>I servizi di pulizia dovranno essere forniti come segue:</P><P>Attività da eseguire su base giornaliera:</P><P>— Svuotare i cestini dei rifiuti, sostituire le buste di plastica, se necessario, e gettare i rifiuti nei contenitori comunali,</P><P>— Spolverare e passare un panno umido su tutte le superfici esposte,</P><P>— Pulire e spazzare le piastrelle di pavimenti e pareti,</P><P>— Pulire, spazzare e disinfestare i servizi igienici, inclusi i bagni, lavandini, posizionando la carta igienica e gli asciugamani di carta, e altri materiali necessari,</P><P>— Pulire, spazzare e disinfestare la cucina, incluso il lavello, e tutte le superficie, posizionando gli asciugamani di carta e altri materiali necessari.</P><P>Compiti da eseguire una volta al mese:</P><P>— Pulire a fondo e disinfestare i servizi igienici,</P><P>— Spolverare e pulire le unità di riscaldamento/raffreddamento,</P><P>— Pulire tutti i vetri delle porte interne e/o pareti divisorie.</P><P>Compiti da eseguire una volta ogni tre (3) mesi:</P><P>— Pulire tutte le finestre e i vetri delle porte esterne, se ci sono,</P><P>— Pulire le tende e veneziane, se ci sono.</P><P>3.2 Termini</P><P>I locali dovranno essere disponibili ad aprile 2018.</P><P>3.3 Procedura</P><P>La presente procedura di indagine si concluderà con una preselezione di un massimo di 3 candidati i cui locali consentono di soddisfare i requisiti. L’EASO potrà invitare il/i proponente/i preselezionato/i ad avviare negoziazioni in una fase successiva distinta dalla presente procedura. Le specifiche tecniche dettagliate saranno inviate ai proponenti preselezionati. I proponenti invitati saranno informati sul contenuto richiesto delle</P><P>proposte e dei documenti da fornire. Con la presentazione della proposta, ciascun candidato preselezionato garantisce:</P><P>— la validità della sua proposta fino all'eventuale firma del contratto,</P><P>— la messa a disposizione di qualsiasi documento relativo ai locali entro i termini precisati dall'EASO.</P><P>La presente pubblicazione non costituisce alcun impegno per l'EASO nel quadro delle procedure di aggiudicazione di appalti. L'EASO si riserva il diritto, fino alla stipula del contratto, di rinunciare all'appalto o di annullare la presente procedura, senza che i proponenti possano pretendere un indennizzo qualsiasi. Prima o durante la fase delle negoziazioni, l'EASO non firmerà alcun contratto di esclusività né alcuna clausola simile a favore di un proponente.</P><P>3.4 Tipo di appalto</P><P>La durata massima totale del contratto di locazione sarà di dieci (10) mesi, con possibilità di rinnovare fino a 3 volte per una durata ulteriore di 12 mesi ogni volta, per una durata complessiva di 3 anni e 10 mesi.</P><P>Il contratto di locazione coprirà il canone di locazione e i servizi accessori. L’EASO potrà annullare il contratto di locazione e i servizi accessori con un preavviso di un mese.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requisiti relativi alle domande di partecipazione alla procedura negoziata</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Contenuto</P><P>Le informazioni contenute nella domanda di partecipazione devono essere trasmesse utilizzando i seguenti moduli:</P><P>1) Formulario d’identificazione e dichiarazione debitamente datato e firmato (con indicazione dei dettagli del candidato; dettagli del proprietario – se diverso, indirizzo completo dei locali; conferma che i servizi minimi richiesti saranno forniti). Il formulario è disponibile al seguente indirizzo: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Descrizione delle superfici; disegni (pavimenti, facciate, sezioni trasversali) e piani che mostrano una disposizione tipo (in caso di dubbio possono essere richiesti disegni in scala 1/50, 1/100 o 1/200);</P><P>4.2 Presentazione delle domande di partecipazione alla procedura negoziata</P><P>Le domande di partecipazione alla procedura negoziata, corredate dall’informazione richiesta al punto 4.1, devono essere trasmesse per e-mail all’indirizzo contracts@easo.europa.eu entro il 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Valutazione delle proposta nella seconda fase (procedura negoziata):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le proposte ricevute dai candidati preselezionati che non siano conformi e/o che non rispettino il perimetro di ricerca e/o la superficie desiderata, secondo quanto indicato al punto 3 del presente avviso, saranno respinte. I proponenti di locali esclusi saranno debitamente notificati.</P><P>Le proposte ammissibili saranno analizzate in base ai criteri della qualità e del prezzo, secondo la seguente ponderazione:</P><P>— prezzo (40 %),</P><P>— qualità (60 %).</P><P>La qualità (Q) dell'offerta sarà stabilita in base ai seguenti elementi (100 punti):</P><P>— La vicinanza fisica all'edificio occupato dal Servizio di asilo cipriota (rif. 3.1., primo paragrafo): 55 punti (minimo richiesto: 35),</P><P>— Distribuzione degli spazio all’interno dei locali — verrà valutata la distribuzione degli spazi per uffici, le aree di attesa e la possibilità di espansione degli uffici: 30 punti (minimo richiesto: 18),</P><P>— Misure di sicurezza e protezione nei locali (oltre ai requisiti minimi indicati al punto II) — sarà valutata la presenza di sicurezza fisica (guardie), installazione di estintori, uscite di emergenza e piani di evacuazione, ecc.: 15 punti (minimo richiesto: 7).</P><P>Verrà stilata una graduatoria sulla base di un punteggio finale (F), secondo la seguente formula:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contatti e informazioni complementari:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>I candidati saranno informati della loro preselezione o della decisione di non invitarli per la procedura negoziata. È vietato qualsiasi contatto tra i candidati e l'EASO, ad eccezione dei casi in cui si devano fornire dei chiarimenti in merito all'avviso di indagine immobiliare. Le richieste di chiarimenti dovranno essere trasmesse per iscritto all’indirizzo contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Aankondiging van een onderzoek van de vastgoedmarkt om te voldoen aan de behoeften van het Europees Ondersteuningsbureau voor asielzaken inzake kantoorruimte</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verantwoordelijk EU-agentschap:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europees Ondersteuningsbureau voor asielzaken</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>„MTC Block A”, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Voorwerp van het onderzoek:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Het Europees Ondersteuningsbureau voor asielzaken (EASO) biedt ondersteuning aan Cyprus in het kader van een speciaal ondersteuningsplan dat is ondertekend met de Regering van Cyprus. In het kader van dit plan zet het Agentschap zijn personeel, deskundigen en tolken in om ondersteuning te bieden bij specifieke maatregelen. Om een werkplek te verzekeren voor medewerkers, deskundigen en tolken kijkt EASO naar de mogelijkheid om faciliteiten/kantoorruimtes te kunnen leasen die voldoen aan de minimale onderstaande vereisten, en wil tevens ondersteunende schoonmaakdiensten aantrekken.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschrijving van de opdracht en van de toepasselijke procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Minimumvereisten</P><P>EASO wenst kantoorruimtes te huren op de kantoorlocatie die wordt gebruikt door de Cypriotische Asieldienst, gelegen op 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia in Cyprus, of in een aangrenzend gebouw.</P><P>De kantoren moeten van 7:00 tot 22:00 en 7 dagen per week toegankelijk zijn voor personeel, deskundigen en tolken van EASO.</P><P>Het Agentschap vereist naar schatting bovengrondse faciliteiten of kantoorruimtes tussen 250 en 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>De faciliteiten of kantoorruimtes moeten plaats kunnen bieden aan:</P><P>- 7 kantoor- of interviewruimtes: te gebruiken voor interviews met voldoende ruimte voor een groep van 3-4 personen,</P><P>- 1 kantoorruimte voor tolken: te gebruiken als vergader-/ wachtruimte voor tolken en ook om eventueel afzonderlijk te kunnen werken (vertalingen, gesprekken met aanvragers, enz.) met voldoende ruimte voor een groep van 6-8 personen,</P><P>- 1 operationeel kantoor: te gebruiken door de EASO-coördinator en werkzame assistent(en) met voldoende kantoorruimte voor archiefkasten inzake archiefbeheer (dossiers van geplande zaken, dossiers in afwachting van een beoordeling, enz.), met voldoende ruimte voor een groep van 3 personen. Naast de werkstations moet er ook voldoende kantoorruimte zijn voor de archiefkasten,</P><P>- 1 keuken met de nodige faciliteiten (aanrecht, keukenkasten, gootsteen),</P><P>- 2 toiletruimtes/toiletten: 1 voor personeel en 1 voor aanvragers,</P><P>- 1 multifunctionele ruimte: tevens te gebruiken als printerruimte, vergaderruimte, wachtruimte voor aanvragers tijdens pauzes, of indien nodig, om ruimte te bieden aan een groep van minstens 15-16 personen,</P><P>- 1 opslagruimte.</P><P>De kantoren moeten voldoende ruimte hebben om de werkplekken waar nodig in te richten met b.v. meubilair en ICT-apparatuur.</P><P>Als er geen permanente beveiligingsbeambte(s) beschikbaar zijn of aangeboden worden, mag EASO zijn eigen beveiligingsbeambten inzetten en de vereiste veiligheidscontrolesystemen installeren. Indien er geen receptiedienst beschikbaar is, mag EASO bovendien eigen receptiepersoneel inzetten en de juiste faciliteiten opstellen met het benodigde meubilair en apparatuur. Hiertoe moet de contractant, behalve de bovenvermelde vereiste kantoorruimte, ook de nodige ruimte op de begane grond/ingangsniveau beschikbaar stellen.</P><P>Het gehele gebouw moet zijn voorzien van een geïntegreerd branddetectiesysteem (rook- en hittedetectoren, brandmeldpanelen). Een speciale nooduitgang is vereist voor elke verdieping.</P><P>Elektrische stroom en aansluitpunten, warm- en koudwatervoorziening, verwarming/koeling/airconditioning, rioolaansluitingen moeten aanwezig zijn en aangesloten zijn op de gemeentelijke/openbare voorzieningen.</P><P>In het geval dat EASO structurele aanpassingen moet doorvoeren, moeten de nodige ondersteunende documenten (op verzoek) door de contractant beschikbaar worden gesteld om de vereiste bouwwerkvergunningen te verkrijgen en de goedkeuring van alle eigenaars van de gebouwen.</P><P>In overleg met de contractant mag EASO op eigen kosten niet-structurele aanpassingen doorvoeren, om producten te kunnen installeren of om kleine verbeteringen aan te brengen in ruimtes.</P><P>De contractant is gedurende de gehele looptijd van de huurovereenkomst verantwoordelijk voor de verzekering van de gebouwen, waarbij elementaire schade wordt gedekt, zoals: brand, diefstal, overstromingen en soortgelijke schade.</P><P>De contractant is verantwoordelijk voor het oplossen van problemen met betrekking tot alle technische diensten, inclusief stroomvoorziening, watervoorziening, riolering, afvalverwerking en ventilatie, alsmede voor de onmiddellijke reparatie van gerelateerde schade die niet aan EASO te wijten valt.</P><P>Schoonmaakdiensten worden als volgt aangeboden:</P><P>Dagelijks uit te voeren taken:</P><P>- legen van afvalmanden, vervangen van plastic vuilniszakken (waar nodig) en het verwijderen van afval naar de gemeenschappelijke containers,</P><P>- stoffen en nat afvegen van alle blootgestelde oppervlakken,</P><P>- reinigen en vegen van wandtegels en vloeren,</P><P>- reinigen, vegen en desinfecteren van de toiletruimtes, inclusief toiletten, gootstenen/wastafels en de ruimtes voorzien van toiletpapier, papieren handdoeken en andere benodigdheden,</P><P>- reinigen, vegen en desinfecteren van de keuken, inclusief de gootsteen en overige oppervlakken en voorzien van papieren handdoeken en andere benodigdheden.</P><P>Maandelijks uit te voeren taken:</P><P>- grondig reinigen en desinfecteren van de toiletten,</P><P>- stoffen en reinigen van verwarmings-/koelingseenheden,</P><P>- reinigen van glas op binnendeuren en/of scheidingswanden.</P><P>Per kwartaal uit te voeren taken:</P><P>- reinigen van alle ramen en glas op buitendeuren, indien aanwezig,</P><P>- reinigen van alle gordijnen en jaloezieën, indien aanwezig.</P><P>3.2 Termijnen</P><P>De kantoorruimtes moeten in april 2018 beschikbaar worden gesteld.</P><P>3.3 Procedure:</P><P>De onderhavige marktonderzoeksprocedure wordt afgesloten met een voorselectie van maximaal 3 aanvragers wiens kantoorruimtes het toelaten aan de behoeften te beantwoorden. EASO kan de aldus voorgeselecteerde aanvrager(s) uitnodigen om de onderhandelingen aan te vangen in een latere afzonderlijke fase van onderhavige procedure. De gedetailleerde technische specificaties worden aan de voorgeselecteerde aanvrager(s) gestuurd. De uitgenodigde aanvrager(s) worden op de hoogte gebracht van de vereiste inhoud van de</P><P>voorstellen en de te verstrekken documenten. Bij de indiening van het voorstel garandeert elke voorgeselecteerde aanvrager:</P><P>— de geldigheid van zijn voorstel tot de eventuele ondertekening van het contract,</P><P>— de terbeschikkingstelling van elk document betreffende het pand binnen de termijnen die EASO opgeeft.</P><P>Onderhavige bekendmaking houdt voor EASO geen enkele verplichting in wat gunningsprocedures voor opdrachten betreft. EASO behoudt zich het recht voor om tot de ondertekening van het contract af te zien van de opdracht of onderhavige procedure te annuleren zonder dat de aanvragers aanspraak kunnen maken op enige schadeloosstelling. EASO zal vóór of tijdens de onderhandelingsfase geen enkel exclusiviteitscontract noch enige soortgelijke clausule ten gunste van een bepaalde aanvrager tekenen.</P><P>3.4 Aard van de opdracht</P><P>De maximale duur van de huurovereenkomst is 10 maanden. Deze kan maximaal driemaal worden verlengd voor een extra periode van 12 maanden per keer voor een totale periode van 3 jaar en 10 maanden.</P><P>De huurovereenkomst dekt de huurkosten en aanverwante diensten. EASO kan de huurovereenkomst en aanverwante diensten met inachtneming van een opzegtermijn van 1 maand opzeggen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vereisten deelnemingsaanvragen conform de onderhandelingsprocedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Inhoud</P><P>De informatie in de deelnemingsaanvragen moet worden ingediend met behulp van de volgende formulieren:</P><P>1) Een gedateerd en ondertekend identificatie- en verklaringsformulier (met vermelding van de gegevens van de aanvrager, gegevens van de eigenaar indien afwijkend; volledig adres van de kantoorruimtes; bevestiging dat de minimaal vereiste diensten worden verleend). Het formulier is beschikbaar op: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Beschrijving van de oppervlakten; tekeningen (verdiepingen, gevels, doorsneden) en plannen met een type-indeling (in geval van twijfel kunnen er worden verzocht om plannen met een schaal van 1:50 of 1:100 of 1:200);</P><P>4.2 Indienen van deelnemingsaanvragen conform de onderhandelingsprocedure</P><P>Deelnemingsaanvragen conform de onderhandelingsprocedure moeten vergezeld zijn van de vereiste informatie benoemd in punt 4.1 hierboven en dienen per e-mail te worden verstuurd aan contracts@easo.europa.eu vóór 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beoordeling van voorstellen in de tweede fase (onderhandelingsprocedure):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ontvangen voorstellen van de voorgeselecteerde aanvrager(s) die niet conform zijn en/of de zone van het onderzoek en/of de gewenste oppervlakte zoals vermeld in punt 3 van deze aankondiging niet naleven, zullen worden verworpen. De aanbieders van kantoorruimtes die worden uitgesloten, worden hiervan op de hoogte gebracht.</P><P>De voorstellen die in aanmerking komen, worden geanalyseerd op basis van de criteria kwaliteit en prijs overeenkomstig de volgende weging:</P><P>- prijs (40 %),</P><P>- kwaliteit (60 %).</P><P>De kwaliteit (K) van de inschrijving wordt vastgesteld op basis van de volgende elementen (100 punten):</P><P>- fysieke nabijheid van het gebouw dat wordt bewoond door de Cypriotische asieldienst (ref. 3.1., eerste lid): 55 punten (vereist minimum: 35),</P><P>- verdeling van de ruimte in het pand - verdeling van kantoorruimte, wachtruimte en uitbreidingsmogelijkheden van de kantoorruimtes worden geëvalueerd: 30 punten (vereist minimum: 18),</P><P>- beveiligings- en veiligheidsmaatregelen in de gebouwen (naast de minimumvereisten onder punt II): de aanwezigheid van fysieke beveiliging (bewakers), installatie van brandblussers, aanwezige nooduitgangen en evacuatieplannen, enz. worden geëvalueerd: 15 punten (vereist minimum: 7).</P><P>Er wordt een rangschikking van de inschrijvingen opgesteld op basis van een eindscore (E) overeenkomstig de volgende formule:</P><P>E = (60 % x K) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contacten en aanvullende inlichtingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aanvragers worden op de hoogte gebracht van hun voorselectie of het besluit om niet te worden uitgenodigd voor de onderhandelingsprocedure. Elk contact tussen de aanvragers en EASO is verboden, behalve waar verduidelijking nodig is inzake de aankondiging van een onderzoek van de vastgoedmarkt. Het verzoek om verduidelijking moet schriftelijk verstuurd worden naar contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Anúncio de prospeção de imóveis para suprir as necessidades em matéria de espaços de escritórios do Gabinete Europeu de Apoio em matéria de Asilo</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Agência UE responsável</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Gabinete Europeu de Apoio em Matéria de Asilo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Objeto da prospeção:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O Gabinete Europeu de Apoio em Matéria de Asilo (EASO) fornece apoio ao Chipre no quadro de um plano de apoio especial assinado com o Governo do Chipre. No quadro do plano supracitado, a Agência destaca o seu pessoal, bem como peritos e intérpretes, para fornecer apoio em medidas específicas. Para assegurar o espaço de trabalho para o pessoal, peritos e intérpretes, o EASO pretende arrendar instalações/espaço de escritório em conformidade com os requisitos mínimos abaixo, e serviços de limpeza auxiliares.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição do contrato e do processo aplicável</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Requisitos mínimos</P><P>O EASO pretende arrendar espaço de escritório localizado nas instalações ocupadas pelo Serviço de Asilo Cipriota em 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Chipre ou num edifício adjacente.</P><P>As instalações devem estar acessíveis ao pessoal da EASO, peritos e intérpretes desde as 7:00 às 22:00 todos os dias da semana.</P><P>A Agência requer um espaço de escritório/instalações acima do solo com um mínimo de 250 e um máximo de 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>As instalações/espaço de escritório deve ser adequado para acomodar:</P><P>— 7 escritórios/salas de entrevista — a serem utilizadas como salas de entrevista - para alojar 3-4 pessoas de cada vez,</P><P>— 1 escritório para intérpretes — para ser utilizado como sala de reuniões/espera para intérpretes e também para os intérpretes trabalharem separadamente, se necessário (traduções, anúncios a candidatos, etc.) — para alojar 6-8 pessoas de cada vez,</P><P>— 1 escritório de operações — a ser utilizado como escritório para o coordenador da EASO e assistente(s) de operações e ter espaço de escritório suficiente para armários de arquivo para gestão de arquivos (ficheiros de casos agendados, ficheiros a aguardar pareceres, etc.) — para alojar 3 pessoas de cada vez e fornecer espaço de escritório suficiente para armários de arquivo, adicionalmente às estações de trabalho,</P><P>— 1 cozinha com instalações apropriadas (balcão, armários, lava-loiça),</P><P>— 2 instalações sanitárias — 1 para pessoal e 1 para candidatos,</P><P>— 1 espaço multiusos — para ser utilizado também como sala da impressora, sala de reuniões, área de espera para candidatos durante intervalos ou consoante necessário — para alojar um mínimo de 15-16 pessoas de cada vez,</P><P>— 1 espaço para armazenamento.</P><P>Os escritórios devem ter espaço suficiente para serem equipados com estações de trabalho, onde necessário (mobiliário e equipamento TIC).</P><P>Caso não estejam disponíveis/não sejam oferecidos guarda(s) de segurança permanentes, o EASO poderá dispor dos seus próprios guardas de segurança e instalar os sistemas de controlo de segurança necessários. Adicionalmente, caso um serviço de receção não esteja disponível, o EASO poderá dispor do seu próprio pessoal de receção e montar instalações adequadas com o mobiliário e equipamento necessário. Para esse fim, o espaço necessário ao nível térreo/entrada será disponibilizado pelo contratante, adicionalmente ao espaço de escritório requerido e indicado acima.</P><P>Todo o edifício deverá estar coberto por um sistema de deteção de incêndio (detetores de fumo e calor, painéis de incêndio). É necessária uma saída de evacuação dedicada em cada piso.</P><P>Devem estar implementados fornecimento e ponto de eletricidade, fornecimento de água quente e fria, aquecimento/refrigeração/ar condicionado, ligações a esgotos devidamente ligados aos serviços municipais/públicos.</P><P>Caso o EASO necessite de realizar adaptações estruturais, os documentos de apoio necessários para adquirir as licenças requeridas para empreitadas de obras e acordo de todos os proprietários do edifício, quando necessários, devem ser disponibilizados pelo contratante.</P><P>O EASO deverá, com o acordo do contratante, ser autorizado a realizar adaptações não-estruturais, a expensas próprias, de forma a instalar itens ou realizar pequenas melhorias nas instalações.</P><P>O contratante será responsável pelo seguro do edifício, para cobertura de danos básicos tais como incêndio, roubo, inundação e danos similares, ao longo da duração do arrendamento.</P><P>O contratante será responsável pela resolução de quaisquer problemas que possam surgir quanto a todos os serviço técnicos, incluindo abastecimento de energia, abastecimento de água, esgotos, eliminação de ruídos e ventilação, bem como a reparação imediata de danos conexos não atribuíveis ao EASO.</P><P>Os serviços de limpeza serão fornecidos da seguinte forma:</P><P>Tarefas a serem executadas diariamente:</P><P>— Esvaziar cestos do lixo, substituição de sacos plásticos, se necessário e remoção de resíduos para os contentores comunitários,</P><P>— Limpeza do pó e passagem de pano húmido em todas as superfícies expostas,</P><P>— Limpeza e varrimento de piso e azulejos,</P><P>— Limpeza, varrimento e desinfeção das instalações sanitárias, incluindo sanitas, lavatórios, colocação de papel higiénico, toalhas de papel e outros fornecimentos necessários,</P><P>— Limpeza, varrimento e desinfeção da cozinha, incluindo o lava-loiça e todas as superfícies, colocação de toalhas de papel e outros fornecimentos necessários.</P><P>Tarefas a serem executadas uma vez por mês:</P><P>— Limpeza a fundo e desinfeção das instalações sanitárias,</P><P>— Limpeza do pó e limpeza de unidades de aquecimento/refrigeração,</P><P>— Limpeza de todos os vidros em portas e/ou divisórias internas.</P><P>Tarefas a serem executadas uma vez a cada três (3) meses:</P><P>— Limpeza de todas as janelas e vidro em portas externas, caso existam,</P><P>— Limpeza de cortinas e persianas, caso existam.</P><P>3.2 Prazos</P><P>As instalações estarão disponíveis em abril de 2018.</P><P>3.3 Procedimento</P><P>O presente processo de prospeção será concluído por uma pré-seleção de 3 candidatos, no máximo, cujas instalações permitam satisfazer as necessidades. O EASO irá convidar o(s) candidato(s) pré-selecionados para entrarem em negociações numa fase subsequente distinta deste procedimento. As especificações técnicas pormenorizadas serão enviadas ao(s) candidato(s) pré-selecionado(s). O(s) candidato(s) convidado(s) será(ão) informado(s) sobre o conteúdo das</P><P>propostas e documentos a serem fornecidos. Com a apresentação da proposta, cada candidato pré-selecionado deve garantir:</P><P>— a validade da sua proposta até à eventual assinatura do contrato,</P><P>— a disponibilização de qualquer documento relativo às instalações dentro dos prazos estipulados pelo EASO.</P><P>O presente anúncio não é de qualquer maneira vinculativo para o EASO quanto aos procedimentos de adjudicação do contrato. O EASO reserva-se o direito, até à assinatura do contrato, de renunciar ao contrato ou de anular o presente concurso sem que os proponentes possam exigir qualquer indemnização. O EASO não assinará, antes ou durante a fase de negociações, qualquer contrato de exclusividade nem qualquer cláusula semelhante a favor de um candidato.</P><P>3.4 Tipo de contrato</P><P>A duração máxima do contrato de arrendamento será de dez (10) meses, com a possibilidade de prorrogação por 3 vezes para uma duração adicional de 12 meses/cada por uma duração total de 3 anos e 10 meses.</P><P>O contrato de arrendamento deverá abranger os custos da locação e os serviços auxiliares. O EASO deverá poder cancelar o contrato de arrendamento e serviços auxiliares com o prazo de um mês de antecedência.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Requisitos referentes a pedidos de participação no processo por negociação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Conteúdo</P><P>A informação contida no pedido de participação deve ser apresentada utilizando os formulários seguintes:</P><P>1) Formulário de identificação e declaração devidamente datado e assinado (indicando os dados do candidato; pormenores sobre o proprietário – se diferente; endereço completo das instalações; confirmação de que o mínimo requerido de serviços será fornecido). O formulário está disponível em: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Descrição das áreas de superfície; desenhos (pisos, fachadas, cortes) e planos ilustrando uma disposição padrão (em caso de dúvida, podem ser solicitados desenhos à escala de 1/50 ou 1/100 ou 1/200);</P><P>4.2 Apresentação de pedidos para participação no processo por negociação</P><P>Os pedidos para participação, no processo por negociação, acompanhados pela informação requerida no ponto 4.1, devem ser enviados por correio eletrónico para contracts@easo.europa.eu até 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaliação das propostas na segunda fase (processo por negociação):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>As propostas recebidas do(s) candidato(s) pré-selecionados não conformes e/ou que não respeitem o perímetro de prospeção e/ou a superfície desejada, tais como mencionados no ponto 3 deste anúncio, serão excluídas. Os candidatos de instalações excluídas serão devidamente informados.</P><P>As propostas elegíveis serão analisadas com base em critérios de qualidade e preço, de acordo com a ponderação seguinte:</P><P>— preço (40%),</P><P>— qualidade (60%).</P><P>A qualidade (Q) da proposta será estabelecida com base nos elementos seguintes (100 pontos):</P><P>— Proximidade física ao edifício ocupado pelo Serviço Cipriota de Asilo (referência 3.1., primeiro ponto): 55 pontos (mínimo requerido: 35),</P><P>— Distribuição do espaço nas instalações - a distribuição do espaço, área de espera e possibilidade de expansão dos escritórios serão avaliadas: 30 pontos (mínimo requerido: 18),</P><P>— Medidas de proteção e segurança nas instalações (adicionalmente aos requisitos mínimos indicados no ponto II.) – a presença de segurança física (guardas), instalações de extintores de incêndio, saídas de emergência e planos de evacuação, etc. implementados serão avaliados: 15 pontos (mínimo requerido: 7).</P><P>A classificação das propostas será baseada numa pontuação final (F) de acordo com a seguinte fórmula:</P><P>F = (60% x Q) + (40% x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contactos e informações adicionais:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Os candidatos serão informados da sua pré-seleção ou da decisão de não serem convidados para o processo por negociação. Qualquer contacto entre os candidatos e o EASO é proibido, salvo quando seja necessário fornecer clarificações quanto ao anúncio de prospeção imobiliário. O pedido de clarificações deverá ser realizado por escrito para contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Meddelande om sökande efter fastigheter för att tillgodose behovet av kontorsytor för Europeiska stödkontoret för asylfrågor</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>EU Agency responsible</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska stödkontoret för asylfrågor</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>”MTC Block A”, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlingens föremål:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeiska stödkontoret för asylfrågor (EASO) tillhandahåller stöd till Cypern i ramverket för en Särskild stödplan, som har avtalats med Cyperns regering. I ramverket för planen placerar kontoret ut sin personal, liksom även experter och tolkar för att bistå med specifika åtgärder. För att garantera arbetsutrymmet för personal, experter och tolkar söker EASO leasa fastigheter/kontorsutrymmen i enlighet med nedan nämnda minimikrav, samt underordnad städtjänst.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivning av upphandlingen och av förfarandet som tillämpas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Minimikrav</P><P>EASO söker leasa kontorsutrymme i lokalerna, där Cypriot Asylum Service är inhysta på 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Cypern eller i en angränsande byggnad.</P><P>Lokalerna ska vara tillgängliga för EASO-personal, experter och tolkar från kl. 7:00 till 22:00 alla veckodagar.</P><P>Byrån kräver en uppskattad anläggning/kontorsrymd ovan jord på minst 250 till högst 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Faciliteter/kontorsutrymme ska passa för att inhysa:</P><P>- 7 kontor/intervjurum - att användas som intervjurum - för att ta emot 3-4 personer samtidigt,</P><P>- 1 kontor för tolkar - att användas som mötes-/väntrum för tolkar och även för tolkar för att arbeta separat om så behövs (översättningar, samtal med sökande, etc) - att ta emot 6-8 personer samtidigt,</P><P>- 1 verksamhetskontor - att användas som kontor för EASO:s samordnare och assistent(er) och ha tillräckligt med utrymme för dokumentskåp för dokumenthantering (dokument för kommande ärenden, dokument som väntar på beslut, etc) - att ta emot 3 personer samtidigt och tillhandahålla tillräckligt kontorsutrymme för dokumentskåp, utöver arbetsstationerna,</P><P>- 1 kök med tillhörande faciliteter (arbetsbänk, skåp, diskbänk),</P><P>- 2 damrum/toaletter - 1 för personal och 1 för sökande,</P><P>- 1 allrum - att användas också som skrivarrum, mötesrum, vänteområde för sökande under rast eller vid behov - att ta emot minst 15-16 personer samtidigt,</P><P>- 1 lagerrum.</P><P>Kontoren måste vara tillräckligt rymliga för att utrustas med arbetsstationer där så krävs (möbler och IKT-utrustning).</P><P>Om säkerhetsvakt(er) inte ställs till förfogande/erbjuds, ska EASO tillåtas ha egna säkerhetsvakter och installera erforderliga system för säkerhetskontroll. Därutöver kommer EASO, om receptionstjänst inte ställs till förfogande, att tillåtas ha sin egen receptionspersonal och att inrätta fullgoda faciliteter med erforderlig inredning och utrustning. För detta ändamål ska entreprenören ställa nödvändigt utrymme på mark/entré-nivå till förfogande, utöver erforderligt kontorsutrymme enligt lista ovan.</P><P>Hela byggnaden ska täckas av ett integrerat brandvarningssystem (rök och värmedetektorer, kontrollpaneler för brand). Tydliga utrymningsskyltar på varje plan krävs.</P><P>Elanslutning och uttag, varmt och kallt vatten, värme/kyla/ luftkonditionering, avlopp ska vara på plats och ansluten till kommunal/offentlig tjänst.</P><P>I händelse av att EASO behöver utföra strukturella anpassningar, ska entreprenören ställa nödvändiga dokument till förfogande för att erhålla de tillstånd, som behövs för byggnadsarbete, samt samtycke med alla fastighetsägare.</P><P>EASO ska i överenskommelse med entreprenören ha tillåtelse att utföra icke-strukturella anpassningar på egen bekostnad för installation av utrustning eller för att göra förbättringar i lokalerna.</P><P>Entreprenören ska vara försäkringsansvarig för byggnaderna, med täckning för primära skador såsom brand, stöld, vattenskador och liknande under leasingperiodens löptid.</P><P>Entreprenören har ansvar för att lösa eventuella problem, som kan uppkomma i samband med all teknisk service, inbegripet strömförsörjning, vattenförsörjning, avlopp, avfallshantering och ventilation, liksom också omedelbar reparation, som har att göra med skador, som inte kan tillskrivas EASO.</P><P>Städtjänster ska tillhandahållas enligt följande:</P><P>Uppgifter som utförs på daglig basis:</P><P>- Tömning av papperskorgar, byte av plastinsatser vid behov och sophämtning till kommunala containrar,</P><P>- Alla exponerade ytor ska dammas och våttorkas,</P><P>- Rengöring och sopning av golv och väggkakel,</P><P>- Städning, sopning och desinficering av toaletter inbegripet toalettstolarna, diskbänk/handfat, utplacering av toalettpapper, pappershanddukar och andra nödvändiga artiklar,</P><P>- Rengöring, sopning och desinficering av kök, inbegripet slask och alla ytor, utplacering av pappershanddukar och andra nödvändiga artiklar.</P><P>Uppgifter som utförs en gång per månad:</P><P>- Grundlig rengöring och desinficering av toaletter,</P><P>- Dammtorkning och rengöring av värme/kylenheter,</P><P>- Rengöring av allt glas på innerdörrar och/eller skiljeväggar.</P><P>Uppgifter som utförs en gång per kvartal:</P><P>- Rengöring av alla fönster och eventuella glas på ytterdörrar,</P><P>- Rengöring av gardiner och persienner, om sådana finns.</P><P>3.2 Frister</P><P>Lokalerna ska vara tillgängliga i april 2018.</P><P>3.3 Förfarande</P><P>Sökningsförfarandet kommer att avslutas med en förhandsuttagning av upp till 3 sökande vars lokaler gör det möjligt att uppfylla kraven. EASO kommer att bjuda in förhandsuttagna sökande att inleda förhandlingar i en efterföljande etapp åtskild från detta förfarande. Utförliga tekniska specifikationer kommer att sändas till de förhandsuttagna sökande. Inbjuden/inbjudna sökande kommer att informeras om vilket innehåll som krävs i</P><P>De förslag och handlingar som ska tillhandahållas. Varje förhandsuttagen sökande ska tillsammans med inlämning av förslag, försäkra:</P><P>- att dennes förslag kommer att vara giltigt fram till undertecknandet av kontraktet,</P><P>- att alla handlingar rörande fastighetsområdet kommer att tillhandahållas inom de tidsfrister, som anges av EASO.</P><P>Detta meddelande är inte på något sätt bindande för EASO med avseende på tilldelningsförfaranden av kontrakt. EASO förbehåller sig rätten att, fram till att kontraktet undertecknats, avsäga sig eller att annullera föreliggande förfarande utan att detta ger de sökande rätt att begära någon som helst ersättning. EASO kommer inte att, före eller under förhandlingsetappen, underteckna något exklusivt kontrakt eller någon liknande klausul till förmån för någon sökande.</P><P>3.4 Typ av kontrakt</P><P>Total högsta löptid för leasingavtalet kommer att vara tio (10) månader, med möjlighet till förlängning 3 gånger, med ytterligare löptid för varje på 12 månader, för en total löptid på 3 år och 10 månader.</P><P>Leasingavtalet ska täcka leasingkostnader och underordnade tjänster. EASO ska kunna säga upp leasingavtalet och underordnade tjänster med en månads varsel.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Krav i samband med ansökan om deltagande i det förhandlade förfarandet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Innehåll</P><P>Informationen i anbudsansökan måste lämnas under följande former:</P><P>1) Identifierings- och anmälningsformulär vederbörligen daterat och undertecknat (med uppgift om detaljer avseende sökanden; detaljer avseende ägaren - om ej samma person; lokalens fullständiga adress; bekräftelse om att det minimum av tjänster som erfordras kommer att tillhandahållas). Formuläret finns tillgängligt på: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Beskrivning av ytans områden; ritningar (våningar, fasader, tvärsnitt) och planritningar som uppvisar standardplanlösning (i tveksamma fall kommer ritningar i skala 1/50 eller 1/100 eller 1/200 att begäras);</P><P>4.2 Inlämning av ansökan om deltagande i det förhandlade förfarandet</P><P>Ansökan om deltagande i det förhandlade förfarandet, tillsammans med erforderlig information under punkt 4.1, ska sändas med e-post till contracts@easo.europa.eu före den 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bedömning av förslag i den andra etappen (förhandlat förfarande)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Förslag mottagna från de förhandsuttagna sökande, som inte uppfyller kriterierna och/eller inte stämmer överens med det eftersökta området och/eller den eftersökta ytan, enligt vad som anges i punkterna 3 i detta meddelande, kommer att förkastas. Uteslutna sökande avseende lokaler kommer att vederbörligen informeras.</P><P>Behöriga förslag kommer att analyseras på basis av kvalitets- och priskriterier i enlighet med följande viktningar:</P><P>- pris (40 %),</P><P>- Kvalitet (60 %).</P><P>Anbudets kvalitet (Q) kommer att fastställas på basis av följande element (100 poäng):</P><P>- Fysisk närhet till byggnaden som innehas av Cypriotiska  Asyltjänsten (ref. 3.1., första paragrafen): 55 poäng (lägsta krav: 35),</P><P>- Fördelning av utrymme i lokalerna - fördelning av kontorsutrymme, väntrum och möjlighet till utvidgning av kontoren kommer att bedömas: 30 poäng (lägsta krav: 18),</P><P>- säkerhetsåtgärder i lokalerna (utöver lägsta krav som anvisas i punkt II) - närvaro av fysisk säkerhet (vakter), installerade brandsläckare, nödutgångar och evakueringsplan, etc. på plats kommer att bedömas: 15 poäng (lägsta krav: 7).</P><P>Klassificering kommer att baseras på ett slutresultat (final score - F) i enlighet med följande formel:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontakter och ytterligare upplysningar:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sökande kommer att informeras om de är förhandsuttagna eller ej till det förhandlade förfarandet. All kontakt mellan sökande och EASO är förbjuden, utom där förtydliganden behövs gällande meddelandet om fastighetsundersökning. Begäran om förtydligande ska ske skriftligen till contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Oznámení o vyhledávání nemovitosti, která bude splňovat požadavky na kancelářské prostory Evropského podpůrného úřadu pro otázky azylu</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zodpovědná agentura EU</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropský podpůrný úřad pro otázky azylu</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Předmět vyhledávání:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Evropský podpůrný úřad pro otázky azylu (EASO) poskytne podporu Kypru v rámci speciálního podpůrného plánu podepsaného s vládou Kypru. V rámci plánu nasadí agentura své zaměstnance, odborníky a tlumočníky na podporu specifických opatření. EASO hledá v rámci zajištění pracovních prostor pro své zaměstnance, odborníky a tlumočníky pronájem zařízení/kancelářské prostory v souladu s minimálními požadavky níže, a také pomocné úklidové služby.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popis zakázky a řízení, které bude použito</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Minimální požadavky</P><P>EASO hledá kancelářské prostory k pronájmu využívané kyperským azylovým úřadem na adrese 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Kypr, nebo v přilehlé budově.</P><P>Prostory budou přístupné zaměstnancům EASO, odborníkům a tlumočníkům od 7:00 do 22:00 každý den v týdnu.</P><P>Agentura požaduje nadzemní povrchovou plochu zařízení/kancelářských prostor odhadem o rozměrech minimálně 250 a maximálně 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Zařízení/kancelářské prostory by měly být schopny umístit:</P><P>– 7 kanceláří / místností pro pohovory – které budou sloužit jako místnosti pro pohovory – a pojmou 3-4 osoby najednou,</P><P>– 1 kancelář pro tlumočníky – která bude sloužit jako zasedací místnost / čekárna pro tlumočníky a také pro jejich potřebu pracovat samostatně (překládání, telefonáty s uchazeči apod.) – a pojme 6-8 osob najednou,</P><P>– 1 operační kancelář – která bude sloužit jako kancelář pro koordinátora EASO a operační asistenty a bude mít dostatečný kancelářský prostor pro kartotéku a správu dokumentace (soubory zadaných případů, soubory čekající na vyjádření, apod.) – a která bude schopna pojmout 3 osoby najednou a poskytnout kromě pracovních stanic i dostatečný prostor pro kartotéku,</P><P>– 1 kuchyň s potřebným zařízením (pult, skříňky, dřez),</P><P>– 2 místnosti s toaletou – 1 pro zaměstnance a 1 pro uchazeče,</P><P>– 1 multifunkční místnost – která bude mimo jiné sloužit jako místnost pro tisk, zasedací místnost, čekárna pro uchazeče během přestávek – a která pojme minimálně 15-16 osob najednou,</P><P>– 1 skladovací místnost.</P><P>Kanceláře musí mít dostatečný prostor, aby se do nich v případě potřeby vešly pracovní stanice (nábytek a vybavení informačních a komunikačních technologií).</P><P>Pokud nebude zajištěna/nabízena stálá ostraha, bude úřadu EASO povoleno obstarat si svou vlastní ostrahu a instalovat bezpečnostní kontrolní systémy. Kromě toho, pokud nebudou zajištěny služby recepce, bude úřadu EASO povoleno obstarat si své vlastní zaměstnance recepce a adekvátně vybavit prostor potřebným nábytkem a vybavením. V tomto smyslu by měl být kromě výše uvedených kancelářských prostor zhotovitelem zpřístupněn potřebný prostor v přízemí / u vchodu.</P><P>Celá budova bude vybavena integrovaným systémem pro detekci požáru (kouřové a teplotní detektory, protipožární panely). Vyžaduje se vyhrazený únikový východ na každém patře.</P><P>Elektrická přípojka a rozvody, přípojka na teplou a studenou vodu, topení/chlazení/klimatizace a přípojky kanalizace by měly být zavedeny a napojeny na veřejnou síť městských služeb.</P><P>V případě, že EASO bude potřebovat provést stavební úpravy, bude mu zhotovitelem zpřístupněna podpůrná dokumentace k získání potřebných povolení ke stavebním pracím, jakož i případný souhlas stavebních vlastníků.</P><P>EASO bude po dohodě se zhotovitelem moci provádět na své náklady drobné stavební úpravy za účelem instalace zařízení či drobných vylepšení prostor.</P><P>Zhotovitel bude po celou dobu trvání nájmu zodpovědný za pojištění budov na pokrytí základních škod jako požár, krádež, povodně a podobné škody.</P><P>Zhotovitel bude zodpovědný za řešení jakýchkoliv problémů, které se budou týkat technických služeb, včetně elektřiny, vody, kanalizace, likvidace odpadu a odvětrávání, jakož i okamžité opravy škod, které nelze přičíst EASO.</P><P>Úklidové služby budou poskytovány následovně:</P><P>Úkoly prováděné denně:</P><P>– vyprazdňování košů na odpadky, výměna plastových sáčků (v případě potřeby) a vynášení odpadků do komunálního odpadu,</P><P>– stírání prachu a čištění nekrytých povrchů,</P><P>– mytí a zametání podlah a dlaždic na stěnách,</P><P>– mytí, zametání a dezinfekce sociálních zařízení, včetně záchodů, umyvadel, výměna toaletního papíru, ručníků a ostatních potřebných zásob,</P><P>– čištění, zametání a dezinfekce kuchyňské místnosti, včetně dřezu a všech povrchů, výměna papírových utěrek a ostatních potřebných zásob.</P><P>Úkoly prováděné měsíčně:</P><P>– hloubkové čištění a dezinfekce toalet,</P><P>– utírání prachu a čištění jednotek topení/klimatizace,</P><P>– čištění všech skleněných ploch na dveřích a/nebo příčkách.</P><P>Úkoly prováděné každé 3 měsíce:</P><P>– mytí všech oken a skleněných ploch na venkovních dveřích,</P><P>– čištění žaluzií a záclon.</P><P>3.2 Lhůty</P><P>Prostory musí být k dispozici v dubnu 2018.</P><P>3.3 Řízení</P><P>Toto vyhledávání nemovitosti bude uzavřeno předběžným výběrem až 3 uchazečů, jejichž prostory umožní splnění daných požadavků. EASO vyzve předběžně zvolené uchazeče k jednání v další fázi, která ovšem nebude součástí tohoto řízení. Podrobné technické specifikace budou zaslány předběžně zvoleným uchazečům. Pozvaní uchazeči budou informováni o požadovaném obsahu</P><P>návrhů a podaných dokumentů. Podáním návrhu každý předběžně zvolený uchazeč garantuje:</P><P>— že jeho návrh zůstane v platnosti až do podepsání případné smlouvy,</P><P>— že jakýkoli dokument týkající se budovy bude poskytnut v termínech stanovených EASO.</P><P>Pokud jde o řízení pro udělení zakázky, není toto oznámení žádným způsobem pro EASO závazné. Kdykoliv v průběhu období před podpisem smlouvy si EASO vyhrazuje právo upustit od tohoto řízení, nebo ho zrušit, aniž by měli uchazeči nárok na jakoukoliv kompenzaci. Před fází vyjednávání nebo v jejím průběhu nepodepíše EASO ve prospěch uchazeče žádné smlouvy o výlučných právech nebo podobná ustanovení.</P><P>3.4 Druh zakázky</P><P>Celková maximální doba trvání nájemní smlouvy bude deset (10) měsíců, s možností prodloužení 3krát pokaždé na dobu 12 měsíců, tzn. celková doba trvání 3 roky a 10 měsíců.</P><P>Nájemní smlouva pokryje náklady na pronájem a podpůrné služby. EASO bude moci vypovědět nájemní smlouvu a podpůrné služby s 1měsíční výpovědní lhůtou.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Požadavky týkající se žádosti o účast v jednacím řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Obsah</P><P>Informace obsažené v žádosti o účast musí být podány v následující formě:</P><P>1) Identifikační formulář a formulář prohlášení musí být řádně podepsané a datované (včetně údajů o žadateli; případně údajů o vlastníkovi, pokud je jiný než žadatel; celá adresa prostor; potvrzení, že budou poskytovány minimální požadavky). Formulář je k dispozici na: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/</P><P>Zásobování</P><P>2) Popis podlahových ploch, výkresy (podlahy, fasády, průřezy) a stavební plány zobrazující standardní rozvržení (v případě pochybností mohou být vyžadovány výkresy v měřítku 1:50, 1:100 či 1:200);</P><P>4.2 Podání požadavků týkajících se žádosti o účast v jednacím řízení</P><P>Požadavky týkající se žádosti o účast spolu s požadovanými informacemi dle bodu 4.1 musí být zaslány elektronickou poštou na contracts@easo.europa.eu do 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hodnocení návrhů ve druhé fázi (jednací řízení):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Návrhy obdržené od předem vybraných uchazečů, které nebudou splňovat a/nebo nedodrží oblast výzkumu a/nebo požadovanou povrchovou plochu dle ustanovení bodu 3 tohoto oznámení, budou vyřazeny. Uchazeči vyloučených prostor budou řádně informováni.</P><P>Způsobilé návrhy budou analyzovány na základě kritérií kvality a ceny, která mají tyto váhy:</P><P>– cena (40 %),</P><P>– kvalita (60 %).</P><P>Kvalita nabídky (Q) bude stanovena na základě následujících prvků (100 bodů):</P><P>– fyzická vzdálenost do budovy využívané kyperským azylovým úřadem (ref. 3.1., první odstavec): 55 bodů (požadované minimum: 35),</P><P>– rozložení prostor v budově – rozložení kancelářských prostor, čekárny a možnost rozšíření kanceláří bude přiděleno: 30 bodů (požadované minimum: 18),</P><P>– bezpečnostní a ochranná opatření v budově (kromě minimálních požadavků uvedených v bodě II.) – přítomnost fyzické ostrahy (stráže), umístění hasicích přístrojů, únikové východy a evakuační plány apod. bude přiděleno: 15 bodů (požadované minimum: 7).</P><P>Klasifikace nabídek bude vycházet z konečného počtu bodů (F) v souladu s následujícím vzorcem:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontakty a další informace:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uchazeči budou informování o svém předvýběru nebo rozhodnutí o nepřizvání k jednacímu řízení. Jakýkoliv kontakt mezi uchazeči a EASO je zakázán, s výjimkou případů, kdy bude potřeba podat vysvětlení vztahující se k oznámení o vyhledávání nemovitostí. Žádost o vysvětlení musí být zaslána písemně na contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Euroopa Varjupaigaküsimuste Tugiameti vajatava büroopinna leidmiseks kinnisvaraturu uurimise teade</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>ELi vastutav talitus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Varjupaigaküsimuste Tugiamet</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Otsingu eesmärk:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopa Varjupaigaküsimuste Tugiamet (EASO) osutab Küprose Vabariigiga allkirjastatud spetsiaalse toetusplaani raamistikus abi Küprosele. Talitus paigutab eelnimetatud plaani raamistikus kohale oma personali, samuti eksperte ja tõlke, et osutada tuge erimeetmete läbiviimisel. EASO sovib võtta personalile, ekspertidele ja tõlkidele tööruumide tagamiseks üürile rajatisi/büroopinda, kooskõlas allpool esitatud miinimumnõuetega, ja toetavaid puhastusteenuseid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu ja rakendatava menetluse kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Miinimumnõuded</P><P>EASO loodab üürida büroopinda Küprose asüüliteenistuse valduses olevates ruumides (70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Küpros) või lähedalasuvas hoones.</P><P>Ruumid peaksid olema EASO personalile, ekspertidele ja tõlkidele juurdepääsetavad igal nädalapäeval kell 7:00–22:00.</P><P>Talitus vajab hinnanguliselt minimaalselt 250 m{^&gt;2 &lt;^}kuni maksimaalselt 320 m{^&gt;2 &lt;^}maapealset rajatise / büroo pinda.</P><P>Rajatise / büroo pind peaks olema sobiv, et mahutada järgmist:</P><P>– 7 ametiruumi/küsitlusruumi – kasutamiseks küsitlusruumidena – korraga 3–4 inimese mahutamiseks,</P><P>– 1 ametiruum tõlkidele – kasutamiseks koosolekuruumi/ooteruumina tõlkidele ja ka tõlkidele eraldi töötamiseks, vajaduse korral (tõlked, telefonikõned taotlejatega jne) – korraga 6–8 inimese mahutamiseks,</P><P>– 1 talitlusruum – kasutamiseks ametiruumina EASO koordinaatorile ja juhi abi(de)le ning toimikute haldamiseks peab selles olema piisavalt ruumi toimikukappidele (plaaniliste juhtumite toimikud, arvamuste ootel toimikud jne) – korraga 3 inimese mahutamiseks ja tagades piisavalt büroopinda toimikukappidele ja ka tööjaamadele,</P><P>– 1 köök koos asjakohaste tarvetega (töötasapind, kapid, kraanikauss),</P><P>– 2 klosetti/tualettruumi – 1 personalile ja 1 taotlejatele,</P><P>– 1 mitmeotstarbeline ruum – kasutamiseks printeriruumina, koosolekuruumina, ootealana taotlejatele pauside ajal või vajaduse korral – korraga vähemalt 15–16 isiku mahutamiseks,</P><P>– 1 panipaik.</P><P>Ametiruumides peab olema piisavalt ruumi, et neid saaks vajadusel sisustada tööjaamadega (mööbel ning info- ja sidetehnoloogia seadmed).</P><P>Juhul kui alalist (alalisi) turvatöötajat (turvatöötajaid) ei ole / ei pakuta, peab EASO-l olema luba kasutada omi turvatöötajaid ja paigaldada nõutavad turvakontrolli süsteemid. Lisaks, kui vastuvõtuteenust ei ole saadaval, peab EASO-l olema luba kasutada oma vastuvõtupersonali ja seada sisse vastavad vahendid, koos nõutava mööbli ja seadmetega. Töövõtja peab lisaks ülalloetletud büroopinnale tagama vastuvõtuteenuse osutamiseks vajaliku ruumi maapinna / sissekäigu tasandil.</P><P>Kogu hoone peab olema hõlmatud ühtse tulekahju avastamissüsteemiga (suitsu- ja soojusandurid, häiresüsteemi juhtpaneelid. Nõutav on spetsiaalse evakueerumisväljapääsu olemasolu igal korrusel.</P><P>Elektrivarustus ja -kontaktid, veevarustus (soe ja külm vesi), küte/jahutus/kliimaseade, kanalisatsiooniühendused peavad olema kohal ja ühendatud kommunaalse / avaliku teenindusvõrguga.</P><P>Juhul kui EASO-l on vaja viia läbi ehituslikke kohandusi, peab töövõtja kandma hoolt ehituslubade hankimiseks nõutavate vajalike lisadokumentide ja hoone kõigi omanike nõusoleku, kui see on vajalik, muretsemise eest.</P><P>EASO-l peab olema luba viia kokkuleppel töövõtjaga sisse mitte-ehituslikke kohandusi omal kulul, et paigaldada üksikesemeid või teha ruumidele pisemaid täiustusi.</P><P>Töövõtja vastutab hoonete kindlustuse eest, et hõlmata peamised kahjud, nagu tulekahju, vargus, veeavarii ja sarnased kahjud, kogu üürimisaja kestel.</P><P>Töövõtja vastutab kõigi probleemide lahendamise eest, mis võivad kerkida esile seoses kõigi tehniliste teenustega, kaasa arvatud elektrivarustus, veevarustus, kanalisatsioon, prügivedu ja ventilatsioon, ja lisaks ka kohese remondiga seotud kahjud, mis ei ole omistatavad EASO-le.</P><P>Puhastusteenuseid peab osutama järgmiselt:</P><P>Igapäevaselt tuleb teostada järgmisi ülesandeid:</P><P>– prügikorvide tühjendamine, plastkatete asendamine (vajadusel) ning prügi äraviimine kohalikesse konteinermahutitesse,</P><P>– tolmu pühkimine ja kõigi avatud pindade pühkimine niiske lapiga,</P><P>– põrandate ja seinte keraamiliste plaatide puhastamine ja pühkimine,</P><P>– puhkeruumide (sh tualettruumid, valamud/pesunõud) puhastamine, pühkimine ja desinfitseerimine, tualettpaberi, paberkäterättide ja muude vajalike tarvikute kohalepanek,</P><P>– köögi (sh valamu ja kõik pinnad) puhastamine, pühkimine ja desinfitseerimine, paberkäterättide ja muude vajalike tarvikute kohalepanek.</P><P>Igakuiselt tuleb teostada järgmisi ülesandeid:</P><P>– tualettruumide põhjalik puhastamine ja desinfitseerimine,</P><P>– soojendus/jahutusseadmetelt tolmu pühkimine ja nende puhastamine,</P><P>– kogu siseustel ja/või lükandvaheseintel oleva klaasi puhastamine.</P><P>Kord iga kolme (3) kuu jooksul teostatavad ülesanded:</P><P>– kõigi akende ja välisustel oleva klaasi (kui on olemas) puhastamine,</P><P>– kardinate ja ruloode (kui on olemas) puhastamine.</P><P>3.2 Tähtajad</P><P>Ruumid peavad olema kasutusvalmis 2018. aasta aprillis.</P><P>3.3 Menetlus</P><P>Kõnealune uurimismenetluse tulemusena valitakse välja kuni 3 pakkuja taotlejat, kelle ruumid võimaldavad nõudeid täita. EASO kutsub eelvalitud kandidaadi(d) läbirääkimistele järgmises, käesolevast menetlusest eraldi etapis. Eelvalitud kandidaadile (kandidaatidele) saadetakse üksikasjalik tehniline kirjeldus. Kutsutud taotlejat (taotlejaid) teavitatakse pakkumuste nõutava sisu ja esitamiseks vajalike dokumentide kohta.</P><P> Iga eelvalitud taotleja peab pakkumuse esitamisega tagama järgmist:</P><P>– et tema pakkumus on jõus kuni võimaliku lepingu allkirjastamiseni,</P><P>– et iga hoonet käsitlev dokument esitatakse EASO määratud tähtajaks.</P><P>Käesolev teade ei ole EASO-le lepingu sõlmimise suhtes mingilgi viisil siduv. EASO-l on õigus igal ajal enne lepingu allkirjastamist keelduda lepingu sõlmimisest või tühistada menetlus ilma taotlejatele kahju hüvitamata. EASO ei sõlmi enne läbirääkimiste etappi ega selle käigus taotlejaga ainuõiguslikke lepinguid ega kehtesta taotleja kasuks samalaadseid tingimusi.</P><P>3.4 Lepingu liik</P><P>Liisingulepingu täielik maksimaalne kestus on kümme (10) kuud, võimalusega pikendada lepingut 3 korda, iga kord täiendavaks 12-kuiseks ajavahemikuks ja kogukestusega 3 aastat 10 kuu.</P><P>Liisinguleping katab liisingu kulud ja tugiteenused. EASO-l peab olema võimalik tühistada rendileping ja tugiteenused ühekuise etteteatamisega.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Läbirääkimistega menetlusel osalemistaotlustega seonduvad nõuded</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Sisu</P><P>Osalemistaotluses sisalduvate andmete esitamisel peab kasutama järgmisi vorme:</P><P>1) nõuetekohaselt kuupäevastatud ja allkirjastatud isikutõend ja avaldusvorm (näidates taotleja isikuandmed; omaniku isikuandmed – kui taotleja ja omanik on erinevad; ruumide täielik aadress; kinnitus selle kohta, et osutatakse vähemalt nõutavad teenuseid). Vorm on saadaval internetiaadressil https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) pindade kirjeldus; joonised (põrandad, fassaadid, läbilõikejoonised) ja standardset asendiplaani näitavad plaanid (kahtluse korral võidakse nõuda 1/50 või 1/100 või 1/200 mõõtkavas jooniseid);</P><P>4.2 Osalemistaotluste esitamine läbirääkimistega menetluses osalemiseks</P><P>Osalemistaotlused, läbirääkimistega menetluses, koos punkti 4.1 järgi nõutavate andmetega, peab saatma hiljemalt 9.4.2018 e-posti teel aadressile contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pakkumiste hindamine teisel etapil (läbirääkimistega menetlus):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eelvalitud taotleja(i)lt saadud pakkumised, mis ei vasta käesoleva teate punktis 3 nimetatud uurimistegevuse valdkonna ja/või soovitava pindala nõuetele, lükatakse tagasi. Välistatud ruume esitanud taotlejaid teavitatakse nõuetekohaselt.</P><P>Sobivaid pakkumisi analüüsitakse kvaliteedi ja hinna kriteeriumi alusel järgmistest osakaaludest lähtudes:</P><P>– hind (40 %),</P><P>– kvaliteet (60 %).</P><P>Pakkuja kvaliteet (Q) selgitatakse välja järgmiste komponentide alusel (100 punkti):</P><P>– füüsiline lähedus Küprose asüüliteenistuse valduses olevale hoonele (vt 3.1., esimene lõik):  55 punkti (miinimumnõue: 35), </P><P>– pinna jaotus ruumides – hinnatakse büroopinna, ooteala jaotust ja ametiruumide laiendamisvõimalust: 30 punkti (miinimumnõue: 18), </P><P>– turva- ja ohutusmeetmed ruumides (lisaks punktis II näidatud miinimumnõuetele) – hinnatakse füüsilise kaitse olemasolu (mehitatud valve), tulekustutite paigaldust, avariiväljapääsude ja evakuatsiooniplaanide jne kohalolu: 15 punkti (miinimumnõue: 7). </P><P>Pakkumuste klassifitseerimise alus on lõplik punktisumma (F), mis saadakse järgmise valemiga:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontaktandmed ja lisateave:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Taotlejaid teavitatakse nende eelvalimisest või otsusest mitte olla kutsutud läbirääkimistega menetlusele. Ükskõik milline ühenduse võtmine taotlejate ja EASO vahel on keelatud, välja arvatud juhtudel, kui kinnisvaraalase eelteate kohta on vaja anda selgitust. Selgitustaotlus peab olema tehtud kirjalikult ja saadetud e-posti aadressile contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: A brüsszeli ingatlanpiac felmérésére irányuló felhívás az Európai Menekültügyi Támogatási Hivatal irodaterület-igényeinek kielégítése céljából</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Felelős uniós ügynökség</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európai Menekültügyi Támogatási Hivatal (EASO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Málta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A keresés tárgya:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Az Európai Menekültügyi Támogatási Hivatal (EASO) támogatást nyújt Ciprusnak a ciprusi kormánnyal aláírt speciális segítségnyújtási terv keretében. A terv keretében az ügynökség munkatársai, valamint szakértői és tolmácsai segítségével nyújt támogatást meghatározott intézkedésekhez. A munkatársak, szakértők és tolmácsok számára szükséges munkaterület biztosítása érdekében az EASO létesítményeket/irodaterületet kíván bérelni az alábbiakban részletezett minimális követelmények szerint, a kapcsolódó takarítási szolgáltatásokkal kiegészítve.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés és az alkalmazandó eljárás ismertetése</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Minimális követelmények</P><P>Az EASO irodaterületet kíván bérelni a Ciprusi Menekültügyi Szolgálat telephelyén (70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Ciprus) vagy egy azzal szomszédos épületben.</P><P>A helyszínnek a hét minden napján 7:00 és 22:00 között kell elérhetőnek lennie az EASO munkatársai, szakértői és tolmácsai számára.</P><P>Az ügynökség számára szükséges felszíni létesítmény/irodaterület becsült mérete legalább 250 és legfeljebb 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>A létesítménynek/irodaterületnek alkalmasnak kell lennie a következők biztosítására:</P><P>— 7 iroda/tárgyalószoba: tárgyalószobaként történő használatra – egyszerre 3-4 fő befogadására,</P><P>— 1 iroda a tolmácsok számára: tárgyaló-/váróhelyiségnek a tolmácsoknak, valamint szükség esetén a tolmácsok önálló munkavégzéséhez (fordítás, telefonbeszélgetés a jelentkezőkkel stb.) – egyszerre 6-8 fő befogadására,</P><P>— 1 műveleti iroda: az EASO koordinátora és operatív asszisztense(i) számára, az iratkezeléshez (ütemezett ügyek iratai, véleményezésre váró iratok stb.) használt iratszekrényekhez szükséges irodaterülettel – egyszerre 3 fő befogadására és a munkaállomásokon túl elegendő irodaterülettel az iratszekrényeknek,</P><P>— 1 megfelelően felszerelt konyha (munkapult, szekrények, mosogató),</P><P>— 2 mellékhelyiség/WC: 1 a munkatársak és 1 a jelentkezők számára,</P><P>— 1 általános célú helyiség: amely használható nyomtatóhelyiségként, tárgyalóteremként, a jelentkezők itt várakozhatnak a szünetekben vagy szükség esetén – egyszerre legalább 15-16 fő befogadására,</P><P>— 1 raktár.</P><P>Az irodákban elegendő helynek kell lennie a munkaállomások elhelyezésére, ahol ez szükséges (bútorok és IKT-berendezés).</P><P>Ha nem áll rendelkezésre vagy nem igényelhető állandó biztonsági szolgálat, az EASO számára engedélyezik saját biztonsági őrök alkalmazását és a szükséges biztonsági rendszer beszerelését. Emellett, ha nem áll rendelkezésre recepció, az EASO számára engedélyezik saját recepciós személyzet alkalmazását és megfelelő berendezés elhelyezését a szükséges bútorokkal és felszerelésekkel. Ennek érdekében, a fentiekben felsorolt irodaterületen túl a nyertes ajánlattevő rendelkezésére kell bocsátani a szükséges területet a földszinti/bejárati szinten.</P><P>A teljes épületben ki kell építeni egy integrált tűzérzékelő rendszert (füst- és hőérzékelők, tűzjelző panelek). Minden szinten külön vészkijárat szükséges.</P><P>Az elektromos berendezéseknek és kimeneteknek, a hideg- és melegvíz-ellátásnak, a fűtésnek/hűtésnek/légkondicionálásnak és a szennyvíz-csatlakozásoknak a települési/közműhálózatra kötve rendelkezésre kell állniuk.</P><P>Abban az esetben, ha az EASO-nak szerkezeti átalakításokat kell végeznie, a nyertes ajánlattevőnek rendelkezésre kell bocsátania az építési munkálatokhoz szükséges engedélyek megszerzéséhez benyújtandó dokumentumokat és – szükség esetén – az épület összes tulajdonosának beleegyezését.</P><P>Az EASO a nyertes ajánlattevő beleegyezésével nem szerkezeti átalakításokat végezhet – saját költségén – berendezések telepítése vagy a helyszínen szükséges kisebb fejlesztések érdekében.</P><P>A bérleti idő alatt a nyertes ajánlattevő felelős az épület biztosításáért és az olyan alapvető károkért, mint a tűz- és vízkár, a lopás és hasonlók.</P><P>A nyertes ajánlattevő felelős a műszaki szolgáltatásokkal – pl. áramellátás, vízszolgáltatás, szennyvízelvezetés, hulladékkezelés, szellőzés – kapcsolatos problémák megoldásáért, valamint minden olyan kapcsolódó kár azonnali elhárításáért, amely nem az EASO-nak tulajdonítható.</P><P>A takarítási szolgáltatásokat a következők szerint kell teljesíteni:</P><P>Napi szinten végrehajtandó feladatok:</P><P>— Szemetesek ürítése, műanyag szemeteszacskók cseréje – szükség esetén –, valamint a hulladék szeméttárolókba szállítása,</P><P>— Minden látható felület pormentesítése és nedves ronggyal történő letörlése,</P><P>— A padló és a csempe tisztítása és felsöprése,</P><P>— A mellékhelyiségek takarítása, felsöprése és fertőtlenítése – beleértve a WC-ket és mosdókagylókat –, WC-papír, papírtörlő és egyéb szükséges cikkek elhelyezése,</P><P>— A konyha takarítása, felsöprése és fertőtlenítése – beleértve a mosogatót és minden felületet –, papírtörlő és egyéb szükséges cikkek elhelyezése.</P><P>Havonta egyszer végrehajtandó feladatok:</P><P>— A WC-k alapos takarítása és fertőtlenítése,</P><P>— A fűtő- és hűtőegységek portalanítása és tisztítása,</P><P>— A belső ajtók és/vagy válaszfalak üvegfelületeinek tisztítása.</P><P>Háromhavonta végrehajtandó feladatok:</P><P>— A külső ajtók összes üvegfelületének tisztítása (ha van),</P><P>— Függönyök és árnyékolók tisztítása (ha van).</P><P>3.2 Határidők</P><P>A helyszínnek 2018. áprilisában rendelkezésre kell állnia.</P><P>3.3 Eljárás</P><P>A szóban forgó eljárás legfeljebb 3 olyan ajánlattevő előzetes kiválasztásával zárul, aki a követelményeknek megfelelő helyszínt kínál. Az EASO az előzetesen kiválasztott ajánlattevő(ke)t a jelen eljárást követő, külön szakaszban tárgyalásokra kéri fel. A részletes műszaki dokumentációt megküldik az előzetesen kiválasztott ajánlattevő(k)nek. A meghívott ajánlattevő(ke)t értesítik az ajánlat tartalmi követelményeiről és a benyújtandó dokumentumokról.</P><P> Ajánlatának benyújtásakor minden előzetesen kiválasztott jelentkezőnek garanciát kell nyújtani arra, hogy:</P><P>— ajánlata a szerződés aláírásáig érvényes marad,</P><P>— az épülettel kapcsolatos dokumentumokat az EASO által meghatározott határidőn belül rendelkezésre bocsátja.</P><P>E hirdetmény semmilyen kötelezettséget nem jelent az EASO-ra nézve a szerződés odaítélésére vonatkozóan. Az EASO fenntartja a jogot arra, hogy a szerződés aláírása előtt bármikor megszüntesse vagy érvénytelenítse az eljárást. Ez esetben az ajánlattevők kártérítésre nem tarthatnak igényt. A tárgyalási szakasz előtt vagy alatt az EASO egyik ajánlattevővel sem ír alá kizárólagosságra vonatkozó szerződést vagy hasonló záradékot.</P><P>3.4 A szerződés típusa</P><P>A bérleti szerződés teljes időtartama maximum tíz (10) hónap, amely 3 alkalommal, alkalmanként 12 hónappal meghosszabbítható (így a teljes összesített időtartam 3 év 10 hónap).</P><P>A bérleti szerződésben rögzíteni kell a bérleti költségeket és a kiegészítő szolgáltatásokat. Az EASO számára egy hónapos felmondási időt kell biztosítani a bérleti szerződésre és a kiegészítő szolgáltatásokra vonatkozóan.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A tárgyalásos eljárásban történő részvételre vonatkozó kérelem követelményei</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Tartalom</P><P>A részvételi kérelemben található információkat a következő formanyomtatványokon kell megadni:</P><P>1) Megfelelően dátumozott és aláírt azonosító és nyilatkozattételi űrlap (az ajánlattevő és – ha eltérőek – a tulajdonos adataival, a helyszín teljes címével, valamint annak megerősítésével, hogy a minimálisan szükséges szolgáltatásokat ellátják). A formanyomtatvány a következő címen elérhető: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Az alapterület bemutatása; ábrák (szintek, homlokzatok, keresztmetszeti ábrázolások) és alaprajzok a hagyományos elrendezésről (kétség esetén 1/50, 1/100 vagy 1/200 arányú rajzok is kérhetők);</P><P>4.2 A tárgyalásos eljárásban történő részvételre vonatkozó kérelmek benyújtása</P><P>A tárgyalásos eljárásban történő részvételre irányú kérelmeket a 4.1. pontban szereplő információkkal együtt kell elküldeni a contracts@easo.europa.eu e-mail címre, legkésőbb a következő dátumig: 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlatok értékelése a második szakaszban (tárgyalásos eljárás):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nem értékelik az előzetesen kiválasztott ajánlattevőktől érkezett azon ajánlatokat, amelyek nem felelnek meg a jelen felhívás 3. pontjában meghatározott keresett területnek és/vagy alapterületnek. A kizárt helyszíneket kínáló pályázókat megfelelően tájékoztatják.</P><P>A megfelelő ajánlatokat a minőségre és árra vonatkozó kritériumok szerint elemzik, a következő súlyozás szerint:</P><P>— ár (40 %),</P><P>— minőség (60 %).</P><P>A pályázat minőségét (Q) a következő elemek alapján határozzák meg (100 pont):</P><P>— A Ciprusi Menekültügyi Szolgálat épületének fizikai közelsége (lásd: 3.1. pont, első bekezdés):  55 pont (minimális elvárás: 35),</P><P>— A helyszínen elérhető terület felosztása: az irodaterület és a várakozásra szolgáló terület felosztását, valamint az irodák bővítésének lehetőségét értékelik: 30 pont (minimális elvárás: 18),</P><P>— A helyszínen elérhető védelmi és biztonsági intézkedések (a II. pontban szereplő minimális követelményeken túl): a biztosított fizikai biztonságot (őrök) és az elhelyezett tűzoltó készülékeket, vészkijáratokat, kiürítési terveket stb. értékelik: 15 pont (minimális elvárás: 7).</P><P>Az ajánlatok osztályozását a végső pontszám (F) alapján végzik a következő képlet szerint:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kapcsolattartási pontok és további információk:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A jelentkezőket tájékoztatják, ha teljesítették az előzetes kiválasztást, vagy ha nem kerülnek meghívásra a tárgyalásos eljárásra. A jelentkezők és az EASO közötti mindenfajta kommunikáció tilos, kivéve, ha pontosításra van szükség az ingatlanpiaci felmérésre irányuló felhívással kapcsolatban. A pontosításra irányuló kérést írásban kell megküldeni a következő e-mail címre: contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Skelbimas apie nuosavybės rinkos tyrimą, siekiant atitikti Europos prieglobsčio paramos biuro reikalavimus</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsakinga ES agentūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos prieglobsčio paramos biuras</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paieškos objektas:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europos prieglobsčio paramos biuras (EASO) teikia paramą Kiprui pagal specialų paramos planą, pasirašytą su Kipro vyriausybe. Pagal planą, agentūra pasitelkia savo darbuotojus, taip pat ekspertus ir vertėjus siūlo bei teikia paramą konkrečioms priemonėms. Tam, kad užtikrintų darbuotojų, ekspertų ir vertėjų darbo vietą, EASO siekia išsinuomoti minimalius žemiau nurodytus reikalavimus atitinkančias patalpas ar biurus bei pagalbines valymo paslaugas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties ir numatomų taikyti procedūrų aprašymas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Minimalūs reikalavimai</P><P>EASO siekia išsinuomoti biurą, esantį patalpose, kurias užima Kipro prieglobsčio tarnyba, adresu 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Kipras arba gretimame pastate.</P><P>Patalpos turi būti prieinamos EASO darbuotojams, ekspertams ir vertėjams nuo 7 iki 22 val. visomis savaitės dienomis.</P><P>Agentūra reikalauja, kad antžeminių patalų ar biurų plotas būtų ne mažesnis kaip 250, bet ne didesnis kaip 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Patalpose ar biure turi būti:</P><P>— 7 biurai ar interviu kambariai, naudojami kaip interviu kambariai, vienu metu talpinantys 3–4 asmenis,</P><P>— 1 biuras vertėjams, naudojamas kaip posėdžių kambarys ar laukiamasis vertėjams, taip pat, jei reikia, skirtas vertėjams dirbti atskirai (vertimams, pokalbiams su pareiškėjais ir kt.), vienu metu talpinantis 6–8 asmenis,</P><P>— 1 operacijų biuras, naudojamas kaip EASO koordinatoriaus ir operacijų asistento (-ų) biuras ir turintis pakankamai vietos failų spintelėms (numatytų bylų failams, failams, dėl kurių laukiama nuomonės ir kt.), vienu metu talpinantis 3 asmenis ir turintis pakankamai vietos failų spintelėms bei darbo vietoms,</P><P>— 1 virtuvė su atitinkamomis patalpomis (bufetu, spintelėmis, kriaukle),</P><P>— 2 tualetai – 1 darbuotojams ir 1 pareiškėjams,</P><P>— 1 daugiafunkcis kambarys, kuris taip pat gali būti naudojamas kaip spausdinimo kambarys, susirinkimų kambarys, pareiškėjų laukimo vieta per pertrauką arba prireikus, vienu metu talpinantis bent 15–16 asmenų,</P><P>— 1 saugykla.</P><P>Biurai turi būti pakankamai dideli, kad prireikus, galima būtų įrengti darbo vietas (baldus ir IRT įrangą).</P><P>Jei nėra numatytas (-i) arba siūlomas (-i) nuolatinis (-ai) apsauginis (-ai), EASO turi būti leidžiama turėti savo apsauginius ir įdiegti reikiamas saugumo kontrolės sistemas. Toliau, jei nėra priėmimo paslaugos, EASO turi būti leidžiama turėti savo priėmimo darbuotojus ir įrengti reikiamas patalpas su reikalingais baldais ir įranga. Be reikalingų biurų, nurodytų aukščiau, rangovas šiuo tikslu turi suteikti reikalingą erdvę pirmame aukšte arba aukšte, kuriame yra įėjimas.</P><P>Visas pastatas turi būti aprūpintas kompleksine gaisro aptikimo sistema (dūmų ir šilumos detektoriais, gaisro skydais). Kiekviename aukšte privalomas evakuacijai skirtas išėjimas.</P><P>Elektros tiekimas ir taškai, karšto ir šalto vandens tiekimas, šildymas, aušinimas, oro kondicionavimas, kanalizacijos jungtys turi būti įrengti ir prijungti prie savivaldybės ar viešųjų paslaugų.</P><P>Jei EASO prireikia atlikti struktūrinius pokyčius, Rangovas turi pateikti patvirtinamuosius dokumentus, reikalingus statybos leidimams gauti, ir, jei reikia, visų pastatų savininkų sutikimą.</P><P>Susitarus su rangovu, EASO turi būti leidžiama savo sąskaita atlikti ne struktūrinius pakeitimus, leidžiančius atlikti įrengimus arba nedidelius patalpų patobulinimus.</P><P>Paslaugų teikėjas yra atsakingas už pastatų draudimą, kuris turi padengti pagrindinius nuostolius, tokius kaip gaisras, vagystė, užtvindymas ir panaši žala per visą nuomos laikotarpį.</P><P>Paslaugų teikėjas yra atsakingas už problemų, susijusių su visomis techninėmis paslaugomis, įskaitant energijos tiekimą, vandens tiekimą, nuotekas, atliekų šalinimą ir vėdinimą, sprendimą, taip pat už susijusių nuostolių, nepriskiriamų EASO, ištaisymą nedelsiant.</P><P>Valymo paslaugos teikiamos taip:</P><P>Darbai, kuriuos reikia atlikti kasdien:</P><P>— šiukšlių dėžių ištuštinimas, šiukšlių maišų keitimas (jei reikia), šiukšlių išnešimas į konteinerius,</P><P>— visų paviršių šluostymas ir valymas šlapiu skudurėliu,</P><P>— grindų ir sienų plytelių valymas ir šveitimas,</P><P>— tualetų, kriauklių ar praustuvių valymas ir dezinfekavimas, tualetinio popieriaus, popierinių rankšluosčių ir kitų reikalingų daiktų keitimas,</P><P>— virtuvės, įskaitant kriauklę ir visus paviršius, valymas ir dezinfekavimas, popierinių rankšluosčių ir kitų reikalingų daiktų keitimas.</P><P>Darbai, kuriuos reikia atlikti kartą per mėnesį:</P><P>— nuodugnus tualetų valymas ir dezinfekavimas,</P><P>— šildymo ir vėsinimo įrenginių šluostymas ir valymas,</P><P>— visų vidaus durų ir (arba) pertvarų stiklo valymas.</P><P>Darbai, kuriuos reikia atlikti kartą per tris (3) mėnesius:</P><P>— visų langų ir išorės durų stiklų (jei yra) valymas,</P><P>— užuolaidų ir žaliuzių (jei yra) valymas.</P><P>3.2 Terminai</P><P>Patalpos turi būti prieinamos nuo 2018 m. balandžio mėn.</P><P>3.3 Procedūra</P><P>Ši paieškos procedūra bus baigta iš anksto atrinkus ne daugiau kaip 3 kandidatus, kurių patalpos atitinka reikalavimus. EASO kvies iš anksto atrinktą (-us) pareiškėją (-us) dalyvauti derybose kitame etape atskirai nuo šios procedūros. Iš anksto atrinktam (-iems) kandidatui (-ams) bus išsiųstos išsamios techninės specifikacijos. Pakviestam (-iems) pareiškėjui (-ams) bus pranešta apie reikalaujamą pasiūlymų turinį</P><P>ir pateiktinus dokumentus. Teikdamas pasiūlymą, kiekvienas iš anksto atrinktas kandidatas garantuoja:</P><P>— kad jo pasiūlymas galioja, kol bus pasirašyta sutartis,</P><P>— kad bet koks su patalpomis susijęs dokumentas bus pateiktas laikantis EASO nustatytų terminų.</P><P>Šis skelbimas jokiu būdu neįpareigoja EASO sutarties skyrimo procedūrų atžvilgiu. EASO pasilieka teisę bet kuriuo metu iki sutarties pasirašymo atsisakyti sudaryti sutartį arba nutraukti šią procedūrą; pareiškėjai neturi teisės reikalauti jokios kompensacijos. Prieš derybas arba jų metu EASO nepasirašys jokių išimtinių sutarčių arba panašių nuostatų, palankių pareiškėjui.</P><P>3.4. Sutarties tipas</P><P>Bendra didžiausia nuomos sutarties trukmė bus dešimt (10) mėnesių, su galimybe pratęsti 3 papildomiems 12 mėnesių laikotarpiams (bendra galima sutarties trukmė – 3 metai ir 10 mėnesių).</P><P>Nuomos sutartis apima nuomos išlaidas ir pagalbines paslaugas. EASO gali nutraukti nuomos sutartį ir pagalbines paslaugas įteikdama išankstinį įspėjimą likus ne mažiau nei mėnesiui.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Reikalavimai, susiję su prašymais dalyvauti derybose</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Turinys</P><P>Prašyme dalyvauti pateikiama informacija turi būti pateikta šiomis formomis:</P><P>1) tinkamai datuota ir pasirašyta identifikavimo ir deklaravimo forma (nurodoma informacija apie kandidatą, informacija apie savininką, jei skiriasi, visas patalpų adresas, patvirtinimas, kad bus teikiamos minimalios reikalaujamos paslaugos). Forma pateikiama šiuo adresu: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) paviršiaus plotų apibūdinimas; brėžiniai (grindys, fasadai, skerspjūviai) ir planai, kuriuose pateikiamas standartinis išdėstymas (kilus abejonių, gali būti prašoma brėžinių, kurių mastelis 1/50, 1/100 arba 1/200);</P><P>4.2 Prašymų dalyvauti derybose teikimas</P><P>Prašymai dalyvauti derybose, kartu su 4.1 punkte nurodyta informacija, turi būti išsiųsti elektroniniu paštu adresu contracts@easo.europa.eu iki 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pasiūlymų vertinimas antrame etape (derybų procedūra):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Iš anksto atrinkto (-ų) kandidato (-ų) gauti pasiūlymai, kurie yra netinkami ir (arba) neapima tyrimo srities ir (arba) ieškomo paviršiaus ploto, kaip nurodyta šio skelbimo 3 punkte, nebus svarstomi. Šalinami pasiūlymų dėl patalpų pareiškėjai bus tinkamai informuojami.</P><P>Tinkami pasiūlymai bus analizuojami remiantis kokybės ir kainos kriterijais vadovaujantis šiais lyginamaisiais svoriais:</P><P>— kaina (40 %),</P><P>— kokybė (60 %).</P><P>Pasiūlymo kokybė (Q) bus nustatoma remiantis šiais elementais (100 balų):</P><P>— artumas Kipro prieglobsčio tarnybos užimamam pastatui (žr. 3.1 punkto pirmą popunktį): 55 balai (mažiausiai reikalaujama: 35),</P><P>— erdvės patalpose paskirstymas – bus vertinamas biurų patalpų, laukiamojo išdėstymas ir galimybė išplėsti biurus: 30 balų (mažiausiai reikalaujama: 18),</P><P>— apsaugos ir saugos priemonės patalpose (be II punkte nurodytų minimalių reikalavimų) – bus vertinama ar yra fizinė sauga (apsauginiai), gesintuvai, avariniai išėjimai ir evakuacijos planai bei kt.: 15 balų (mažiausiai reikalaujama: 7).</P><P>Pasiūlymų klasifikacija bus grindžiama galutiniu balu (F) remiantis šia formule:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontaktai ir papildoma informacija:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pareiškėjai bus informuoti apie sprendimą juos kviesti arba nekviesti į derybų procedūrą. Bet koks bendravimas tarp pareiškėjų ir EASO yra draudžiamas, išskyrus atvejus, kai reikia paaiškinti skelbimą apie pastatų paiešką. Prašymas paaiškinti teikiamas raštu, adresu contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Paziņojums par īpašuma izpēti, lai izpildītu ar Eiropas Patvēruma atbalsta biroja telpām saistītās prasības</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atbildīgā ES aģentūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Patvēruma atbalsta birojs</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Izpētes priekšmets:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eiropas Patvēruma atbalsta birojs (EASO) sniedz atbalstu Kiprai īpašā atbalsta plāna, kas noslēgts ar Kipras valdību, ietvaros. Saskaņā ar šo plānu aģentūra norīko savus darbiniekus, kā arī ekspertus un tulkus, lai sniegtu atbalstu konkrētos pasākumos. Lai darbiniekiem, ekspertiem un tulkiem nodrošinātu darba vietu, EASO vēlas nomāt telpas/birojus atbilstoši turpmāk norādītajām minimālajām prasībām, kā arī saņemt papildu uzkopšanas pakalpojumus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma un piemērojamās procedūras apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1. Minimālās prasības</P><P>EASO vēlas nomāt biroja telpas, kas atrodas Kipras Patvēruma dienesta ēkā (adrese: 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Kipra) vai blakus esošā ēkā.</P><P>Telpām jābūt atvērtām EASO darbiniekiem, ekspertiem un tulkiem visās nedēļas dienās no plkst. 7:00 līdz 22:00.</P><P>Aģentūrai ir nepieciešamas telpas/biroji, kuru virszemes platība ir vismaz 250 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}, bet ne vairāk kā 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Telpām/birojiem jābūt piemērotiem šādai ietilpībai:</P><P>— 7 biroji / interviju telpas, lai tās izmantotu kā interviju telpas, kurās var uzņemt 3–4 personas vienlaikus,</P><P>— 1 birojs tulkiem, lai to izmantotu kā sanāksmes/uzgaidāmo telpu tulkiem, kā arī tulku individuālajam darbam, ja nepieciešams (tulkojumi, saziņa ar pretendentiem pa tālruni utt.); šajā birojā ir jābūt iespējai uzņemt 6–8 personas vienlaikus,</P><P>— 1 darba birojs, lai to izmantotu EASO koordinators un darba asistents(-i) un tajā būtu pietiekami daudz vietas dokumentu pārvaldībai nepieciešamiem skapjiem (grafikā paredzēto lietu dokumentiem, tādiem dokumentiem, kuriem nepieciešami atzinumi u. c.); šajā birojā ir jābūt iespējai uzņemt 3 personas vienlaikus un ir jābūt atvēlētai vietai dokumentu skapjiem papildu darba zonām,</P><P>— 1 virtuve ar piemērotām iekārtām (galdu, skapjiem, izlietni),</P><P>— 2 telpas labierīcībām / tualetes (1 – darbiniekiem un 1 – pretendentiem),</P><P>— 1 daudzfunkcionāla telpa, lai to izmantotu kā telpu dokumentu drukāšanai, kā sanāksmju telpu, uzgaidāmo telpu pretendentiem pauzes laikā vai citiem nolūkiem un lai tajā varētu uzņemt vismaz 15–16 personas vienlaikus,</P><P>— 1 uzglabāšanas telpa.</P><P>Birojos jābūt pietiekami daudz vietas darba zonu iekārtošanai, kur nepieciešams (ar mēbelēm un IKT aprīkojumu).</P><P>Ja nav pieejami / netiek piedāvāti pastāvīgas apsardzes pakalpojumi, EASO drīkst norīkot savu apsardzi un uzstādīt nepieciešamās drošības kontroles sistēmas. Turklāt, ja nav pieejami reģistratūras pakalpojumi, EASO drīkst norīkot savus reģistratūras darbiniekus un atvēlēt tiem telpas, iekārtojot ar nepieciešamajām mēbelēm un aprīkojumu. Šajā nolūkā papildus iepriekš uzskaitītajām biroja telpām darbuzņēmējam jānodrošina arī piekļuve vajadzīgajām 1. stāva/ieejas telpām.</P><P>Visai ēkai jābūt aprīkotai ar integrētu ugunsdrošības signalizācijas sistēmu (dūmu un siltuma detektoriem un ugunsdrošības paneļiem). Katrā stāvā jābūt noteiktai avārijas izejai.</P><P>Jābūt ierīkotai elektroapgādei un sadales punktiem, siltā un aukstā ūdens apgādei, gaisa kondicionēšanas sistēmai ar siltu/aukstu gaisu un notekūdeņu izvadiem komunālo/sabiedrisko pakalpojumu ietvaros.</P><P>Ja EASO nepieciešams veikt strukturālus pielāgojumus, darbuzņēmējam jānodrošina vajadzīgie apliecinošie dokumenti, lai saņemtu būvdarbu atļaujas, kā arī, ja nepieciešams, visu ēku īpašnieku piekrišana.</P><P>Vienojoties ar darbuzņēmēju, EASO drīkst veikt nestrukturālus pielāgojumus par saviem izdevumiem, lai telpās uzstādītu iekārtas vai veiktu nelielas izmaiņas.</P><P>Darbuzņēmējam jāatbild par ēku apdrošināšanu, lai tiktu segti pamata zaudējumi, piemēram, ar ugunsgrēku, zādzību, applūdināšanu saistīti un līdzīgi bojājumi visa nomas līguma laikā.</P><P>Darbuzņēmējam jāatbild par visu to problēmu risināšanu, kas saistītas ar tehniskajiem pakalpojumiem, tostarp elektroapgādi, ūdensapgādi, notekūdeņiem, atkritumu likvidēšanu un ventilāciju, kā arī par tādu saistīto bojājumu tūlītēju remontu, kuros nav vainojama EASO.</P><P>Uzkopšanas pakalpojumi jānodrošina turpmāk norādītajā veidā:</P><P>Ikdienā veicamie uzdevumi:</P><P>— atkritumu grozu iztukšošana, plastmasas atkritumu maisu nomaiņa, ja nepieciešams, atkritumu savākšana komunālajos atkritumu konteineros,</P><P>— visu atklāto virsmu putekļu slaucīšana un notīrīšana ar mitrām drānām,</P><P>— grīdu un sienas flīžu tīrīšana un slaucīšana,</P><P>— labierīcību telpu, tostarp tualešu, izlietņu tīrīšana, slaucīšana un dezinfekcija, tostarp tualetes papīra, papīra dvieļu un citu nepieciešamo līdzekļu izvietošana,</P><P>— virtuves, tostarp izlietnes un visu virsmu, tīrīšana, slaucīšana un dezinfekcija, kā arī papīra dvieļu un citu nepieciešamo līdzekļu izvietošana.</P><P>Vienu reizi mēnesī veicamie uzdevumi:</P><P>— tualešu padziļināta tīrīšana un dezinfekcija,</P><P>— siltā/aukstā gaisa iekārtu putekļu slaucīšana un tīrīšana,</P><P>— iekšējo durvju un/vai atdalošo elementu stiklu tīrīšana.</P><P>Ik pēc 3 mēnešiem veicamie uzdevumi:</P><P>— visu logu un ārējo durvju stiklu (ja tādi ir) tīrīšana,</P><P>— aizkaru un žalūziju (ja tādas ir) tīrīšana.</P><P>3.2. Termiņi</P><P>Telpām jābūt pieejamām 2018. gada aprīlī.</P><P>3.3. Procedūra</P><P>Šī izpētes procedūra noslēgsies ar ne vairāk kā 3 tādu pieteikuma iesniedzēju iepriekšēju izraudzīšanos, kuri var nodrošināt prasībām atbilstošās telpas. EASO aicinās iepriekš izraudzīto(-os) pieteikuma iesniedzēju(-us) sākt sarunas turpmākajā posmā, kas norisināsies atsevišķi no šīs procedūras. Iepriekš izraudzītajam(-iem) pieteikuma iesniedzējam(-iem) tiks nosūtītas detalizētas tehniskās specifikācijas. Uzaicinātais(-ie) pieteikuma iesniedzējs(-i) tiks informēts(-i) par iesniedzamo</P><P>piedāvājumu un dokumentu saturu. Piedāvājumu iesniedzot, katram iepriekš izraudzītajam pieteikuma iesniedzējam jāapliecina, ka:</P><P>— tā piedāvājums paliek spēkā līdz līguma parakstīšanai,</P><P>— ar telpām saistītie dokumenti tiek iesniegti EASO noteiktajos termiņos.</P><P>Šis paziņojums nekādā veidā nav saistošs EASO attiecībā uz līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas procedūrām. EASO saglabā tiesības jebkurā brīdī pirms līguma parakstīšanas atteikties vai atcelt šo procedūru, un pieteikumu iesniedzējiem šādā gadījumā nebūs tiesību pieprasīt kompensāciju. Pirms sarunu posma vai tā laikā EASO neparakstīs nekādus ekskluzīvu tiesību līgumus vai līdzīgus noteikumus kāda pieteikuma iesniedzēja labā.</P><P>3.4. Līguma veids</P><P>Nomas līguma kopējais maksimālais darbības laiks būs 10 mēneši ar iespēju to pagarināt 3 reizes, katru reizi uz 12 mēnešu periodu (kopējais darbības laiks tad būtu 3 gadi un 10 mēneši).</P><P>Nomas līgums sedz nomas izmaksas un papildu pakalpojumus. EASO drīkst izbeigt nomas un papildu pakalpojumu līgumu, par to paziņojot 1 mēnesi iepriekš.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ar dalības pieteikumiem sarunu procedūrā saistītās prasības</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1. Saturs</P><P>Dalības pieteikumā ietvertā informācija ir jāiesniedz turpmāk norādītajā veidā</P><P>1) Jāiesniedz atbilstoši datēta un parakstīta identifikācijas un apliecinājuma veidlapa, kurā norādīti pieteikuma iesniedzēja dati un īpašnieka dati (ja tā nav viena un tā pati persona), telpu pilna adrese, kā arī apstiprinājums par pakalpojumu minimālo prasību izpildes spēju. Veidlapa ir pieejama šeit: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Jāiesniedz platības apraksts, rasējumi (grīdas, fasādes, šķērsgriezumi) un plānojumi standarta izkārtojumā (šaubu gadījumā var tikt pieprasīti rasējumi mērogā 1/50, 1/100 vai 1/200);</P><P>4.2. Dalības pieteikumu sarunu procedūrā iesniegšana</P><P>Dalības pieteikumi sarunu procedūrā kopā ar 4.1. punktā prasīto informāciju jānosūta uz e-pasta adresi contracts@easo.europa.eu līdz 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Piedāvājumu novērtēšana 2. posmā (sarunu procedūra):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tiks noraidīti tie no iepriekš izraudzītā(-o) pieteikuma iesniedzēja(-u) saņemtie piedāvājumi, kuri neatbilst izpētes jomai un/vai meklēto telpu platībai, kā minēts šā paziņojuma 3. punktā, un/vai kuros minētais netiek ievērots. Personas, kas būs iesniegušas pieteikumus par ēkām, kuras izslēgs, tiks atbilstoši informētas.</P><P>Atbilstošos piedāvājumus analizēs, pamatojoties uz kvalitātes un cenas kritērijiem saskaņā ar šādu svērumu:</P><P>— cena (40 %),</P><P>— kvalitāte (60 %).</P><P>Piedāvājuma kvalitāti (quality – Q) noteiks, pamatojoties uz šādiem elementiem (100 punkti):</P><P>— fiziskais attālums līdz ēkai, kurā atrodas Kipras Patvēruma dienests (atsauce uz 3.1. punkta pirmo rindkopu): 55 punkti (nepieciešamais minimums: 35),</P><P>— vietas sadalījums telpās – tiks vērtēts biroju telpu, uzgaidāmās telpas sadalījums un iespēja šīs telpas paplašināt: 30 punkti (nepieciešamais minimums: 18),</P><P>— drošības un drošuma pasākumi telpās (papildus II. punktā norādītajām minimālajām prasībām) – tiks vērtēta fiziskā drošība (apsargi), uzstādīti ugunsdzēsības aparāti, avārijas izejas, evakuācijas plāni utt.: 15 punkti (nepieciešamais minimums: 7).</P><P>Piedāvājumu klasifikācijas pamatā būs galīgais punktu skaits (final score – F), ko aprēķina saskaņā ar šādu formulu:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontaktpersonas un papildu informācija:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pieteikuma iesniedzēji tiks informēti par to iepriekšēju izraudzīšanos vai arī lēmumu tos neaicināt uz sarunu procedūru. Jebkāda veida saziņa starp pieteikuma iesniedzējiem un EASO ir aizliegta, izņemot gadījumus, kur nepieciešami skaidrojumi saistībā ar paziņojumu par īpašuma izpēti. Skaidrojumu pieprasījumi jāsūta rakstveidā uz contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Avviż dwar tiftix għall-proprjetà biex jintlaħqu l-ħtiġijiet marbuta mal-ispazju għall-uffiċċji tal-Uffiċċju Ewropew ta' Appoġġ fil-qasam tal-Asil</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-Aġenzija tal-UE responsabbli</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>L-Uffiċċju Ewropew ta' Appoġġ fil-qasam tal-Asil</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-għan tat-tiftix:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-Uffiċċju Ewropew ta' Appoġġ fil-qasam tal-Asil (EASO) jipprovdi appoġġ lil Ċipru fil-qafas ta' Pjan ta' Appoġġ Speċjali ffirmat mal-Gvern ta' Ċipru. Fil-qafas tal-Pjan, l-Aġenzija tiskjera l-persunal, kif ukoll l-esperti u l-interpreti tagħha, biex tipprovdi appoġġ għal miżuri speċifiċi. Biex jiġi żgurat l-ispazju tax-xogħol għall-persunal, l-esperti u l-intepreti, l-EASO qed tfittex li tikri faċilitajiet/spazju għall-uffiċċji bi qbil mal-ħtiġijiet minimi ta' hawn taħt, u servizzi ta' tindif anċillari.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-deskrizzjoni tal-kuntratt u l-proċedura li se tintuża</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Il-ħtiġijiet</P><P>L-EASO qed ifittex li jikri spazju għall-uffiċċji li jinsab fil-binjiet okkupati mis-Servizz tal-Asil ta' Ċipru fl-indirizz: 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Ċipru jew f'bini li jinsab fil-qrib.</P><P>Il-binjiet għandhom ikunu aċċessibbli mill-persunal, l-esperti u l-interpreti tal-EASO, mis-7:00 sal-22:00 fil-ġranet kollha tal-ġimgħa.</P><P>L-Aġenzija teħtieġ faċilitajiet/spazju għall-uffiċċji fuq l-art stmat ta' mill-inqas 250 m{^&gt;2&lt;^} sa massimu ta' 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Il-faċilitajiet/l-ispazju għall-uffiċċji għandhom ikunu tajbin biex jakkomodaw:</P><P>— 7 uffiċċji/kmamar għall-intervisti — li se jintużaw bħala kmamar għall-intervisti - li jakkomodaw 3-4 persuni f'daqqa,</P><P>— uffiċċju 1 għall-interpreti — biex jintuża bħala kamra għal-laqgħat/ta' stennija għall-interpreti kif ukoll biex l-interpreti jaħdmu separatament, jekk meħtieġ (traduzzjonijiet, telefonati ma' applikanti, eċċ.) — li jakkomoda 6-8 persuni f'daqqa,</P><P>— uffiċċju operattiv 1 — li jintuża bħala uffiċċju għall-Koordinatur tal-EASO u l-Assistent(i) Operattiv(i) u li jkollu biżżejjed spazju fl-uffiċċju għal-lokers tal-fajls għall-immaniġġjar tal-fajls (fajls ta' każijiet skedati, fajls li qed jistennew opinjoni, eċċ.) — li jakkomoda 3 persuni f'daqqa u jipprovdi biżżejjed spazju fl-uffiċċju għal-lokers tal-fajls, flimkien mal-istazzjonijiet tax-xogħol,</P><P>— kċina 1 b'faċilitajiet xierqa (bank, armarji, sink),</P><P>— 2 kmamar tal-banju/tojlits — 1 għall-persunal u 1 għall-applikanti,</P><P>— kamra 1 għal diversi użi — biex tintuża wkoll bħala kamra għall-istampatur, kamra għal-laqgħat, kamra ta' stennija għall-applikanti waqt il-pawża jew kif meħtieġ — li takkomoda 15-16-il persuna f'daqqa,</P><P>— kamra 1 għall-ħażna.</P><P>L-uffiċċji jrid ikollhom biżżejjed spazju biex ikunu mgħammra bi stazzjonijiet tax-xogħol, fejn meħtieġ (l-għamara u t-tagħmir tat-TIK).</P><P>Jekk gwardja/i tas-sigurtà permanenti mhumiex disponibbli/offruti, l-EASO għandu jkun jista' jkollu l-gwardi tas-sigurtà tiegħu stess u jinstalla s-sistemi ta' kontroll tas-sigurtà meħtieġa. Barra minn hekk, jekk servizz ta' reception ma jkunx disponibbli, l-EASO għandu jkun permess li jkollu l-persunal tar-reception tiegħu stess u li jistabbilixxi faċilitajiet xierqa bit-tagħmir u l-għamara meħtieġa. Għal dan l-għan, l-ispazju meħtieġ fis-sular t'isfel/tad-dħul għandu jsir disponibbli mill-Kuntrattur, flimkien mal-ispazju għall-uffiċċji meħtieġ imniżżel hawn fuq.</P><P>Il-bini sħiħ għandu jkun kopert b'sistema integrata ta' detezzjoni tan-nar (ditekters tad-duħħan u tas-sħana, pannelli f'każ ta' nar). Huwa meħtieġ ħruġ iddedikat għall-evakwazzjoni f'kull sular.</P><P>Il-provvista u punti tal-elettriku, il-provvista tal-ilma sħun u kiesaħ, it-tisħin/tkessiħ/arja kkondizzjonata, il-konnessjonijiet tad-drenaġġ għandhom ikunu mwaħħla u konnessi mas-servizzi muniċipali/pubbliċi.</P><P>Fil-każ li l-EASO jeħtieġ li jwettaq adattamenti strutturali, id-dokumenti ta' appoġġ meħtieġa biex jinkisbu l-permessi meħtieġa għax-xogħlijiet ta' kostruzzjoni, u ftehim mas-sidien kollha tal-bini, fejn meħtieġ, għandhom ikunu pprovduti mill-Kuntrattur.</P><P>L-EASO għandu, bi qbil mal-Kuntrattur, jkun jista' jagħmel adattamenti mhux strutturali, fuq spiża tiegħu, sabiex jinstalla oġġetti u jagħmel titjib żgħir fil-binjiet tiegħu.</P><P>Il-Kuntrattur għandu jkun responsabbli mill-assigurazzjoni tal-binjiet, biex ikopri ħsarat bażiċi bħal nar, serq, tifwir tal-ilma u ħsarat simili, matul iż-żmien tal-kiri.</P><P>Il-Kuntrattur għandu jkun responsabbli li jsolvi kwalunkwe problema li tista' tinqala' fir-rigward tas-servizzi tekniċi kollha, inkluża l-provvista tal-enerġija, il-provvista tal-ilma, id-drenaġġ, ir-rimi tal-iskart u l-ventilazzjoni, kif ukoll għat-tiswija immedjata tal-ħsara relatata li ma tistax tiġi attribwita għall-EASO.</P><P>Is-servizzi ta' tindif għandhom jiġu pprovduti kif ġej:</P><P>Ix-xogħlijiet li għandhom jitwettqu kuljum:</P><P>— Tbattil tal-laned taż-żibel, tibdil tal-liners tal-plastik, jekk meħtieġ, u t-tneħħija tal-iskart mill-kontejners komunali,</P><P>— Tfarfir u msiħ bl-ilma tal-uċuħ mikxufa kollha,</P><P>— Tindif u knis tal-art u tal-madum tal-ħajt,</P><P>— Tindif, knis u diżinfezzjoni tal-kmamar tal-banju, inkluż tojlits, sinkijiet, tqegħid ta' karta iġenika, xugamani tal-karti u fornimenti meħtieġa oħra,</P><P>— Tindif, knis u diżinfezzjoni tal-kċina, inkluż is-sink u l-uċuħ kollha, tqegħid ta' xugamani tal-karti u fornimenti meħtieġa oħra.</P><P>Ix-xogħlijiet li għandhom jitwettqu kull xahar:</P><P>— Tindif fil-fond u diżinfezzjoni tat-tojlits,</P><P>— Tfarfir u tindif tal-unitajiet tat-tisħin/tkessiħ,</P><P>— Tindif tal-ħġieġ kollu fuq il-bibien ta' ġewwa u/jew diviżorji.</P><P>Ix-xogħlijiet li għandhom jitwettqu darba kull tliet (3) xhur:</P><P>— Tindif tat-twieqi kollha u l-ħġieġ tal-bibien ta' barra, jekk ikun hemm,</P><P>— Tindif ta' purtieri u blinds, jekk ikun hemm.</P><P>3.2 Id-dati tal-għeluq</P><P>Il-binjiet għandhom ikunu disponibbli f'April tal-2018.</P><P>3.3 Il-proċedura</P><P>Din il-proċedura ta' tiftix għall-proprjetà se tintemm bl-għażla preliminari ta' mhux iktar minn 3 applikanti li l-binjiet tagħhom jistgħu jissodisfaw l-ħtiġijiet. L-EASO se jistieden lill-applikant(i) li jintgħażel (jintgħażlu) fil-fażi preliminari biex jidħol (jidħlu) f'negozjati f'fażi oħra sussegwenti li hija distinta minn din il-proċedura. L-ispeċifikazzjonijiet tekniċi ddettaljati se jintbagħtu lill-applikant(i) magħżula minn qabel. L-applikant(i) mistiedna se jkunu infurmati dwar il-kontenut meħtieġ</P><P>tal-proposti u d-dokumenti li għandhom jiġu pprovduti. Mat-tfigħ tal-proposta, kull applikant magħżul minn qabel għandu jiżgura:</P><P>— li l-proposta tiegħu se tibqa' tgħodd sakemm ikun iffirmat il-kuntratt,</P><P>— li kwalunkwe dokument li għandu x'jaqsam mal-binjiet se jingħata skont id-dati tal-għeluq li jingħataw mill-EASO.</P><P>Dan l-avviż bl-ebda mod ma jorbot lill-EASO f'dak li għandu x'jaqsam mal-proċeduri tal-għoti tal-kuntratt. L-EASO jżomm id-dritt, f'kull waqt qabel l-iffirmar tal-kuntratt, li jwaqqaf jew iħassar din il-proċedura, u l-applikanti ma jkollhom l-ebda dritt li jitolbu xi kumpens. Qabel jew matul il-fażi tal-innegozjar, l-EASO mhux se jiffirma l-ebda kuntratt ta' esklussività jew klawżoli simili favur applikant.</P><P>3.4 It-tip ta' kuntratt</P><P>L-itwal tul ta' żmien totali tal-ftehim ta' kiri se jkun għaxar (10) xhur, li jista' jiġġedded sa 3 darbiet iktar għal 12-il xahar kull darba għal tul ta' żmien totali ta' 3 snin u 10 xhur.</P><P>Il-ftehim ta' kiri għandu jkopri l-ispejjeż tal-kiri u s-servizzi anċillari. L-EASO għandu jkun jista' jħassar il-ftehim ta' kiri u s-servizzi anċillari b'avviż minn xahar qabel.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-ħtiġijiet relatati mat-talbiet biex wieħed jieħu sehem fil-proċedura nnegozjata</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Il-kontenut</P><P>L-informazzjoni li tinsab fit-talba biex wieħed jieħu sehem għandha tingħata permezz tal-formoli li ġejjin:</P><P>1) Il-formola ta' identifikazzjoni u dikjarazzjoni bid-data u l-firma kif xieraq (li tindika d-dettalji tal-applikant; id-dettalji tas-sid – jekk differenti; l-indirizz sħiħ tal-binjiet; il-konferma li s-servizzi meħtieġa minimi għandhom ikunu pprovduti). Il-formola hija disponibbli fuq: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Id-deskrizzjoni tal-meded tal-art; dijagrammi (pavimenti, faċċati, taqsimiet) u pjanti li juru t-tqassim bażiku (fil-każ ta' dubju, jistgħu jintalbu tpinġijiet fuq skala ta' 1/50 jew 1/100 jew 1/200);</P><P>4.2 It-tfigħ tat-talbiet biex wieħed jieħu sehem fil-proċedura nnegozjata</P><P>It-talbiet biex wieħed jieħu sehem fil-proċedura nnegozjata, flimkien mal-informazzjoni meħtieġa taħt il-punt 4.1, għandhom jintbagħtu b'Email lil contracts@easo.europa.eu sad-9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-evalwazzjoni tal-proposti fit-tieni fażi (il-proċedura nnegozjata):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-proposti li jaslu mill-applikant(i) magħżul(a) minn qabel li ma jkunux jaqblu u/jew ma jimxux mal-qasam tar-riċerka u/jew il-medda tal-art li hi mfittxija kif imsemmi fil-punt 3 ta' dan l-avviż, se jitwarrbu. Jekk l-applikanti jispiċċaw imwarrba, huma se jkunu mgħarrfa kif xieraq.</P><P>Il-proposti li jikkwalifikaw se jkunu analizzati skont il-kriterji marbuta mal-kwalità u l-prezz skont il-punteġġi li ġejjin:</P><P>— il-prezz (40 %),</P><P>— il-kwalità (60 %).</P><P>Il-kwalità tal-offerta (Q) se tkun iddeterminata fuq il-bażi tal-elementi li ġejjin (100 punt):</P><P>— Kemm ikun fiżikament viċin tal-bini okkupat mis-Servizz tal-Asil ta' Ċipru (ref. 3.1., l-ewwel paragrafu): 55 punt (il-minimu meħtieġ: 35),</P><P>— Id-distribuzzjoni tal-ispazju fil-binjiet - id-distribuzzjoni tal-ispazju għall-uffiċċji, il-kamra ta' stennija u l-possibilità ta' espansjoni tal-uffiċċji se tkun evalwata: 30 punt (il-minimu meħtieġ: 18),</P><P>— Il-miżuri ta' sikurezza u sigurtà fil-binjiet (flimkien mal-ħtiġijiet minimi indikati fil-punt II.) – il-preżenza ta' sigurtà fiżika (gwardji), twaħħil ta' apparat għat-tifi tan-nar, ħruġ ta' emerġenza u pjanijiet ta' evakwazzjoni, eċċ. se jiġu evalwati: 15-il punt (il-minimu meħtieġ: 7).</P><P>Il-klassifika tal-offerti se tkun ibbażata fuq punteġġ aħħari (F) skont il-formula li ġejja:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-kuntatti u tagħrif addizzjonali:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-applikanti se jkunu infurmati dwar l-għażla minn qabel tagħhom jew id-deċiżjoni li ma jkunux mistiedna għall-proċedura nnegozjata. Ma jista' jsir ebda kuntatt bejn l-applikanti u l-EASO, ħlief fejn ikun meħtieġ li tingħata kjarifika dwar l-avviż ta' tiftix għall-proprjetà. It-talba għal kjarifika għandha ssir bil-miktub lil contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Ogłoszenie o rozpoznaniu rynku nieruchomości w celu zaspokojenia potrzeb Europejskiego Urzędu Wsparcia w dziedzinie Azylu w zakresie powierzchni biurowych</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Wyznaczona Agencja UE</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europejski Urząd Wsparcia w dziedzinie Azylu</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Przedmiot ogłoszenia:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europejski Urząd Wsparcia w dziedzinie Azylu (EASO) udziela wsparcia na rzecz Cypru w ramach specjalnego planu wsparcia podpisanego z rządem Cypru. W ramach planu Agencja deleguje swoich pracowników, a także ekspertów i tłumaczy ustnych w celu zapewnienia wsparcia w zakresie konkretnych środków. Aby zapewnić personelowi, ekspertom i tłumaczom przestrzeń roboczą, EASO planuje pozyskać obiekty/powierzchnie biurowe spełniające minimalne wymogi określone poniżej oraz dodatkowe usługi sprzątania.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis zamówienia i procedury</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Minimalne wymogi</P><P>EASO poszukuje powierzchni biurowej znajdującej się w pomieszczeniach zajmowanych przez cypryjską Służbę Azylową pod adresem 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nikosia, Cypr lub w sąsiednim budynku.</P><P>Pomieszczenia powinny być dostępne dla pracowników Urzędu, ekspertów i tłumaczy ustnych od godziny 7:00 do 22:00 we wszystkie dni tygodnia.</P><P>Agencja wymaga, aby szacowana powierzchnia obiektów/powierzchni biurowych powyżej poziomu gruntu wynosiła przynajmniej 250 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}, lecz nie więcej niż 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Obiekty/przestrzeń biurowa powinny pomieścić:</P><P>— 7 biur/pomieszczeń do przeprowadzania rozmów — zdolne pomieścić 3-4 osoby jednocześnie,</P><P>— 1 biuro tłumaczy ustnych — do wykorzystania jako sala spotkań/poczekalnia dla tłumaczy ustnych oraz, w razie potrzeby, przez tłumaczy ustnych do samodzielnej pracy (tłumaczenia pisemne, rozmowy z wnioskodawcami itp.) - zdolne pomieścić 6-8 osób jednocześnie,</P><P>— 1 biuro operacyjne — do wykorzystania jako biuro dla koordynatora Urzędu i asystenta(-ów) operacyjnego(-ych), z wystarczającą powierzchnią biurową dla szaf na dokumenty (akta zaplanowanych spraw, akta oczekujące na opinię itp.) — mogące pomieścić 3 osoby na raz i zapewnić wystarczającą przestrzeń biurową dla szaf na akta oraz stanowisk roboczych,</P><P>— 1 kuchnia z odpowiednimi udogodnieniami (blat, szafki, zlewozmywak),</P><P>— 2 łazienki/toalety — 1 dla pracowników oraz 1 dla wnioskodawców,</P><P>— 1 pomieszczenie wielofunkcyjne — do wykorzystania również jako pomieszczenie do drukowania, sala konferencyjna, poczekalnia dla wnioskodawców w czasie przerwy lub w razie potrzeby — mogące pomieścić co najmniej 15-16 osób jednocześnie,</P><P>— 1 pomieszczenie do przechowywania.</P><P>Biura muszą dysponować, w razie potrzeby, wystarczającą powierzchnią do wyposażenia ich w stanowiska pracy (meble i sprzęt teleinformatyczny).</P><P>Jeżeli pracownicy ochrony nie są dostępni/proponowani, EASO może posiadać własnych pracowników ochrony i instalować wymagane systemy kontroli bezpieczeństwa. Ponadto, jeżeli nie można skorzystać z usług recepcji, Urząd może dysponować własnym personelem i wybrać odpowiednie pomieszczenia z wymaganymi meblami i wyposażeniem. W tym celu wykonawca udostępni niezbędną przestrzeń na poziomie parteru/wejścia, oprócz wymaganej powierzchni biurowej wymienionej powyżej.</P><P>Cały budynek powinien być objęty zintegrowanym systemem wykrywania pożaru (czujki dymu i ciepła, centrale sygnalizacji pożaru). Wymagane jest specjalne wyjście ewakuacyjne na każdym piętrze.</P><P>Zaopatrzenie w energię i punkty poboru energii elektrycznej, zaopatrzenie w ciepłą i zimną wodę, ogrzewanie/chłodzenie/klimatyzacja oraz przyłącza kanalizacyjne muszą być zainstalowane i podłączone do sieci komunalnej/publicznej.</P><P>W przypadku gdy Urząd będzie musiał przeprowadzić dostosowania konstrukcji, wykonawca udostępni dokumenty niezbędne w celu uzyskania wymaganych pozwoleń na budowę oraz, w razie potrzeby, zgodę wszystkich właścicieli.</P><P>Urząd, w porozumieniu z wykonawcą, będzie mógł na własny koszt przeprowadzić prace niezwiązane z konstrukcją w celu zainstalowania elementów lub wprowadzenia drobnych ulepszeń w pomieszczeniach.</P><P>Wykonawca ponosi odpowiedzialność za ubezpieczenie budynków, w celu pokrycia podstawowych szkód, takich jak pożar, kradzież, zalanie i podobnych szkód, przez cały okres najmu.</P><P>Wykonawca jest odpowiedzialny za rozwiązanie wszelkich problemów związanych z usługami technicznymi dotyczącymi zasilania, wodociągów, kanalizacji, usuwania odpadów i wentylacji, jak również za natychmiastową naprawę szkód z tym związanych, które nie wynikają z winy EASO.</P><P>Usługi sprzątania świadczone będą w następujący sposób:</P><P>Czynności wykonywane codziennie:</P><P>— opróżnianie koszy na śmieci, w razie potrzeby wymiana plastikowych worków oraz wywóz odpadów do pojemników zbiorczych,</P><P>— odkurzanie i wycieranie na mokro wszystkich powierzchni,</P><P>— zamiatanie/czyszczenie i mycie podłóg oraz kafelków na ścianach,</P><P>— czyszczenie, zamiatanie i dezynfekcja sanitariatów, w tym toalet, zlewozmywaków/umywalek, zapewnianie papieru toaletowego, ręczników papierowych i innych niezbędnych materiałów,</P><P>— czyszczenie, zamiatanie i dezynfekcja kuchni, w tym zlewu i wszystkich powierzchni, zapewnianie ręczników papierowych i innych niezbędnych materiałów.</P><P>Czynności wykonywane raz w miesiącu:</P><P>— dogłębne mycie i dezynfekcja toalet,</P><P>— odkurzanie i czyszczenie urządzeń grzewczych/chłodzących,</P><P>— mycie szklanych powierzchni drzwi i/lub ścian działowych.</P><P>Czynności wykonywane raz na 3 miesiące:</P><P>— mycie wszystkich okien i szklanych powierzchni drzwi zewnętrznych, jeśli takie są,</P><P>— czyszczenie zasłon i rolet, jeśli takie są.</P><P>3.2. Terminy</P><P>Pomieszczenia powinny zostać udostępnione w kwietniu 2018 r.</P><P>3.3 Procedura</P><P>Niniejsza procedura rozpoznania zakończy się wstępnym wyborem maksymalnie 3 propozycji umożliwiających zaspokojenie zapotrzebowania. EASO może zaprosić wybranego(-ych) w ten sposób oferenta(-ów) do podjęcia negocjacji na późniejszym odrębnym etapie po niniejszej procedurze. Szczegółowe specyfikacje techniczne zostaną wysłane do wstępnie wybranego (-ych) kandydata (-ów). Zaproszeni kandydaci zostaną poinformowani o wymaganej treści</P><P>wniosków oraz o dokumentach, które należy złożyć. Wraz ze złożeniem wniosku każdy wstępnie wybrany wnioskodawca gwarantuje:</P><P>— ważność oferty do czasu ewentualnego podpisania umowy,</P><P>— udostępnienie wszelkich dokumentów dotyczących budynku w terminach wyznaczonych przez EASO.</P><P>Niniejsza publikacja nie stanowi w żadnym wypadku zobowiązania ze strony EASO w ramach procedur udzielania zamówień. Do czasu podpisania umowy EASO zastrzega sobie prawo do odstąpienia od zamówienia lub unieważnienia niniejszej procedury. Oferenci nie mają wówczas prawa do dochodzenia odszkodowania. Przed etapem negocjacji lub w jego trakcie EASO nie podpisze żadnej umowy o wyłączności ani żadnej podobnej klauzuli na korzyść oferenta.</P><P>3.4 Rodzaj zamówienia</P><P>Całkowity maksymalny okres trwania umowy najmu wyniesie dziesięć (10) miesięcy, z możliwością 3-krotnego przedłużenia każdorazowo na dodatkowy okres 12 miesięcy, na łączny okres 3 lat i 10 miesięcy.</P><P>Umowa najmu obejmuje koszty dzierżawy i usługi pomocnicze. EASO może wypowiedzieć umowę dzierżawy i usługi pomocnicze z zachowaniem jednomiesięcznego okresu wypowiedzenia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Wymogi dotyczące wniosków o dopuszczenie do udziału w procedurze negocjacyjnej</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Treść</P><P>Informacje zawarte we wniosku o dopuszczenie do udziału w postępowaniu należy przedłożyć na następujących formularzach:</P><P>1) należycie podpisany i opatrzony datą formularz identyfikacyjny i zgłoszeniowy (ze wskazaniem danych wnioskodawcy; danych właściciela – jeżeli jest to inna osoba; pełnego adresu siedziby; potwierdzenia świadczenia usług na minimalnym wymaganym poziomie). Formularz dostępny jest w witrynie internetowej pod adresem: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Opis powierzchni; rysunki (podłogi, elewacje, przekroje) oraz plany przedstawiające standardowy układ (w razie wątpliwości mogą być wymagane rysunki w skali 1/50 lub 1/100 lub 1/200);</P><P>4.2 Składanie wniosków o dopuszczenie do udziału w procedurze negocjacyjnej</P><P>Wnioski o dopuszczenie do udziału w procedurze negocjacyjnej wraz z informacjami wymaganymi w pkt 4.1 należy przesłać pocztą elektroniczną na adres contracts@easo.europa.eu do dnia 9.4.2018 r.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ocena wniosków w drugim etapie (procedura negocjacyjna):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Oferty otrzymane od wstępnie wybranych kandydatów niezgodne z wymogami lub nieodpowiadające zakresowi poszukiwań lub wymaganej powierzchni zgodnie z pkt 3 niniejszego ogłoszenia zostaną odrzucone. Oferenci, których oferta budynku zostanie wykluczona, otrzymają stosowną informację.</P><P>Akceptowalne oferty zostaną przeanalizowane na podstawie kryteriów jakości i ceny według następującej punktacji:</P><P>— cena (40%),</P><P>— jakość (60 %).</P><P>Jakość (Q) oferty zostanie oceniona na podstawie następujących elementów (100 pkt):</P><P>— Fizyczna bliskość budynku zajmowanego przez cypryjską służbę azylową (nr ref. 3.1, pierwszy akapit): 55 punktów (wymagane minimum: 35),</P><P>Rozkład powierzchni w lokalu – ocenione zostaną rozkład powierzchni biurowych, poczekalnia i możliwość rozbudowy biur: 30 punktów (wymagane minimum: 18),</P><P>— Oceniane będą środki bezpieczeństwa i ochrony w pomieszczeniach (oprócz minimalnych wymagań określonych w pkt II.) – obecność zabezpieczeń fizycznych (ochrony), instalacja gaśnic przeciwpożarowych, obecność wyjść ewakuacyjnych i planów ewakuacji itp: 15 punktów (wymagane minimum: 7).</P><P>Oferty zostaną sklasyfikowane na podstawie oceny końcowej (F) zgodnie z następującym wzorem:</P><P>F = (60 % x jakość) + (40 % x cena)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontakt i dodatkowe informacje:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kandydaci zostaną poinformowani o ich wstępnej selekcji do udziału w procedurze negocjacyjnej lub decyzji o odrzuceniu. Zakazuje się wszelkich kontaktów między wnioskodawcami a Urzędem, z wyjątkiem sytuacji, w których konieczne byłoby udzielenie wyjaśnień dotyczących ogłoszenia o rozpoznaniu rynku nieruchomości. Wnioski o wyjaśnienia należy przesyłać w formie pisemnej na adres contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Oznámenie o vyhľadávaní nehnuteľností na splnenie požiadaviek na kancelárske priestory pre Európsky podporný úrad pre azyl</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zodpovedná agentúra EÚ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európsky podporný úrad pre azyl</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predmet obstarávania:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Európsky podporný úrad pre azyl (EASO) poskytuje podporu Cypru v rámci plánu osobitnej podpory, ktorý bol podpísaný s cyperskou vládou. V rámci plánu nasadí agentúra svojich zamestnancov, ako aj odborníkov a tlmočníkov na poskytnutie podpory špecifických opatrení. S cieľom zabezpečiť pracovné priestory pre zamestnancov, odborníkov a tlmočníkov hľadá EASO na prenájom zariadenia/kancelárske priestory v súlade s minimálnymi požiadavkami uvedenými ďalej a doplnkové upratovacie služby.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis obstarávania a postup, ktorý sa má uplatniť</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Minimálne požiadavky</P><P>EASO ma v úmysle prenajať si kancelárske priestory situované v priestoroch využívaných Cypriot Asylum Service na adrese 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Cyprus, alebo v susediacej budove.</P><P>Priestory musia byť prístupné zamestnancom EASO, odborníkom a tlmočníkom od 7:00 do 22:00 všetky dni v týždni.</P><P>Agentúra požaduje nadzemné zariadenia/kancelárske priestory s odhadovanou rozlohou minimálne 250 a maximálne 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>V zariadeniach/kancelárskych priestoroch musí byť priestor na:</P><P>— 7 kancelárií/vyšetrovacích miestností, ktoré sa budú používať ako vyšetrovacie miestnosti s kapacitou 3 – 4 osoby,</P><P>— 1 kanceláriu pre tlmočníkov, ktorú budú tlmočníci využívať ako zasadaciu miestnosť/čakáreň a v prípade potreby tiež na samostatnú prácu (preklady, telefonovanie so žiadateľmi, atď.), s kapacitou 6-8 osôb,</P><P>— 1 prevádzkovú kanceláriu, ktorá sa bude používať ako kancelária koordinátora a operačných asistentov EASO, s dostatkom priestoru na skrinky na spisy za účelom správy spisov (spisov týkajúcich sa plánovaných prípadov, spisov čakajúcich na vyjadrenie, atď.), s kapacitou 3 osoby a s dostatkom priestoru na skrinky na spisy k pracovným miestam,</P><P>— 1 kuchynku s príslušným vybavením (pult, skrinky, drez),</P><P>— 2 toalety: 1 pre zamestnancov, 1 pre žiadateľov,</P><P>— 1 viacúčelovú miestnosť, ktorá sa bude používať ako miestnosť pre tlačiareň, zasadacia miestnosť, čakáreň pre žiadateľov počas prestávok alebo podľa potreby, s kapacitou 15 – 16 osôb,</P><P>— 1 skladovacia miestnosť.</P><P>V kanceláriách musí byť dostatok priestoru na vybavenie pracovnými stanicami, kde sa to vyžaduje (nábytkom a zariadením IKT).</P><P>V prípade, že trvalá bezpečnostná služba nie je k dispozícii/ponúkaná, musí sa EASO umožniť disponovať vlastnou bezpečnostnou službou a nainštalovať požadované systémy bezpečnostnej kontroly. Navyše, ak nie sú dostupné služby recepcie, musí sa EASO umožniť disponovať vlastnými zamestnancami recepcie a zariadiť priestory potrebným nábytkom a vybavením. S týmto cieľom poskytne dodávateľ, okrem požadovaného kancelárskeho priestoru uvedeného vyššie, potrebný priestor na úrovni pozemku / vstupu.</P><P>Celá budova bude vybavená integrovaným systémom hlásenia požiaru (detektormi dymu a tepla, protipožiarnymi panelmi). Vyžaduje sa vyhradený núdzový východ na každom podlaží.</P><P>Na mieste musia byť zavedené a pripojené na mestské/verejné služby: elektrická sieť a elektrické zásuvky, dodávka teplej a studenej vody, kúrenie/chladenie/klimatizácia a kanalizačné prípojky.</P><P>V prípade, že bude EASO musieť vykonať štrukturálne úpravy, na požiadanie poskytne dodávateľ podporné dokumenty na získanie požadovaných stavebných povolení a súhlas všetkých majiteľov budovy.</P><P>Po dohode s dodávateľom musí mať EASO povolené vykonať na vlastné náklady neštrukturálne úpravy s cieľom inštalácie položiek alebo drobných zdokonalení priestorov.</P><P>Dodávateľ je v dobe prenájmu zodpovedný za poistenie budov pokrývajúce základné škody ako je požiar, krádež, vytopenie a podobne.</P><P>Dodávateľ bude zodpovedný za vyriešenie akýchkoľvek problémov v súvislosti s technickými službami, ktoré by mohli nastať, vrátane dodávky elektrickej energie a vody, kanalizácie, odvozu odpadu a ventilácie, ako aj za okamžitú opravu súvisiacich škôd, ktoré nie je možné pripísať EASO.</P><P>Upratovacie služby budú poskytované nasledujúcim spôsobom:</P><P>Úlohy, ktoré musia byť vykonávané denne:</P><P>– vysypanie košov, v prípade potreby výmena plastového sáčku a odvoz odpadu z komunálnych kontajnerov,</P><P>– utieranie prachu a utieranie na mokro všetkých nekrytých plôch,</P><P>– čistenie a zametanie podlahy a obkladačiek,</P><P>– čistenie, zametanie a dezinfekcia hygienických zariadení vrátane toaliet, drezov/umývadiel, umiestňovanie toaletného papiera, papierových utierok a ďalších potrebných tovarov,</P><P>– čistenie, zametanie a dezinfekcia kuchyne, vrátane drezu a všetkých plôch, umiestňovanie papierových utierok a ďalších potrebných tovarov.</P><P>Úlohy, ktoré musia byť vykonávané mesačne:</P><P>– dôkladné čistenie a dezinfekcia toaliet,</P><P>– utieranie prachu na vykurovacích/chladiacich jednotkách a ich čistenie,</P><P>– čistenie všetkých sklenených plôch na vnútorných dverách a/alebo prepážkach.</P><P>Úlohy, ktoré musia byť vykonávané každé 3 mesiace:</P><P>– čistenie všetkých okien a skiel vonkajších dverí, ak existujú,</P><P>– čistenie závesov a žalúzii, ak existujú.</P><P>3.2 Konečné termíny</P><P>Priestory musia byť k dispozícii v apríli 2018.</P><P>3.3 Konanie</P><P>Toto vyhľadávacie konanie bude ukončené predbežným výberom 3 uchádzačov, ktorých objekty umožňujú splnenie požiadaviek. EASO v ďalšej fáze vyplývajúcej z tohto konania vyzve uchádzača (uchádzačov) na základe predbežného výberu na začatie rokovaní. Podrobné technické špecifikácie budú zaslané predbežne vybranému (vybraným) uchádzačovi (uchádzačom). Pozvaný uchádzač bude informovaný (pozvaní uchádzači budú informovaní) o obsahu</P><P>návrhov a dokumentov, ktoré majú byť predložené. Predložením návrhu každý predbežne vybraný uchádzač zaručuje:</P><P>— že jeho návrh zostane v platnosti až do podpísania akejkoľvek zmluvy,</P><P>— že všetky dokumenty týkajúce sa objektov budú poskytnuté do konečného termínu stanoveného EASO.</P><P>Toto oznámenie nie je pre EASO nijako záväzné, čo sa týka konania v súvislosti s pridelením obstarávania. EASO si vyhradzuje právo kedykoľvek pred podpísaním zmluvy upustiť od konania alebo ho zrušiť bez toho, aby uchádzači mali nárok na akékoľvek odškodnenie. EASO nepodpíše pred alebo počas rokovacej fázy žiadnu zmluvu o výlučnosti ani podobné klauzuly v prospech niektorého uchádzača.</P><P>3.4 Typ obstarávania</P><P>Celkové trvanie nájomnej zmluvy je maximálne 10 (desať) mesiacov s možnosťou predĺženia 3-krát, vždy o 12 mesiacov, na celkové trvanie 3 rokov a 10 mesiacov.</P><P>Nájomná zmluva musí pokryť náklady na prenájom a doplnkové služby. EASO môže zrušiť nájomnú zmluvu a doplnkové služby s výpovednou lehotou 1 mesiaca.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Požiadavky týkajúce sa žiadostí o účasť na rokovacom konaní</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Obsah</P><P>Informácie obsiahnuté v žiadosti o účasť musia byť predložené s použitím nasledovných formulárov:</P><P>1) Identifikačný formulár a formulár vyhlásenia, riadne datovaný a podpísaný (s podrobne uvedenými údajmi o uchádzačovi a majiteľovi – ak nie je totožný, úplná adresa priestorov, potvrdenie, že budú poskytnuté minimálne požadované služby). Tento formulár je dostupný na: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Popis povrchových plôch; výkresy (podlažia, fasády, prierezy) a plány zobrazujúce štandardnú rozlohu (v prípade pochybnosti môžu byť požadované nákresy v merítku 1/50 alebo 1/100 alebo 1/200);</P><P>4.2 Predloženie žiadostí o účasť na rokovacom konaní</P><P>Žiadosť o účasť na rokovacom konaní, s priloženými informáciami požadovanými v bode 4.1, musí byť zaslaná do 9.4.2018 emailom na contracts@easo.europa.eu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Posudzovanie návrhov v druhej fáze (rokovacie konanie):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Návrhy obdržané od predbežne vybraného (vybraných) uchádzača (uchádzačov), ktoré nebudú vyhovovať a/alebo nespĺňajú oblasť vyhľadávania a/alebo požadovanú povrchovú plochu, ako je uvedené v bode 3 tohto oznámenia, budú odmietnuté. Navrhovatelia vylúčených objektov o tom budú riadne informovaní.</P><P>Spôsobilé návrhy sa budú analyzovať na základe kvality a kritérií ceny v súlade s týmto váhovaním:</P><P>— cena (40 %),</P><P>— kvalita (60 %).</P><P>Kvalita ponuky (Q) sa stanoví na základe týchto položiek (100 bodov):</P><P>— fyzická blízkosť k budove využívanej Cypriot Asylum Service (bod 3.1., prvý odstavec): 55 bodov (požadované minimum: 35),</P><P>— priestorové rozloženie – bude hodnotené rozloženie kancelárskych priestorov, čakární a možnosť rozšírenia kancelárii: 30 bodov (požadované minimum: 18),</P><P>— bezpečnostné a ochranné opatrenia v priestoroch (okrem minimálnych požiadaviek popísaných v bode II.) – bude hodnotená prítomnosť fyzickej ochrany (stráží), inštalácia hasiacich prístrojov, evakuačné plány a plány núdzových východov atď.: 15 bodov (požadované minimum: 7).</P><P>Klasifikácia ponúk bude vychádzať z konečného počtu bodov (F) v súlade s týmto vzorcom:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontakty a ďalšie informácie:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uchádzači budú informovaní o ich predbežnom výbere alebo rozhodnutí, že nebudú pozvaní na rokovacie konanie. Akýkoľvek kontakt medzi uchádzačmi a EASO je zakázaný, s výnimkou potreby objasnenia ohľadne oznámenia o vyhľadávaní nehnuteľností. Žiadosti o objasnenie musia byť zaslané písomne na contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Obvestilo o iskanju nepremičnin za izpolnitev zahtev glede pisarniškega prostora Evropskega azilnega podpornega urada</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Odgovorna agencija EU</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropski azilni podporni urad</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predmet iskanja:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Evropski azilni podporni urad (EASO) podpira Ciper v okviru posebnega podpornega načrta, sklenjenega z vlado Cipra. Agencija v okviru načrta napotuje svoje osebje ter strokovnjake in tolmače za zagotavljanje podpore v okviru posebnih ukrepov. Da bi zagotovil delovni prostor za svoje osebje, strokovnjake in tolmače, želi EASO najeti objekte/pisarniške prostore v skladu z minimalnimi zahtevami, navedenimi v nadaljevanju, in pomožne storitve čiščenja.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis naročila in postopka, ki bo uporabljen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Minimalne zahteve</P><P>EASO želi najeti pisarniške prostore, ki se nahajajo v prostorih, ki jih zaseda ciprska azilna služba, na naslovu 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Ciper ali v sosednji stavbi.</P><P>Prostori morajo biti osebju, strokovnjakom in tolmačem EASO na voljo vse dni v tednu od 7:00 do 22:00.</P><P>Ocenjena površina nadzemnih objektov/pisarniških prostorov, ki jih potrebuje agencija, je od 250 do 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Objekti/pisarniški prostori morajo biti primerni za namestitev:</P><P>— 7 pisarn/prostorov za razgovore, ki se bodo uporabljali kot prostori za razgovore in ki lahko sprejmejo 3–4 osebe hkrati,</P><P>— 1 pisarne za tolmače, ki se bo uporabljala kot sejna soba/čakalnica za tolmače in po potrebi za samostojno delo tolmačev (prevodi, klici s prosilci itd.) in ki lahko sprejme 6–8 oseb hkrati,</P><P>— 1 operativne pisarne, ki se bo uporabljala kot pisarna za koordinatorja in operativnega(-e) asistenta(-e) EASO, nudila dovolj prostora za omarice z datotekami za upravljanje dokumentov (datoteke načrtovanih primerov, datoteke, ki čakajo na mnenja, itd.) ter ki lahko sprejme 3 osebe hkrati in zagotovi dovolj pisarniškega prostora za omarice z datotekami, poleg delovnih postaj,</P><P>— 1 kuhinje z ustrezno opremo (pultom, omarami, koritom),</P><P>— 2 toaletnih prostorov/stranišč, 1 za osebje in 1 za prosilce,</P><P>— 1 večnamenskega prostora, ki se bo uporabljal tudi kot prostor za tiskanje, sejna soba, čakalnica za prosilce med odmori ali po potrebi in ki lahko sprejme najmanj 15–16 oseb hkrati,</P><P>— 1 prostora za shranjevanje.</P><P>Pisarne morajo vključevati dovolj površin, ki se po potrebi opremijo z delovnimi postajami (pohištvom in opremo IKT).</P><P>Če stalni varnostnik(-i) ni(-so) na voljo/ponujen(-i), lahko EASO uporabi svoje varnostnike in namesti potrebne sisteme varnostnega nadzora. Če storitev recepcije ni na voljo, lahko EASO uporabi svoje osebje za delo na recepciji in vzpostavi ustrezne prostore s potrebnim pohištvom in opremo. Izvajalec mora v ta namen poleg zgoraj navedenih pisarniških prostorov zagotoviti tudi potreben prostor v pritličju/pri vhodu.</P><P>Celotna stavba mora biti pokrita z integriranim sistemom za odkrivanje ognja (detektorji dima in toplote, protipožarne plošče). Zahteva se poseben zasilni izhod na vsakem nadstropju.</P><P>Zagotovljeni morajo biti oskrba z električno energijo in priključki, oskrba s toplo in hladno vodo, ogrevanje/hlajenje/prezračevanje ter kanalizacijski priključki v okviru komunalnih/javnih storitev.</P><P>V primeru, da mora EASO izvesti strukturne prilagoditve, mora izvajalec zagotoviti potrebno podporno dokumentacijo za pridobitev potrebnih dovoljenj za gradbena dela in po potrebi soglasje vseh lastnikov stavbe.</P><P>EASO lahko v dogovoru z izvajalcem na lastne stroške izvede nestrukturne prilagoditve za namestitev predmetov ali majhne izboljšave prostorov.</P><P>Izvajalec je v obdobju trajanja najema odgovoren za zavarovanje stavbe in kritje osnovne škode, kot je požar, kraja, poplava in podobna škoda.</P><P>Izvajalec je odgovoren za reševanje morebitnih težav, ki bi se lahko pojavile v zvezi z vsemi tehničnimi storitvami, vključno z oskrbo z električno energijo, oskrbo z vodo, kanalizacijo, odstranjevanjem odpadkov in prezračevanjem, ter za takojšnje popravilo povezane škode, ki se ne more pripisati EASO.</P><P>Storitve čiščenja se bodo zagotavljale na naslednji način:</P><P>naloge, ki se opravljajo vsak dan:</P><P>— praznjenje košev za odpadke, po potrebi zamenjava plastičnih vrečk in odlaganje odpadkov v komunalne zabojnike,</P><P>— brisanje prahu in mokro brisanje vseh izpostavljenih površin,</P><P>— čiščenje in brisanje tal in stenskih ploščic,</P><P>— čiščenje, brisanje in razkuževanje toaletnih prostorov, vključno s stranišči, koriti/umivalniki, oskrba s toaletnim papirjem, papirnatimi brisačami in drugimi potrebnimi sredstvi,</P><P>— čiščenje, brisanje in razkuževanje kuhinje, vključno s koritom in vsemi površinami, oskrba s papirnatimi brisačami in drugimi potrebnimi sredstvi.</P><P>Naloge, ki se opravljajo enkrat mesečno:</P><P>— globinsko čiščenje in razkuževanje stranišč,</P><P>— brisanje prahu in čiščenje enot za ogrevanje/hlajenje,</P><P>— čiščenje stekel na notranjih vratih in/ali predelnih stenah.</P><P>Naloge, ki se opravljajo vsake 3 mesece:</P><P>— čiščenje vseh oken in stekel na zunanjih vratih, če obstajajo,</P><P>— čiščenje zaves in senčil, če obstajajo.</P><P>3.2 Skrajni roki</P><P>Prostori morajo biti na voljo aprila 2018.</P><P>3.3 Postopek</P><P>Ta postopek iskanja nepremičnin bo sklenjen s predizborom največ 3 kandidatov, katerih prostori omogočajo izpolnjevanje potreb. EASO bo predhodno izbranega(-e) kandidata(-e) povabil k začetku pogajanj v naslednji fazi, ki je ločena od tega postopka. Podrobne tehnične specifikacije bodo poslane predhodno izbranemu(-im) kandidatu(-om). Povabljeni kandidat(-i) bo(-do) obveščen(-i) o zahtevani vsebini</P><P>predlogov in dokumentih, ki jih je treba predložiti. S predložitvijo predloga vsak predhodno izbrani kandidat zagotavlja:</P><P>— da bo njegov predlog veljaven do podpisa kakršne koli pogodbe,</P><P>— da bodo vsi dokumenti o prostorih predloženi v skrajnih rokih, ki jih določi EASO.</P><P>To obvestilo urada EASO na noben način ne zavezuje glede postopkov za oddajo naročila. EASO si pridržuje pravico, da se v katerem koli trenutku pred podpisom pogodbe odpove ali prekliče ta postopek, ne da bi bili kandidati upravičeni do odškodnine. Pred ali med fazo pogajanj EASO ne bo podpisal nobenih ekskluzivnih pogodb ali podobnih klavzul v prid kandidata.</P><P>3.4 Vrsta naročila</P><P>Skupno najdaljše trajanje pogodbe o najemu bo 10 mesecev z možnostjo 3 podaljšanj, vsakič za dodatno 12-mesečno obdobje, kar pomeni skupno trajanje 3 let in 10 mesecev.</P><P>Pogodba o najemu bo zajemala stroške najema in pomožne storitve. EASO lahko pogodbo o najemu in pomožne storitve prekliče z enomesečnim predhodnim obvestilom.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zahteve glede prijav za sodelovanje v postopku s pogajanji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Vsebina</P><P>Informacije, ki jih vsebuje prijava za sodelovanje, je treba predložiti z uporabo naslednjih obrazcev:</P><P>(1) obrazca za identifikacijo in izjavo, ustrezno opremljenega z datumom in podpisom (z navedbo podatkov kandidata; podatkov lastnika – če je drugačen; polnega naslova prostorov; potrditve, da bodo minimalne zahtevane storitve zagotovljene). Obrazec je na voljo na: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>(2) Opis površin; risbe (tla, fasade, prečni prerezi) in načrti, ki izkazujejo standardno ureditev (v primeru dvoma se lahko zahtevajo risbe v merilu 1:50 ali 1:100 ali 1:200);</P><P>4.2 Predložitev prijav za sodelovanje v postopku s pogajanji</P><P>Prijave za sodelovanje v postopku s pogajanji, skupaj z zahtevanimi informacijami iz točke 4.1, je treba poslati po e-pošti na contracts@easo.europa.eu do 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ocena predlogov v drugi fazi (postopek s pogajanji):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Predlogi, prejeti od predhodno izbranih kandidatov, ki niso skladni in/ali ne upoštevajo področja raziskave in/ali iskane površine, kot je opredeljeno v točki 3 tega obvestila, ne bodo upoštevani. Kandidati izključenih prostorov bodo o tem ustrezno obveščeni.</P><P>Upravičeni predlogi bodo analizirani na podlagi merila kakovosti in cenovnega merila v skladu z naslednjim ponderiranjem:</P><P>— cena (40 %),</P><P>— kakovost (60 %).</P><P>Kakovost ponudbe (Q) bo določena na podlagi naslednjih elementov (100 točk):</P><P>— fizična bližina stavbe, ki jo zaseda ciprska azilna služba (glej točko 3.1., prvi odstavek): 55 točk (zahtevani minimum: 35),</P><P>— razdelitev prostora v prostorih – ocenjeni bodo razdelitev pisarniškega prostora, območje čakalnice in možnost razširitve pisarn: 30 točk (zahtevani minimum: 18),</P><P>— ukrepi za zaščito in varnost v prostorih (poleg minimalnih zahtev iz točke II) – ocenjeni bodo prisotnost varnostnikov, namestitev gasilnih aparatov, zasilni izhodi in načrti za evakuacijo itd.: 15 točk (zahtevani minimum: 7).</P><P>Razvrstitev ponudb bo temeljila na končnem rezultatu (F), pridobljenem z naslednjo formulo:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontaktne točke in dodatne informacije:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kandidati bodo obveščeni o svojem predizboru ali o odločitvi, da ne bodo vabljeni k postopku s pogajanji. Stiki med kandidati in EASO so prepovedani, razen v primeru, da je potrebno pojasnilo glede obvestila o iskanju nepremičnin. Prošnjo za pojasnilo je treba poslati v pisni obliki na contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Fógra um chuardach réadmhaoine chun freastal ar riachtanais spás don Oifig Tacaíochta Eorpach do Chúrsaí Tearmainn</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Gníomhaireacht fhreagrach an AE</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Oifig Eorpach um Thacaíocht don Chóras Tearmainn</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Málta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cuspóir an chuardaigh:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Soláthraíonn an Oifig Tacaíochta Eorpach do Chúrsaí Tearmainn (EASO) tacaíocht don Chipir i gcreat Plean Tacaíochta Speisialta arna shíniú le Rialtas na Cipire. Is i gcreat an Phlean a imlonnaíonn an Gníomhaireacht a cuid foirne, maille le saineolaithe agus ateangairí, chun tacaíocht a sholáthar faoi bhearta sonracha. Chun spás oibre a áirithiú don fhoireann, saineolaithe agus ateangairí tá EASO ag féachaint le saoráidí/spás oifige a léasú i gcomhréir leis na híosriachtanais thíos, agus le seirbhísí glantacháin choimhdeacha.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ar an gconradh agus ar an nós imeachta le bheith curtha i bhfeidhm</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Íosriachtanais</P><P>Tá EASO ag iarraidh spás oifige a léasú atá suite san áitreabh atá áitithe ag Seirbhís Tearmainn na Cipire ag 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, an Chipir nó i bhfoirgneamh in aice láimhe.</P><P>Ba cheart go mbeadh an t-áitreabh inrochtana d’fhoireann EASO, saineolaithe agus ateangairí idir 7:00 agus 22:00 gach lá den tseachtain.</P><P>Teastaíonn saoráidí os cionn na talún/spás oifige ón nGníomhaireacht d’íosmhéid 250 go huasmhéid 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Ba chóir go mbeadh na saoráidí/an spás oifige oiriúnach chun feidhmiú mar chóiríocht do:</P><P>— 7 n-oifig/seomra agallóireachta — le húsáid mar sheomraí agallóireachta - chun 3-4 duine a óstáil in aghaidh na huaire,</P><P>— 1 oifig d’ateangairí — le húsáid mar sheomra cruinnithe/feithimh d’ateangairí agus freisin d ‘ateangairí a oibríonn ar leithligh, má theastaíonn (aistriúcháin, glaonna le hiarratasóirí, etc.) — chun idir 6-8 daoine a óstáil in aghaidh na huaire,</P><P>— 1 oifig d’oibríochtaí — le húsáid mar oifig do Chomhordaitheoir agus Cúntóir(í) Oibríochtaí EASO agus ina mbeidh dóthain spás oifige do thaisceadáin chomhad um bainistiú comhad (comhaid de chásanna sceidealaithe, comhaid ag feitheamh ar thuairimí, etc.) — chun 3 daoine a óstáil in aghaidh na huaire agus dóthain spás oifige a sholáthar do thaisceadáin chomhad, i dteannta leis na stáisiúin oibre,</P><P>— 1 chistin amháin le saoráidí iomchuí (cuntar, cupaird, doirteal),</P><P>— 2 sheomra scíthe/leithreas — 1 don fhoireann agus 1 d’iarratasóirí,</P><P>— 1 sheomra ilfheidhme amháin — le húsáid freisin mar sheomra printéirí, seomra cruinnithe, limistéar feithimh d’iarratasóirí le linn sosa nó de réir mar a theastaíonn — chun íoslíon 15-16 daoine a óstáil in aghaidh na huaire,</P><P>— 1 seomra stórála amháin.</P><P>Ba chóir go mbeadh dóthain spáis sna hoifigí lena bhfeistiú le stáisiúin oibre, de réir mar a theastaíonn (troscán agus trealamh TFC).</P><P>Mura mbíonn garda(í) slándála buan(a) ar fáil/ar tairiscint, ceadófar d’EASO a cuid gardaí slándála féin a bheith aici agus na córais rialaithe slándála riachtanacha a shuiteáil. Ina theannta sin, mura mbíonn seirbhís fáiltithe ar fáil, ceadófar d’EASO a baill foirne fáiltithe a bheith aici, agus chun saoráidí leordhóthanacha a bhunú leis an troscán agus trealamh riachtanach. Chun na críche sin, cuirfidh an Conraitheoir an spás riachtanach agus leibhéal na talún/na slí isteach ar fáil, i dteannta leis an spás oifige riachtanach thuasliostaithe.</P><P>Clúdófar an foirgneamh go léir le córas braite dóiteáin chomhtháite (braiteoirí deataigh agus teasa, painéil dóiteáin). Teastaíonn slí éalaithe thiomanta ar gach urlár.</P><P>Soláthar agus pointí leictreacha, soláthar uisce the agus fhuair, téamh/fuarú/aerchóireáil, ceangail séaraigh; beidh siad ann agus ceangailte le seirbhísí bardasacha/poiblí.</P><P>Sa chás go dteastaíonn ó EASO oiriúnuithe struchtúracha a fheidhmiú, soláthróidh an Conraitheoir na doiciméid tacaíochta riachtanacha chun na ceadanna riachtanacha a fháil do na hoibreacha tógála, agus comhaontú le gach úinéir foirgneamh, nuair a theastaíonn.</P><P>Ceadófar d’EASO, i gcomhaontú leis an gConraitheoir, oiriúnuithe neamhstruchtúrtha a dhéanamh, ar a chostais féin, chun míreanna a shuiteáil nó chun feabhsuithe beaga a dhéanamh don áitreabh.</P><P>Is é an conraitheoir a bheidh freagrach as árachas na bhfoirgneamh, chun damáistí bunúsacha a chlúdach ar nós dóiteáin, gadaíochta, róshreabhadh uisce agus damáistí comhchosúla, ar feadh fhad an léasa.</P><P>Is é an conraitheoir a bheidh freagrach as réiteach aon fhadhbanna a d’fhéadfadh teacht aníos i ndáil le gach seirbhís theicniúil, lena n-áirítear soláthar cumhachta, séarach, diúscairt dramhaíola agus aeráil, chomh maith le deisiú láithreach na ndamáistí gaolmhara nach EASO ba chúis leo.</P><P>Soláthrófar na seirbhísí glantacháin mar seo a leanas:</P><P>Tascanna le feidhmiú ar bhonn laethúil:</P><P>— Folmhú araidí, athsholáthar líneálacha plaisteacha, má theastaíonn, agus baint na dramhaíola chuig taisceadáin chomónta,</P><P>— Dustáil agus glanadh gach dromchla nochta le ceirtín tais,</P><P>— Glanadh agus scuabadh na n-urlár agus na dtíleanna balla,</P><P>— Glanadh, scuabadh agus dífhabhtú na seomraí scíthe, lena n-áirítear leithris, doirtil/báisíní níocháin, páipéar leithris, tuáillí páipéir agus soláthairtí riachtanacha eile a sholáthar,</P><P>— Glanadh, scuabadh agus dífhabhtú na cistine, lena n-áirítear an doirteal agus gach dromchla, tuáillí páipéir agus soláthairtí riachtanacha eile a sholáthar.</P><P>Tascanna le feidhmiú go míosúil:</P><P>— Domhainghlanadh agus dífhabhtú na leithreas,</P><P>— Dustáil agus glanadh na n-aonad téimh/fuaraithe,</P><P>— Glanadh gach gloine ar chomhlaí dorais agus/nó spiaraí inmheánacha.</P><P>Tascanna le feidhmiú gach trí (3) mhí:</P><P>— Glanadh gach fuinneoige agus gloine ar chomhlaí dorais seachtracha, más ann dóibh,</P><P>— Glanadh cuirtíní agus dallóg, más ann dóibh.</P><P>3.2 Spriocdhátaí</P><P>Beidh an t-áitreabh ar fáil i mí Aibreáin 2018.</P><P>3.3 Nós imeachta</P><P>Cuirfear an nós imeachta um chuardach seo i gcrích le réamhroghnú suas le 3 iarratasóirí a gcumasaítear sásamh na riachtanas lena n-áitreabh. Féadfaidh EASO cuireadh a thabhairt don iarratasóir (do na hiarratasóirí) réamhroghnaithe idirbheartaíocht a dhéanamh i gcéim ina dhiaidh sin a bheidh leithleach ón nós imeachta seo. Seolfar na sonraíochtaí teicniúla mionsonraithe chuig an iarratasóir/na hiarratasóirí réamhroghnaithe. Cuirfear an t-iarratasóir/do na hiarratasóirí ar an eolas faoin inneachar riachtanach</P><P>de thograí agus de na doiciméid atá le soláthar. Le taisceadh an togra, ráthóidh gach iarratasóir réamhroghnaithe an méid seo a leanas:</P><P>— go mbeidh an togra seo bailí go dtí go síneofar aon chonradh,</P><P>— go soláthrófar aon doiciméad a bhaineann leis an áitreabh laistigh de na spriocdhátaí atá forordaithe ag EASO.</P><P>Ní chuireann an fógra seo ceangal ar EASO ar chor ar bith maidir le nósanna imeachta um chonradh a dhámhachtain. Forchoimeádann EASO an ceart, ag am ar bith sula síneofar an conradh, cinneadh a dhéanamh gan an conradh a dhámhachtain nó an nós imeachta seo a chur ar ceal, agus ní bheidh iarratasóirí i dteideal cúitimh ar bith a éileamh. Ní shíneoidh EASO aon chonarthaí eisiachais ná clásail chomhchosúla i bhfabhar iarratasóra roimh an gcéim idirbheartaíochta nó le linn na céime idirbheartaíochta.</P><P>3.4 Cineál an chonartha</P><P>Is ionann uasfhad iomlán an chomhaontaithe léasa agus deich (10) mí, leis an bhféidearthacht é a shíneadh faoi 3 ar feadh tréimhse bhreise 12 mhí/an ceann ar feadh tréimhse iomlán de 3 bliana agus 10 mí.</P><P>Clúdófar leis an gcomhaontú léasaithe na costais léasa agus na seirbhísí coimhdeacha. Beidh EASO in ann an comhaontú léasaithe agus seirbhísí coimhdeacha a chealú le fógra mí amháin roimh ré.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Riachtanais i ndáil le hiarratais chun bheith rannpháirteach sa nós imeachta idirbheartaithe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Ábhar</P><P>Caithfear an t-eolas a fhaightear san iarratas chun bheith rannpháirteach a thaisceadh ach leas a bhaint as na foirmeacha seo a leanas:</P><P>1) Sainaithint agus foirm dhearbhúcháin arna dátú agus arna síniú go hiomchuí (lena dtásctar sonraí an iarratasóra; sonraí an úinéara – más éagsúil iad; seoladh iomlán an áitribh; deimhniú go soláthrófar na seirbhísí íosta a theastaíonn). Tá an fhoirm ar fáil ar: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Tuairisc ar na limistéir dhromchla; líníochtaí (urláir, aghaidheanna, trasghearrthaí) agus pleananna ina léirítear leagan amach caighdeánach (i gcás amhrais is féidir líníochtaí scála 1/50 nó 1/100 nó 1/200 a iarraidh);</P><P>4.2 Taisceadh iarratas chun bheith rannpháirteach sa nós imeachta idirbheartaithe</P><P>Iarratais chun bheith rannpháirteach, sa nós imeachta idirbheartaithe, i dteannta leis an bhfaisnéis a theastaíonn faoi phointe 4.1, caithfear iad a sheoladh trí ríomhphost chuig contracts@easo.europa.eu faoi 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Measúnú tograí sa dara céim (nós imeachta idirbheartaithe):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Na tograí a fhaightear ón iarratasóir/ó na hiarratasóirí nach bhfuil comhlíontach nó nach gcomhlíonann réimse an taighde agus/nó an t-achar dromchla arna iarraidh, de réir mar atá luaite i bpointe 3 den fhógra seo; is amhlaidh a dhiúscrófar iad. Cuirfear in iúl go cuí d'iarratasóirí na n-áitreabh eisiata.</P><P>Déanfar anailís ar thograí incháilithe ar bhonn na gcritéar cáilíochta agus praghais de réir na n-ualuithe seo a leanas:</P><P>— praghas (40 %),</P><P>— cáilíocht (60 %).</P><P>Déanfar cáilíocht (Q) na tairisceana a shocrú ar bhonn na n-eilimintí a leanas (100 pointe):</P><P>— Cóngaracht don fhoirgneamh atá áitithe ag Seirbhís Tearmainn na Cipire (tag. 3.1., an chéad mhír): 55 pointe (an t-íosmhéid atá riachtanach: 35),</P><P>— Leithdháileadh spáis san áitreabh - leithdháileadh spáis oifige, limistéir feithimh agus féidearthacht do mhéadú na n-oifigí; is amhlaidh a dhéanfar meastóireacht orthu: 30 pointe (an t-íosmhéid riachtanach: 18),</P><P>— Bearta slándála agus sábháilteachta san áitreabh (i dteannta leis na híosriachtanais a thásctar i bpointe II.) – (gardaí) slándála fisiciúla bheith ann, suiteáil múchtóirí dóiteáin, bealaí éalaithe agus pleananna aslonnaithe atá i bhfeidhm, etc.; is amhlaidh a dhéanfar meastóireacht orthu: 15 phointe (an t-íosmhéid riachtanach: 7).</P><P>Beidh aicmiú na dtairiscintí bunaithe ar scór deiridh (F) i gcomhréir leis an bhfoirmle seo a leanas:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Conarthaí agus faisnéis bhreise:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cuirfear iarratasóirí ar an eolas faoina réamhroghnú nó faoin gcinneadh gan cuireadh a thabhairt dóibh i leith an nós imeachta idirbheartaithe. Toirmisctear teagmháil ar bith idir iarratasóirí agus EASO, seachas i gcás mar a dteastódh soiléiriú maidir leis an bhfógra um chuardach maoine. Déanfar an t-iarratas ar shoiléiriú i scríbhinn chuig contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Обявление за проучване за недвижими имоти, отговарящи на изискванията на Европейска служба за подкрепа в областта на убежището</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Отговорна агенция на ЕС</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейска служба за подкрепа в областта на убежището</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Малта</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Цел на търсенето:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Европейската служба за подкрепа в областта на убежището (EASO) предоставя подкрепа на Кипър в рамките на специален план за подкрепа, подписан с правителството на Кипър. В рамките на плана Агенцията изпраща свой персонал, както и експерти и устни преводачи, за да предостави подкрепа по конкретни мерки. С цел да осигури работно място за служителите, експертите и устните преводачи, EASO търси да наеме съоръжения/офис пространство в съответствие с посочените по-долу минимални изисквания и свързани услуги за почистване.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Описание на поръчката и процедура, която ще бъде приложена</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Минимални изисквания</P><P>EASO търси да наеме офис пространство в помещенията, използвани от Службата по въпросите на убежището на Кипър, с адрес 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Кипър, или в съседна сграда.</P><P>Помещенията следва да бъдат достъпни за персонала, експертите и устните преводачи на EASO, от 7:00 ч. до 22:00 ч., през всички дни на седмицата.</P><P>Агенцията се нуждае от надземни съоръжения/офис пространство, приблизително с площ, не по-малка от 250 m{^&gt;2&lt;^} и не по-голяма от 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Съоръженията/офис пространството следва да бъдат подходящи за разполагането на:</P><P>— 7 офиса/стаи за провеждане на интервюта — които ще се използват като стаи за интервюта — които могат да поберат едновременно от 3 до 4 души,</P><P>— 1 офис за устни преводачи — който ще се използва като стая за срещи/чакалня за устните преводачи, а така също и при необходимост ще се използва от устните преводачи за самостоятелна работа (писмени преводи, телефонни разговори с кандидатите) — в който могат да се поберат едновременно от 6 до 8 души,</P><P>— 1 оперативен офис — който ще се използва като офис за координатора на EASO и оперативния(ите) асистент(и) и в който ще има достатъчно пространство за шкафове за документи за управление на досиетата (досиета на планирани за разглеждане случаи, досиета, изчакващи становище и др.) — в който могат да се поберат едновременно 3 души и има достатъчно пространство за шкафовете за документите в допълнение към работните станции,</P><P>— 1 кухня с подходящи съоръжения (работен плот, шкафове, мивка),</P><P>— 2 санитарни помещения/тоалетни — 1 за персонала и 1 за кандидатите,</P><P>— 1 мултифункционално помещение — което ще се използва като стая за печатане на документи, стая за срещи, чакалня за кандидатите по време на почивките или според необходимото — в което могат да се поберат едновременно 15–16 души,</P><P>— 1 складово помещение.</P><P>Офисите трябва да бъдат с достатъчно пространство, за да могат да бъдат оборудвани с работни станции, когато се изисква (обзавеждане и ИКТ оборудване).</P><P>Ако няма/не се предлага постоянна охрана, трябва да се разреши на EASO да разположи свои собствени охранители и да монтира необходимите системи за контрол на сигурността. Освен това, ако няма рецепция, трябва да се разреши на EASO да разположи свой собствен персонал за посрещане и подходящите съоръжения с необходимото обзавеждане и оборудване. За тази цел, изпълнителят трябва да осигури необходимото пространство на призмения/входния етаж в допълнение към посоченото по-горе необходимо офис пространство.</P><P>Цялата система трябва да бъде обхваната от интегрирана система за откриване на пожар (детектори за дим и топлина, противoпожарни табла). При всеки етаж се изисква специален изход за евакуация.</P><P>Трябва да има инсталации и точки за електрозахранване, снабдяване с гореща и топла вода, отопление/охлаждане/климатизация и канализация и те трябва да са свързани към общинските/обществените услуги.</P><P>В случай че EASO трябва да извърши конструктивни промени, изпълнителят трябва да осигури необходимите подкрепящи документи за получаване на изискваните разрешителни за строителните работи и съгласието на всички собственици на сградите, когато е необходимо.</P><P>На EASO трябва да бъде разрешено да извършва със съгласието на изпълнителя неконструктивни промени за своя собствена сметка, за да монтира съоръжения или за да направи дребни подобрения в помещенията.</P><P>Изпълнителят е длъжен да осигури застраховка на сградите, която да покрива основни щети, като щети в случай на пожар, кражба, наводнение и други сходни щети, за цялата продължителност на договора за наем.</P><P>Изпълнителят ще отговаря за разрешаването на всички проблеми, които могат да възникнат във връзка с всички технически услуги, включително електрозахранване, водоснабдяване, канализация, обезвреждане на отпадъци и вентилация, както и за незабавната поправка на свързаните щети, които не са причинени от EASO.</P><P>Услугите по почистване, които трябва да се предоставят, са следните:</P><P>Задачи, които трябва да се извършват ежедневно:</P><P>— изпразване на кошчетата за отпадъци, подмяна на пластмасовите торби за отпадъци, ако е необходимо, и изхвърляне на отпадъците в общите контейнери,</P><P>— почистване на прах и влажно забърсване на всички открити повърхности,</P><P>— почистване и метене на подови повърхности и облицовки на стени,</P><P>— почистване, метене и дезинфекциране на санитарните помещения, включително тоалетните, мивките/умивалниците, поставяне на тоалетна хартия, хартиени кърпи и други необходими консумативи,</P><P>— почистване, метене и дезинфекциране на кухнята, включително мивката и всички повърхности, поставяне на хартиени кърпи и други необходими консумативи.</P><P>Задачи, които трябва да се извършват веднъж месечно:</P><P>— дълбоко почистване и дезинфекциране на тоалетните,</P><P>— забърсване и почистване на уредите за отопление/охлаждане,</P><P>— почистване на всички стъкла на вътрешни врати и/или преградни стени.</P><P>Задачи, които трябва да се извършват веднъж на всеки три (3) месеца:</P><P>— почистване на всички прозорци и стъкла на външни врати, ако има такива,</P><P>— почистване на завеси и щори, ако има такива.</P><P>3.2 Крайни срокове</P><P>Помещенията трябва да бъдат на разположение през април 2018 г.</P><P>3.3 Процедура</P><P>Настоящата процедура за проучване ще приключи с предварителния подбор на не повече от 3 кандидати, чиито помещения дават възможност да бъдат изпълнени изискванията. EASO ще покани предварително избрания(те) кандидат(и) да започне(ат) преговори на следващ етап, различен от настоящата процедура. Подробните технически спецификации ще бъдат изпратени на предварително избрания(ите) кандидат(и). Поканеният(ите) кандидат(и) ще бъде(ат) информиран(и) за необходимото съдържание на</P><P>предложенията и документите, които трябва да се представят. С подаването на предложението всеки предварително избран кандидат гарантира:</P><P>— че неговото предложение ще остане валидно до подписването на евентуален договор,</P><P>— че всеки документ относно помещенията ще бъде представен в рамките на крайните срокове, посочени от EASO.</P><P>Настоящото обявление по никакъв начин не обвързва EASO по отношение на процедурата по възлагане на поръчки. EASO си запазва правото по всяко време преди подписването на договора да отмени или да анулира настоящата процедура, без кандидатите да имат право да изискват каквито и да било компенсации. Преди или по време на етапа на договаряне, EASO няма да подписва никакви договори за изключителни права или клаузи с подобен смисъл в полза на даден кандидат.</P><P>3.4 Вид на поръчката</P><P>Общата максимална продължителност на споразумението за наем ще бъде десет (10) месеца, с възможност за удължаване 3 пъти, всеки път с още 12 месеца, за обща продължителност от 3 години и 10 месеца.</P><P>Споразумението за наем трябва да обхваща разходите за наем и свързаните услуги. EASO трябва да има възможност да отмени споразумението за наем и свързаните услуги с едномесечно предизвестие.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Изисквания, свързани със заявленията за участие в процедурата на договаряне</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Съдържание</P><P>Информацията, съдържаща се в заявлението за участие, трябва да бъде изпратена, като се използват следните формуляри:</P><P>1) формуляр за идентификация и декларация, с надлежно отбелязана дата и подпис (в който са посочени данните на кандидата, данните на собственика, ако е различен, пълният адрес на помещенията, потвърждение, че ще бъдат предоставени минималните изисквани услуги). Формулярът е наличен на следния уебсайт: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/</P><P>Доставки</P><P>2) описание на площите, чертежи (етажи, фасади, напречни сечения) и планове със стандартно оформление (в случай на съмнение може да се поискат чертежи в мащаб 1/50, 1/100 или 1/200);</P><P>4.2 Подаване на заявленията за участие в процедурата на договаряне</P><P>Заявленията за участие в процедурата на договаряне, заедно с приложената към тях информация, която се изисква съгласно точка 4.1, трябва да се изпратят до 9.4.2018 г. по електронна поща на следния адрес: contracts@easo.europa.eu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Оценка на предложенията през втората фаза (процедура на договаряне):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Предложенията, които са получени от предварително избрания(ите) кандидат(и) и които не отговарят и/или не съответстват на областта на проучване и/или на изискваната площ, посочена в точка 3 от настоящото обявление, ще бъдат отхвърлени. Кандидатите, чиито предложения за помещения са изключени, ще бъдат надлежно уведомени.</P><P>Допустимите предложения ще бъдат анализирани въз основа на критериите за качество и цена в съответствие със следните тежести:</P><P>— цена (40 %),</P><P>— качество (60 %).</P><P>Качеството на офертата (Q) ще бъде определено въз основа на следните елементи (100 точки):</P><P>— физическа близост до сградата, заемана от Службата по въпросите на убежището на Кипър (вж. точка 3.1., първия параграф): 55 точки (изискван минимум: 35),</P><P>— разпределение на пространството в помещенията — ще се оценяват разпределението на офис пространството и възможността за разширяване на офисите: 30 точки (изискван минимум: 18),</P><P>— мерки за сигурност и безопасност в помещенията (в допълнение към минималните изисквания, посочени в точка II) — ще бъдат оценявани наличието на физическа охрана (охранители), наличието на монтирани пожарогасители, аварийни изходи и въведени планове за евакуация и др.: 15 точки (изискван минимум: 7).</P><P>Класификацията на офертите ще се определи въз основа на крайния резултат (F) в съответствие със следната формула:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Контакти и допълнителна информация:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Заявителите ще бъдат информирани, ако бъдат избрани предварително, или за решението да не бъдат поканени да участват в процедурата на договаряне. Забранен е всеки контакт между заявителите и EASO, освен в случаите, когато ще е необходимо да се предостави разяснение относно обявлението за проучване на недвижими имоти. Искането за разяснение трябва да се изпрати в писмен вид на следния адрес: contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Anunț de prospectare a pieței imobiliare pentru îndeplinirea cerințelor Biroului European de Sprijin pentru Azil</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Agenția UE responsabilă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Biroul European de Sprijin pentru Azil</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Obiectul studiului:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Biroul European de Sprijin pentru Azil (EASO) oferă sprijin Ciprului în cadrul unui Plan de Sprijin Special semnat cu Guvernul Ciprului. În cadrul Planului, Agenția își detașează personalul, precum și experții și interpreții, pentru a oferi sprijin cu privire la măsuri specifice. Pentru a asigura spațiul de lucru pentru personal, experți și interpreți, EASO caută să închirieze echipament/spații de birouri în conformitate cu cerințele minime de mai jos și servicii de curățenie auxiliare.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea contractului și a procedurii care va fi aplicată</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Cerințe minime</P><P>EASO dorește să închirieze spații de birouri situate în incinta ocupată de Serviciul Cipriot de Azil situat la adresa 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Cipru sau într-o clădire adiacentă.</P><P>Spațiile trebuie să fie accesibile personalului EASO, experților și interpreților de la ora 7:00 până la ora 22:00 în toate zilele săptămânii.</P><P>Agenția are nevoie de o suprafață estimată pentru incintă/spații de birouri de minimum 250 până la maxim 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Incinta / spațiile de birouri ar trebui să fie potrivite pentru a găzdui:</P><P>— 7 birouri / săli de interviu - pentru a fi utilizate ca săli de interviu - ce vor găzdui 3 - 4 persoane la un moment dat,</P><P>— 1 birou pentru interpreți - pentru a fi utilizat ca sală de ședințe/așteptare pentru interpreți și, de asemenea, de către interpreți pentru a lucra separat, dacă este nevoie (traduceri, apeluri cu solicitanții etc.) - ce va găzdui 6 - 8 persoane la un moment dat,</P><P>- 1 birou de operațiuni - ce va fi utilizat ca birou pentru Coordonatorul EASO și asistentul (asistenții) de operațiuni și va avea un spațiu de birouri suficient pentru dulapurile de acte necesare gestionării documentelor (dosare ale cazurilor programate, dosare care așteaptă avize, etc.) — pentru a găzdui 3 persoane la un moment dat și a oferi spațiu de birouri suficient pentru dulapurile de acte, în plus față de stațiile de lucru,</P><P>— 1 bucătărie cu facilități adecvate (blat de bucătărie, dulapuri, chiuvetă),</P><P>— 2 băi/toalete — 1 pentru personal și 1 pentru candidați,</P><P>— 1 cameră multifuncțională - poate fi utilizată și ca sală de imprimantă, sală de ședințe, zonă de așteptare pentru solicitanți în timpul pauzelor sau la nevoie — care să găzduiască minim 15 - 16 persoane la un moment dat,</P><P>— 1 cameră de depozitare.</P><P>Birourile trebuie să dispună de spațiu suficient pentru a fi echipate cu stații de lucru, acolo unde este necesar (mobilier și echipament TIC).</P><P>În cazul în care nu sunt disponibili/puși la dispoziție agenți de securitate permanenți, EASO va avea dreptul să aibă proprii agenți de securitate și să instaleze sistemele de securitate necesare. În plus, în cazul în care nu este disponibil un serviciu de recepție, EASO va avea dreptul să aibă personal propriu de recepție și să amenajeze instalații adecvate cu mobilierul și echipamentele necesare. În acest scop, spațiul necesar la parter/intrare va fi pus la dispoziția contractantului, în plus față de spațiul de birouri necesar, menționat mai sus.</P><P>Întreaga clădire va fi acoperită de un sistem integrat de detectare a incendiilor (detectoare de fum și căldură, panouri de incendiu). Este necesară o ieșire de evacuare specială pe fiecare etaj.</P><P>Surse și puncte de alimentare cu energie electrică, alimentare cu apă caldă și rece, surse de încălzire / răcire / climatizare, racordarea la canalizare trebuie să fie instalate și conectate la serviciile municipale/publice.</P><P>În cazul în care EASO trebuie să efectueze adaptări structurale, contractantul trebuie să pună la dispoziție documentele justificative necesare în vederea obținerii autorizațiilor care se impun pentru lucrările de construcție și acordul tuturor proprietarilor de clădiri, la nevoie.</P><P>EASO va avea dreptul, în acord cu contractantul, să efectueze adaptări nestructurale, pe cheltuiala proprie, pentru a instala elemente sau pentru a aduce mici îmbunătățiri spațiilor.</P><P>Contractantul este responsabil pentru asigurarea clădirilor, pentru a acoperi daunele de bază cum ar fi incendiul, furtul, deversările de apă și daunele similare, pe întreaga durată a contractului de închiriere.</P><P>Contractantul va fi responsabil pentru rezolvarea oricăror probleme care ar putea apărea în legătură cu toate serviciile tehnice, inclusiv sursa de alimentare, alimentarea cu apă, canalizarea, eliminarea deșeurilor și ventilația, precum și pentru repararea imediată a avariilor aferente care nu pot fi puse pe seama EASO.</P><P>Serviciile de curățenie sunt furnizate după cum urmează:</P><P>Sarcini care trebuie executate zilnic:</P><P>— Golirea coșurilor de gunoi, înlocuirea garniturilor de plastic, dacă este necesar, și eliminarea deșeurilor în containerele colective,</P><P>— Ștergerea de praf și ștergerea umedă a tuturor suprafețelor expuse,</P><P>— Curățarea și maturarea pardoselilor și curățarea plăcilor de perete,</P><P>— Curățarea, igienizarea și dezinfectarea grupurilor sanitare, inclusiv a toaletelor, chiuvetelor, aprovizionarea cu hârtie igienică, prosoape de hârtie și alte consumabile necesare,</P><P>— Curățarea, igienizarea și dezinfectarea bucătăriei, inclusiv chiuveta și toate suprafețele, aprovizionarea cu prosoape de hârtie și alte consumabile necesare.</P><P>Sarcini care trebuie executate o dată pe lună:</P><P>— Curățarea și dezinfectarea temeinică a toaletelor,</P><P>— Ștergerea de praf și curățarea unităților de încălzire/răcire,</P><P>— Curățarea tuturor geamurilor la ușile și / sau pereții despărțitori din interior.</P><P>Sarcini care trebuie executate o dată la trei (3) luni:</P><P>— Curățarea tuturor ferestrelor și a geamului de pe ușile exterioare, dacă există,</P><P>— Curățarea perdelelor și jaluzelelor, dacă există.</P><P>3.2 Termene-limită</P><P>Spațiile vor fi disponibile în aprilie 2018.</P><P>3.3 Procedură</P><P>Prezenta procedură de prospectare se va încheia cu preselecția a maximum 3 candidați ale căror spații să permită îndeplinirea cerințelor. EASO va invita candidatul (candidații) preselectat (preselectați) să inițieze negocieri în cadrul unei etape ulterioare distincte de prezenta procedură. Specificațiile tehnice detaliate vor fi trimise candidatului (candidaților) preselectat (preselectați). Candidatul (candidații) invitat (invitați) va (vor) fi informat (informați) cu privire la conținutul necesar al</P><P>Propunerilor și documentelor care trebuie furnizate. Odată cu depunerea propunerii, fiecare candidat preselectat garantează:</P><P>— validitatea propunerii sale până la eventuala semnare a contractului,</P><P>— punerea la dispoziție a oricărui document privind spațiile în termenele-limită specificate de EASO.</P><P>Prezentul anunț nu constituie în niciun caz un angajament pentru EASO în cadrul procedurilor de atribuire de contracte. EASO își rezervă dreptul, până la semnarea contractului, de a renunța sau de a anula prezenta procedură, fără ca respectivii candidați să poată pretinde vreo compensație. EASO nu va semna, înainte sau pe parcursul etapei de negociere, niciun contract de exclusivitate sau vreo clauză similară în favoarea unui candidat.</P><P>3.4 Tipul contractului</P><P>Durata maximă totală a contractului de închiriere va fi de zece (10) luni, cu posibilitatea de prelungire de 3 ori pentru o durată suplimentară de 12 luni / fiecare pentru o durată totală de 3 ani și 10 luni.</P><P>Contractul de închiriere acoperă costurile de închiriere și serviciile auxiliare. EASO poate anula contractul de închiriere și serviciile auxiliare cu un preaviz de o lună.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cerințe referitoare la cererile de participare la procedura negociată</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Conținutul</P><P>Informațiile din cererea de participare trebuie trimise folosind următoarele formulare:</P><P>1) Formularul de identificare și declarație, datat și semnat corespunzător (indicând detaliile candidatului, detaliile proprietarului - dacă este diferit, adresa completă a sediului, confirmarea că vor fi furnizate serviciile minime solicitate). Formularul este disponibil la adresa: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Descrierea suprafețelor; desene (pardoseli, fațade, secțiuni transversale) și planuri care prezintă o dispunere standard (în caz de îndoială pot fi cerute desene la scară de 1/50 sau 1/100 sau 1/200);</P><P>4.2 Depunerea cererilor de participare la procedura negociată</P><P>Cererile de participare la procedura negociată, însoțite de informațiile cerute la punctul 4.1, trebuie trimise prin e-mail la contracts@easo.europa.eu până la data de 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Evaluarea propunerilor în faza a doua (procedura de negociere):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Propunerile primite din partea candidatului (candidaților) preselectat (preselectați) care sunt neconforme și/sau care nu respectă perimetrul de prospectare și/sau suprafața dorită, astfel cum sunt menționate la punctul 3 din prezentul anunț, vor fi respinse. Candidații pentru spațiile excluse vor fi informați în mod corespunzător.</P><P>Ofertele eligibile vor fi analizate pe baza criteriilor privind calitatea și prețul, în conformitate cu următoarele ponderi:</P><P>— prețul (40%),</P><P>— calitatea (60%).</P><P>Calitatea ofertei (Q) va fi determinată pe baza următoarelor elemente (100 de puncte):</P><P>— Apropierea fizică față de clădirea ocupată de Serviciul Cipriot de Azil (ref. 3.1., primul alineat): 55 puncte (cerința minimă: 35),</P><P>— Distribuția spațiului în incintă - distribuția spațiilor de birouri, a zonei de așteptare și posibilitatea de extindere a birourilor va fi evaluată: 30 puncte (cerința minimă: 18),</P><P>— Măsuri de securitate și siguranță pentru spații (în plus față de cerințele minime indicate la punctul II) - va fi evaluată prezența securității fizice (gardieni), instalarea stingătoarelor de incendiu, ieșirile de urgență și planurile de evacuare etc.: 15 puncte (cerința minimă: 7).</P><P>Clasificarea ofertelor se va baza pe un punctaj final (F) conform următoarei formule:</P><P>F = (60% x Q) + (40% x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Puncte de contact și informații suplimentare:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Candidații vor fi informați cu privire la preselecția lor sau privind decizia de a nu fi invitați la procedura negociată. Orice contact între candidați și EASO este interzis, cu excepția cazului în care sunt necesare clarificări cu privire la anunțul de prospectare imobiliară. Cererea de clarificare se face în scris la adresa contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>MT-Valletta: Obavijest o predviđanjima za nekretnine radi ispunjavanja zahtjeva za uredskim prostorijama Europskog potpornog ureda za azil</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Odgovorna agencija EU-a</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europski potporni ured za azil</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, MTC Block A, Winemakers Wharf, Grand Harbour </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Valletta</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MRS 1917, Malta</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predmet istraživanja:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europski potporni ured za azil (EASO) pruža potporu Cipru u okviru plana posebne potpore potpisane s vladom Cipra. U okviru Plana, Agencija upućuje svoje osoblje, kao i stručnjake i tumače kako bi pružila potporu specifičnim mjerama. Kako bi se osiguralo radno mjesto za osoblje, stručnjake i prevoditelje, EASO želi iznajmiti objekte/uredski prostor u skladu s minimalnim zahtjevima u nastavku i pomoćne usluge čišćenja.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis ugovora i postupka koji će se primjenjivati</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.1 Najmanji zahtjevi</P><P>EASO želi zakupiti uredski prostor koji se nalazi u objektima koje koristi Ciparska služba azila na 70 Archbishop Makarios III Avenue, Afemia House, 1077 Nicosia, Cipru ili u susjednoj zgradi.</P><P>Prostori bi trebali biti dostupni osoblju EASO-a, stručnjacima i tumačima od 7:00 do 22:00 svih dana u tjednu.</P><P>Agencija zahtijeva procjenu nadzemnih objekata/uredskih prostora od najmanje 250 do maksimalno 320 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}.</P><P>Objekti/uredski prostor bi trebali biti prikladni za smještaj:</P><P>— 7 ureda/soba za razgovor — koji će se koristiti kao sobe za razgovore — koje istovremeno mogu primiti 3-4 osobe,</P><P>— 1 ureda za prevoditelje — koji će se koristiti kao sastajalište/čekaonica za tumače te za odvojeni rad tumača, ako je potrebno (prevođenje, pozivi s prijaviteljima, itd.) — koji istovremeno može primiti 6-8 osoba,</P><P>— 1 operativnog ureda — koji će se koristiti kao ured za koordinatora i operativne asistente za EASO i imati dovoljno uredskog prostora za ormariće za vođenje spisa (spise za dogovorene predmete, spise za predmete koji čekaju na mišljenje itd. — koji istovremeno može primiti 3 osobe i koji osim radnih stanica ima i dovoljno uredskog prostora za ormariće za spise,</P><P>— 1 kuhinje s odgovarajućim sadržajima (pult, ormari, sudoper),</P><P>— 2 sanitarne prostorije/zahoda — 1 za osoblje i 1 za prijavitelje,</P><P>—1 višenamjenske sobe — koja se također može koristi kao soba za pisač, soba za sastanke, čekaonica za prijavitelje tijekom stanke ili prema potrebi — može istovremeno primiti najmanje 15-16 osoba,</P><P>— 1 prostorije za skladištenje.</P><P>Uredi moraju imati dovoljno prostora za opremanje radnim stanicama, gdje je to potrebno (namještaj i ICT oprema).</P><P>Ako stalni zaštitari nisu dostupni/ponuđeni, EASO-u će biti dopušteno imati svoje zaštitare i instalirati potrebne sigurnosne sustave kontrole. Osim toga, ako usluga prijema nije dostupna, EASO-u će biti dopušteno imati vlastito prijemno osoblje i postaviti odgovarajuće objekte s potrebnim namještajem i opremom. U tu svrhu, Izvoditelj će pored gore navedenog potrebnog uredskog prostora staviti na raspolaganje i potrebni prostor na razini tla/ulaza.</P><P>Cijela zgrada mora biti pokrivena integriranim sustavom detekcije požara (detektori dima i topline, vatrogasne ploče). Na svakom katu potreban je poseban izlaz za evakuaciju.</P><P>Opskrba električnom energijom i točke, opskrba toplom i hladnom vodom, grijanje/hlađenje/klimatizacija, priključci kanalizacije moraju biti na mjestu i spojeni na usluge komunalnih/javnih službi.</P><P>U slučaju da EASO mora izvršiti strukturne prilagodbe, izvoditelj će staviti na raspolaganje potrebne popratne dokumente za dobivanje potrebnih dozvola za građevinske radove i suglasnost svih vlasnika zgrada, kada je to potrebno.</P><P>EASO-u će, u dogovoru s Izvoditeljem, biti dopušteno napraviti ne-strukturne prilagodbe, na vlastiti trošak, kako bi se instalirali predmeti ili izvela mala poboljšanja u prostorijama.</P><P>Izvoditelj je odgovoran za osiguranje zgrade, kako bi pokrio osnovne štete kao što su požar, krađa, poplava i slične štete, tijekom cijelog trajanja najma.</P><P>Izvoditelj je odgovoran za rješavanje svih problema koji mogu nastati vezano na sve tehničke usluge, uključujući opskrbu električnom energijom, vodoopskrbu, kanalizaciju, zbrinjavanje otpada i ventilaciju, kao i za hitno popravljanje povezanih šteta koje se ne mogu pripisati EASO-u.</P><P>Usluge čišćenja pružat će se kako slijedi:</P><P>Poslovi koje treba obavljati svakodnevno:</P><P>— pražnjenje košara za otpatke, eventualna zamjena plastičnih vreća za otpatke i uklanjanje otpada u komunalne spremnike,</P><P>— brisanje prašine i mokro brisanje svih izloženih površina,</P><P>— pranje i brisanje podova i zidnih pločica,</P><P>— pranje, brisanje i dezinficiranje sanitarnih prostorija, uključujući i zahode, umivaonike, stavljanje toaletnog papira, papirnatih ručnika i drugih potrepština,</P><P>— pranje, brisanje i dezinficiranje kuhinje, uključujući sudoper i sve površine, postavljanje papirnatih ručnika i drugih potrepština.</P><P>Poslovi koje treba obavljati jednom mjesečno:</P><P>— dubinsko čišćenje i dezinfekcija zahoda,</P><P>— brisanje prašine i čišćenje jedinica za grijanje/hlađenje,</P><P>— pranje svih staklenih površina na unutarnjim vratima i/ili pregradama.</P><P>Poslovi koje treba obavljati svaka 3 mjeseca:</P><P>— pranje svih prozora i staklenih površina na vanjskim vratima, ako ih ima,</P><P>— pranje zavjesa i roleta, ako ih ima.</P><P>3.2 Rokovi</P><P>Prostori će biti dostupni u travnju 2018.</P><P>3.3 Postupak</P><P>Postupak traženja nekretnina zaključit će se prethodnim odabirom najviše 3 prijavitelja čiji će prostori omogućiti ispunjavanje zahtjeva. EASO će pozvati prethodno odabranog(e) ponuditelja(e) da stupi u pregovore u kasnijoj fazi koja će se razlikovati od ovog postupka. Detaljne tehničke specifikacije bit će poslane prethodno odabranim prijaviteljima. Pozvani prijavitelji bit će obaviješteni o traženom sadržaju</P><P>Prijedlozi i dokumenti koji će biti dostavljeni. Podnošenjem prijedloga, svaki prethodno odabrani prijavitelj jamči:</P><P>— da će njegova ponuda biti valjana do potpisivanja bilo kojeg ugovora,</P><P>— da će dostaviti sve dokumente o prostoru unutar rokova koje je propisao EASO.</P><P>Ova obavijest ni na koji način ne obvezuje EASO u vezi postupaka sklapanja ugovora. EASO zadržava pravo odustajanja od ili otkazivanja ovog postupka u bilo kojem trenutku prije potpisivanja ugovora, pri čemu natjecatelji neće imati pravo na potraživanje novčanih naknada. Prije ili tijekom faze pregovaranja, EASO neće potpisati nikakve ugovore o isključivosti ili slične klauzule u korist natjecatelja.</P><P>3.4 Vrsta ugovora</P><P>Najduže trajanje ugovora o najmu iznosi deset (10) mjeseci, s mogućnošću produženja 3 puta za dodatno trajanje od 12 mjeseci/svaki za ukupno trajanje od 3 godine i 10 mjeseci.</P><P>Ugovor o najmu pokriva troškove najma i pomoćne usluge. EASO će moći otkazati ugovor o najmu i pomoćne usluge prethodnom obavijesti dostavljenom mjesec dana unaprijed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uvjeti koji se odnose na zahtjeve za sudjelovanje u pregovaračkom postupku</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>4.1 Sadržaj</P><P>Informacije sadržane u zahtjevu za sudjelovanje moraju se dostaviti na sljedećim obrascima:</P><P>1) Obrazac za identifikaciju i deklaraciju, uredno datiran i potpisan (navodeći podatke o prijavitelju, podatke o vlasniku – ako se razlikuju, punu adresu objekta, potvrdu da će se osigurati minimalno potrebne usluge). Obrazac je dostupan na: https://www.easo.europa.eu/about-us/Procurement</P><P/><P>2) Opis nadzemnih površina; nacrti (podovi, fasade, poprečni presjeci) i planovi koji prikazuju standardni izgled (u slučaju sumnje mogu se zatražiti nacrti u mjerilu 1/50 ili 1/100 ili 1/200);</P><P>4.2 Podnošenje zahtjeva za sudjelovanje u pregovaračkom postupku</P><P>Zahtjevi za sudjelovanje u pregovaračkom postupku, zajedno s podacima iz točke 4.1., moraju se poslati e-poštom na contracts@easo.europa.eu do 9.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procjena prijedloga u drugoj fazi (pregovarački postupak):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ponude zaprimljene od odabranih prijavitelja koje nisu u skladu i/ili koje ne obuhvaćaju područje istraživanja i/ili traženu površinu kako je navedeno u točki 3. ove obavijesti, neće se ocjenjivati. Natjecatelji koji su podnijeli ponude za prostore koje su isključene bit će valjano obaviješteni.</P><P>Prihvatljive ponude analizirat će se na temelju kriterija kvalitete i cjenovnog kriterija u skladu sa sljedećim ponderima:</P><P>— cijena (40 %),</P><P>— kvaliteta (60 %).</P><P>Kvaliteta ponude (Q) odredit će se na temelju sljedećih elemenata (100 bodova):</P><P>— fizička blizina zgrade koju zauzima Ciparska služba azila (ref. 3.1., prvi stavak): 55 bodova (traženi minimum: 35),</P><P>— raspored prostora u objektima - ocjenjivat će se raspored uredskog prostora, čekaonice i mogućnost proširenja ureda: 30 bodova (traženi minimum: 18),</P><P>— zaštitne i sigurnosne mjere u objektu (uz minimalne zahtjeve navedene u točki II.) - ocjenjivat će se prisutnost fizičke sigurnosti (zaštitara), ugradnja aparata za gašenje požara, izlaza u nuždi i planova evakuacije itd.: 15 bodova (traženi minimum: 7).</P><P>Klasifikacija ponuda temeljit će se na konačnoj ocjeni (F), u skladu sa sljedećom formulom:</P><P>F = (60 % x Q) + (40 % x P)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Službe za kontakt i dodatne informacije:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prijavitelji će biti obaviješteni o njihovom prethodnom odabiru ili odluci da se ne pozovu na pregovarački postupak. Svaki kontakt između prijavitelja i EASO-a je zabranjen, osim u slučajevima kada bi se trebala objasniti obavijest o traženju imovine. Zahtjev za pojašnjenjem bit će sastavljen u pisanom obliku na contracts@easo.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>