<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="141443-2018" EDITION="2018063"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-144080-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180413</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>63</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180330</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 063-141443</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141443-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="MK"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>https://e-nabavki.gov.mk/PublicAccess</IA_URL_GENERAL><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71221000">Architectural services for buildings</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71223000">Architectural services for building extensions</ORIGINAL_CPV><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="MK007">Североисточен (Severoistočen)</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS><VALUES_LIST/></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180329</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DD_DATE_REQUEST_DOCUMENT>20180411 10:00</DD_DATE_REQUEST_DOCUMENT><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180411 10:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="8">Other</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="8">Other</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="1">Lowest price</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>02302</HEADING><DIRECTIVE VALUE="2004/18/EC"/></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бивша югославска република Македония</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Архитектурно проектиране на сгради</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Bývalá jugoslávská republika Makedonie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Architektonické služby pro budovy</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Tidligere Jugoslaviske Republik Makedonien, Den</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Arkitekters tjenesteydelser i forbindelse med bygninger</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>die ehemalige jugoslawische Republik Mazedonien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Dienstleistungen von Architekturbüros bei Gebäuden</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>πρώην Γιουγκοσλαβική Δημοκρατία της Μακεδονίας</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Αρχιτεκτονικές υπηρεσίες για κτίρια</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Architectural services for buildings</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Antigua República Yugoslava de Macedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Servicios de arquitectura para edificios</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>endine Jugoslaavia Makedoonia Vabariik</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ehitiste arhitektuuriteenused</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>entinen Jugoslavian tasavalta Makedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Rakennusten arkkitehtipalvelut</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Ancienne République yougoslave de Macédoine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Services d'architecte pour les bâtiments</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Poblacht iar-Iúgslavach na Macadóine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Architectural services for buildings</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>bivša jugoslavenska Republika Makedonija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Arhitektonske usluge za zgrade</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Macedónia Volt Jugoszláv Köztársaság</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Épületekkel kapcsolatos építészeti szolgáltatások</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>ex Repubblica iugoslava di Macedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Servizi di progettazione di edifici</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>buvusioji Jugoslavijos Respublika Makedonija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Architektūrinės pastatų paslaugos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>bijusī Dienvidslāvijas Maķedonijas Republika</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ēku arhitektūras pakalpojumi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>Dik li kienet ir-Repubblika Jugoslava tal-Maċedonja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Servizzi ta' l-arkitettura dwar il-bini</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>voormalige Joegoslavische Republiek Macedonië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Diensten door architectenbureaus voor gebouwen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Była jugosłowiańska republika Macedonii</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Usługi architektoniczne w zakresie obiektów budowlanych</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>antiga República jugoslava da Macedónia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Serviços de arquitectura para edifícios</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>fosta Republică iugoslavă a Macedoniei</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Servicii de arhitectură pentru construcţii</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>bývalá Juhoslovanská republika Macedónsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Architektonické služby pre budovy</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Nekdanja jugoslovanska republika Makedonija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Arhitekturne storitve v zvezi s stavbami</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>F. d. jugoslaviska republiken Makedonien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lipkovo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Arkitekttjänster avseende byggnader</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Lipkovo Municipality</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><CONTRACT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="2" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"><CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION><NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Lipkovo Municipality</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Lipkovo</ADDRESS><TOWN>Lipkovo</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>1307</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="MK"/><CONTACT_POINT>Vaxhid Alija</CONTACT_POINT><PHONE>+389 31463180</PHONE><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>m_likova@yahoo.com</E_MAIL></E_MAILS><FAX>+389 31463179</FAX></CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><URL_GENERAL>https://e-nabavki.gov.mk/PublicAccess</URL_GENERAL></INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><FURTHER_INFORMATION><IDEM/></FURTHER_INFORMATION><SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><IDEM/></SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO><IDEM/></TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO></NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_OTHER VALUE="OTHER">Municipality of Lipkovo</TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_OTHER><TYPE_OF_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION><OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><TITLE_CONTRACT><P>Drafting technical documentation in the field of infrastructure</P></TITLE_CONTRACT><TYPE_CONTRACT_LOCATION><TYPE_CONTRACT VALUE="SERVICES"/><SERVICE_CATEGORY>12</SERVICE_CATEGORY></TYPE_CONTRACT_LOCATION><LOCATION_NUTS><LOCATION><P>Municipality of Lipkovo</P></LOCATION><n2016:NUTS CODE="MK007"/></LOCATION_NUTS><NOTICE_INVOLVES><PUBLIC_CONTRACT/></NOTICE_INVOLVES><SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><P>The subject of the public procurement contract is public procurement of services — Drafting technical documentation in the field of infrastructure. A detailed description of the contract is provided in the technical specifications within this tender documentation.</P></SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><CPV><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="71221000"/><CPV_SUPPLEMENTARY_CODE CODE="DA17"/><CPV_SUPPLEMENTARY_CODE CODE="IA01"/></CPV_MAIN><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="71223000"/><CPV_SUPPLEMENTARY_CODE CODE="IA01"/><CPV_SUPPLEMENTARY_CODE CODE="IA36"/><CPV_SUPPLEMENTARY_CODE CODE="IA38"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL></CPV><F02_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><DIV_INTO_LOT_NO/></F02_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><ACCEPTED_VARIANTS VALUE="NO"/></DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><PERIOD_WORK_DATE_STARTING><MONTHS>12</MONTHS></PERIOD_WORK_DATE_STARTING></OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><LEFTI_CONTRACT><CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><P>Guarantee for quality performance of the contract.</P><P>The condition for signing the contract with the selected most favorable bidder is to provide a guarantee by the selected most favorable bidder for quality performance of the contract in the amount of 10 % (the amount of the bank guarantee for quality performance of the contract can be from 5 % to 15 % of the value of the contract) of the value of the contract.</P><P>The guarantee referred to in item 7.5.1 shall be submitted in the form of a bank guarantee in writing. The guarantee should be submitted in its original form. Copies are not accepted.</P><P>The guarantee for quality performance of the contract will be valid until the full realization of the contract. After the selection of the most favorable bidder, the contracting authority shall additionally determine the final date of validity of the guarantee.</P><P>The bank guarantee for quality performance of the contract will be in the currency of the agreement. The guarantee for quality performance of the contract should be issued by a bank.</P><P>The best-performing bidder shall submit the guarantee for quality performance of the contract after the received notification for the selection made, and before the conclusion of the contract within the deadline specified by the Contracting Authority with the notification.</P><P>The guarantee for quality performance of the contract shall be delivered within the specified time period, as follows: by mail or personally to the contact person referred to in item 1.2.2 of the tender documentation. The guarantee for quality performance of the contract will be collected if the holder of the procurement fails to meet some of the obligations from the public procurement contract within the deadline, and will notify the contractor in writing in writing. If the guarantee for quality performance of the contract is collected, the Contracting Authority will publish a negative reference to the ESPP. For the collection of the bank guarantee for quality performance of the contract and for the publication of a negative reference on the ESPP, the contractor may raise a dispute before the competent court.</P><P>If the public procurement contract is fully realized in accordance with the agreed contract, the Contracting Authority shall return the bank guarantee for quality performance of the contract to the contractor within 14 days from the full realization of the contract.</P><P>The Contracting Authority shall return the guarantee for quality performance of the contract to the contractor by post, personally at the head office of the economic operator or personally at the head office of the Contracting Authority.</P></DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED></CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><F02_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI><T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>1 In order to qualify as competent for carrying out the said public procurement contract in terms of its technical and professional capacity, the economic operator must meet the following minimum conditions:</P><P>— to provide a copy of at least 3 contracts for providing design work services (drafting technical documentation) in the last 3 years (2015, 2016, 2017), as well as certificates verifying their the successful realisation,</P><P>— to provide 3 certificates verifying that the economic operator has successfully completed basic infrastructure projects for 2016, pursuant to the Law on Construction (“Official Gazette of the Republic of Macedonia”, nº 137/13, 163/13, 27/14, 28/14, 42/14, 115/14, 149/14, 187/14, 44/15, 129/15, 217/15, 226/15, 30/16, 31/16, 39/16, 71/16 and 132/16), (certificates submitted by a group of economic operators, that is, a group of bidders, are acceptable),</P><P>— to provide a statement verifying that technical personnel and technical bodies are to be hired regardless whether they are directly employed by the economic operator or not; the economic operator has to hire at least: 4 engineers — 2 civil engineers (one of whom has a type “A” authorisation for drafting design documentation, and one with a type “B” authorisation for drafting design documentation, and 2 architects (one of whom has a type “A” authorisation for drafting design documentation, and one authorised to draw up urban plans – a planner).</P></T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><T_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL><P>The economic operator verifies meeting the minimum conditions of subitem 2.5.1 by submitting:</P><P>— a copy of at least 3 contracts for providing design work services (drafting technical documentation) in the last 3 years (2015, 2016, 2017), as well as certificates verifying their the successful realisation,</P><P>— to provide three certificates verifying that the economic operator has successfully completed basic infrastructure projects for 2016, pursuant to the Law on Construction (“Official Gazette of the Republic of Macedonia”, nº 137/13, 163/13, 27/14, 28/14, 42/14, 115/14, 149/14, 187/14, 44/15, 129/15, 217/15, 226/15, 30/16, 31/16, 39/16, 71/16 and 132/16), (certificates submitted by a group of economic operators, that is, a group of bidders, are acceptable),</P><P>— to provide a statement verifying that technical personnel and technical bodies are to be hired regardless whether they are directly employed by the economic operator or not; the economic operator has to hire at least: 4 engineers – 2 civil engineers (one of whom has a type “A” authorisation for drafting design documentation, and one with a type “B” authorisation for drafting design documentation, and 2 architects (one of whom has a type “A” authorisation for drafting design documentation, and one authorised to draw up urban plans – a planner).</P></T_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL></TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI></F02_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION></LEFTI_CONTRACT><PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE><PT_OPEN/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE><AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><LOWEST_PRICE/></AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE><USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION><P>The Contracting Authority will use the electronic auction as the last stage in the open procedure. The subject of the electronic auction is the total price for each list individually, including all costs and discounts, without the VAT initially submitted prices to each of the qualified bidders. The initial price of the electronic auction is the lowest price of the acceptable tenders filed in the initial phase of the procedure for each list individually. Invitations to participate in the auction will be submitted in electronic form through ESPP after the full evaluation of the initial bids, to all economic operators that have submitted acceptable bids in the first phase of the procedure and which are registered in the ESPP.</P><P>The invitation to participate in the auction will be electronically sent to the mailbox of the user profile of the ESPP, to the person who will submit an offer for the appropriate procedure electronically.</P><P>The invitation to participate in the auction shall contain the following data: the starting price of the auction, ie the lowest price of the initially submitted bids; the date and time of the commencement and completion of the auction; the interval in which the negative bidding will be conducted (minimum and maximum difference in the offered prices). If only one bid or only one acceptable tender is submitted, the Contracting Authority will invite the only bidder to submit a final price through the ESPP. The final price submission invitation contains the following data: identification of the bid portion that will be the subject of submission of the final price, information available to it before the submission of the final price and the time period for submission of the final price. The only bidder submits the final price at the set time only once, and if it does not submit the final price, the initially offered price will be considered final.</P></USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION></IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE></AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><TIME_LIMIT><DAY>11</DAY><MONTH>04</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>10:00</TIME></TIME_LIMIT></CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><DAY>11</DAY><MONTH>04</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>10:00</TIME></RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><LANGUAGE><LANGUAGE_EC VALUE="EN"/></LANGUAGE><MINIMUM_TIME_MAINTAINING_TENDER><PERIOD_DAY>90</PERIOD_DAY></MINIMUM_TIME_MAINTAINING_TENDER><CONDITIONS_FOR_OPENING_TENDERS><DATE_TIME><DAY>11</DAY><MONTH>04</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>10:00</TIME></DATE_TIME><PLACE_OPENING><PLACE_NOT_STRUCTURED><P>Municipality of Lipkovo</P></PLACE_NOT_STRUCTURED></PLACE_OPENING><NO_EXISTENCE_AUTHORISED_PERSONS/></CONDITIONS_FOR_OPENING_TENDERS></ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/><RELATES_TO_EU_PROJECT_NO/><ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><P>2. Capacity of the Economic Operators</P><P>2.1.1 Along with their bid, the economic operator has to provide further documentation that shall verify their:</P><P>— individual capacity,</P><P>— capacity to perform professional activity,</P><P>— technical and professional capacity.</P><P>2.1.2 The economic operator has to scan the documentation and submit it electronically. The economic operator may use the e-PPS profile for economic operators in order to verify meeting the required verification criteria. Should the documentation be too ample to be scanned and attached to the e-PPS, the economic operators may submit it in hard copy, in a non-standard format and size, prior to the bid submission deadline. The non-standard format and size documentation is delivered in hard-copy in a sealed inner envelope bearing the full name and address of the economic operator, no later than the bid opening deadline. The sealed inner envelope is then enclosed in an outer envelope that:</P><P>— is accurately addressed to the Contracting Authority,</P><P>— contains information about the number of the notice for awarding a public procurement contract and the date on which it has been published,</P><P>— in the upper left-hand corner bears the warning “Do not open”, so that the envelope is not opened prior to the time and date of the bid opening.</P><P>2.1.3 When assessing whether the documentation that verifies the capacity of the economic operator is complete and valid, and when evaluating the bid, it is mandatory that through the e-PPS, the committee asks the bidders to clarify and complete the documents that verify their capacity within five working days starting from the bid submission deadline.</P><P>2.1.4 The economic operator submits the requested clarification in an electronic form through the e-PPS, by attaching the document containing the clarification or the completion in the “Clarification/Completion of submitted documents” section, within five days starting from the day the economic operator receives the request by the bidder.</P><P>2.1.5 No changes in the bid, except for correction of arithmetical mistakes are to be requested, offered or allowed by the committee or the economic operator.</P><P>2.1.6 In case of a group of economic operators, all members of the group shall prove their individual capacity and the capacity to perform professional activity.</P><P>2.2 Individual capacity</P><P>2.2.1 The Contracting Authority shall exclude from the procedure for awarding a public procurement contract any economic operator that:</P><P>— in the course of the last 5 years has had an effective court decision passed against them for participating in a criminal organisation, corruption, fraud, or money-laundering,</P><P>— has bankruptcy proceedings or liquidation procedure underway,</P><P>— has back taxes, back contributions and other public charges, except in case when the economic operator has been approved to obtain deferred payment of taxes, contributions and other public charges in accordance with the appropriate regulations, and regularly defrays those charges,</P><P>— has had а secondary penalty of prohibition to participate in public call procedures, be awarded public procurement contracts and public private partnership contracts, passed against them,</P><P>— has had a secondary penalty of temporary or permanent prohibition to perform individual activity passed against them,</P><P>— has a misdemeanour sanction passed against them – prohibition to perform profession, activity or other duty, or temporary prohibition to perform certain activity, and</P><P>— has given false data or has not submitted the data requested by the Contracting Authority.</P><P>2.2.2 In order to verify their individual capacity, the economic operator has to submit the following documents:</P><P>— a statement that no effective court decision has been passed against the economic operator in the course of the last 5 years for participating in a criminal organisation, corruption, fraud and money- laundering,</P><P>— a certificate stating that no bankruptcy proceedings are underway, issued by a competent authority,</P><P>— a certificate stating that no liquidation procedure is underway, issued by a competent authority,</P><P>— a certificate of paid taxes, contributions and other public charges, issued by the competent authority of the country where the economic operator is registered,</P><P>— a certificate from the Register of penalties for committed crimes by legal persons, stating that no secondary penalty of prohibition to participate in public call procedures, be awarded public procurement contracts and public/private partnership contracts has been passed against the economic operator,</P><P>— a certificate from the Register of penalties for committed crimes by legal persons, stating that no secondary penalty of temporary or permanent prohibition to perform individual activity has been passed against the economic operator,</P><P>— a certificate stating that no effective court decision – misdemeanor sanction has been passed against the economic operator – prohibition to perform profession, activity or other duty, or temporary prohibition to perform certain activity.</P><P>2.2.3 The statement in indent 1, subitem 2.2.2 is prepared and signed by the economic operators themselves and it need not be certified by a competent authority.</P><P>2.2.4 The certificates of absence of bankruptcy proceedings and liquidation procedure, as well as the certificates from the Register of penalties for committed crimes, indents 5 and 6, subitem 2.2.2 are issued by competent authorities of the country where the economic operator is registered. In the Republic of Macedonia, the competent authority responsible for issuing these certificates is the Central Register of the Republic of Macedonia.</P><P>2.2.5 The certificate of paid taxes, contributions and other charges is issued by a competent authority of the country where the economic operator is registered. In the Republic of Macedonia, the competent authority responsible for issuing this certificate is the Public Revenue Office.</P><P>2.2.6 The certificate required in indent 7, subitem 2.2.2 is issued by a competent authority of the country where the economic operator is registered. In the Republic of Macedonia, the competent authority responsible for issuing this certificate is the Central Register of the Republic of Macedonia.</P><P>2.2.7 The documents required in subitem 2.2.2 must not be older than six months, the final bid submission deadline being the reference date.</P><P>2.2.8 If the country where the economic operator is registered does not issue the documents required in subitem 2.2.2, or if they do not encompass the aforementioned instances, the economic operator may submit a statement certified by a competent authority.</P><P>2.3 Capacity to perform professional activity</P><P>2.3.1 In order to verify their capacity to perform professional activity, the economic operator has to submit a document for registered activity, issued by the Central Register of the Republic of Macedonia, as verification that they are registered as a natural or legal person that performs the activity related to the subject of the public procurement contract, or evidence that they belong to a corresponding professional association in accordance with the regulations of the country where the economic operator is registered.</P><P>2.3.2 Evidence issued by a competent authority which proves that the economic operator meets the required conditions prescribed by law for performing the activity related to the subject of the contract.</P><P>— Pursuant to article 148, Paragraph 2, in order to verify the professional capacity of the economic operators, the contracting authority requests evidence issued by a competent authority to verify that the economic operators meet the required conditions prescribed by law for performing the activity related to the subject of the contract: “B” Licence for Design Work.</P><P>2.5 Technical or professional capacity</P><P>2.5.1 In order to qualify as competent for carrying out the said public procurement contract in terms of its technical and professional capacity, the economic operator must meet the following minimum conditions:</P><P>— to provide a copy of at least 3 contracts for providing design work services (drafting technical documentation) in the last three years (2015, 2016, 2017), as well as certificates verifying their the successful realisation,</P><P>— to provide 3 certificates verifying that the economic operator has successfully completed basic infrastructure projects for 2016, pursuant to the Law on Construction (“Official Gazette of the Republic of Macedonia”, nº 137/13, 163/13, 27/14, 28/14, 42/14, 115/14, 149/14, 187/14, 44/15, 129/15, 217/15, 226/15, 30/16, 31/16, 39/16, 71/16 and 132/16), (certificates submitted by a group of economic operators, that is, a group of bidders, are acceptable),</P><P>— to provide a statement verifying that technical personnel and technical bodies are to be hired regardless whether they are directly employed by the economic operator or not; the economic operator has to hire at least: 4 engineers — 2 civil engineers (one of whom has a type “A” authorisation for drafting design documentation, and one with a type “B” authorisation for drafting design documentation, and 2 architects (one of whom has a type “A” authorisation for drafting design documentation, and one authorised to draw up urban plans — a planner).</P></ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>State Commission on Public Procurement</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Bul. "Ilinden" 63a</ADDRESS><TOWN>Skopje</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>1000</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="MK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>dkzjn@gs.gov.mk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS><PHONE>+389 23251251</PHONE><URL>http://dkzjn.mk/</URL><FAX>+389 23251250</FAX></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><LODGING_INFORMATION_FOR_SERVICE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>State Commission on Public Procurement</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Bul. "Ilinden" 63a</ADDRESS><TOWN>Skopje</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>1000</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="MK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>dkzjn@gs.gov.mk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS><PHONE>+389 23251251</PHONE><URL>http://dkzjn.mk/</URL><FAX>+389 23251250</FAX></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></LODGING_INFORMATION_FOR_SERVICE></PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE><DAY>29</DAY><MONTH>03</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR></NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></FD_CONTRACT></CONTRACT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>