<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="031828-2018" EDITION="2018016"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-019392-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180326</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>16</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180124</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 016-031828</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:031828-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="66171000">Financial consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="LU">LUXEMBOURG</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180115</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180326</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="I">Call for expressions of interest</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="Z">Not specified</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>BI302</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Luxembourg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser: til udvælgelse af formidlere under den litauiske gearede fond til gennemførelsen af et finansinstrument til garantier i Litauen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Aufruf zur Interessenbekundung: zwecks Auswahl von Finanzintermediären im Rahmen des litauischen „Leveraged Fund“ für die Umsetzung eines Garantie-Finanzinstruments in Litauen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Luxembourg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Call for Expression of Interest: to select financial intermediaries under the Lithuanian Leveraged Fund to implement a guarantee financial instrument in Lithuania</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Luxemburgo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburgo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés: para seleccionar intermediarios financieros bajo el Fondo Apalancado de Lituania para implementar un instrumento financiero de garantía en Lituania</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIP - Kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntö rahoituksen välittäjien valitsemiseksi Liettuan vipurahaston tuella rahoitusvälineen täytäntöönpanoa varten Liettuassa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Luxembourg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Appel de manifestations d'intérêt: en vue de la sélection d’intermédiaires financiers en vertu du fonds lituanien à effet de levier pour la mise en œuvre d’un instrument financier donné en garantie en Lituanie</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Λουξεμβούργο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Λουξεμβούργο</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΕπ - Πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος: επιλογή ενδιάμεσων χρηματοπιστωτικών οργανισμών υπό το Ταμείο Μόχλευσης Λιθουανίας για την εφαρμογή χρηματοδοτικού μέσου εγγύησης στη Λιθουανία</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Lussemburgo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lussemburgo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Invito a manifestare interesse per la selezione di intermediari finanziari ai sensi del fondo lituano soggetto a leva finanziaria per l’attuazione di uno strumento finanziario di garanzia in Lituania</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling: om financiële tussenpersonen te selecteren onder het Lithuanian Leveraged Fund om een financieel instrument in Litouwen ten uitvoer te leggen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Luxemburgo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburgo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Convite à manifestação de interesse: para selecionar intermediários financeiros no âmbito do Fundo de Alavancagem Lituano para implementar um instrumento financeiro de garantia na Lituânia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Uppmaning till intresseanmälan: val av finansiella intermediärer inom ramen för den litauiska hävstångsfonden för att genomföra ett garanterat finansiellt instrument i Litauen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Lucembursko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lucemburk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Výzva k vyjádření zájmu: vybrat finanční zprostředkovatele v rámci litevského fondu Leveraged Fund za účelem zavedení garančního finančního nástroje v Litvě</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIP - Huvi väljendamise kutse: finantsvahendajate valimine Lithuanian Leveraged Fundi kaudu Leedus finantstagatisinstrumendi loomiseks</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBB - Felhívás szándéknyilatkozat benyújtására: pénzügyi közvetítők kiválasztása Litvánia tőkeáttétellel működő befektetési alapjának keretében, garanciafinanszírozási eszköz létrehozásához Litvániában</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Liuksemburgas</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Liuksemburgas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Kvietimas pareikšti susidomėjimą: atrinkti Lietuvos svertą naudojančio fondo finansų tarpininkus, siekiant įgyvendinti garantijos finansinę priemonę Lietuvoje</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Luksemburga</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luksemburga</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Uzaicinājums paust ieinteresētību: izraudzīties finanšu starpniekus Lietuvas aizņemto līdzekļu fonda ietvaros garantijas finanšu instrumenta īstenošanai Lietuvā</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Lussemburgu</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lussemburgu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess: biex jintgħażlu intermedjarji finanzjarji taħt il-Fond Ingranat Litwan biex jiġi implimentat strument finanzjarju ta' garanzija fil-Litwanja</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luksemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBI - Zaproszenie do wyrażenia zainteresowania: wybranie pośredników w ramach litewskiego funduszu dźwigni finansowej w celu zapewnienia instrumentu gwarancji finansowych na Litwie</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Luxembursko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Výzva na vyjadrenie záujmu: výber finančných sprostredkovateľov v rámci litovského fondu s pákovým efektom na vykonanie záručného finančného nástroja v Litve</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Poziv k prijavi interesa za izbiro finančnih posrednikov v okviru litovskega sklada z vzvodom z namenom izvajanja finančnega instrumenta jamstva v Litvi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Lucsamburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lucsamburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Glao ar Léiriú Spéise: d’fhonn idirghabhálaithe airgeadais a roghnú faoi Chiste Giaráilte na Liotuáine chun ionstraim airgeadais ráthaíochta a chur chun feidhme sa Liotuáin</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Люксембург</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Люксембург</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕИБ - Покана за изразяване на интерес: за избор на финансови посредници по Литовския заемен фонд за изпълнение на гаранционен финансов инструмент в Литва</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Cererea de scrisori de interes: selectarea de intermediarii financiari în cadrul Fondului lituanian cu efect de levier pentru a pune în aplicare un instrument financiar de garantare în Lituania</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Poziv na iskazivanje interesa: za odabir financijskih posrednika u okviru Litavskog fonda s financijskom polugom u svrhu provedbe jamstvenog financijskog instrumenta u Litvi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den Europæiske Investeringsbank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Investitionsbank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Investment Bank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">Banco Europeo de Inversiones</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan investointipankki</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Banque européenne d'investissement</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Ευρωπαϊκή Τράπεζα Επενδύσεων</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Banca europea per gli investimenti</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europese Investeringsbank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">Banco Europeu de Investimento</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska investeringsbanken</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská investiční banka</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Investeerimispank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Európai Beruházási Bank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos investicijų bankas</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Investīciju banka</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">Bank Ewropew tal-Investiment</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Europejski Bank Inwestycyjny</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európskou investičnou bankou</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska investicijska banka</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An Banc Eorpach Infheistíochta</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейска инвестиционна банка</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Banca Europeană de Investiții</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska investicijska banka</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser: til udvælgelse af formidlere under den litauiske gearede fond til gennemførelsen af et finansinstrument til garantier i Litauen (LU-Luxembourg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Reference: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Bekendtgørelse til offentliggørelse i EU-Tidende, S-udgaven)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Bekendtgørelse om indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jessica II fonden over fonde i Litauen, repræsenteret inden for rammerne af denne indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser af</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den Europæiske Investeringsbank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>Luxembourg, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Der fungerer som indkøbsenheden.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Genstand for indkaldelsen af interessetilkendegivelser</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Inden for 2014-2020 programlægningsperioden for »det operationelle program for unionens fondes investeringer i 2014-2020« som godkendt af Europa-Kommissionens afgørelse nr. C(2014)6397 (»Operationelt Program«) og med det formål at bekæmpe det markedssvigt, der blev identificeret af de indledende og opdaterede »ex-ante«-vurderinger, der blev godkendt af evaluerings- og overvågningsudvalget for projektet for offentlig infrastruktur og energieffektivitet på henholdsvis 7.11.2014 og 29.8.2016 (»Ex-ante vurdering«), har finansministeriet i Republikken Litauen, som forvaltningsmyndighed, dedikeret midler til gennemførelsen af den litauiske gearede fond (»Den gearede fond«). I den gearede fonds kontekst, ved at udfærdige en ændring til Jessica II fonden over fonde i Litauens (»Jessica II« eller »FoF«) finansieringsaftalen, der trådte i kraft d. 7.5.2015 (som ændret d. 5.10.2016) mellem henholdsvis Finans- og Miljøministerierne i Republikken Litauen (»Ministerierne«) og Den Europæiske Investeringsbank (»EIB«) (»Finansieringsaftalen« eller »FA«), blev EIB udpeget som et organ, der gennemførte et finansinstrument (»Finansinstrumentet«) i form af en garanti til fordel for Republikken Litauen (»Garantien«), i overensstemmelse med Artikel 38 (4)(b)(i) af forordningen om fælles bestemmelser (»CPR«).</P><P>De relevante gennemførelsesbestemmelser for det finansielle instrument er først og fremmest fastlagt i forordningen om fælles bestemmelser, Kommissionens delegerede forordning (»CDR« — the Commission Delegated Regulation), Kommissionens gennemførelsesforordning, forordningen om Den Europæiske Fond for Regionaludvikling (»ERDF«) (som henholdsvis defineret nedenfor) og gældende Litauisk lovgivning og nationale bestemmelser.</P><P>Formålet med indkaldelsen af interessetilkendegivelser (»Indkaldelsen af interessetilkendegivelser«) er at udvælge valgbare finansielle institutioner i Litauen, der kan blive finansielle formidlere (»Finansielle Formidlere«), der under garantiaftalen (»Garantiaftalen«) vil modtage garantier funderet af de europæiske struktur- og investeringsfonde (»ESIF«). Garantien vil delvist dække kreditrisikoen, der er beslægtet med en ny portfolie af præferencelån, der vil blive tildelt af finansielle formidlere til fysiske eller juridiske personer, der ejer lokaler i multi-lejlighedsbygninger (»Endelige Modtager«) eller til forvaltere af fælleseje (»Forvaltere af Fælleseje«) til energieffektivitetsrelateret renovering af multi-lejlighedsbygninger (»Projekter«) i overensstemmelse med det Litauiske retsgrundlag (»Moderniseringslån«).</P><P>Udbudsmaterialet inklusive bilag kan rekvireres ved at sende en e-mail til CS-procurement@eib.org med emnet »PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents«.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ansøgningsprocedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Forslagene skal indgives på engelsk pr. post til adressen anført i punkt 1, i nøje overensstemmelse med de specifikke instruktioner, der er fastlagt i udbudsmaterialet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Generel beskrivelse af fremgangsmåden</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Denne indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser udgør ikke en offentlig udbudsprocedure i henhold til direktiv 2004/18/EF eller 2014/24/EU.</P><P>Interesserede parter opfordres til at indgive deres forslag i overensstemmelse med bestemmelserne fastsat i denne bekendtgørelse og i udbudsmaterialet.</P><P>Principperne og metoden, der anvendes i evalueringsprocesserne, samt faserne i evalueringsprocessen er beskrevet i udbudsmaterialet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sidste frist for afgivelse af forslag</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskyttelse af personoplysninger</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De indgivne personoplysninger vil blive behandlet i overensstemmelse med Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EF) nr. 45/2001 af 18.12.2000 om beskyttelse af fysiske personer i forbindelse med behandling af personoplysninger i fællesskabsinstitutionerne og -organerne og om fri udveksling af sådanne oplysninger og enhver fremtidig lovgivning, der ændrer eller ophæver det. Oplysningerne, der anmodes om til denne indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser, er nødvendige for at vurdere dit forslag og vil udelukkende blive anvendt til dette formål af EIB's indkøbsafdeling (CS/IMP/PROCUR) i overensstemmelse med EIB's vejledning om indkøb, godkendt af EIB's direktion. Bemærk venligst, at det kan være obligatorisk at besvare nogle af eller alle spørgsmålene i erklæringen, som ansøgeren skal aflægge, for at forslaget kan tages i betragtning. Spørgsmålenes obligatoriske/valgfrie karakter er beskrevet i udbudsmaterialet. Medlemmer af udvælgelseskomitéen og direktoratet, der anmodede om interesseindkaldelser, vil have adgang til de indgivne personlige oplysninger for at kunne vurdere ansøgeren. EIB's ledende funktionær for overensstemmelse, den juridiske tjeneste eller generalinspektoratet kan efter anmodning tildels adgang til disse data. Den valgte ansøgers oplysninger opbevares i de centrale arkiver i kontraktens løbetid plus 2 år, medmindre der er brug herfor i forbindelse med tvister eller klager. Oplysninger på ikke-valgte ansøgere opbevares i 4 år, medmindre der er brug herfor i forbindelse med tvister eller klager. Du har ret til at få adgang til, rette og opdatere dine oplysninger. Rettighederne kan udøves ved at kontakte lederen af afdeling CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Du har også til enhver tid ret til at henvende dig til Den Europæiske Tilsynsførende for Databeskyttelse.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udelukkelseskriterier, udvælgelses- og tildelingskriterier</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De udelukkelseskriterier, administrative kriterier og vurderingskriterier, der gælder for dette udbud, er beskrevet i udbudsmaterialet og bilagene hertil.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dato for afsendelse af bekendtgørelsen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dato for modtagelse af bekendtgørelsen i Publikationskontoret</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Aufruf zur Interessenbekundung: zwecks Auswahl von Finanzintermediären im Rahmen des litauischen „Leveraged Fund“ für die Umsetzung eines Garantie-Finanzinstruments in Litauen (LU-Luxemburg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenz: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Bekanntmachung zur Veröffentlichung im Amtsblatt, Reihe S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Bekanntmachung eines Aufrufs zur Interessenbekundung</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Öffentlicher Auftraggeber</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Der „Jessica II-Dachfonds“ für Litauen, vertreten für die Zwecke des vorliegenden Aufrufs zur Interessenbekundung durch die</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Investitionsbank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, 2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg, E-Mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>die als Beschaffungsstelle fungiert.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ziel des Aufrufs zur Interessenbekundung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Innerhalb des Programmplanungszeitraums 2014-2020 des operativen Programms für Investitionen aus Mitteln der Europäischen Union für den Zeitraum 2014-2020 „Operational programme for union funds investments in 2014-2020”, das über den Beschluss der Europäischen Kommission Nr. C (2014)6397 („Operational Programme“) zugelassen wurde, um das Marktversagen zu bekämpfen, das im Rahmen von ursprünglichen und aktualisierten „Ex-ante“-Bewertungen festgestellt wurde, bildeten diese Bewertungen zuvor den Gegenstand einer Genehmigung seitens der öffentlichen Infrastruktur, der Bewertung des Energieeffizienz-Projekts und des Beobachtungsausschusses vom 7.11.2014 und 29.8.2016 („Exante assessment“). Hierbei fungiert das Ministerium für Finanzen der Republik Litauen als Verwaltungsbehörde und verfügt über spezielle Ressourcen für die Umsetzung des litauischen „Leveraged Fund“ („Leveraged Fund“). Im Rahmen des „Leveraged Fund“ sowie durch die Vereinbarung eines Nachtrags zum Jessica II Fonds des Litauen-Fonds („Jessica II“ oder „FoF“) trat die Finanzierungsvereinbarung am 7.5.2015 (in der geänderten Fassung vom 5.10.2016) zwischen den Ministerien für Finanzen und Umwelt der Republik Litauen („Ministries“) und der Europäischen Investitionsbank („EIB“) („Funding Agreement“ oder „FA“) in Kraft. Hierbei wurde die EIB zur zuständigen Stelle für die Umsetzung eines Finanzierungsinstruments („Financial Instrument“) in Form einer Garantie zugunsten der Republik Litauen („Guarantee“), gemäß Artikel 38 (4)(b)(i) der Verordnung mit gemeinsamen Bestimmungen (Common Provisions Regulation/CPR) ernannt.</P><P>Die einschlägigen Vorschriften für die Umsetzung des Finanzinstruments sind überwiegend in der CPR, der delegierten Verordnung der Kommission (Commission Delegated Regulation — CDR), der Durchführungsverordnung der Kommission und der Verordnung über den Europäischen Fonds für regionale Entwicklung (European Regional Development Fund — EFRE) – gemäß untenstehender Definition – und den geltenden litauischen Rechtsvorschriften und Verordnungen zu finden.</P><P>Ziel dieses Aufrufs zur Interessenbekundung („Call for EoI“) ist die Auswahl geeigneter Finanzinstitutionen in Litauen, um als Finanzintermediäre („Financial Intermediaries“) zu fungieren, die im Rahmen einer Garantievereinbarung („Guarantee Agreement“), vom Europäischer Struktur- und Investitionsfonds („ESIF“) finanzierte Garantien erhalten. Diese Garantie sollte einen Teil des Kreditrisikos, das mit einem neuen Portfolio oder Präferenz-Darlehen verbunden ist, das die Finanzintermediäre einer natürlichen oder juristischen Personen, die sich im Besitz eines Gebäudes mit mehreren Wohnungen („Final Recipient“) befinden oder Administratoren von Gemeinschaftseigentum („Administrators of Common Property“) für die Energieeffizienz-Renovierung eines Gebäudes mit mehreren Wohnungen („Projects“) gemäß der litauischen Rechtsgrundlage („Modernisation Loans“), einräumen sollen, decken.</P><P>Die Ausschreibungsunterlagen einschließlich Anhängen können mittels einer Anfrage per E-Mail an CSprocurement@eib.org mit der Betreffzeile „PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents“ angefordert werden.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verfahren der Antragstellung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Die Angebote sind in englischer Sprache per Post an die unter Ziffer 1 angegebene Anschrift zu senden, wobei die in den Ausschreibungsunterlagen aufgeführten spezifischen Anweisungen strikt einzuhalten sind.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Allgemeine Beschreibung des Verfahrens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bei diesem Aufruf zur Interessenbekundung handelt es sich nicht um ein Verfahren zur Vergabe öffentlicher Aufträge im Sinne der Richtlinien 2004/18/EG oder 2014/24/EU.</P><P>Interessierte Parteien werden aufgefordert, ihre Angebote gemäß den in dieser Bekanntmachung und den Ausschreibungsunterlagen enthaltenen Bestimmungen einzureichen.</P><P>Die für das Bewertungsverfahren geltenden Grundsätze und Vorgehensweisen sowie die Phasen der Bewertungsverfahren werden in den Ausschreibungsunterlagen beschrieben.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Schlusstermin für den Eingang der Angebote</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Schutz personenbezogener Daten</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Die Verarbeitung der vorgelegten personenbezogenen Daten erfolgt gemäß Verordnung (EG) Nr. 45/2001 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 18.12.2000 zum Schutz natürlicher Personen bei der Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten durch die Organe und Einrichtungen der Gemeinschaft und zum freien Datenverkehr sowie beliebiger zukünftiger, dies ändernder oder aufhebender Rechtsvorschriften. Die im Rahmen des Aufrufs zur Interessenbekundung geforderten Angaben sind zur Bewertung der Angebote erforderlich und werden ausschließlich zu diesem Zweck unter der Aufsicht der Einkaufsabteilung der EIB (CS/IMP/PROCUR) und in Übereinstimmung mit dem vom Direktorium der EIB genehmigten Leitfaden der EIB für die Auftragsvergabe verwendet. Damit das Angebot berücksichtigt werden kann, ist es möglicherweise verpflichtend, einige oder sämtliche Fragen zu beantworten, die in der vom Antragsteller abzugebenden Erklärung enthalten sind. Der verbindliche/optionale Charakter dieser Fragen wird in den Ausschreibungsunterlagen erläutert. Zur Bewertung der Antragsteller erhalten Mitglieder des Auswahlgremiums und der Direktion, auf deren Verlangen der Aufruf zur Interessenbekundung in die Wege geleitet wurde, Zugriff auf die vorgelegten personenbezogenen Daten. Auf Anfrage kann dem Compliance Office der EIB, dem juristischen Dienst oder der Generalinspektion Zugang zu den Daten gewährt werden. Die Daten des erfolgreichen Antragstellers werden 2 Jahre über die Laufzeit des Vertrags hinaus in den zentralen Archiven gespeichert, es sei denn, sie werden im Zusammenhang mit einer Rechtsstreitigkeit oder Klage benötigt. Die Daten nicht erfolgreicher Antragsteller werden 4 Jahre gespeichert, es sei denn, sie werden im Zusammenhang mit einer Rechtsstreitigkeit oder Klage benötigt. Die Antragsteller sind berechtigt, auf ihre Daten zuzugreifen und diese abzuändern oder zu aktualisieren. Zur Ausübung dieses Rechts ist der Leiter der Abteilung CS/IMP/PROCUR zu kontaktieren (CS-procurement@eib.org). Es besteht ebenfalls das Recht, sich jederzeit an den Europäischen Datenschutzbeauftragten zu wenden.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ausschlusskriterien, Auswahl- und Vergabekriterien</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Die für diesen Aufruf geltenden Ausschlusskriterien, administrativen Kriterien und Bewertungskriterien sind den Ausschreibungsunterlagen und ihren Anhängen zu entnehmen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum der Absendung der vorliegenden Bekanntmachung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum des Eingangs beim Amt für Veröffentlichungen</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Call for Expression of Interest: to select financial intermediaries under the Lithuanian Leveraged Fund to implement a guarantee financial instrument in Lithuania (LU-Luxembourg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Reference: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Notice to be published in the Official Journal, S series)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Notice of call for expression of interest</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contracting authority</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Jessica II Fund of Funds Lithuania, represented for the purpose of this call for expression of interest by the</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Investment Bank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxembourg, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Which is acting as the procuring entity.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Objective of the Call for Expression of Interest</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Within the 2014-2020 programming period of the “operational programme for union funds investments in 2014-2020” approved by the decision of the European Commission nº C (2014)6397 (“Operational Programme”) and with the purpose of tackling the market failure identified by the initial and updated ex-ante assessments approved by the public infrastructure and energy efficiency project evaluation and monitoring committee on 7.11.2014 and 29.8.2016 respectively (“exante assessment”), the Ministry of Finance of the Republic of Lithuania acting as managing authority, has dedicated resources to the implementation of the Lithuanian leveraged fund (”leveraged fund”). In the context of the leveraged fund, by concluding an amendment to the Jessica II fund of funds Lithuania (“Jessica II” or “FoF”) funding agreement entered into force on 7.5.2015 (as amended on 5.10.2016) between the Ministries of Finance and of Environment of the Republic of Lithuania (the “Ministries”) respectively and the European Investment Bank (“EIB”) (“Funding Agreement” or “FA”), EIB was appointed a body implementing a financial instrument ("Financial Instrument") in the form of a guarantee for the benefit of the Republic of Lithuania ("Guarantee"), in accordance with Article 38 (4)(b)(i) of the Common Provisions Regulation (“CPR”).</P><P>Relevant rules for implementing the Financial Instrument are primarily stipulated in the CPR, the Commission Delegated Regulation (“CDR”), the Commission Implementing Regulation and the European Regional Development Fund (“ERDF”) Regulation (respectively as defined below), and applicable Lithuanian laws and regulations.</P><P>The aim of the call for expression of Interest (“Call for EoI”) is to select eligible financial institutions in Lithuania to become financial intermediaries (“Financial Intermediaries”), which shall, under the guarantee agreement (“Guarantee Agreement”), receive guarantee funded by European Structural and Investment Funds (“ESIF”). The guarantee shall partly cover the credit risk associated with a new portfolio of preferential loans to be granted by financial intermediaries to natural or legal persons owning premises in multi-apartment buildings (“Final Recipient”) or to administrators of common property (“Administrators of Common Property”) for the energy efficiency renovation of a multi-apartment buildings (“Projects”) in accordance with the Lithuanian legal basis ("Modernisation Loans").</P><P>The terms of reference including annexes can be requested by sending an email to CSprocurement@eib.org with the subject PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Application procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The proposals should be submitted in English by post to the address indicated in point 1, in strict compliance with the specific instructions laid down in the terms of reference.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>General description of the procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>This call for expression of Interest does not represent a public procurement procedure in the sense of directives 2004/18/EC or 2014/24/EU.</P><P>Interested parties are invited to submit their proposals in accordance with the rules set out in this notice and in the terms of reference.</P><P>The principles and method applicable to the evaluation process, as well as the stages of the evaluation processes, are described in the terms of reference.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Deadline for submission of proposals</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Protection of personal data</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The personal data provided by you will be processed in accordance with regulation (EC) 45/2001 of the European Parliament and of the council of 18.12.2000 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data by the community institutions and bodies and on the free movement of such data and any future legislation amending or repealing it. The information requested for the CEoI is necessary in order to assess your proposal and will be used solely for that purpose under the authority of the EIB purchasing division (CS/IMP/PROCUR), in accordance with the EIB guide for procurement, approved by the management committee of the EIB. Please note that for your proposal to be considered, it may be mandatory to answer some or all of the questions in the declaration to be made by the applicant. The mandatory /optional nature of these questions is outlined in the terms of reference document. In order to assess the applicant, the personal data provided by you will be accessed by members of the selection panel and the directorate which requested the CEoI. Upon request, access to this data may be granted to the EIB’s office of the chief compliance officer, the legal service or the inspectorate general. The data of the successful applicant shall be retained for the duration of the contract, plus 2 years in the central archives, unless these are needed in the context of litigation or claims. The data of unsuccessful applicants shall be retained for 4 years, unless these are needed in the context of litigation or claims. You have the right to access and rectify or update your data. You can exercise these rights by contacting the Head of the CS/IMP/PROCUR division (CS-procurement@eib.org). You also have the right to have recourse at any time to the European data protection supervisor.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Exclusion criteria, selection and award criteria</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The exclusion criteria, administrative criteria and assessment criteria applicable for this call are described in the terms of reference and its annexes.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date of dispatch of notice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date of receipt by the Publications Office</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BEI - Convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés: para seleccionar intermediarios financieros bajo el Fondo Apalancado de Lituania para implementar un instrumento financiero de garantía en Lituania (LU-Luxemburgo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referencia: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Anuncio que se publicará en el Diario Oficial, serie S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anuncio de convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de contratación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El Fondo de Fondos Jessica II Lituania, representado a efectos de esta convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés por el</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Banco Europeo de Inversiones</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburgo, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>que se ha constituido como entidad adjudicadora.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Objeto de la convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Dentro del período de programación 2014-2020 del «programa operativo para inversiones de fondos sindicales en 2014-2020» aprobado por decisión de la Comisión Europea n.º C (2014) 6397 («Programa operativo») y con el objetivo de abordar la falla del mercado identificada a través de evaluaciones ex ante iniciales y actualizadas aprobadas por el comité de evaluación y supervisión del proyecto de infraestructura y eficiencia energética los días 7.11.2014 y 29.8.2016 respectivamente («evaluación exante»), el Ministerio de Finanzas de la República de Lituania, actuando en calidad de autoridad de gestión, cuenta con recursos dedicados a la implementación del fondo apalancado lituano («fondo apalancado»). En el contexto del fondo apalancado, al concluir una enmienda al fondo de fondos Jessica II Lituania («Jessica II» o «FoF»), el acuerdo de financiación entrado en vigor el 7.5.2015 (y enmendado el 5.10.2016) entre los ministerios de Finanzas y Medio Ambiente de la República de Lituania (los «Ministerios») respectivamente y el Banco Europeo de Inversiones («BEI») («Acuerdo de Financiación» o «FA»), el BEI fue designado organismo implementador de un instrumento financiero («Instrumento Financiero») en forma de garantía en beneficio de la República de Lituania («Garantía»), de conformidad con el artículo 38 (4) (b) (i) del Reglamento de Disposiciones Comunes («RDC»).</P><P>Las normas pertinentes para la aplicación del Instrumento financiero se estipulan principalmente en el CPR, el Reglamento Delegado de la Comisión («CDR»), el Reglamento de aplicación de la Comisión y el Reglamento del Fondo Europeo de Desarrollo Regional («FEDER») (respectivamente, según se definen a continuación), y las leyes y reglamentos nacionales aplicables.</P><P>El objetivo de la convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés («Convocatoria de MdI») es la selección de instituciones financieras elegibles en Lituania para convertirse en intermediarios financieros («Intermediarios financieros»), que, de conformidad con el acuerdo de garantía («Acuerdo de garantía»), reciban garantía financiada por los Fondos Estructurales y de Inversión Europeos («ESIF»). La garantía cubrirá parcialmente el riesgo de crédito asociado con la nueva cartera de préstamos preferenciales que otorgarán los intermediarios financieros a personas físicas o jurídicas propietarias de locales en edificios de apartamentos múltiples («Destinatario final») o a administradores de propiedad común («Administradores de Propiedad común») para la renovación de eficiencia energética de edificios de apartamentos múltiples («Proyectos») de conformidad con la base jurídica lituana («Préstamos de modernización»).</P><P>El pliego de condiciones y los anexos podrán solicitarse enviando un correo electrónico a CS-procurement@eib.org con el asunto PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedimiento de solicitud</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Las propuestas se presentarán en inglés por correo a la dirección mencionada en el punto 1, en estricta conformidad con las instrucciones específicas establecidas en el pliego de condiciones.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción general del procedimiento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>La presente convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés no es un procedimiento de contratación pública en el sentido de las Directivas 2004/18/CE o 2014/24/UE.</P><P>Se invita a las partes interesadas a presentar sus propuestas de acuerdo con las normas establecidas en el presente anuncio y en el pliego de condiciones.</P><P>Los principios y métodos aplicables al proceso de evaluación, así como las fases de los procesos de evaluación, se describen en el pliego de condiciones.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plazo para la presentación de las propuestas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Protección de los datos personales</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Los datos personales presentados serán procesados de acuerdo con el Reglamento (CE) 45/2001 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 18.12.2000, relativo a la protección de las personas físicas en lo que respecta al tratamiento de datos personales por las instituciones y los organismos comunitarios y a la libre circulación de estos datos y cualquier legislación futura que la modifique o derogue. La información solicitada en la convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés es necesaria para la evaluación de la propuesta y se utilizará únicamente para este fin con arreglo a la autoridad de la división de adquisiciones del BEI (CS/IMP/PROCUR), de conformidad con la guía de contratación del BEI, aprobada por el Comité de Gestión del BEI. Se informa de que para tener en cuenta las propuestas podrá ser obligatorio responder a todas o algunas de las preguntas que figuran en la declaración que se pide al solicitante. La naturaleza obligatoria o facultativa de estas preguntas se detalla en el pliego de condiciones. A fin de evaluar al candidato, los datos personales facilitados podrán ser consultados por los miembros del comité de selección y por la Dirección en la que se pedía la convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés. Previa petición, podrá concederse el acceso a estos datos a la Oficina de Verificación de la Conformidad del BEI, al servicio jurídico o a la Inspección General del BEI. Los datos del candidato seleccionado se conservarán durante el tiempo que dure el contrato, más 2 años en el archivo central, salvo que estos sean necesarios en el marco de un litigio o reclamación. Los datos de los candidatos no seleccionados se conservarán durante 4 años, a no ser que estos sean necesarios en el contexto de un litigio o reclamación. Los candidatos tendrán derecho a acceder, rectificar o actualizar sus datos. Podrán ejercer sus derechos poniéndose en contacto con el jefe de la división CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Además, los candidatos tendrán derecho también a presentar un recurso en cualquier momento al Supervisor Europeo de Protección de Datos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criterios de exclusión, criterios de selección y adjudicación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Los criterios de exclusión, criterios administrativos y criterios de evaluación aplicables a esta licitación se describen en el pliego de condiciones y sus anexos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha de envío del anuncio</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha de recepción por la Oficina de Publicaciones</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIP - Kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntö rahoituksen välittäjien valitsemiseksi Liettuan vipurahaston tuella rahoitusvälineen täytäntöönpanoa varten Liettuassa (LU-Luxemburg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Viite: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Euroopan unionin virallisen lehden S-sarjassa julkaistava ilmoitus)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntö</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jessica II -rahastojen rahasto Liettua, jota edustaa tämän kiinnostuksenilmaisupyynnön yhteydessä</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan investointipankki</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxembourg, sähköpostiosoite: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Euroopan investointipankki toimii hankintaviranomaisena.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kiinnostuksenilmaisupyynnön tavoite:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Liettuan tasavallan valtiovarainministeriö on kohdentanut resursseja Liettuan vipurahaston täytäntöönpanoa varten asiaa hoitavana viranomaisena Euroopan komission päätöksellä C (2014) 6397 hyväksytyn "Euroopan unionin varojen investointia koskevan toimenpideohjelman 2014-2020" puitteissa ohjelmakaudella 2014-2020. Tarkoituksena on torjua markkinoiden toimimattomuutta, joka tunnistettiin alkuperäisissä ja päivitetyissä ennakkoarvioinneissa, jotka julkista infrastruktuuria ja energiatehokkuutta koskevien hankkeiden arviointi- ja seurantakomitea hyväksyi 7.11.2014 ja 29.8.2016. Euroopan investointipankki (EIP) nimitettiin rahoitusvälineen (’rahoitusväline’) täytäntöönpanosta vastaavaksi elimeksi takauksen (’takaus’) muodossa Liettuan tasavallalle yhteisiä säännöksiä (’CPR’ – Common Provisions Regulation) koskevan asetuksen artiklan 38 kohdan 4 alakohdan b alakohdan i mukaisesti vipurahaston yhteydessä muuttamalla 7.5.2015 (sellaisena kuin se on muutettuna 5.10.2016) voimaan tullutta Jessica II -rahastojen rahasto Liettuaa (’Jessica II’ tai ’FoF’ – fund of funds) koskevaa rahoitussopimusta Liettuan valtiovarain- ja ympäristöministeriön (’ministeriöt’) ja EIP:n välillä.</P><P>Rahoitusvälineen täytäntöönpanoa koskevista asiaankuuluvista säännöistä säädetään ensisijaisesti yhteisiä säännöksiä koskevassa asetuksessa, komission delegoidussa asetuksessa (Commission Delegated Regulation – CDR), täytäntöönpanoasetuksessa, Euroopan aluekehitysrahastoa (EAKR) koskevassa asetuksessa (vastaavasti jäljempänä määritetyn mukaisesti) sekä sovellettavassa Liettuan lainsäädännössä ja määräyksissä.</P><P>Kiinnostuksenilmaisupyynnön tavoitteena on valintakelpoisten rahoituslaitosten valitseminen rahoituksen välittäjiksi, jotka saavat Euroopan rakenne- ja investointirahastojen rahoittaman takauksen takaussopimuksen nojalla. Takauksen on määrä kattaa osittain se luottoriski, joka liittyy uusiin sosiaalisin perustein myönnettäviin lainoihin, joita rahoituksen välittäjät myöntävät kerros- tai rivitaloissa tiloja omistaville luonnollisille henkilöille tai oikeushenkilöille (’lopullinen vastaanottaja’) tai yhteishallinnassa olevien kiinteistöjen hallinnoijille (’yhteishallinnassa olevien kiinteistöjen hallinnoija’) Liettuan lakien mukaisesti (’uudistuslainat’).</P><P>Tehtävänkuvauksen ja liitteet voi pyytää lähettämällä sähköpostia osoitteeseen cs-procurement@eib.org (viestin aihekentässä on oltava seuraava teksti: ”PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund – Request for documents”).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hakemusmenettely:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ehdotukset on toimitettava englannin kielellä postitse kohdassa 1 ilmoitettuun osoitteeseen. Tehtävänkuvauksessa annettuja erityisiä ohjeita on ehdottomasti noudatettava.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yleinen kuvaus menettelystä:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tämä kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntö ei ole direktiivissä 2004/18/EY tai direktiivissä 2014/24/EU tarkoitettu julkinen hankintamenettely.</P><P>Kiinnostuneita hakijoita pyydetään toimittamaan ehdotuksensa tässä ilmoituksessa ja tehtävänkuvauksessa annettujen sääntöjen mukaisesti.</P><P>Arviointimenettelyssä käytettävät periaatteet ja menetelmät sekä arviointimenettelyn vaiheet on kuvattu tehtävänkuvauksessa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ehdotusten jättämisen määräaika:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Henkilötietojen suojaus:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kaikki toimitetut henkilötiedot käsitellään yksilöiden suojelusta yhteisöjen toimielinten ja elinten suorittamassa henkilötietojen käsittelyssä ja näiden tietojen vapaasta liikkuvuudesta 18.12.2000 annetun Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetuksen (EY) N:o 45/2001 ja sen muuttamisesta tai kumoamisesta annetun tulevan lainsäädännön mukaisesti. Kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntöä varten pyydettävät tiedot tarvitaan, jotta ehdotus voidaan arvioida, ja tietoja käytetään ainoastaan tätä tarkoitusta varten EIP:n hankintaosaston (yrityspalvelut / tietohallinto ja hankintamenettelyt / hankintamenettelyt ja hankinnat (Corporate Services / Information Management and Procurement / Procurement and Purchasing – CS/IMP/PROCUR)) valvonnassa ja EIP:n hallituksen hyväksymän EIP:n hankintoja koskevan oppaan mukaisesti. Hakijoita pyydetään huomioimaan, että ehdotuksen huomioon ottamiseksi saattaa olla pakollista vastata joihinkin tai kaikkiin hakijan täyttämässä vakuutuksessa olevista kysymyksistä. Kysymysten pakollisuus/vapaaehtoisuus on määritetty tehtävänkuvausasiakirjassa. Hakijan arvioimiseksi valintalautakunnan sekä kiinnostuksenilmaisupyynnön tilanneen osaston jäsenet tarkastelevat hakijan toimittamia henkilökohtaisia tietoja. Pääsy kyseisiin tietoihin voidaan myöntää pyynnöstä myös EIP:n vaatimuksenmukaisuudesta vastaavan pääjohtajan (Chief Compliance Officer) toimistolle, lakiasioiden osastolle tai hallinnon tarkastuksen osastolle. Valitun hakijan tietoja säilytetään sopimuksen keston ajan ja tämän jälkeen 2 vuoden ajan keskusarkistoissa, ellei niitä tarvita riita-asioiden tai korvausvaatimusten yhteydessä. Hylättyjen hakijoiden tietoja säilytetään 4 vuoden ajan, ellei niitä tarvita riita-asioiden tai korvausvaatimusten yhteydessä. Hakijalla on oikeus saada ja oikaista tai ajantasaistaa omat tietonsa. Näitä oikeuksia voi harjoittaa ottamalla yhteyttä hankintaosaston (CS/IMP/PROCUR) päällikköön (CS-procurement@eib.org). Hakija voi milloin tahansa turvautua Euroopan tietosuojavaltuutetun palveluihin.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Poissulkemisperusteet, valintaperusteet ja sopimuksentekoperusteet:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tähän pyyntömenettelyyn sovellettavat poissulkemisperusteet, hallinnolliset perusteet ja arviointiperusteet on kuvattu tehtävänkuvauksessa ja sen liitteissä.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen lähetyspäivä:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen vastaanottopäivä julkaisutoimistossa:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BEI - Appel de manifestations d'intérêt: en vue de la sélection d’intermédiaires financiers en vertu du fonds lituanien à effet de levier pour la mise en œuvre d’un instrument financier donné en garantie en Lituanie (LU-Luxembourg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Référence: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Avis à publier au Journal officiel, série S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avis d'appel de manifestations d'intérêt</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pouvoir adjudicateur</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le Fonds de fonds Jessica II pour la Lituanie, représenté, aux fins du présent appel de manifestations d'intérêt, par la</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Banque européenne d'investissement</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxembourg, Courriel : </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>agissant en qualité d'entité adjudicatrice.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Objectif de l'appel de manifestations d'intérêt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Au cours de la période de programmation 2014-2020 du «programme opérationnel pour les investissements des fonds de l’union en 2014-2020» approuvé par la décision de la Commission européenne no C (2014)6397 («Programme opérationnel») et dans le but de faire face aux défaillances du marché identifiées par les évaluations ex-ante initiales et mises à jour approuvées par le comité d’évaluation et de suivi du projet des infrastructures publics et de l’efficacité énergétique le 7.11.2014 et le 29.8.2016 respectivement («évaluation ex-ante»), le ministère des finances de la République de Lituanie, agissant comme autorité de gestion, a consacré des ressources à la mise en œuvre du fonds lituanien à effet de levier («fonds à effet de levier»). Dans le cadre du fonds à effet de levier, en signant un avenant à l’accord de financement du fonds de fonds lituanien Jessica II («Jessica II» ou «FoF») entré en vigueur le 7.5.2015 (tel que modifié le 5.10.2016) entre les ministères des finances et de l’environnement de la République de Lituanie (les «ministères») respectivement et la banque européenne d’investissement («BEI») («Accord de financement» ou «AF»), la BEI a été nommé comme organe chargé de la mise en œuvre de l’instrument financier («Instrument financier») sous forme de garantie en faveur de la République de Lituanie («Garantie»), conformément à l’article 38, paragraphe 4, point b), i) du règlement portant dispositions communes.</P><P>Les règles applicables à la mise en œuvre de l'instrument financier sont principalement énoncées dans le règlement portant dispositions communes, dans le règlement délégué de la Commission, dans le règlement d’application de la commission et dans le règlement relatif au Fonds européen de développement régional (tels que respectivement définis ci-après), ainsi que dans les lois et règlements lituaniens en vigueur.</P><P>Le présent appel de manifestations d’intérêt vise à sélectionner des institutions financières en Lituanie comme intermédiaires financiers («intermédiaires financiers»), qui doivent bénéficier, en vertu de l’accord de garantie («accord de garantie»), d’une garantie financée par les fonds structurels et d’investissement européens («Fonds ESI»). La garantie sera en partie couverte par le risque de crédit combinée à un nouveau portefeuille de prêts préférentiels à être accordés aux personnes physiques ou morales possédant des locaux dans des immeubles comprenant plusieurs appartements («bénéficiaire final») ou aux administrateurs de propriété commune («Administrateurs de propriété commune») par des intermédiaires financiers en vue de la rénovation éco-énergétique d’immeubles comprenant plusieurs appartements («Projets») conformément au cadre juridique lituanien («Prêts pour la modernisation»).</P><P>Le cahier des charges et ses annexes peuvent être demandés par courriel à l'adresse CS-procurement@eib.org avec en objet la mention: «PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — request for documents».</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure de candidature</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les propositions doivent être rédigées en anglais et transmises par courrier à l'adresse indiquée au point 1, dans le strict respect des instructions spécifiques énoncées dans le cahier des charges.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description générale de la procédure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le présent appel de manifestations d'intérêt ne constitue pas une procédure de marché public conformément aux directives 2004/18/CE ou 2014/24/UE.</P><P>Les parties intéressées sont invitées à soumettre leurs propositions en respectant les règles énoncées dans le présent avis et dans le cahier des charges.</P><P>Les principes et la méthode applicables à la procédure d'évaluation ainsi que ses étapes sont décrits dans le cahier des charges.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date limite de réception des propositions</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Protection des données personnelles</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les données à caractère personnel fournies seront traitées conformément aux dispositions du règlement (CE) 45/2001 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 18.12.2000 relatif à la protection des personnes physiques à l'égard du traitement des données à caractère personnel par les institutions et organes communautaires et à la libre circulation de ces données ainsi que toute législation future modifiant ou abrogeant ce règlement. Les informations demandées pour l'appel de manifestations d'intérêt sont nécessaires à l'évaluation des propositions et seront uniquement utilisées à cette fin sous l'autorité de la division des achats de la BEI (CS/IMP/PROCUR), conformément au guide de la BEI relatif aux marchés approuvé par le Comité de direction de la BEI. Il convient de noter que pour que les propositions soient prises en considération, il peut être obligatoire de répondre à certaines ou à l'ensemble des questions figurant sur la déclaration demandée au candidat. La nature obligatoire/facultative de ces questions est définie dans le cahier des charges. Afin d'évaluer le candidat, les données à caractère personnel fournies seront accessibles aux membres du comité de sélection et à la direction qui a lancé l'appel de manifestations d'intérêt. À la demande, ces données pourront être accessibles au Bureau du chef de conformité, au service juridique ou à l'inspection générale de la BEI. Les données fournies par le candidat retenu seront conservées pendant la durée du contrat et pendant 2 années supplémentaires dans les archives centrales, sauf si ces données sont nécessaires dans le cadre de litiges ou de réclamations. Les données fournies par les candidats non retenus seront conservées pendant 4 ans, sauf si elles sont nécessaires dans le cadre de litiges ou de réclamations. Les candidats ont le droit d'accéder à leurs données, de les rectifier ou de les mettre à jour. Il est possible d'exercer ces droits en contactant le chef de la division CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Les candidats ont également le droit de faire appel, à tout moment, au Contrôleur européen de la protection des données.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critères d'exclusion, de sélection et d'attribution</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les critères d'exclusion, administratifs et d'évaluation applicables au présent appel sont décrits dans le cahier des charges et ses annexes.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date d'envoi de l'avis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date de réception de l'avis par l'Office des publications</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΕπ - Πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος: επιλογή ενδιάμεσων χρηματοπιστωτικών οργανισμών υπό το Ταμείο Μόχλευσης Λιθουανίας για την εφαρμογή χρηματοδοτικού μέσου εγγύησης στη Λιθουανία (LU-Λουξεμβούργο)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Αριθμός αναφοράς: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Προκήρυξη προς δημοσίευση στην Επίσημη Εφημερίδα, σειρά S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα αρχή</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ταμείο Συμμετοχών Jessica II Λιθουανία, εκπροσωπούμενο για τον σκοπό της παρούσας πρόσκλησης εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος από την</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ευρωπαϊκή Τράπεζα Επενδύσεων</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Λουξεμβούργο, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Η οποία ενεργεί ως αναθέτων φορέας.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Στόχος της πρόσκλησης εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Στο πλαίσιο της προγραμματικής περιόδου 2014-2020 του «επιχειρησιακού προγράμματος για επενδύσεις ενωσιακών ταμείων την περίοδο 2014-2020» που εγκρίθηκε με την απόφαση της Ευρωπαϊκής Επιτροπής αριθ. (2014)6397 («Επιχειρησιακό πρόγραμμα») και με σκοπό την αντιμετώπιση της αδυναμίας της αγοράς που προσδιορίστηκε από τις αρχικές και συμπληρωματικές εκ των προτέρων αξιολογήσεις που εγκρίθηκαν από δημόσιες υποδομές και την επιτροπή αξιολόγησης και παρακολούθησης του σχεδίου ενεργειακής απόδοσης στις 7.11.2014 και τις 29.8.2016 αντίστοιχα («εκ των προτέρων αξιολόγηση»), το Υπουργείο Οικονομικών της Δημοκρατίας της Λιθουανίας, το οποίο ενεργεί ως αρχή διαχείρισης, έχει διαθέσει αποκλειστικά πόρους για τη δημιουργία του ταμείου μόχλευσης Λιθουανίας («ταμείο μόχλευσης»). Στο πλαίσιο του ταμείου μόχλευσης, με τη συνομολόγηση τροποποίησης στη συμφωνία χρηματοδότησης για το ταμείο συμμετοχών της Λιθουανίας Jessica II («Jessica II» ή «ταμείο συμμετοχών») που τέθηκε σε ισχύ στις 7.5.2015 (όπως τροποποιήθηκε στις 5.10.2016) μεταξύ των υπουργείων Οικονομικών και Περιβάλλοντος της Δημοκρατίας της Λιθουανίας (τα «Υπουργεία») αντίστοιχα και της Ευρωπαϊκής Τράπεζας Επενδύσεων (ΕΤΕπ) («συμφωνία χρηματοδότησης»), η ΕΤΕπ ορίστηκε φορέας εφαρμογής χρηματοδοτικού μέσου («χρηματοδοτικό μέσο») με τη μορφή εγγύησης προς όφελος της Δημοκρατίας της Λιθουανίας («εγγύηση»), σύμφωνα με το άρθρο 38 παράγραφος 4 στοιχείο β) σημείο i) του κανονισμού περί κοινών διατάξεων (ΚΚΔ).</P><P>Σχετικοί κανόνες για την εφαρμογή του χρηματοδοτικού μέσου προβλέπονται κυρίως στον ΚΚΔ, στον κατ' εξουσιοδότηση κανονισμό της Επιτροπής (CDR), στον εκτελεστικό κανονισμό της Επιτροπής και στον κανονισμό του Ευρωπαϊκού Ταμείου Περιφερειακής Ανάπτυξης (ΕΤΠΑ) (όπως ορίζονται αντιστοίχως κατωτέρω), και στις ισχύουσες νομοθετικές και κανονιστικές διατάξεις της Λιθουανίας.</P><P>Σκοπός της παρούσας πρόσκλησης εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος («πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος») είναι η επιλογή επιλέξιμων χρηματοπιστωτικών ιδρυμάτων στη Λιθουανία προκειμένου να καταστούν ενδιάμεσοι χρηματοπιστωτικοί οργανισμοί («χρηματοπιστωτικοί διαμεσολαβητές»), οι οποίοι, στο πλαίσιο της συμφωνίας εγγύησης («συμφωνία εγγύησης»), λαμβάνουν εγγύηση που χρηματοδοτείται από τα Ευρωπαϊκά Διαρθρωτικά και Επενδυτικά Ταμεία (ΕΔΕΤ). Η εγγύηση θα καλύψει εν μέρει τους πιστωτικούς κινδύνους, που σχετίζονται με τα νέα χαρτοφυλάκια δανείων με ευνοϊκούς όρους που πρόκειται να χορηγηθούν από χρηματοπιστωτικούς διαμεσολαβητές, σε φυσικά ή νομικά πρόσωπα, που έχουν στην κατοχή τους ακίνητη περιουσία σε πολυκατοικίες («τελικός αποδέκτης») ή σε διαχειριστές κοινής ιδιοκτησίας («διαχειριστές κοινής ιδιοκτησίας») για την ενεργειακά αποδοτική ανακαίνιση των πολυκατοικιών («σχέδια»), σε συμφωνία με τη νομοθεσία της Λιθουανίας («δάνεια εκσυγχρονισμού»).</P><P>Οι όροι αναφοράς συμπεριλαμβανομένων των παραρτημάτων μπορούν να ζητηθούν μέσω της αποστολής μηνύματος ηλεκτρονικού ταχυδρομείου στη διεύθυνση CS-procurement@eib.org με θέμα «PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents».</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Διαδικασία υποβολής υποψηφιοτήτων</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Οι προτάσεις πρέπει να υποβληθούν στα αγγλικά μέσω ταχυδρομείου στη διεύθυνση που αναφέρεται στο σημείο 1, με αυστηρή τήρηση των συγκεκριμένων οδηγιών που παρέχονται στους όρους αναφοράς.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Γενική περιγραφή της διαδικασίας</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Η παρούσα πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος δεν συνιστά διαδικασία σύναψης δημόσιας σύμβασης κατά την έννοια των οδηγιών 2004/18/ΕΚ ή 2014/24/EΕ.</P><P>Οι ενδιαφερόμενοι καλούνται να υποβάλουν τις προτάσεις τους σύμφωνα με τους κανόνες που ορίζονται στην παρούσα προκήρυξη και στους όρους αναφοράς.</P><P>Οι αρχές και η μέθοδος που εφαρμόζονται για τη διαδικασία αξιολόγησης, καθώς και τα στάδια των διαδικασιών αξιολόγησης περιγράφονται στους όρους αναφοράς.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προθεσμία υποβολής των προτάσεων</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προστασία δεδομένων προσωπικού χαρακτήρα</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Τα δεδομένα προσωπικού χαρακτήρα που θα παράσχετε θα υποστούν επεξεργασία σύμφωνα με τον κανονισμό (ΕΚ) 45/2001 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 18.12.2000, σχετικά με την προστασία των φυσικών προσώπων έναντι της επεξεργασίας δεδομένων προσωπικού χαρακτήρα από τα όργανα και τους οργανισμούς της Κοινότητας και σχετικά με την ελεύθερη κυκλοφορία των δεδομένων αυτών και οποιαδήποτε μελλοντική νομοθεσία τροποποίησης ή κατάργησης. Οι πληροφορίες που ζητούνται για την πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος είναι απαραίτητες για την αξιολόγηση της πρότασής σας και θα χρησιμοποιηθούν αποκλειστικά για τον σκοπό αυτό, υπό την εποπτεία του τμήματος αγορών της ΕΤΕπ (CS/IMP/PROCUR), σύμφωνα με τον οδηγό για τις δημόσιες συμβάσεις της ΕΤΕπ, κατόπιν έγκρισης από τη Διευθύνουσα Επιτροπή της ΕΤΕπ. Πρέπει να σημειωθεί ότι προκειμένου να εξεταστεί η πρότασή σας, ενδέχεται να είναι υποχρεωτική η απάντηση σε ορισμένες ή όλες τις ερωτήσεις στη δήλωση που θα υποβληθεί από τον υποψήφιο. Η υποχρεωτική/προαιρετική φύση των εν λόγω ερωτήσεων διευκρινίζεται στο έγγραφο των όρων αναφοράς. Για την αξιολόγηση του υποψήφιου, τα δεδομένα προσωπικού χαρακτήρα που θα παράσχετε θα αξιολογηθούν από τα μέλη της επιτροπής επιλογής και από τη Διεύθυνση που ζήτησε την πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος. Κατόπιν αιτήματος, ενδέχεται να επιτραπεί η πρόσβαση στα εν λόγω δεδομένα για την υπηρεσία του υπεύθυνου συμμόρφωσης, τη νομική υπηρεσία ή τη Γενική Επιθεώρηση Υπηρεσιών της ΕΤΕπ. Τα δεδομένα του επιλεγέντος υποψήφιου θα διατηρηθούν στα κεντρικά αρχεία για τη διάρκεια της σύμβασης, συν 2 έτη, εκτός εάν απαιτηθούν στο πλαίσιο δικαστικών διαφορών ή απαιτήσεων. Τα δεδομένα των μη επιλεγέντων υποψηφίων θα διατηρηθούν για 4 έτη, εκτός εάν απαιτηθούν στο πλαίσιο δικαστικών διαφορών ή απαιτήσεων. Έχετε δικαίωμα να δείτε και να διορθώσετε ή να ενημερώσετε τα δεδομένα σας. Μπορείτε να ασκήσετε τα εν λόγω δικαιώματά σας επικοινωνώντας με τον επικεφαλής του τμήματος CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Έχετε επίσης το δικαίωμα να προσφύγετε ανά πάσα στιγμή στον Ευρωπαίο Επόπτη Προστασίας Δεδομένων.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Κριτήρια αποκλεισμού, κριτήρια επιλογής και ανάθεσης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Τα κριτήρια αποκλεισμού, τα διοικητικά κριτήρια και τα κριτήρια αξιολόγησης που ισχύουν για την παρούσα πρόσκληση περιγράφονται στους όρους αναφοράς και τα παραρτήματά τους.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ημερομηνία αποστολής της παρούσας προς δημοσίευση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ημερομηνία παραλαβής της από την Υπηρεσία Εκδόσεων</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BEI - Invito a manifestare interesse per la selezione di intermediari finanziari ai sensi del fondo lituano soggetto a leva finanziaria per l’attuazione di uno strumento finanziario di garanzia in Lituania (LU-Lussemburgo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Riferimento: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Avviso da pubblicare nella Gazzetta ufficiale, serie S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invito a manifestare interesse</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Amministrazione aggiudicatrice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il fondo di fondi lituano "Jessica II", rappresentato ai fini del presente invito a manifestare interesse dalla</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Banca europea per gli investimenti</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Lussemburgo, e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>che agisce in qualità di amministrazione aggiudicatrice.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oggetto dell'invito a manifestare interesse</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nell'ambito del periodo di programmazione 2014-2020 del "programma operativo per gli investimenti dei fondi dell'UE nel 2014-2020", approvato dalla decisione della Commissione europea n. C(2014) 6397 ("Programma operativo"), e allo scopo di porre rimedio al fallimento del mercato identificato dalle valutazioni ex ante iniziali e aggiornate approvate rispettivamente il 7.11.2014 e il 29.8.2016 dal comitato di valutazione e monitoraggio dei progetti di infrastruttura pubblica ed efficienza energetica ("valutazione ex ante"), il ministero delle Finanze della Repubblica di Lituania, agendo in qualità di autorità di gestione, ha stanziato risorse per l'attuazione del fondo lituano soggetto a leva finanziaria ("fondo soggetto a leva finanziaria"). Nel contesto del fondo soggetto a leva finanziaria, modificando l'accordo di finanziamento per il fondo di fondi lituano "Jessica II" ("Jessica II" o "FdF"), entrato in vigore il 7.5.2015 (modificato il 5.10.2016) e stipulato tra i ministeri delle Finanze e dell'Ambiente della Repubblica di Lituania (i "ministeri") da una parte e la Banca europea per gli investimenti ("BEI") dall'altra ("accordo di finanziamento" o "AF"), la BEI è stata nominata organismo che attua uno strumento finanziario ("Strumento finanziario") sotto forma di garanzia a beneficio della Repubblica di Lituania ("Garanzia "), conformemente all'articolo 38, paragrafo 4, lettera b), punto i), del regolamento recante disposizioni comuni ("RDC").</P><P>Le pertinenti norme di attuazione dello strumento finanziario sono stipulate principalmente nel RDC, nel regolamento delegato della Commissione, nel regolamento di attuazione della Commissione e nel regolamento per il Fondo europeo di sviluppo regionale ("FESR") (come definiti di seguito), nonché nella legislazione e nei regolamenti lituani applicabili.</P><P>L'obiettivo dell'invito a manifestare interesse consiste nella selezione di istituti finanziari ammissibili in Lituania, affinché questi operino come intermediari finanziari ("Intermediari finanziari") che, in base all'accordo di garanzia ("Accordo di garanzia"), ricevono una garanzia finanziata dai Fondi strutturali e di investimento europei ("fondi SIE"). La garanzia copre in parte il rischio di credito associato a un nuovo portafoglio di prestiti agevolati che dovrà essere concesso dagli intermediari finanziari a persone fisiche o giuridiche che possiedono locali in condomini ("Destinatario finale") o ad amministratori di proprietà comune ("Amministratori di proprietà comune ") per l'ammodernamento dell'efficienza energetica dei condomini ("Progetti") in conformità con la base giuridica lituana ("Prestiti di ammodernamento").</P><P>Il capitolato d'oneri compresi gli allegati può essere richiesto inviando un'e-mail a CSprocurement@eib.org indicando come oggetto "PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents".</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Modalità procedurali della domanda</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le offerte dovranno essere presentate in lingua inglese per posta all'indirizzo di cui al punto 1, nel rispetto rigoroso delle specifiche istruzioni stabilite nel capitolato d'oneri.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione generale della procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il presente invito a manifestare interesse non rappresenta una procedura di appalto pubblico ai sensi delle direttive 2004/18/CE o 2014/24/UE.</P><P>Le parti interessate sono invitate a presentare le loro proposte in conformità delle norme stabilite nel presente avviso e nel capitolato d'oneri.</P><P>I principi e le modalità applicabili alla procedura di valutazione nonché le fasi della procedura di valutazione sono descritti nel capitolato d'oneri.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Termine ultimo per la presentazione delle proposte</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Protezione dei dati personali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>I dati personali forniti saranno trattati conformemente al regolamento (CE) n. 45/2001 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, del 18.12.2000, concernente la tutela delle persone fisiche in relazione al trattamento dei dati personali da parte delle istituzioni e degli organismi comunitari, nonché la libera circolazione di tali dati, e in conformità con qualsiasi eventuale modifica o abrogazione di tale regolamento. Le informazioni richieste per l'invito a manifestare il proprio interesse saranno necessarie per valutare la proposta e saranno utilizzate esclusivamente a tal fine sotto l'autorità della divisione Acquisti della BEI (CS/IMP/PROCUR), conformemente alla guida sugli appalti della BEI, approvata dal comitato di gestione della BEI. Si noti che affinché la proposta venga presa in considerazione, sarà obbligatorio rispondere ad alcune o a tutte le domande nella dichiarazione che sarà presentata dal candidato. La natura opzionale/obbligatoria di tali domande è indicato nei documenti relativi al capitolato d'oneri. Per valutare il candidato, i dati personali forniti dovranno essere accessibili dal comitato di selezione e dalla direzione che ha indetto l'invito a manifestare interesse. Su richiesta, l'accesso a tali dati potrà essere concesso all'ufficio del responsabile del controllo della conformità ("Office of the Chief Compliance Officer"), al servizio giuridico o all'ispettorato generale. I dati relativi al candidato selezionato dovranno essere conservati per tutta la durata del contratto, più 2 anni negli archivi centrali, salvo nel caso in cui questi siano necessari nel contesto di controversie o reclami. I dati dei candidati non selezionati saranno conservati per 4 anni, salvo nel caso in cui questi siano necessari nel contesto di controversie o reclami. Il candidato avrà diritto di accesso, rettifica o aggiornamento dei propri dati. Sarà possibile esercitare tale diritto contattando il capo della divisione CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Il candidato avrà altresì il diritto di presentare ricorso al Garante europeo della protezione dei dati in qualsiasi momento.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteri di esclusione, selezione e aggiudicazione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>I criteri di esclusione, i criteri amministrativi e i criteri di valutazione applicabili al presente invito sono descritti nel capitolato d'oneri e nei suoi allegati.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data di spedizione dell'avviso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data di ricevimento del bando da parte dell'Ufficio delle pubblicazioni</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling: om financiële tussenpersonen te selecteren onder het Lithuanian Leveraged Fund om een financieel instrument in Litouwen ten uitvoer te leggen (LU-Luxemburg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referentie: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Aankondiging voor bekendmaking in het Publicatieblad, reeks S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Aankondiging van een oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Het Jessica II-fonds van fondsen voor Litouwen, in het kader van deze oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling vertegenwoordigd door de</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europese Investeringsbank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg, e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>die optreedt als de aanbestedende instantie.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Voorwerp van de oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Binnen de programmeringsperiode 2014-2020 van het „operationele programma voor fondsinvesteringen van de Unie in 2014-2020“ goedgekeurd door de beslissing van de Europese Commissie nr. C (2014)6397 („Operationeel programma”) en met als doel het aanpakken van het marktfalen geïdentificeerd door de initiële en bijgewerkte ex ante-beoordelingen goedgekeurd door het comité voor de evaluatie van en het toezicht op openbare infrastructuur en energie-efficiëntie op 7.11.2014 en 29.8.2016 respectievelijk („ex ante-beoordeling”), het Ministerie van Financiën van de Republiek Litouwen optredend als de beheersautoriteit, heeft middelen toegekend voor de tenuitvoerlegging van het Lithuanian Leveraged Fund. In het kader van het Leveraged Fund werd door middel van een wijziging op het Jessica II-fonds van fondsen voor Litouwen („Jessica II” of „FoF”) de financieringsovereenkomst die in werking is getreden op 7.5.2015 (zoals gewijzigd op 5.10.2016) tussen de Ministeries van Financiën en Milieu van de Republiek Litouwen (de „Ministeries”) respectievelijk en de Europese Investeringsbank („EIB”) („Financieringsovereenkomst” of „FA”), en werd het EIB aangesteld voor de tenuitvoerlegging van een financieel instrument („Financieel instrument”) in de vorm van een garantie ten behoeve van de Republiek Litouwen („Garantie”), overeenkomstig artikel 38, lid 4, onder i) van de verordening gemeenschappelijke bepalingen.</P><P>De relevante regels voor tenuitvoerlegging van het financiële instrument (zoals hieronder beschreven) zijn voornamelijk vervat in de verordening gemeenschappelijke bepalingen, de gedelegeerde verordening van de Commissie, de uitvoeringsverordening van de Commissie, de EFRO-verordening (respectievelijk hieronder beschreven) en de toepasselijke Litouwse wet- en regelgeving.</P><P>De doelstelling van deze oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling is het selecteren van in aanmerking komende financiële instellingen in Litouwen om financiële tussenpersonen te worden („Financiële tussenpersonen”), die uit hoofde van de garantieovereenkomst („Garantieovereenkomst”) een garantie zullen ontvangen die is gefinancierd door Europese structuur- en investeringsfondsen („ESIF”). De garantie zal gedeeltelijk het kredietrisico dekken dat verbonden is aan een nieuwe portfolio van toe te kennen preferentiële leningen door financiële tussenpersonen aan natuurlijke of rechtspersonen die gebouwen bezitten in gebouwen met meerdere appartementen („Eindbegunstigde”) of aan beheerders van gemeenschappelijk eigendom („Beheerders van gemeenschappelijk eigendom”) voor de renovatie van de energie-efficiëntie in gebouwen met meerdere appartementen („Projecten”) overeenkomstig de Litouwse juridische basis („Moderniseringsleningen”).</P><P>De taakomschrijving met inbegrip van bijlagen kan worden aangevraagd door een e-mail te sturen naar CS-procurement@eib.org met het onderwerp „PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — request for documents”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanvraagprocedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De voorstellen moeten in het Engels worden ingediend via de post op het adres dat vermeld is in punt 1, waarbij de instructies die zijn vastgesteld in de taakomschrijving strikt moeten worden nageleefd.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Algemene beschrijving van de procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Deze oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling is geen openbare aanbesteding in de zin van de Richtlijnen 2004/18/EG of 2014/24/EU.</P><P>Geïnteresseerde partijen worden uitgenodigd hun voorstellen in te dienen in overeenstemming met de bepalingen die zijn vastgesteld in deze aankondiging en in de taakomschrijving.</P><P>De beginselen en methode die worden toegepast bij het evaluatieproces en de fasen van het evaluatieproces zijn beschreven in de taakomschrijving.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uiterste datum voor de indiening van inschrijvingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bescherming van persoonsgegevens:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uw persoonsgegevens zullen worden verwerkt overeenkomstig Verordening (EG) nr. 45/2001 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 18.12.2000 betreffende de bescherming van natuurlijke personen in verband met de verwerking van persoonsgegevens door de communautaire instellingen en organen en betreffende het vrije verkeer van die gegevens en enige toekomstige wetgeving die dit wijzigt of intrekt. De informatie die in het kader van de oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling wordt gevraagd, is nodig om uw voorstel te beoordelen en zal uitsluitend voor dat doel worden gebruikt in opdracht van de inkoopafdeling van de EIB (CS/IMP/PROCUR), in overeenstemming met de gids voor opdrachtprocedures van de EIB die is goedgekeurd door het Comité van beheer van de EIB. Gelieve op te merken dat het voor de inachtneming van uw voorstel verplicht kan zijn om enkele of alle vragen te beantwoorden in de verklaring die door de aanvrager moet worden opgesteld. De verplichte/vrijblijvende aard van deze vragen is beschreven in de taakomschrijving. Om de aanvrager te beoordelen zullen de door u verstrekte persoonsgegevens worden bekeken door leden van het selectiecomité en het directoraat die de oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling uitschreef. Op verzoek kan toegang tot deze gegevens worden verleend aan het kantoor van het hoofd Compliance, de juridische dienst of de Algemene Inspectiedienst van de EIB. De gegevens van de geselecteerde aanvrager zullen worden bijgehouden gedurende de looptijd van de opdracht, plus 2 jaar in het centrale archief, tenzij ze nodig zijn in het kader van geschillen of vorderingen. De gegevens van niet-geselecteerde aanvragers zullen 4 jaar worden bijgehouden, tenzij ze nodig zijn in het kader van geschillen of vorderingen. U heeft het recht op toegang tot uw persoonsgegevens en op rectificatie of actualisering van die gegevens. U kan deze rechten uitoefenen door contact op te nemen met het hoofd van de afdeling CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). U heeft eveneens het recht om de Europese Toezichthouder voor gegevensbescherming te allen tijde aan te zoeken.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uitsluitings-, selectie- en gunningscriteria:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De uitsluitingscriteria, administratieve criteria en beoordelingscriteria die op deze aanbesteding van toepassing zijn, worden beschreven in de aanbestedingsstukken en de bijbehorende bijlagen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum van verzending van de aankondiging:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum van ontvangst door het Publicatiebureau:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BEI - Convite à manifestação de interesse: para selecionar intermediários financeiros no âmbito do Fundo de Alavancagem Lituano para implementar um instrumento financeiro de garantia na Lituânia (LU-Luxemburgo)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referência: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(O anúncio será publicado no Jornal Oficial, série S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Convite à manifestação de interesse</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fundo de fundos Jessica II da Lituânia, representado, para efeitos do presente convite à manifestação de interesse, pelo</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Banco Europeu de Investimento</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburgo, Endereço eletrónico: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>que atua como entidade contratante.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Objeto do convite à manifestação de interesse</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>No período de programação 2014-2020 do "programa operacional para investimentos de fundos sindicais em 2014-2020" aprovado pela decisão da Comissão Europeia n.º C (2014)6397 ("Programa Operacional") e com o objetivo de resolver a deficiência do mercado identificada pelas avaliações prévias iniciais e atualizadas aprovadas pelo comité de avaliação e monitorização de projetos de infraestrutura pública e eficiência energética em 7.11.2014 e 29.8.2016, respetivamente ("avaliação ex-ante"), o Ministério das Finanças da República da Lituânia, atuando como autoridade de gestão, tem recursos dedicados à implementação do fundo de alavancagem da Lituânia ("fundo de alavancagem"). No contexto do fundo de alavancagem, ao concluir uma alteração ao fundo de fundos Jessica II, o acordo de financiamento Lituânia ("Jessica II" ou "FoF") entrou em vigor em 7.5.2015 (conforme alterado em 5.10.2016) entre os Ministérios de Finanças e de Meio Ambiente da República da Lituânia (os "Ministérios") e o Banco Europeu de Investimento ("BEI") ("Acordo de Financiamento" ou "AF"), o BEI foi nomeado um órgão que implementa um instrumento financeiro ("Instrumento Financeiro") sob a forma de garantia em benefício da República da Lituânia ("Garantia"), em conformidade com o n.º 4, alínea b), alínea i), do artigo 38.º do Regulamento das Disposições Comuns ("RDC").</P><P>As regras relevantes para a implementação do instrumento financeiro encontram-se estipuladas principalmente no RDC, nos regulamentos de execução da Comissão, no regulamento de execução e no Fundo Europeu de Desenvolvimento Regional (FEDER) (respetivamente conforme definido infra), e nos regulamentos e nas legislações da Lituânia aplicáveis.</P><P>O objetivo do convite à manifestação de interesse ("Call for EoI") é selecionar as instituições financeiras elegíveis na Lituânia para se tornarem intermediários financeiros ("Intermediários financeiros"), que devem, nos termos do contrato de garantia ("Contrato de garantia"), receber garantia financiada pelos fundos europeus estruturais e de investimento («ESIF»). A garantia abrangerá, em parte, o risco de crédito associado a uma nova carteira de empréstimos preferenciais a serem concedidos por intermediários financeiros a pessoas físicas ou jurídicas que possuam instalações em edifícios de vários apartamentos ("Beneficiário final") ou a administradores de propriedade comum ("Administradores de propriedade comum") para a renovação da eficiência energética de edifícios de vários apartamentos ("Projetos") de acordo com a base jurídica da Lituânia ("Empréstimos de modernização").</P><P>Os termos de referência incluindo os anexos podem ser solicitados através de correio eletrónico para: CSprocurement@eib.org com o assunto «PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents».</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Modalidades de apresentação das candidaturas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>As propostas devem ser enviadas em inglês, por correio, para o endereço indicado no ponto 1, em plena conformidade com as instruções específicas estabelecidas nos termos de referência.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição geral do procedimento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O presente convite à manifestação de interesse não representa um processo de concurso público, na aceção das Diretivas 2004/18/CE ou 2014/24/UE.</P><P>As partes interessadas são convidadas a apresentar as suas propostas em conformidade com as regras estabelecidas no presente anúncio e nos termos de referência.</P><P>Os princípios e o método aplicável ao processo de avaliação, bem como as fases do processo de avaliação, estão descritos nos termos de referência.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data-limite para a apresentação das propostas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Proteção de dados pessoais</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Os dados pessoais fornecidos pelos candidatos serão tratados de acordo com o Regulamento (CE) 45/2001 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 18.12.2000, relativo à proteção das pessoas singulares no que diz respeito ao tratamento de dados pessoais pelas instituições e pelos órgãos comunitários e à livre circulação desses dados e qualquer futura legislação que a altere ou revogue. As informações solicitadas para o convite à manifestação de interesse são necessárias para avaliar as propostas dos candidatos e serão utilizadas exclusivamente para esse efeito, sob a autoridade da divisão de compras do BEI (CS/IMP/PROCUR), em conformidade com o guia de contratos do BEI, aprovado pelo Comité de Gestão do BEI. Para que a proposta seja considerada, importa notar que poderá assumir um caráter obrigatório a resposta a algumas ou a todas as questões formuladas na declaração a preencher pelo candidato. O caráter obrigatório/facultativo dessas perguntas encontra-se descrito nos termos do documento de referência. A fim de avaliar o candidato, os membros do painel de seleção e da Direção que solicitou o convite à manifestação de interesse acederão aos dados pessoais facultados pelo referido candidato. Mediante pedido, o acesso a estes dados poderá ser concedido ao Gabinete de Conformidade do BEI, ao serviço jurídico ou à Inspeção-Geral. Os dados do candidato selecionado devem ser conservados durante a vigência do contrato, mais 2 anos nos arquivos centrais, salvo se estes forem necessários no contexto de litígios ou queixas. Os dados dos candidatos não selecionados devem ser conservados durante 4 anos, salvo se estes forem necessários no contexto de litígios ou queixas. Os candidatos têm o direito de acesso e de retificação ou atualização dos seus dados. Pode exercer os referidos direitos mediante pedido dirigido ao chefe de divisão do CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Têm ainda o direito de recorrer, em qualquer altura, à Autoridade Europeia para a Proteção de Dados.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critérios de exclusão, seleção e adjudicação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Os critérios de exclusão, critérios administrativos e critérios de avaliação aplicáveis ao presente convite encontram-se descritos nos termos de referência e respetivos anexos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data de envio do anúncio</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data da receção pelo Serviço das Publicações</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Uppmaning till intresseanmälan: val av finansiella intermediärer inom ramen för den litauiska hävstångsfonden för att genomföra ett garanterat finansiellt instrument i Litauen (LU-Luxemburg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referens: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Meddelande för offentliggörande i Europeiska unionens officiella tidning, S-serien)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Meddelande om uppmaning till intresseanmälan</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Litauens fondandelsfond Jessica II, som för syftet med denna uppmaning till intresseanmälan representeras av</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska investeringsbanken</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, 2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg, e-post: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>som agerar som upphandlande enhet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Målet med uppmaningen till intresseanmälan</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Under programperioden 2014-2020 för “det operationella programmet för investeringar av unionens medel under 2014-2020” som godkänts genom Europeiska kommissionens beslut nr C (2014)6397 (“operationella programmet”) och med syftet att ta itu med marknadsmisslyckandet som identifierats genom de initiala och uppdaterade förhandsbedömningar som godkänts av kommittén för utvärdering och övervakning av offentliga infrastrukturs -och energieffektivitetsprojekt den 7.11.2014 respektive den 29.8.2016 (“förhandsbedömningar”), då Republiken finansministeriet i Litauen i egenskap av förvaltande myndighet tillägnade resurser till genomförandet av den litauiska hävstångsfonden (“leveraged fund”). I kontexten för hävstångsfonden blev xxx genom att göra en ändring i fondandelsfonden Jessica II Litauen (“Jessica II” eller “FoF”) fonderingsöverenskommelse som trätt ikraft 7.5.2015 (i ändrad lydelse 5.10.2016) mellan finansministeriet och Miljministeriet i Republiken Litauen (“ministerierna”) och europeiska investeringsbanken (“EIB”) (Funding Agreement” eller “FA”), EIB utpekad som enhet för implementering av finansiellt instrument (F”Financial Instrument”) i form av en garanti till förmån för Republiken Litauen (“Guarantee”), i enlighet med artikel 38 ( (4) (b)(i) Common Provisions Regulation (“CPR”).</P><P>Relevanta bestämmelser för tillämpningen av det finansiella instrumentet anges främst i CPR, kommissionens delegerade förordning (Commission Delegated Regulation – CDR), Kommissionens tillämpningsföreskrifter och Eruf-förordningen (såsom definieras nedan) samt tillämplig litauisk lagstiftning och förordningar.</P><P>Syftet med uppmaningen till intresseanmälan (“Call for Eol”) är att välja ut behöriga finansiella institutioner i Litauen till att bli finansiella intermediärer (“Financial Intermediaries”), som under garantiavtalet (“Guarantee Agreement”) erhåller garanterade medel av europeiska struktur- och investeringsfonder (“ESIF”). Garantin ska delvis täcka kreditrisken i anknytning till en ny portfölj av förmånliga lån som ska beviljas av finansiella intermediärer till fysiska eller juridiska personer som äger lokaler i flerfamiljshus (“Final Recipient”) eller till förvaltare av gemensam egendom (“Administrators of Common Property”) för energieffektivisering av flerfamiljshus (“Projects”) i enlighet med litauisk rättslig grund (“Modernisation Loans”).</P><P>Förfrågningsunderlag inbegripet bilagor kan beställas genom att skicka ett e-postmeddelande till CSprocurement@eib.org med titeln PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund ― Request for documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ansökningsförfarande</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Förslagen ska brevledes lämnas in, på engelska, till den adress som anges i punkt 1, i strikt överensstämmelse med de särskilda anvisningar som anges i kravspecifikationerna.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Allmän beskrivning av förfarandet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Denna uppmaning till intresseanmälan utgör inte ett offentligt upphandlingsförfarande i den mening som avses i direktiven 2004/18/EG eller 2014/24/EU.</P><P>Berörda parter uppmanas att lämna in sina förslag i enlighet med de regler som anges i detta meddelande och i kravspecifikationerna.</P><P>Principerna och metoden som kommer att tillämpas under utvärderingsförfarandet, samt utvärderingsförfarandets etapper, beskrivs i förfrågningsunderlaget.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sista inlämningsdag för projektförslag</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Skydd av personuppgifter</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Inlämnade personuppgifter kommer att behandlas i enlighet med Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EG) nr 45/2001 av den 18.12.2000 om skydd för enskilda då gemenskapsinstitutionerna och gemenskapsorganen behandlar personuppgifter och om den fria rörligheten för sådana uppgifter och eventuell framtida lagstiftning som ändrar eller upphäver den. Den information som erfordras för uppmaningen till intresseanmälan (call for expression of interest – CEoI) krävs för att kunna utvärdera förslaget och kommer att användas endast för detta syfte under ledning av EIB:s inköpsavdelning (CS/IMP/PROCUR), i enlighet med EIB:s vägledning för upphandling som har godkänts av EIB:s direktion. Observera att för att förslaget ska beaktas kan det vara obligatoriskt att besvara några eller alla frågor i försäkran som sökanden ska tillhandahålla. Huruvida dessa frågor är av obligatorisk/frivillig karaktär anges i kravspecifikationerna. För att kunna utvärdera den sökande kommer medlemmarna i uttagningsjuryn samt direktoratet som erfordrar denna CEoI att ha tillgång till de inlämnade personuppgifterna. På begäran får tillgång till dessa uppgifter beviljas EIB:s huvudsakliga regelefterlevnadsansvariges kansli, rättstjänsten och allmänna tjänsteinspektionen. Uppgifterna för den sökande som väljs ut kommer att bevaras under kontraktets löptid samt ytterligare 2 år i centralarkiven, såvida inte dessa behövs i samband med rättstvister eller fordringar. Uppgifterna för sökande som inte valts ut kommer att bevaras under 4 år, såvida inte dessa behövs i samband med rättstvister eller fordringar. Man har rätt att få åtkomst till och rätta eller aktualisera de inlämnade uppgifterna. Dessa rättigheter kan utövas genom att kontakta chefen för avdelningen CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Man har också rätt att när som helst vända sig till Europeiska datatillsynsmannen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uteslutningskriterier, uttagningskriterier och tilldelningskriterier</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De uteslutningskriterier, administrativa kriterier och bedömningskriterier som gäller för denna uppmaning till intresseanmälan beskrivs i kravspecifikationerna och tillhörande bilagor.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum då meddelandet sänts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum då detta meddelande mottogs av publikationsbyrån</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Výzva k vyjádření zájmu: vybrat finanční zprostředkovatele v rámci litevského fondu Leveraged Fund za účelem zavedení garančního finančního nástroje v Litvě (LU-Lucemburk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenční číslo: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Oznámení ke zveřejnění v Úředním věstníku, řada S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Oznámení o výzvě k vyjádření zájmu</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veřejný zadavatel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fond fondů Jessica II pro region Litva, který zastupuje pro účely této výzvy k vyjádření zájmu</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská investiční banka</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Lucembursko, e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>, která jedná jako zadavatelský subjekt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Předmět výzvy k vyjádření zájmu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>V programovém období 2014-2020 „operačního programu pro investice fondů Unie v letech 2014-2020“ schváleném rozhodnutím Evropské komise č. C (2014) 6397 („Operační program“) a za účelem řešení selhání trhu identifikovaných počátečními a aktualizovanými posouzeními ex-ante schválenými veřejnou infrastrukturu a výborem pro hodnocení a monitorování projektů v oblasti energetické účinnosti dne 7.11.2014 a 29.8.2016 (dále jen „posouzení exante“), přičemž Ministerstvo financí Litevské republiky, řídící orgán, vyčlenila prostředky na realizaci litevského fondu leveraged fund („leveraged fund“). V souvislosti s fondem leveraged fund uzavřením dodatku k dohodě o financovánín fondu fondů Jessica II pro region Litva („Jessica II“ nebo „FoF“), která vstoupila v platnost dne 7.5.2015 (ve znění pozdějších změn 5.10.2016) mezi Ministerstvem financí a Ministerstvem životní prostředí Litevské republiky („ministerstva“) a Evropskou investiční bankou (EIB) (dále jen „dohoda o financování“ nebo „FA“) byla EIB jmenována orgánem, který provádí finanční nástroj („finanční nástroj“) ve formě záruky ve prospěch Litevské republiky („záruka“) v souladu s čl. 38 odst. 4 písm. b) bodem i) nařízení o společných ustanoveních (CPR).</P><P>Příslušná pravidla pro provádění finančního nástroje jsou primárně stanovena v nařízení o společných ustanoveních (Common Provisions Regulation – CPR), nařízení v přenesené pravomoci (Commission Delegated Regulation – CDR), prováděcím nařízení a nařízení o Evropském fondu pro regionální rozvoj (European Regional Development Fund – ERDF) (respektive dle vymezení níže) a platných zákonech a nařízeních Litvy.</P><P>Cílem výzvy k vyjádření zájmu („Call for EoI“) je vybrat v Litvě způsobilé finanční instituce, aby se staly finančními zprostředkovateli („finanční zprostředkovatelé“), kteří podle záruční smlouvy („záruční smlouva“) obdrží zárukou financovanou evropskými strukturálními a investičními fondy („ESIF“). Záruka bude částečně pokrývat úvěrové riziko spojené s novým portfoliem preferenčních úvěrů poskytnutých finančními zprostředkovateli fyzickým nebo právnickým osobám, které vlastní prostory v budovách s více byty („konečný příjemce“) nebo správcům společného majetku („správci společného majetku“) na renovaci budov s více byty s energetickou účinností („projekty“) v souladu s litevským právním základem („modernizační úvěry“).</P><P>Podmínky kompetence včetně příloh lze vyžádat zasláním e-mailu na adresu CSprocurement@eib.org s předmětem PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents (PC-1439 fond Leveraged Fund pro region Litva – žádost o dokumenty).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Proces podávání přihlášek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Návrhy musí být podány v angličtině poštou na adresu uvedenou v bodě 1, v přísném souladu s konkrétními pokyny stanovenými v referenčních podmínkách.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Obecný popis řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tato výzva k vyjádření zájmu nepředstavuje výběrové řízení pro zadání veřejné zakázky ve smyslu směrnic 2004/18/ES nebo 2014/24/EU.</P><P>Zainteresované strany se vyzývají k podání svých návrhů v souladu s pravidly uvedenými v tomto oznámení a v referenčních podmínkách.</P><P>Zásady a metoda, které se týkají procesu hodnocení, jakož i fází procesu hodnocení, jsou popsány v podmínkách kompetence.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lhůta pro podání návrhů</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ochrana osobních údajů</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Vámi poskytnuté osobní údaje budou zpracovávány v souladu s nařízením Evropského parlamentu a Rady (ES) č. 45/2001 ze dne 18.12.2000 o ochraně fyzických osob v souvislosti se zpracováním osobních údajů orgány a institucemi Společenství a o volném pohybu těchto údajů a veškeré budoucí právní předpisy, které jej změní nebo zruší. Informace požadované pro výzvu k vyjádření zájmu (CEoI) jsou nezbytné za účelem vyhodnocení vašeho návrhu a budou použity výhradně za tímto účelem v rámci pravomocí nákupního oddělení EIB (CS/IMP/PROCUR) v souladu s návodem k veřejným zakázkám EIB, schváleným řídícím výborem EIB. Upozorňujeme, že aby váš návrh byl zvážen, může být požadována povinná odpověď na některé nebo všechny otázky v prohlášení, které má být uchazečem učiněno. Povinná / volitelná povaha těchto otázek je uvedena v podmínkách kompetence. Za účelem hodnocení uchazeče budou vámi poskytnuté osobní údaje zpřístupněny členům výběrové komise a ředitelství, které zažádalo o výzvu k vyjádření zájmu (CEol). Na základě žádosti může být přístup k těmto údajům poskytnut oddělení vedoucího pracovníka pověřeného kontrolou souladu postupů a činností v rámci EIB, právní službě nebo generálnímu inspektorátu. Údaje úspěšného uchazeče budou uchovávány po celou dobu trvání zakázky a další 2 roky v ústředním archivu, pokud nebudou zapotřebí v souvislosti se soudním sporem nebo pohledávkami. Údaje neúspěšných uchazečů musí být uchovávány po dobu 4 let, pokud nebudou zapotřebí v souvislosti se soudním sporem nebo pohledávkami. Máte právo na přístup ke svým údajům a jejich opravu nebo aktualizaci. Tato práva můžete uplatnit kontaktováním vedoucího oddělení CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Máte rovněž právo se kdykoliv obrátit na evropského inspektora ochrany údajů.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kritéria pro vyloučení, výběr uchazečů a zadání zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kritéria pro vyloučení, administrativní kritéria a hodnotící kritéria platná pro tuto výzvu jsou popsána v referenčních podmínkách a jejich přílohách.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Den odeslání oznámení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum přijetí Úřadem pro publikace</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIP - Huvi väljendamise kutse: finantsvahendajate valimine Lithuanian Leveraged Fundi kaudu Leedus finantstagatisinstrumendi loomiseks (LU-Luxembourg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Viide: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(ELT S-seerias avaldatav teade)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Huvi väljendamise kutse teade</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaliku sektori hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jessica II Fund of Funds Lithuania, keda esindab kõnealuse huvi väljendamise kutse eesmärgil</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Investeerimispank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxembourg, e-post: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>(kes tegutseb hankijana).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Huvi väljendamise kutse eesmärk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopa Komisjoni otsusega nr C (2014)6397 vastu võetud "Euroopa Liidu fondiinvesteeringute rakenduskava aastateks 2014–2020" ("rakenduskava") programmitöö perioodil aastatel 2014–2020, eesmärgiga võidelda turutõrkega, mis tuvastati esialgsel ja uuendati järgnevate avaliku taristu ja energiatõhususe projekti hindamis- ja seirekomitee poolt vastavalt 7.11.2014 ja 29.8.2016 (eelhindamine) kinnitatud hindamiste käigus, eraldas Leedu Vabariigi Rahandusministeerium korraldusasutusena tegutsedes ressursid Leedu finantsvõimendusega fondi (edaspidi "finantsvõimendusega fond") käivitamiseks. Finantsvõimendusega fondi kontekstis jõustus Jessica II Fund of Funds Lithuania (edaspidi "Jessica II" või "FoF") muudatuse sisseviimisega 7.5.2015 (parandatud 5.10.2016) rahastamisleping ühelt poolt Leedu Vabariigi Rahandusministeeriumi ja Keskkonnaministeeriumi ning teiselt poolt Euroopa Investeerimispanga ("EIB") vahel ("rahastamisleping" või "FA"), millega EIB määrati asutuseks, kes rakendab finantsinstrumenti ("finantsinstrument") Leedu Vabariigile antava garantii vormis ("garantii") vastavalt ühissätete määruse ("CPR") 38. artikli 4. alapunkti alapunktile (b)(i).</P><P>Finantsinstrumendi rakendamiseks asjakohased eeskirjad on sätestatud peamiselt ühissätete määruses, komisjoni delegeeritud määruses, komisjoni rakendusmääruses, Euroopa Regionaalarengu Fondi määruses (määratletud vastavalt allpool) ning kohaldatavates Leedu õigusaktides ja määrustes.</P><P>Huvi väljendamise kutse eesmärk on valida välja kõlblikud finantsvahendajatena tegutsevad Leedu finantseerimisasutused, mis saavad garantiilepingu alusel Euroopa struktuuri- ja investeerimisfondide poolt rahastatava garantii. Garantii katab osaliselt krediidiriski, mis seondub uue finantsvahendajate poolt korterelamutes ruume omavatele füüsilistele või juriidilistele isikutele ("lõppsaaja") või ühisvara halduritele ("ühisvara haldur") korterelamute energiatõhusaks renoveerimiseks ("projektid") antavate eelislaenude portfelliga vastavalt Leedu seadusandlusele ("moderniseerimislaenud").</P><P>Pädevustingimuste (sh lisade) saamiseks tuleb saata e-kiri aadressil CSprocurement@eib.org pealkirjaga "PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents".</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Taotluskord</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pakkumised tuleb saata inglise keeles tähitud postiga punktis 1 nimetatud aadressil ning pädevustingimustes sätestatud konkreetseid juhiseid rangelt järgides.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menetluse üldkirjeldus:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Käesolev huvi väljendamise kutse ei ole avalik hankemenetlus direktiivide 2004/18/EÜ ega 2014/24/EL mõistes.</P><P>Huvitatud pooli kutsutakse esitama oma pakkumisi kooskõlas eeskirjadega, mis on sätestatud käesolevas teates ja pädevustingimustes.</P><P>Hindamisprotsessidele kohaldatavad põhimõtteid ja meetodit ning ka hindamisprotsessi etappe on kirjeldatud pädevustingimustes.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pakkumiste esitamise tähtpäev:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Isikuandmete kaitse</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Teie esitatud isikuandmeid töödeldakse kooskõlas Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 18.12.2000 määrusega (EÜ) nr 45/2001 üksikisikute kaitse kohta isikuandmete töötlemisel ühenduse institutsioonides ja asutustes ning selliste andmete vaba liikumise kohta, samuti mis tahes eelnimetatud akte muutva või tühistava tulevase seadusandlusega. Huvi väljendamise kutse jaoks nõutud teave on vajalik pakkumise hindamiseks ning seda kasutatakse ainult sellel eesmärgil Euroopa Investeerimispanga ostude osakonna (CS/IMP/PROCUR) volitusel ning kooskõlas Euroopa Investeerimispanga hangete juhendiga, mille on heaks kiitnud Euroopa Investeerimispanga halduskomitee. Palume tähele panna, et teie ettepaneku kaalumiseks võib taotleja olla kohustatud vastama mõnele või kõigile küsimustele, mis on tema esitatavas kinnituses. Nende küsimuste kohustuslik/valikuline laad on esitatud pädevustingimuste dokumendis. Taotleja hindamiseks hindavad teie esitatud isikuandmeid valikukomisjoni liikmed ja huvi väljendamise kutset nõudnud direktoraadi liikmed. Nõudmise korral võidakse juurdepääs võimaldada Euroopa Investeerimispanga vastavusbüroo vanemametnikule, õigusteenistusele või peainspektsioonile. Eduka taotleja andmeid hoitakse lepingu kestuse ajal ja 2 lisa-aastal keskarhiivis, kui neid ei ole vaja kohtuvaidluste ja nõuete jaoks. Ebaeduka taotleja andmeid hoitakse 4 aastat, kui neid ei ole vaja kohtuvaidluste ja nõuete kontekstis. Teil on õigus oma andmetele ligi pääseda ning neid parandada või ajakohastada. Nende õiguste kasutamiseks võite võtta ühendust CS/IMP/PROCURi osakonna juhiga (CS-procurement@eib.org). Teil on igal hetkel õigus pöörduda Euroopa andmekaitseinspektori poole.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kõrvalejätmiskriteeriumid, valiku- ja lepingu sõlmimise kriteeriumid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kõnealusele kutsele kohaldatavaid kõrvalejätmiskriteeriume, halduskriteeriume ja hindamiskriteeriume on kirjeldatud pädevustingimustes ja selle lisades.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teate lähetamise kuupäev:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Väljaannete talitusse laekumise kuupäev:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBB - Felhívás szándéknyilatkozat benyújtására: pénzügyi közvetítők kiválasztása Litvánia tőkeáttétellel működő befektetési alapjának keretében, garanciafinanszírozási eszköz létrehozásához Litvániában (LU-Luxembourg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hivatkozás: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(A felhívást a Hivatalos Lap S sorozatában teszik közzé)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Felhívás szándéknyilatkozat benyújtására</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A Litván Jessica II Alapok Alapja, amelynek képviselője e szándéknyilatkozati felhívás tekintetében az</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európai Beruházási Bank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>amely beszerző jogalanyként működik.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szándéknyilatkozati felhívás célja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A C(2014)6397 bizottsági határozattal („Operatív program”) jóváhagyott az „Uniós alapokból történő beruházások operatív programja (2014–2020)” programozási időszakának (2014–2020) keretében, valamint az állami infrastruktúrára és az energiahatékonyságra vonatkozó projekt értékelését és felügyeletét végző bizottság által sorban 7.11.2014 és 29.8.2016 keltezéssel jóváhagyott eredeti és frissített „ex ante” értékelésben („ex ante értékelés”) azonosított piaci hiányosság megszüntetése érdekében a Litván Köztársaság irányító hatóságként eljáró pénzügyminisztériuma erőforrásokat biztosít Litvánia tőkeáttétellel működő befektetési alapjának létrehozásához („tőkeáttétellel működő befektetési alap”). A tőkeáttétellel működő befektetési alappal összefüggésben, a 7.5.2015 keltezéssel (5.10.2016 keltezéssel történt módosítással) a Litván Köztársaság pénzügy- és környezetvédelmi minisztériuma („minisztériumok”) és az Európai Beruházási Bank („EBB”) között hatályba lépett Litván Jessica II Alapok Alapja („Jessica II” vagy „FoF”) finanszírozási megállapodás („finanszírozási megállapodás”) módosítására vonatkozó megállapodással az EBB pénzügyi eszköz végrehajtására kijelölt szervvé vált a Litván Köztársaság javára vállalt garancia formájában („garancia”), a Közös rendelkezésekről szóló rendelet 38. cikkének (4)(b)(i) pontjával összhangban.</P><P>A pénzügyi eszköz végrehajtására vonatkozó szabályokat elsősorban a Közös rendelkezésekről szóló rendelet („CPR”), a Felhatalmazáson alapuló bizottsági rendelet („CDR”), a Bizottsági végrehajtási rendelet és az Európai Regionális Fejlesztési Alapról („ERFA”) szóló rendelet (az alábbiakban meghatározottak szerint), valamint a vonatkozó litván törvények és rendeletek tartalmazzák.</P><P>A szándéknyilatkozat benyújtására vonatkozó felhívás célja megfelelő pénzügyi intézmények kiválasztása a litván pénzügyi közvetítők szerepére, melyek a garanciamegállapodás értelmében az Európai strukturális és beruházási alapok által finanszírozott garanciát kapnak. A garanciának részben fedeznie kell a pénzügyi közvetítők által többlakásos épületekben ingatlannal rendelkező természetes vagy jogi személyeknek („végső kedvezményezettek”), illetve közös képviselőknek társasházak energiahatékonysági felújítására („projekt”) a litván jogszabályoknak megfelelően nyújtott kedvezményes kölcsönökből („felújítási hitel”) álló új portfólióhoz kapcsolódó hitelkockázatot.</P><P>A feladatmeghatározási dokumentum és annak mellékleteinek igényléséhez küldjön e-mailt a CSprocurement@eib.org e-mail-címre „PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund – Request for documents” tárgymegjelöléssel.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Jelentkezési eljárás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Az ajánlatokat angol nyelven, postai úton kell benyújtani az 1. pontban közölt címre, a feladatmeghatározásban ismertetett konkrét utasítások szigorú betartásával.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az eljárás általános bemutatása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jelen szándéknyilatkozati felhívás nem jelent a 2004/18/EK irányelv, illetve a 2014/24/EU irányelv értelmében vett közbeszerzési eljárást.</P><P>Az érdeklődő feleknek a jelen felhívásban és a feladatmeghatározásban előírt szabályok szerint kell benyújtaniuk ajánlatukat.</P><P>Az értékelési folyamatra alkalmazandó elveket és módszereket, valamint az értékelési folyamat szakaszait a feladatmeghatározás ismerteti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlatok benyújtásának határideje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A személyes adatok védelme</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A közölt személyes adatok feldolgozása a személyes adatok közösségi intézmények és szervek által történő feldolgozása tekintetében az egyének védelméről, valamint az ilyen adatok szabad áramlásáról szóló, 18.12.2000 keltezésű 45/2001/EK európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet, valamint az azt módosító vagy hatályon kívül helyező bármely későbbi jogszabály előírásai szerint történik. A szándéknyilatkozati felhíváshoz igényelt információkra az ajánlatok értékelése céljából van szükség, és felhasználásukra kizárólag e célból az EBB közbeszerzési szakterülete (CS/IMP/PROCUR) felügyeletével, az EBB igazgatási bizottsága által jóváhagyott EBB közbeszerzési iránymutatás alapján kerül sor. Az ajánlat figyelembevételének feltételeként az ajánlattevő által benyújtandó nyilatkozatban meg kell válaszolni a kötelezően megválaszolandó kérdéseket (ez lehet a nyilatkozat néhány vagy összes kérdése). Az ilyen kérdések kötelező/opcionális jellegét a feladatmeghatározási dokumentum határozza meg. Az ajánlattevő értékelése céljából a közölt személyes adatokhoz az értékelő bizottság és a szándéknyilatkozati felhívást igénylő igazgatóság tagjai férhetnek hozzá. Kérés esetén az adatokhoz való hozzáférés az EBB megfelelésért felelős főtisztviselőjének hivatala, a jogi szolgálat, illetve a főfelügyelőség számára is biztosítható. A sikeres pályázó adatai a szerződés időtartamára és még további 2 évig megőrzésre kerülnek a központi adattárban, kivéve ha peres eljárással vagy reklamációval kapcsolatban van rájuk szükség. A sikertelen pályázók adatai 4 évig kerülnek megőrzésre, kivéve, ha peres eljárással vagy reklamációval kapcsolatban van rájuk szükség. Az ajánlatkérőknek jogukban áll megtekinteni, helyesbíteni vagy aktualizálni a rájuk vonatkozó adatokat. E jogok gyakorlása érdekében a CS/IMP/PROCUR szakterület vezetőjével kell felvenni a kapcsolatot (CS-procurement@eib.org). Az ajánlattevők bármikor fordulhatnak az európai adatvédelmi biztoshoz is.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kizárási, kiválasztási és odaítélési szempontok</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Az e felhívás tekintetében alkalmazandó kizárási, adminisztratív és értékelési szempontokat a feladatmeghatározás és annak mellékletei ismertetik.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A hirdetmény feladásának dátuma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A felhívás Kiadóhivatalba történő beérkezésének dátuma</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Kvietimas pareikšti susidomėjimą: atrinkti Lietuvos svertą naudojančio fondo finansų tarpininkus, siekiant įgyvendinti garantijos finansinę priemonę Lietuvoje (LU-Liuksemburgas)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Nuoroda: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Skelbimas, skirtas publikuoti Oficialiojo leidinio S serijoje)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Skelbimas apie kvietimą pareikšti susidomėjimą</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Perkančioji organizacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jessica II fondų fondas Lietuvoje, kuriam šio kvietimo išreikšti susidomėjimą tikslu atstovauja</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos investicijų bankas</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Liuksemburgas, el. paštas: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Kuris yra perkančioji organizacija.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kvietimo pareikšti susidomėjimą uždavinys:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>„2014-2020 metų Europos Sąjungos fondų investicijų veiksmų programos“, patvirtintos Europos Komisijos sprendimu Nr. C (2014) 6397 (toliau – Veiksmų programa), 2014-2020 metų programavimo laikotarpiu, o taip pat siekiant išspręsti rinkos nepakankamumus, nustatytus pirminiais ir atnaujintais išankstiniais ex-ante vertinimais, kuriuos patvirtinto Viešosios infrastruktūros ir energinio efektyvumo projektų vertinimų ir priežiūros komitetas atitinkamai 7.11.2014 ir 29.8.2016 (toliau – Ex ante vertinimas), Lietuvos Respublikos finansų ministerija, veikianti kaip valdymo institucija, paskyrė išteklius Lietuvos svertą naudojančio fondo įgyvendinimui (toliau – Svertą naudojantis fondas). Svertą naudojančio fondo kontekste, įvedant pakeitimą Jessica II Lietuvos fondų fondo (toliau – Jessica II arba FoF) finansavimo sutartyje, įsigaliojusioje 7.5.2015 (kaip buvo pakeista 5.10.2016) ir sudarytoje atitinkamai tarp Lietuvos Respublikos finansų ir aplinkos ministerijų (toliau – Ministerijos) bei Europos investicijų banko (EIB) (toliau – Finansavimo sutartis arba FS), Europos investicijų bankui buvo paskirtas subjektas, įgyvendinantis finansinę priemonę (toliau – Finansinė priemonė) garantijos forma Lietuvos Respublikos naudai (toliau – Garantija) pagal Bendrų nuostatų reglamento (toliau – BNR) 38 straipsnio 4 dalies b punkto i papunktį.</P><P>Susijusios finansinės priemonės įgyvendinimo taisyklės pirmiausia yra nustatytos Bendrųjų nuostatų reglamente, Komisijos deleguotajame reglamente, Komisijos įgyvendinimo reglamente ir Europos regioninės plėtros fondo reglamente (atitinkamai paaiškinti toliau) bei taikomuose nacionaliniuose įstatymuose ir reglamentuose.</P><P>Kvietimo pareikšti susidomėjimą (toliau – Kvietimas PS) tikslas yra atrinkti Lietuvoje veikiančias tinkamas finansines institucijas, galinčias tapti finansų tarpininkais (toliau – Finansų tarpininkai), privalančiais pagal garantijos susitarimą (toliau – Garantijos susitarimas) gauti Europos struktūrinių ir investicinių fondų (toliau – ESIF) finansuojamą garantiją. Garantija turi dalinai apimti kredito riziką, susijusią su lengvatinių paskolų, kurias finansų tarpininkai suteiks fiziniams arba juridiniams asmenims, valdantiems patalpas daugiabučiuose pastatuose (toliau – Galutinis gavėjas), arba bendro turto valdytojams (toliau – Bendro turto valdytojai), nauju portfeliu, skirtu daugiabučių pastatų (toliau – Projektai) renovavimui, numatančiam energinio efektyvumo didinimą, pagal Lietuvos teisinį pagrindą (toliau – Paskolos modernizavimas).</P><P>Techninių užduočių su priedais galima paprašyti parašant el. adresu CS-procurement@eib.org laišką, kurio tema – „PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents“.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paraiškų teikimo procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pasiūlymai turėtų būti teikiami anglų kalba paštu 1 punkte nurodytu adresu, griežtai laikantis konkrečių nurodymų, išdėstytų techninėse užduotyse.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bendras procedūros aprašymas:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Šis kvietimas pareikšti susidomėjimą nėra viešųjų pirkimų procedūra Direktyvų 2004/18/EB arba 2014/24/ES prasme.</P><P>Susidomėjusios šalys yra kviečiamos teikti pasiūlymus remiantis šiame skelbime ir techninėse užduotyse išdėstytomis taisyklėmis.</P><P>Principai ir metodas, taikomas vertinimo procesui, bei vertinimo proceso etapai yra aprašyti techninėse užduotyse.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pasiūlymų pateikimo terminas:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Asmens duomenų apsauga:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jūsų pateikti asmens duomenys bus tvarkomi pagal 18.12.2000 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentą (EB) Nr. 45/2001 dėl asmenų apsaugos Bendrijos institucijoms ir įstaigoms tvarkant asmens duomenis, laisvo tokių duomenų judėjimo bei bet kokio duomenis pakeičiančio ar panaikinančio būsimo teisės akto. Kvietimui pareikšti susidomėjimą pageidaujama informacija yra būtina siekiant įvertinti jūsų pasiūlymą ir tik šiuo tikslu ją naudos EIB pirkimo padalinio (CS/IMP/PROCUR) tarnyba, vadovaudamasi EIB pirkimų vadovu, kurį patvirtino EIB valdybos komitetas. Prašome atkreipti dėmesį, kad, norint, jog jūsų pasiūlymas būtų svarstomas, gali būti privaloma atsakyti į kai kuriuos ar visus klausimus pareiškėjo parengtoje deklaracijoje. Privalomo / pasirenkamo pobūdžio klausimai yra pateikti orientacinio dokumento sąlygose. Kad pareiškėjas būtų įvertintas, jūsų pateiktus asmens duomenis matys atrankos komisijos nariai ir direktoratas, kuris pageidavo kvietimo pareikšti susidomėjimą. Paprašius prieiga prie šių duomenų gali būti suteikta vyriausiojo atitikties pareigūno EIB biurui, teisinei tarnybai ar bendrajai inspekcijai. Laimėjusio pareiškėjo duomenys turi būti saugomi sutarties laikotarpiu ir papildomai 2 metus centriniuose archyvuose, nebent jie būtų reikalingi nagrinėjant ginčus ar skundus. Nelaimėjusių pareiškėjų duomenys bus laikomi 4 metus, nebent jie būtų reikalingi nagrinėjant ginčus ar skundus. Turite teisę savo duomenis pataisyti ar atnaujinti. Šia teise pasinaudoti galite susisiekdami su CS/IMP/PROCUR padalinio vadovu (CS-procurement@eib.org). Taip pat turite teisę bet kada kreiptis į Europos duomenų apsaugos priežiūros pareigūną.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Šalinimo, atrankos ir sutarties sudarymo kriterijai:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Šiam konkursui taikomi šalinimo, administraciniai ir vertinimo kriterijai yra aprašyti techninėse užduotyse ir jų prieduose.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Šio skelbimo išsiuntimo data:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Skelbimo gavimo Leidinių biure data:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Uzaicinājums paust ieinteresētību: izraudzīties finanšu starpniekus Lietuvas aizņemto līdzekļu fonda ietvaros garantijas finanšu instrumenta īstenošanai Lietuvā (LU-Luksemburga)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Atsauce: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(“Oficiālā Vēstneša” S sērijā publicējams paziņojums)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paziņojums par uzaicinājumu paust ieinteresētību</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lietuvas fondu fonds Jessica II, ko attiecībā uz šo uzaicinājumu paust ieinteresētību pārstāv</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Investīciju banka</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luksemburga, e-pasts: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>kā iepirkuma piešķīrēja.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uzaicinājuma paust ieinteresētību mērķis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>“Eiropas Savienības fondu investīciju darbības programmas 2014.–2020. gadam”, kas apstiprināta ar Eiropas Komisijas Lēmumu Nr. (2014)6397 (“Darbības programma”) 2014.–2020. gada plānošanas perioda ietvaros, un ar mērķi novērst tirgus nepilnības, kas identificētas sākotnējos un papildinātajos ex-ante novērtējumos, kurus attiecīgi apstiprinājusi valsts infrastruktūras un energoefektivitātes projekta izvērtēšanas un pārraudzības komiteja 7.11.2014 un 29.8.2016 (“ex-ante novērtējums”), Lietuvas Republikas Finanšu ministrija, kas darbojas kā vadošā iestāde, ir paredzējusi resursus Lietuvas aizņemto līdzekļu fonda īstenošanai (“aizņemto līdzekļu fonds”). Saistībā ar aizņemto līdzekļu fondu, veicot grozījumu Lietuvas fondu fonda Jessica II (“Jessica II” vai fund of funds – “FoF”) finansēšanas līgumā, kas stājās spēkā 7.5.2015 (ar 5.10.2016 grozījumiem), attiecīgi starp Lietuvas Republikas Finanšu ministriju un Vides ministriju (“Ministrijas”) un Eiropas Investīciju banku (“EIB”) (“Finansēšanas līgums” vai funding agreement – “FA”), EIB tika iecelta par iestādi, kas īsteno finanšu instrumentu (“Finanšu instruments”) garantijas formā par labu Lietuvas Republikai saskaņā ar Kopīgo noteikumu regulas (“KNR”) 38. panta 4. punkta b) apakšpunkta i) punktu.</P><P>Noteikumi, kas attiecas uz Finanšu instrumenta īstenošanu, ir galvenokārt izklāstīti KNR, Komisijas deleģētajā regulā (Commission Delegated Regulation – “CDR”), Komisijas īstenošanas regulā un Eiropas Reģionālā attīstības fonda (“ERAF”) regulā (attiecīgi norādītas turpmāk) un piemērojamajos Lietuvas tiesību aktos un noteikumos.</P><P>Uzaicinājuma paust ieinteresētību mērķis ir izraudzīties atbilstīgās finanšu iestādes Lietuvā, kas kļūtu par finanšu starpniekiem (“Finanšu starpnieki”) un uz garantijas līguma (“Garantijas līgums”) pamata saņemtu Eiropas strukturālo un investīciju fondu (“ESIF”) finansētu garantiju. Garantija daļēji segs riskus, kas saistīti ar jaunu preferenciālu aizdevumu portfeli, kurus finanšu starpnieki piešķirs fiziskām un juridiskām personām, kam pieder telpas daudzdzīvokļu ēkās (“Gala saņēmējs”), vai kopīgā īpašuma administratoriem daudzdzīvokļu ēku energoefektivitātes atjaunošanai (“Projekti”) saskaņā ar Lietuvas tiesisko pamatu (“Modernizācijas aizdevumi”).</P><P>Darba uzdevumu un pielikumus var pieprasīt, nosūtot e-pasta ziņojumu uz adresi CSprocurement@eib.org un norādot šādu tematu: “PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pieteikumu iesniegšanas kārtība</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Piedāvājumi jāiesniedz angļu valodā, nosūtot tos pa pastu uz 1. punktā norādīto adresi un stingri ievērojot konkrētos norādījumus, kas sniegti darba uzdevumā.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūras vispārējs apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Šis uzaicinājums paust ieinteresētību nav publiskā iepirkuma procedūra Direktīvas 2004/18/EK vai Direktīvas 2014/24/ES nozīmē.</P><P>Ieinteresētās personas tiek aicinātas iesniegt piedāvājumus atbilstoši noteikumiem, kas izklāstīti šajā paziņojumā un darba uzdevumā.</P><P>Izvērtēšanas procesā piemērojamie principi un metode, kā arī izvērtēšanas procesu posmi ir aprakstīti darba uzdevumā.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Piedāvājumu iesniegšanas termiņš</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Personas datu aizsardzība</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jūsu iesniegtie personas dati tiks apstrādāti saskaņā ar Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes 18.12.2000 Regulu (EK) Nr. 45/2001 par fizisku personu aizsardzību attiecībā uz personas datu apstrādi Kopienas iestādēs un struktūrās un par šādu datu brīvu apriti un saskaņā ar jebkuru citu tiesisko regulējumu nākotnē, kas to grozīs vai atcels. Uzaicinājumā paust ieinteresētību pieprasītā informācija ir nepieciešama, lai novērtētu jūsu piedāvājumu, un EIB Iepirkumu daļas (CS/IMP/PROCUR) vadībā tā tiks izmantota tikai šādā nolūkā atbilstoši EIB Iepirkumu rokasgrāmatai, ko apstiprinājusi EIB Vadības komiteja. Lūdzam ņemt vērā: lai jūsu piedāvājums tiktu izskatīts, varētu būt obligāti jāatbild uz dažiem vai visiem jautājumiem, kas ietverti pieteikuma iesniedzēja deklarācijā. Tas, vai uz minētajiem jautājumiem ir vai nav jāatbild obligāti, ir noteikts darba uzdevuma dokumentā. Pieteikumu iesniedzēju novērtēšanas procesā jūsu iesniegtie personas dati būs pieejami atlases komisijas dalībniekiem un direktorātam, kurš pieprasījis uzaicinājumu paust ieinteresētību. Pēc pieprasījuma piekļuvi šiem datiem var piešķirt arī EIB Galvenā atbilstības speciālista birojam, kas ir Ģenerālinspektorāta juridiskais dienests. Uzvarējušā pieteikuma iesniedzēja dati tiks glabāti centrālajā arhīvā līguma darbības laikā un vēl 2 gadus pēc tam, ja vien tie nebūs nepieciešami saistībā ar tiesvedību vai pretenzijām. Neuzvarējušo pieteikumu iesniedzēju dati tiks glabāti 4 gadus, ja vien tie nebūs nepieciešami saistībā ar tiesvedību vai pretenzijām. Jums ir tiesības piekļūt saviem datiem, precizēt vai atjaunot tos. Lai to izdarītu, jāsazinās ar CS/IMP/PROCUR daļas vadītāju (CS-procurement@eib.org). Jums ir arī tiesības jebkurā laikā vērsties pie Eiropas Datu aizsardzības uzraudzītāja.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Izslēgšanas, atlases un līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas kritēriji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Saistībā ar šo uzaicinājumu piemērojamie izslēgšanas kritēriji, administratīvie kritēriji un novērtēšanas kritēriji ir aprakstīti darba uzdevumā un tā pielikumos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paziņojuma nosūtīšanas datums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Saņemšanas datums Publikāciju birojā</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BEI - Sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess: biex jintgħażlu intermedjarji finanzjarji taħt il-Fond Ingranat Litwan biex jiġi implimentat strument finanzjarju ta' garanzija fil-Litwanja (LU-Lussemburgu)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ir-referenza: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Avviż li jrid ikun ippubblikat fil-Ġurnal Uffiċjali, serje S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avviż ta' sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-Fond tal-Fondi Jessica II tal-Litwanja, irrappreżentat għall-għan ta' din is-sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess mill-</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Bank Ewropew tal-Investiment</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Lussemburgu, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Li qiegħed jaġixxi bħala l-entità tal-ksib.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-objettiv tas-Sejħa għal Espressjoni ta' Interess</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fil-perijodu ta' programmazzjoni 2014-2020 tal-"programm operattiv għall-investimenti tal-fondi tal-Unjoni fl-2014-2020" approvat bid-Deċiżjoni tal-Kummissjoni Ewropea Nru C (2014)6397 ("Programm operattiv") u bl-iskop li jiġi indirizzat il-falliment tas-suq identifikat mill-valutazzjonijiet ex ante tal-bidu u aġġornati approvati mill-kumitat tal-evalwazzjoni u tal-monitoraġġ tal-proġett tal-infrastruttura pubblika u l-effiċjenza fl-enerġija fis-7.11.2014 u fid-29.8.2016 rispettivament ("valutazzjoni ex ante"), il-Ministeru tal-Finanzi tar-Repubblika tal-Litwanja li jaġixxi bħala l-awtorità għall-immaniġġjar, għandu riżorsi ddedikati għall-implimentazzjoni tal-fond ingranat Litwan ("fond ingranat"). Fil-kuntest tal-fond ingranat, bil-konklużjoni ta' emenda għall-fond tal-fondi Jessica II tal-Litwanja ("Jessica II" jew "FoF") il-ftehim dwar l-iffinanzjar li daħal fis-seħħ fis-7.5.2015 (kif emendat fil-5.10.2016) bejn il-Ministeri tal-Finanzi u tal-Ambjent tar-Repubblika tal-Litwanja (il-"Ministeri") rispettivament u l-Bank Ewropew tal-Investiment ("BEI") ("Ftehim dwar l-Iffinanzjar" jew "FA"), il-BEI ġie maħtur bħala l-korp li jimplimenta l-istrument finanzjarju ("Strument Finanzjarju") fil-forma ta' garanzija għall-benefiċċju tar-Repubblika tal-Litwanja ("Garanzija"), skont l-Artikolu 38 (4)(b)(i) tar-Regolament dwar Dispożizzjonijiet Komuni ("CPR").</P><P>Ir-regoli rilevanti għall-implimentazzjoni tal-Istrument Finanzjarju huma stipulati prinċipalment fis-CPR, ir-Regolament ta' Delega tal-Kummissjoni ("CDR"), ir-Regolament tal-Implimentazzjoni tal-Kummissjoni u r-Regolament tal-Fond Ewropew għall-Iżvilupp Reġjonali ("FEŻR") (rispettivament kif imfisser hawn taħt), u l-liġijiet u r-regolamenti applikabbli tal-Litwanja.</P><P>L-għan tas-sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess ("Sejħa għal EoI") huwa li jintgħażlu istituzzjonijiet finanzjarji eliġibbli fil-Litwanja biex isiru intermedjarji finanzjarji ("Intermedjarji Finanzjarji"), li għandhom, taħt il-ftehim ta' garanzija ("Ftehim ta' Garanzija"), jirċievu garanzija ffinanzjata mill-Fondi Strutturali u ta' Investiment Ewropej ("FSIE"). Il-garanzija għandha parzjalment tkopri r-riskju ta' kreditu assoċjat ma' portafoll ġdid ta' self preferenzjali li għandu jingħata mill-intermedjarji finanzjarji lil persuni naturali jew legali li għandhom proprjetà f'bini b'iktar minn appartament wieħed ("Destinatarju Finali") jew lill-amministraturi ta' proprjetà komuni ("Amministraturi ta' Proprjetà Komuni") għar-rinnovazzjoni tal-effiċjenza fl-enerġija ta' bini b'iktar minn appartament wieħed ("Proġetti") skont il-bażi legali Litwana ("Self għall-Modernizzazzjoni").</P><P>It-termini ta' referenza inkluż l-annessi jistgħu jintalbu permezz ta' Email lil CSprocurement@eib.org bis-suġġett PC-1439 Fond Ingranat Litwan — Talba għal dokumenti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-proċedura tal-applikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-proposti għandhom jintefgħu bl-Ingliż bil-posta fl-indirizz indikat fil-punt 1, bi qbil strett mal-istruzzjonijiet speċifiċi mniżżla fit-termini ta' referenza.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Deskrizzjoni ġenerali tal-proċedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Din is-sejħa għal espressjoni ta' Interess ma tirrappreżentax proċedura għal ksib pubbliku fis-sens tad-Direttivi 2004/18/KE jew 2014/24/UE.</P><P>Il-partijiet interessati huma mistiedna jitfgħu l-proposti tagħhom bi qbil mar-regoli speċifikati f'dan l-avviż u fit-termini ta' referenza.</P><P>Il-prinċipji u l-metodu applikabbli għall-proċess ta' evalwazzjoni, kif ukoll l-istadji tal-proċessi ta' evalwazzjoni, huma deskritti fit-termini ta' referenza.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-data tal-għeluq għat-tfigħ tal-proposti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-ħarsien tad-dejta personali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Id-dejta personali pprovduta minnek se tkun ipproċessata skont ir-Regolament (KE) Nru 45/2001 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tat-18 ta' Diċembru 2000 dwar il-protezzjoni ta' individwu fir-rigward tal-ipproċessar ta' data personali mill-istituzzjonijiet u l-korpi tal-Komunità u dwar il-movement liberu ta' dak id-data u kwalunkwe leġiżlazzjoni futura li temenda jew tħassar dan ir-Regolament. It-tagħrif mitlub għas-CEol hu neċessarju sabiex jivvaluta l-proposta tiegħek u se jintuża biss għal dak l-iskop taħt l-awtorità tad-diviżjoni tal-ksib tal-BEI (CS/IMP/PROCUR), bi qbil mal-gwida għall-ksib tal-BEI, approvata mill-kumitat għall-immaniġġjar tal-BEI. Jekk jogħġbok innota li biex tiġi kkunsidrata l-proposta tiegħek, jista' jkun mandatorju li twiegeb xi wħud jew il-mistoqsijiet kollha fid-dikjarazzjoni li ssir mill-applikant. In-natura mandatorja /b'għażla ta' dawn il-mistoqsijiet hi speċifikata fid-dokument tat-termini ta' referenza. Sabiex jiġi vvalutat l-applikant, id-dejta personali pprovduta minnek se tkun aċċessata mill-membri tal-penil tal-għażla u d-direttorat li talab is-CEol. Fuq talba, l-aċċess għal din id-dejta jista' jingħata lill-uffiċċju tal-uffiċjal ewlieni tal-konformità tal-BEI, is-servizz legali jew l-ispettorat ġenerali. Id-dejta tal-applikant li jintagħżel se tinżamm għat-tul ta' żmien tal-kuntratt, kif ukoll għal sentejn (2) fl-arkivji ċentrali, sakemm dawn ma jkunux meħtieġa fil-kuntest tal-litigazzjoni jew tat-talbiet. Id-dejta ta' applikanti li ma jintagħżlux se tinżamm għal 4 snin, sakemm din ma tkunx meħtieġa fil-kuntest ta' litigazzjoni jew talbiet. Għandek id-dritt taċċessa u tikkoreġi jew taġġorna d-dejta tiegħek. Tista' teżerċita dawn id-drittijiet billi tikkuntattja lill-Kap tat-taqsima CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Għandek ukoll id-dritt li fi kwalunkwe waqt tirrikorri għand il-kontrollur Ewropew għall-ħarsien tad-dejta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-kriterji tat-twarrib, tal-għażla u tal-għoti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-kriterji tat-twarrib, il-kriterji amministrattivi u l-kriterji tal-valutazzjoni applikabbli għal din is-sejħa huma deskritti fit-termini ta' referenza u l-annessi tagħha.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-data tad-dispaċċ tal-avviż</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-data tal-wasla għand l-Uffiċċju tal-Pubblikazzjonijiet</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBI - Zaproszenie do wyrażenia zainteresowania: wybranie pośredników w ramach litewskiego funduszu dźwigni finansowej w celu zapewnienia instrumentu gwarancji finansowych na Litwie (LU-Luksemburg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Numer referencyjny: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Ogłoszenie ma zostać opublikowane w Dzienniku Urzędowym, seria S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zaproszenie do wyrażenia zainteresowania</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Instytucja zamawiająca</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fundusz funduszy Jessica II na rzecz Litwy, reprezentowany na potrzeby niniejszego zaproszenia do wyrażenia zainteresowania przez</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europejski Bank Inwestycyjny</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luksemburg, email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>, który występuje jako podmiot zamawiający.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Przedmiot zaproszenia do wyrażenia zainteresowania:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>W okresie programowania 2014-2020 programu operacyjnego dla inwestycji realizowanych ze środków unijnych na lata 2014-2020, zatwierdzonego na podstawie decyzji Komisji Europejskiej nr C (2014)6397 (“Program operacyjny”) w celu zaradzenia nieprawidłowościom w funkcjonowania rynku, zdiagnozowanych w ramach początkowej oceny ex-ante i jej aktualizacji, potwierdzonej przez komisję ds. oceny i monitorowania projektów w zakresie infrastruktury publicznej i wydajności energetycznej w dniach 7.11.2014 i 29.8.2016 (“ocena ex-ante”), Ministerstwo Finansów Republiki Litewskiej, w roli instytucji zarządzającej, przeznaczyło środki na wdrożenie litewskiego funduszu dźwigni finansowej (Lithuanian Leveraged Fund). W kontekście funduszu dźwigni finansowej, na podstawie poprawki do umowy ustanawiającej fundusz funduszy Jessica II na rzecz Litwy („Jessica II” lub „FoF”), umowa o finansowaniu została zawarta dnia 7.5.2015 (z poprawkami z dnia 5.10.2016) między Ministerstwem Finansów i Ministerstwem Środowiska Republiki Litewskiej („Ministerstwa”) a Europejskim Bankiem Inwestycyjnym („EBI”) („Umowa o finansowaniu), EBI został powołany do wdrożenia instrumentu finansowego („instrument finansowy”) w formie gwarancji na rzecz Republiki Litewskiej („Gwarancja”), zgodnie z art. 38 pkt (4) lit. (b) oraz (i) rozporządzenia w sprawie wspólnych przepisów (“CPR”).</P><P>Odpowiednie normy regulujące wdrażanie instrumentu finansowego zostały zawarte przede wszystkim w rozporządzeniu w sprawie wspólnych przepisów (CDR), a także w rozporządzeniu wykonawczym, rozporządzeniu w sprawie Europejskiego Funduszu Rozwoju Regionalnego (EFRR), (jak określono poniżej) oraz odpowiednich aktach ustawowych i wykonawczych na Litwie.</P><P>Celem zaproszenia do wyrażenia zainteresowania jest wybranie kwalifikujących się instytucji finansowych na Litwie, które staną się pośrednikami finansowych („Pośrednicy finansowi”) i które powinny, zgodnie z umową gwarancyjną („Umowa gwarancyjna”), otrzymać gwarancje ustanowione w ramach europejskich funduszy strukturalnych i inwestycyjnych (EFSI). Gwarancja musi pokrywać częściowo ryzyko kredytowe związane z nową ofertą kredytów preferencyjnych, które będą przyznawane przez pośredników finansowych osobom fizycznym i prawnym posiadającym lokale w budynkach wielorodzinnych („Odbiorca ostateczny”) lub administratorom nieruchomości wspólnej („Administratorzy nieruchomości wspólnej”) w celu renowacji służącej zwiększeniu efektywności energetycznej budynków wielorodzinnych („Projekty”) zgodnie z litewskimi ramami prawnymi („Kredyty modernizacyjne”).</P><P>O specyfikację istotnych warunków zamówienia wraz z załącznikami można zwrócić się wysyłając wiadomość pocztą elektroniczną na adres CSprocurement@eib.org o temacie „PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents”.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura składania wniosków:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Propozycje należy składać w języku angielskim pocztą na adres wskazany w pkt 1, ściśle zgodnie z konkretnymi instrukcjami określonymi w specyfikacji istotnych warunków zamówienia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ogólny opis procedury:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niniejsze zaproszenie do wyrażenia zainteresowania nie stanowi procedury zamówień publicznych w rozumieniu dyrektyw 2004/18/WE lub 2014/24/UE.</P><P>Zainteresowane strony proszone są o składanie propozycji zgodnie z zasadami określonymi w niniejszym ogłoszeniu i w specyfikacji istotnych warunków zamówienia.</P><P>Zasady i metody stosowane do procesu oceny, jak również etapy procesu oceny zostały określone w specyfikacji istotnych warunków zamówienia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Termin składania propozycji:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ochrona danych osobowych:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Przekazane dane osobowe będą przetwarzane zgodnie z rozporządzeniem (WE) nr 45/2001 Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady z dnia 18.12.2000 o ochronie osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych przez instytucje i organy wspólnotowe oraz o swobodnym przepływie takich danych, oraz zgodnie z każdym późniejszym prawem zmieniającym je albo uchylającym. Informacje wymagane w zaproszeniu do wyrażenia zainteresowania są konieczne do oceny propozycji i zostaną wykorzystane wyłącznie w tym celu w ramach upoważnienia komórki EBI odpowiedzialnej za zakupy (CS/IMP/PROCUR), zgodnie z przewodnikiem dotyczącym zamówień EBI zatwierdzonym przez Komitet Zarządzający EBI. Należy pamiętać, że aby propozycja została wzięta pod uwagę, konieczne może być udzielenie odpowiedzi na kilka lub wszystkie pytania zawarte w oświadczeniu kandydata. Obowiązkowy/dobrowolny charakter tych pytań określono w specyfikacji istotnych warunków zamówienia. W celu oceny wnioskującego przekazane dane osobowe zostaną poddane ocenie przez członków komisji selekcyjnej i Dyrekcji, która wystąpiła o zaproszenie do wyrażenia zainteresowania. Na ich żądanie dostęp do tych danych może zostać przyznany dla Biura Nadzoru EBI, działu prawnego lub Inspektora Generalnego. Dane zwycięskiego kandydata przechowuje się przez okres trwania zamówienia plus 2 lata w archiwach centralnych, chyba że są niezbędne w kontekście sporu sądowego lub roszczeń. Dane niewybranych podmiotów składających propozycje przechowuje się przez okres 4 lat, chyba że są niezbędne w kontekście sporu sądowego lub roszczeń. Podmiotom składającym propozycje przysługuje prawo dostępu do swoich danych oraz ich korekty lub aktualizacji. Można skorzystać z tych praw poprzez skontaktowanie się z kierownikiem działu CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Podmiotom składającym propozycje przysługuje także prawo do odwołania się w każdej chwili do Europejskiego Inspektora Ochrony Danych.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kryteria wykluczenia, kryteria wyboru i udzielenia zamówienia:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kryteria wykluczenia, kryteria administracyjne i kryteria oceny mające zastosowanie do niniejszego zaproszenia są opisane w specyfikacji istotnych warunków zamówienia i załącznikach do niej.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data wysłania ogłoszenia:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data otrzymania przez Urząd Publikacji</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Výzva na vyjadrenie záujmu: výber finančných sprostredkovateľov v rámci litovského fondu s pákovým efektom na vykonanie záručného finančného nástroja v Litve (LU-Luxemburg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenčné číslo: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Oznámenie bude zverejnené v Úradnom vestníku Európskej únie, séria S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Oznámenie o výzve na vyjadrenie záujmu</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verejný obstarávateľ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fond fondov Jessica II pre Litvu, zastúpený na ciele tejto výzvy na vyjadrenie záujmu</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európskou investičnou bankou</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxembursko, e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>ktorá vystupuje v úlohe verejného obstarávateľa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cieľ výzvy na vyjadrenie záujmu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>V rámci programového obdobia 2014 – 2020 „operačného programu pre investovanie finančných prostriedkov Únie v období rokov 2014 – 2020“, ktorý bol schválený rozhodnutím Európskej komisie č. C (2014)6397 („operačný program“) a s cieľom riešiť zlyhanie trhu, ktoré bolo zistené počiatočnými a aktualizovanými ex ante hodnoteniami schválenými hodnotiacim a monitorovacím výborom pre verejnú infraštruktúru a projekty energetickej hospodárnosti dňa 7.11.2014 a následne 29.8.2016 („ex ante hodnotenie“), Ministerstvo financií Litovskej republiky, konajúce ako riadiaci orgán, vyčlenilo prostriedky na vykonanie litovského fondu s pákovým efektom. V kontexte fondu s pákovým efektom a uzatvorením dodatku k dohode o financovaní týkajúcej sa fondu fondov Jessica II pre Litvu („Jessica II“ alebo „FF“), ktorá nadobudla platnosť 7.5.2015 (zmenená a doplnená 5.10.2016) medzi Ministerstvom financií a Ministerstvom životného prostredia Litovskej republiky („ministerstvá“) jednotlivo na jednej strane a Európskou investičnou bankou („EIB“) na druhej strane, EIB bola vymenovaná ako orgán, ktorý vykonáva finančný nástroj v podobe záruky v prospech Litovskej republiky („záruka“), v súlade s článkom 38 ods. 4 písm. b) bodom i) nariadenia o spoločných ustanoveniach („NSU“).</P><P>Relevantné pravidlá na vykonávanie finančného nástroja sú prevažne stanovené v NSU, delegovanom nariadení Komisie („CDR“), vykonávacom nariadení Komisie a nariadení o Európskom fonde regionálneho rozvoja („EFRR“), ako je uvedené nižšie, a platných litovských právnych predpisoch a nariadeniach.</P><P>Cieľom výzvy na vyjadrenie záujmu („VVZ“) je vybrať oprávnené finančné inštitúcie v Litve, ktoré sa stanú finančnými sprostredkovateľmi a na základe dohody o záruke získajú záruku financovanú z európskych štrukturálnych a investičných fondov („EŠIF“). Záruka čiastočne pokryje úverové riziko spojené s novým portfóliom preferenčných úverov, ktoré budú finanční sprostredkovatelia poskytovať fyzickým alebo právnickým osobám vlastniacim priestory vo viacbytových budovách („konečný príjemca“) alebo správcom spoločného majetku na účel energeticky hospodárnej renovácie viacbytových budov („projekty“) v súlade s litovským právnym základom („úvery na modernizáciu“).</P><P>Súťažné podmienky vrátane príloh si možno vyžiadať zaslaním e-mailu na adresu CSprocurement@eib.org s predmetom „PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents“.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postup prihlásenia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Návrhy by mali byť predložené v angličtine poštou na adresu uvedenú v bode 1 a v prísnom súlade s osobitnými požiadavkami stanovenými v súťažných podmienkach.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Všeobecný opis konania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Táto výzva na vyjadrenie záujmu nepredstavuje postup verejného obstarávania v zmysle smerníc 2004/18/ES alebo 2014/24/EÚ.</P><P>Vyzývame všetky strany prejavujúce záujem, aby predložili svoje ponuky v súlade s pravidlami stanovenými v tomto oznámení a súťažných podmienkach.</P><P>Zásady a metóda platné pre proces hodnotenia, ako aj fázy procesov hodnotenia, sú opísané v súťažných podmienkach.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Konečný termín podania návrhov</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ochrana osobných údajov</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Osobné údaje, ktoré poskytnete, sa spracujú v súlade s nariadením Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (ES) č. 45/2001 z 18.12.2000 o ochrane jednotlivcov so zreteľom na spracovanie osobných údajov inštitúciami a orgánmi Spoločenstva a o voľnom pohybe takýchto údajov a prípadnými budúcimi právnymi predpismi, ktoré ho zmenia alebo zrušia. Informácie požadované pre VVZ sú potrebné s cieľom posúdiť váš návrh a použijú sa výlučne na tento účel v rámci právomoci oddelenia pre nákup EIB (CS/IMP/PROCUR), v súlade s usmernením EIB pre obstarávanie schváleným predstavenstvom EIB. Upozorňujeme, že na to, aby bol váš návrh posúdený, sa môže vyžadovať zodpovedanie určitých alebo všetkých otázok vo vyhlásení, ktoré vypracuje uchádzač. Povinný/nepovinný charakter týchto otázok je uvedený v zmluvných podmienkach. S cieľom posúdiť uchádzača budú vami poskytnuté osobné údaje posudzovať členovia výberovej komisie a riaditeľstva, ktoré požiadalo o VVZ. Prístup k týmto údajom sa môže na požiadanie udeliť úradu hlavného úradníka zodpovedného za dodržiavanie súladu EIB, právnemu oddeleniu alebo generálnemu inšpektorátu. Údaje o úspešnom uchádzačovi sa zachovajú počas trvania obstarávania a 2 roky po ňom v ústrednom archíve, pokiaľ nebudú potrebné v súvislosti s konaním pred súdom alebo sťažnosťami. Údaje o neúspešných uchádzačoch sa zachovajú po dobu 4 rokov, pokiaľ nebudú potrebné v súvislosti s konaním pred súdom alebo sťažnosťami. Máte právo na prístup k vašim údajom, ich opravu alebo aktualizáciu. Tieto práva si môžete uplatniť kontaktovaním vedúceho oddelenia CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Máte tiež právo kedykoľvek sa obrátiť na európskeho dozorného úradníka pre ochranu údajov.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kritériá vylúčenia, kritériá výberu a vyhodnotenia ponúk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kritériá vylúčenia, administratívne kritériá a kritériá hodnotenia platné pre túto výzvu sú opísané v súťažných podmienkach a prílohách k nim.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dátum odoslania tohto oznámenia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dátum prijatia Úradom pre vydávanie publikácií</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Poziv k prijavi interesa za izbiro finančnih posrednikov v okviru litovskega sklada z vzvodom z namenom izvajanja finančnega instrumenta jamstva v Litvi (LU-Luxembourg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenčna številka: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Obvestilo bo objavljeno v Uradnem listu, serija S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Obvestilo o pozivu k prijavi interesa</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sklad skladov Jessica II za Litvo, ki ga za namene tega poziva k prijavi interesa zastopa</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska investicijska banka</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luksemburg, e-pošta: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>v vlogi naročnika.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cilj poziva k prijavi interesa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ministrstvo za finance Republike Litve, ki deluje kot organ upravljanja, je namenilo sredstva za izvajanje litovskega sklada z vzvodom („sklad z vzvodom“) za programsko obdobje 2014–2020 „operativnega programa za naložbe skladov Unije v obdobju 2014–2020“, odobrenega s Sklepom Evropske komisije C(2014) 6397 („operativni program“), z namenom odpravljanja tržne pomanjkljivosti, ugotovljene v okviru začetne predhodne ocene in posodobljene predhodne ocene, ki ju je potrdil odbor za ocenjevanje in spremljanje projektov javne infrastrukture in energetske učinkovitosti dne 7.11.2014 oziroma 29.8.2016. V zvezi s skladom z vzvodom je bila na podlagi spremembe sporazuma o financiranju glede sklada skladov Jessica II za Litvo („Jessica II“ ali „SS“), sklenjenega dne 7.5.2015 (kakor je bil spremenjen 5.10.2016) med ministrstvoma za finance in za okolje Republike Litve (v nadaljnjem besedilu: ministrstvi) ter Evropsko investicijsko banko („EIB“) („sporazum o financiranju“ ali „SOF“), EIB imenovana za organ za izvajanje finančnega instrumenta v obliki jamstva v korist Republike Litve („jamstvo“) v skladu s členom 38(4)(b)(i) uredbe o skupnih določbah.</P><P>Zadevna pravila za izvajanje finančnega instrumenta so v prvi vrsti določena v uredbi o skupnih določbah, delegirani uredbi Komisije, izvedbeni uredbi Komisije in uredbi o Evropskem skladu za regionalni razvoj („ESRR“) (kot je opredeljeno spodaj) ter veljavnih litovskih zakonih in predpisih.</P><P>Namen poziva k prijavi interesa je izbrati upravičene finančne institucije v Litvi kot finančne posrednike, ki bodo na podlagi jamstvenega sporazuma prejeli jamstvo, financirano s strani evropskih strukturnih in investicijskih skladov („skladi ESI“). Jamstvo bo delno pokrilo kreditno tveganje, povezano z novim portfeljem preferenčnih posojil, ki jih odobrijo finančni posredniki fizičnim ali pravnim osebam, ki imajo v lasti prostore v večstanovanjskih stavbah, („končni prejemniki“) ali upraviteljem skupne lastnine za obnovo energetske učinkovitosti večstanovanjskih stavb („projekti“) v skladu z litvansko pravno podlago („posojila za posodobitev“).</P><P>Formalne pogoje in priloge se lahko zahtevajo po e-pošti na naslov CSprocurement@eib.org z naslednjo navedbo v zadevi: „PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents“.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Prijavni postopek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Predloge je treba pripraviti v angleščini in poslati po pošti na naslov, naveden v točki 1, ob doslednem upoštevanju posebnih navodil, določenih v formalnih pogojih.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Splošni opis postopka</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ta poziv k prijavi interesa ni odprti razpisni postopek v smislu Direktive 2004/18/ES ali 2014/24/EU.</P><P>Zainteresirane strani so vabljene, da oddajo svoje predloge v skladu s pravili, določenimi v tem obvestilu, in formalnimi pogoji.</P><P>Načela in metoda, ki se uporabljajo v postopku ocenjevanja, ter faze postopka ocenjevanja so opisani v formalnih pogojih.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rok za oddajo predlogov</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Varstvo osebnih podatkov</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Osebni podatki, ki jih posredujete, bodo obdelani v skladu z Uredbo (ES) št. 45/2001 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 18.12.2000 o varstvu posameznikov pri obdelavi osebnih podatkov v institucijah in organih Skupnosti in o prostem pretoku takih podatkov ter morebitnimi prihodnjimi zakonodajnimi akti o spremembi ali razveljavitvi te uredbe. Informacije, zahtevane za poziv k prijavi interesa, so potrebne zato, da bi ocenili vaš predlog, in se bodo uporabljale izključno za ta namen v okviru pooblastil oddelka EIB za nabave (CS/IMP/PROCUR), in sicer v skladu z vodnikom EIB za javna naročila, ki ga je odobril upravni odbor EIB. Upoštevajte, da bo morda treba za to, da bi bil vaš predlog upoštevan, odgovoriti na nekatera ali vsa vprašanja v izjavi, ki jo mora podati kandidat. Obvezna/neobvezna narava teh vprašanj je navedena v dokumentu s formalnimi pogoji. Da bi lahko ocenili kandidata, bodo osebne podatke, ki jih posredujete, ocenili člani odbora za izbor in direktorat, ki je zahteval poziv k prijavi interesa. Na zahtevo se lahko dostop do teh podatkov omogoči uradu glavnega vodje za skladnost poslovanja EIB, pravni službi ali generalnemu inšpektoratu. Podatki izbranega kandidata bodo v osrednjem arhivu shranjeni za obdobje trajanja naročila in dodatni 2 leti, razen če so potrebni v kontekstu pravdnih sporov ali zahtevkov. Podatki neizbranih kandidatov bodo shranjeni za obdobje 4 let, razen če so potrebni v kontekstu pravdnih sporov ali zahtevkov. Imate pravico do dostopa in popravljanja ali posodobitve svojih podatkov. Te pravice lahko uveljavljate tako, da kontaktirate vodjo oddelka CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Prav tako imate pravico do tega, da se kadar koli obrnete na Evropskega nadzornika za varstvo podatkov.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Merila za izključitev, izbor in oddajo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Merila za izključitev, upravna merila in merila za ocenjevanje, ki se uporabljajo pri tem pozivu k prijavi interesa, so opisana v formalnih pogojih in njihovih prilogah.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum odpošiljanja obvestila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum prejema na Uradu za publikacije</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BEI - Glao ar Léiriú Spéise: d’fhonn idirghabhálaithe airgeadais a roghnú faoi Chiste Giaráilte na Liotuáine chun ionstraim airgeadais ráthaíochta a chur chun feidhme sa Liotuáin (LU-Lucsamburg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tagairt: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Fógra le bheith foilsithe san Iris Oifigiúil, sraith S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Fógra maidir le glao ar léiriú spéise</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás conarthach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ciste Cistí Jessica II na Liotuáine, arna ionadú chun críche an ghlao seo ar léiriú spéise ag</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An Banc Eorpach Infheistíochta</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Lucsamburg, Ríomhphost: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>atá ag feidhmiú mar an t-eintiteas soláthair.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cuspóir an ghlao ar léiriú spéise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Laistigh de chlárthréimhse 2014-2020 den “chlár oibriúcháin le haghaidh infheistíochtaí chistí an aontais sna blianta idir 2014-2020” arna fhormheas ag cinneadh uimh. 6397 ón gCoimisiún Eorpach (2014)(“Clár Oibriúcháin”) agus is é is cuspóir leis aghaidh a thabhairt ar theipeanna margaidh a shainaithnítear ag na chéad mheasúnuithe agus nuashonraithe ex ante arna bhformheas ag an gcoiste meastóireachta agus monatóireachta um thionscadal an bhonneagair phoiblí agus na héifeachtúlachta fuinnimh an 7.11.2014 agus an 29.8.2016 faoi seach (“measúnú ex ante”); tá Aireacht Airgeadais Phoblacht na Liotuáine agus í ag feidhmiú mar údarás bainistíochta tar éis acmhainní a thiomnú do chur chun feidhme Chiste Giaráilte na Liotuáine (“an ciste giaráilte”). I gcomhthéacs an chiste ghiaráilte, ba le leasú a thabhairt i gcrích ar Chiste Cistí Jessica II na Liotuáine (“Jessica II” nó “FoF”) a tháinig an comhaontú cistiúcháin i bhfeidhm an 7.5.2015 (arna leasú an 5.10.2016) idir Aireachtaí Airgeadais agus Comhshaoil Phoblacht na Liotuáine (na “hAireachtaí”) faoi seach agus an Banc Eorpach Infheistíochta (“BEI”)(“Comhaontú Cistiúcháin” nó “CC”); ceapadh an BEI ina chomhlacht ag cur ionstraime airgeadais chun feidhme (“Ionstraim Airgeadais”) i bhfoirm ráthaíochta chun tairbhe Phoblacht na Liotuáine (“Ráthaíocht”), i gcomhréir le hAirteagal 38 (4)(b)(i) maidir le Rialachán na bhForálacha Coiteanna (“CPR”).</P><P>Forordaítear rialacha ábhartha do chur chun feidhme na hionstraime airgeadais den chuid is mó sa CPR, sa Rialachán tarmligthe ón gcoimisiún (“CDR”), sa rialachán cur chun feidhme ón gcoimisiún agus i Rialachán Chiste Forbraíochta Réigiúnaí na hEorpa (“CFRE”)(de réir mar atá sainithe thíos faoi seach), agus i ndlíthe agus rialacháin náisiúnta na Liotuáine is infheidhme.</P><P>Is éard is aidhm leis an nglao ar léiriú spéise ná institiúidí incháilithe airgeadais sa Liotuáin a roghnú le bheith ina n-idirghabhálaithe airgeadais (“Idirghabhálaithe Airgeadais”), a gheobhaidh ráthaíocht ar chistiú ó Chistí Struchtúrtha agus Infheistíochta na hEorpa (“CSIE”) faoin gconradh ráthaíochta (“Conradh Ráthaíochta”). Cumhdófar leis an ráthaíocht, cuid den riosca creidmheasa a bhaineann le punann na iasachtaí tosaíochta arna dtabhairt ag idirghabhálaithe airgeadais do dhaoine nádúrtha nó dlítheanacha ar leo áitreabh i bhfoirgnimh ilárasán (“An Faighteoir Deiridh”) nó do riarthóirí áitreabh comhchoiteann (“Riarthóirí ar Thalamh Comhchoiteann”) le haghaidh athchóiriú ar mhaithe le héifeachtúlacht fuinnimh ar fhoirgnimh ilárasán (‘Tionscadail”) i gcomhréir le bunús dlí na Liotuáine (“Iasachtaí um Athchóiriú”).</P><P>Is féidir na téarmaí tagartha, lena n-áirítear na hiarscríbhinní, a iarraidh trí ríomhphost a chur chuig CS-procurement@eib.org faoin ábhar PC-1439 Ciste Giaráilte na Liotuáine — Iarratas ar dhoiciméid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nós imeachta iarratais</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ba cheart na tograí a chur isteach i mBéarla sa phost chuig an seoladh atá léirithe i bpointe 1, de réir na ag cloí go docht leis na treoracha sainiúla atá leagtha síos sna téarmaí tagartha.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ginearálta ar an nós imeachta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ní hionann an glao seo ar léiriú spéise agus nós imeachta soláthair phoiblí ó thaobh treoracha 2004/18/CE ná 2014/24/AE de.</P><P>Tugtar cuireadh do pháirtithe leasmhara chun a dtograí a chur isteach de réir na rialacha atá leagtha amach san fhógra seo agus sna téarmaí tagartha.</P><P>Tá cur síos ar na prionsabail agus ar an modh is infheidhme ar an bpróiseas meastóireachta, agus ar chéimeanna den phróiseas meastóireachta sna téarmaí tagartha.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>An spriocdháta chun tograí a chur isteach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sonraí pearsanta a chosaint</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Déanfar na sonraí pearsanta leatsa a phróiseáil i gcomhréir le Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 45/2001 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 18.12.2000 maidir le cosaint daoine aonair i dtaca le próiseáil sonraí pearsanta ag institiúidí agus comhlachtaí an chomhphobail, agus maidir le saorghluaiseacht na sonraí sin agus aon reachtaíocht sa todhchaí lena leasófar nó lena n-aisghairfear é. Teastaíonn an fhaisnéis arna hiarraidh don CEoI (glao ar léirithe spéise) d'fhonn do thogra a mheasúnú, agus ní bhainfear leas aisti ach amháin chun na críche sin faoi údarás rannán ceannacháin an BEI (CS/IMP/PROCUR), i gcomhréir le treoir an BEI um sholáthar, arna faomhadh ag coiste bainistíochta an BEI. Tabhair faoi deara go bhféadfadh sé a bheith riachtanach roinnt de na ceisteanna nó na ceisteanna uile sa dearbhú le comhlánú ag an iarratasóir a fhreagairt sular féidir do thogra a bhreithniú. Tugtar achoimre ar chineál éigeantach /roghnach na gceisteanna sin sa doiciméad um théarmaí tagartha. D'fhonn an t-iarratasóir a mheasúnú, is iad baill an phainéil roghnúcháin agus na stiúrthóireachta a d'iarr an CEoI a gheobhadh rochtain ar na sonraí pearsanta a sholáthair tú féin. D'fhéadfaí rochtain ar na sonraí sin a dhámhachtain ach iarratas a fháil, d'oifig an phríomhoifigigh um chomhlíonadh le BEI, don tseirbhís dlí nó don ard-chigireacht. Coinneofar sonraí an iarratasóra rathúil ar feadh tréimhse an chonartha, móide 2 bhliain sna cartlanna lárnacha, mura dteastaíonn siad i gcomhthéacs na dlíthíochta nó na n--éileamh. Coinneofar sonraí iarratasóirí mírathúla ar feadh 4 bliana, mura dteastaíonn siad i gcomhthéacs na dlíthíochta nó na n-éileamh. Tá sé de cheart agat do shonraí a rochtain agus a cheartú nó a nuashonrú. Is féidir leat na cearta sin a chleachtadh ach teagmháil a dhéanamh le ceann an rannáin CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Tá sé de cheart agat freisin dul ar iontaoibh an Mhaoirseora Eorpaigh ar Chosaint Sonraí ag am ar bith.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critéir eisiaimh, critéir roghnúcháin agus dámhachtana</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tá cur síos ar na critéir eisiaimh, riaracháin agus measúnaithe is infheidhme ar an nglao seo sna téarmaí tagartha agus sna hiarscríbhinní lena mbaineann.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dáta seolta an fhógra seo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dáta fála ag Oifig na bhFoilseachán</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕИБ - Покана за изразяване на интерес: за избор на финансови посредници по Литовския заемен фонд за изпълнение на гаранционен финансов инструмент в Литва (LU-Люксембург)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Справка: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Обявление за публикуване в Официален вестник, серия S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Обявление за покана за изразяване на интерес</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Фондът на фондовете „Jessica II“ на Литва, представляван за целта на тази покана за изразяване на интерес от</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейска инвестиционна банка</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Люксембург, електронна поща: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>която действа като възложител.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Предмет на поканата за изразяване на интерес</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>В програмния период 2014—2020 г. на оперативна програма за инвестиции на фондовете на Съюза, одобрена с Решение С (2014) 6397 на Европейската комисия („Оперативна програма“) и с цел справяне с неуспехите на пазара, открити от първоначалната и актуализираната екс анте оценка, одобрени от Комисията за оценка и мониторинг на проекта за публична инфраструктура и енергийна ефективност съответно на 7.11.2014 г. и на 29.8.2016 г. („екс анте оценка“), Министерството на финансите на република Литва, действащо като управляващ орган, определи ресурси на изпълнението на Литовския заемен фонд („заемен фонд“). В контекста на заемния фонд, сключвайки изменение на споразумението за финансиране с Фонда на фондовете „Jessica II“ на Литва („Jessica II“ или „ФнФ“), влязло в сила на 7.5.2015 г. (с поправката от 5.10.2016 г.) между Министерствата на финансите и на околната среда на република Литва („Министерствата“) съответно и Европейската инвестиционна банка („ЕИБ“) („Споразумение за финансиране“ или „СФ“), ЕИБ е назначена за орган за изпълнение на финансовия инструмент („Финансов инструмент“) под формата на гаранция в полза на република Литва („Гаранция“), в съответствие с член 38, ал. 4, букви б) и и) на Регламента за общоприложимите разпоредби („CPR“).</P><P>Съответните правила за прилагането на финансовия инструмент са посочени на първо място в CPR, CDR (Делегиран регламент на Комисията), в регламента за прилагане на Комисията и в регламента за ЕФРР (Европейски фонд за регионално развитие) (съответно както е определено по-долу) и в приложимото литовско законодателство и подзаконови разпоредби.</P><P>Целта на поканата за изразяване на интерес („Покана за ИИ“) е да избере допустими финансови институции в Литва, които да станат финансови посредници („Финансови посредници“), които, съгласно гаранционното споразумение („Гаранционно споразумение“), ще получават гаранция, финансирана от Европейския структурен и инвестиционен фонд (ЕСИФ). Гаранцията ще покрива частично кредитния риск, свързан с ново портфолио от преференциални заеми, които да се предоставят от финансовите посредници на физически или юридически лица, притежаващи помещения в сгради с много апартаменти („Краен получател“) или на администратори на обща собственост („Администратори на обща собственост“) за реновации за енергийна ефективност в сгради с много апартаменти („Проекти“) в съответствие с литовското правно основание („Заеми за модернизация“).</P><P>Референтните условия, включително приложенията, могат да бъдат поискани чрез изпращане на електронно писмо до CS-procurement@eib.org с тема „PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — request for documents“.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Процедура за кандидатстване</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Предложенията трябва да бъдат подадени на английски език по пощата на адреса, посочен в точка 1, в строго съответствие с конкретните изисквания, определени в техническото задание.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Общо описание на процедурата</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Тази покана за изразяване на интерес не представлява процедура за обществена поръчка по смисъла на Директива 2004/18/ЕО или Директива 2014/24/ЕС.</P><P>Заинтересованите лица се поканват да подадат своите предложения, в съответствие с правилата, определени в настоящото обявление и техническото задание.</P><P>Принципите и методът, приложими за процеса на оценяване, както и неговите етапи, са описани в техническото задание.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Краен срок за подаване на заявления</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Защита на лични данни</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Предоставените от Вас лични данни ще бъдат обработвани в съответствие с Регламент (ЕО) № 45/2001 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 18.12.2000 г. относно защитата на физическите лица по отношение на обработката на лични данни от институции и органи на Общността и за свободното движение на такива данни и всяко бъдещо законодателство, което го коригира или отхвърля. Информацията, поискана за поканата за изразяване на интерес (CEoI), е необходима за оценка на Вашето предложение и ще бъде използвана единствено за тази цел под ръководството на отдела за закупуване на ЕИБ (CS/IMP/PROCUR), в съответствие с ръководството на ЕИБ за възлагане на обществени поръчки, утвърдено от комитета за управление на ЕИБ. Моля, имайте предвид, че, за да бъде взето под внимание Вашето предложение, е задължително да се отговори на някои или на всички въпроси в декларацията, която трябва да се изготви от кандидата. Задължителното/възможното естество на тези въпроси е посочено в документа с техническото задание. За да се оцени кандидата, предоставените от Вас лични данни ще бъдат оценени от членове на екипа за подбор и Дирекцията, която е поискала поканата за изразяване на интерес CEoI. При поискване може да бъде предоставен достъп до тези данни на службата на главното длъжностно лице за съответствие на ЕИБ, правната служба или главния инспекторат. Данните за успешния кандидат трябва да се съхраняват за срока на договора плюс 2 години в централния архив, освен ако са необходими в контекста на съдебни спорове или претенции. Данните на неуспешните кандидат трябва да се съхраняват 4 години, освен ако са необходими в контекста на съдебни спорове или претенции. Вие имате право на достъп и коригиране или актуализиране на своите лични данни. Можете да упражните тези права, като се свържете с ръководителя на отдела CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Също така имате право да се обръщате по всяко време към Европейския надзорен орган по защита на личните данни.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Критерии за изключване, подбор и критерии за възлагане</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Критериите за изключване, административните критерии и критериите за оценка, приложими за тази покана, са описани в референтните условия и техните приложения.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Дата на изпращане на обявлението</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Дата на получаване от Службата за публикации</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BEI - Cererea de scrisori de interes: selectarea de intermediarii financiari în cadrul Fondului lituanian cu efect de levier pentru a pune în aplicare un instrument financiar de garantare în Lituania (LU-Luxemburg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referința: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Anunțul urmează să fie publicat în Jurnalul Oficial, seria S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anunț privind o cerere de scrisori de interes</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea contractantă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fondul de fonduri lituanian Jessica II , reprezentat în scopul prezentei cereri de exprimare a interesului de către</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Banca Europeană de Investiții</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg, e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Care acționează în calitate de entitate contractantă.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Obiectivul anunțului privind o cerere de exprimare a interesului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>În perioada de programare 2014-2020 a "Programului operațional pentru investiții în fonduri sindicale 2014-2020" aprobat prin decizia Comisiei Europene nr. C (2014) 6397 ("Programul operațional") și cu scopul de a combate eșecul pieței identificate prin evaluările ex-ante inițiale și actualizate aprobate de comitetul de evaluare și monitorizare a proiectelor privind infrastructura publică și eficiența energetică din 7.11.2014 și, respectiv, 29.8.2016 ("evaluare ex-ante ), Ministerul Finanțelor al Republicii Lituania în calitate de autoritatea de gestionare, are resurse dedicate punerii în aplicare a fondului cu efect de levier din Lituania ("fond cu efect de levier"). În contextul fondului cu efect de levier, prin încheierea unui amendament la acordul de finanțare a fondului de fonduri lituanian Jessica II ("Jessica II" sau "Fondul de fonduri) a intrat în vigoare la 7.5.2015 (astfel cum a fost modificat la 5.10.2016) între ministerele de finanțe și de mediu ale Republicii Lituania ("ministerele") și Banca Europeană de Investiții ("BEI") ("Acordul de finanțare" sau "AF"), BEI a fost desemnat un organism care pune în aplicare un instrument financiar (" Instrumentul financiar "), sub forma unei garanții în beneficiul Republicii Lituania ("garanție "), în conformitate cu articolul 38 alineatul (4) litera (b) punctul (i) din Regulamentul privind dispozițiile comune (RDC).</P><P>Normele relevante pentru punerea în aplicare a instrumentului financiar sunt în principal stipulate în RDC, regulamentul delegat al Comisiei, Regulamentul de punere în aplicare al Comisiei și Regulamentul (FEDER) al Fondului european de dezvoltare regională ("FEDER"), și legile și regulamentele lituaniene aplicabile..</P><P>Scopul cererii de scrisori de interes este de a selecta instituțiile financiare eligibile din Lituania pentru a deveni intermediari financiari ("intermediari financiari"), care, în temeiul acordului de garanție ("Contractul de garanție"), primesc garanție finanțată de Fondurile Structurale și de Investiții ("ESIF"). Garanția acoperă parțial riscul de credit asociat unui nou portofoliu de împrumuturi preferențiale acordate de intermediarii financiari persoanelor fizice sau juridice care dețin sedii în clădiri cu mai multe apartamente ("beneficiarul final") sau administratorilor de bunuri comune ("Administratorii de Proprietate comună ") pentru renovarea eficientă din punct de vedere energetic a unei clădiri cu mai multe apartamente (" Proiecte "), în conformitate cu temeiul juridic lituanian (" împrumuturi de modernizare ").</P><P>Caietul de sarcini, inclusiv anexele, poate fi solicitat prin trimiterea unui e-mail la adresa CSprocurement@eib.org with the subject PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura de depunere a candidaturilor</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Propunerile trebuie trimise în limba engleză, prin poștă la adresa indicată la punctul 1, respectând strict instrucțiunile specifice stabilite în caietul de sarcini.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea generală a procedurii</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Această cerere de exprimare a interesului nu reprezintă o procedură de achiziții publice în sensul Directivei 2004/18/CE sau al Directivei 2014/24/UE.</P><P>Părțile interesate sunt invitate să își depună propunerile în conformitate cu normele prevăzute în acest anunț și în caietul de sarcini.</P><P>Principiile și metoda aplicabile în procesul de evaluare, precum și etapele proceselor de evaluare sunt descrise în caietul de sarcini.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Termenul-limită de depunere a propunerilor</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Protecția datelor cu caracter personal</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Datele cu caracter personal furnizate vor fi prelucrate în conformitate cu Regulamentul (CE) nr. 45/2001 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 18.12.2000 privind protecția persoanelor fizice cu privire la prelucrarea datelor cu caracter personal de către instituțiile și organele comunitare și privind libera circulație a acestor date și orice viitoare legislație care să-l modifice sau să-l abroge. Informațiile solicitate pentru cererea de exprimare a interesului sunt necesare pentru a evalua propunerile și vor fi utilizate numai în acest scop, sub autoritatea Diviziei pentru achiziții publice a BEI (CS/IMP/PROCUR), în conformitate cu ghidul BEI pentru achiziții, aprobat de Comitetul de direcție al BEI. A se avea în vedere că, pentru ca propunerea să fie luată în considerare, poate fi obligatoriu să se răspundă la unele sau la toate întrebările din declarația care trebuie făcută de candidat. Caracterul obligatoriu/opțional al acestor întrebări este menționat în caietul de sarcini. Pentru a evalua candidatul, datele cu caracter personal furnizate vor fi accesate de către membrii comitetului de selecție și ai direcției care a solicitat cererea de exprimare a interesului. La cerere, accesul la aceste date poate fi acordat Biroului responsabilului-șef pentru conformitate din cadrul BEI, serviciului juridic sau Inspectoratului general. Datele candidatului câștigător sunt păstrate pe întreaga durată a contractului, plus 2 ani, în arhivele centrale, cu excepția cazului în care acestea sunt necesare în contextul unui litigiu sau al unor reclamații. Datele candidaților necâștigători sunt păstrate 4 ani, cu excepția cazului în care acestea sunt necesare în contextul unui litigiu sau al unor reclamații. Candidații au dreptul de a accesa și de a rectifica sau actualiza datele acestora. Aceste drepturi pot fi exercitate contactând șeful Diviziei CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). De asemenea, candidații au dreptul de a apela în orice moment la Autoritatea Europeană pentru Protecția Datelor.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteriile de excludere, de selecție și de atribuire</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Criteriile de excludere, criteriile administrative și criteriile de evaluare aplicabile pentru această cerere sunt descrise în caietul de sarcini și anexele acestuia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data expedierii anunțului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data primirii de către Oficiul pentru Publicații</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EIB - Poziv na iskazivanje interesa: za odabir financijskih posrednika u okviru Litavskog fonda s financijskom polugom u svrhu provedbe jamstvenog financijskog instrumenta u Litvi (LU-Luxembourg)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Uputa: PC-1439</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>(Obavijest će biti objavljena u Službenom listu, seriji S)</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Obavijest o pozivu na iskazivanje interesa</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fond fondova Jessica II za Litvu, koji u svrhu ovog poziva na iskazivanje interesa zastupa</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska investicijska banka</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98-100 boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luksemburg, e-pošta: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>koja djeluje kao javni naručitelj.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cilj poziva na iskazivanje interesa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>U sklopu programskog razdoblja 2014.–2020. za „operativni program za ulaganja u fondove Unije u razdoblju 2014.–2020” , odobren odlukom Europske komisije br. C (2014)6397 („Operativni program”) i sa svrhom rješavanja problema tržišnih propusta utvrđenih početnim i ažuriranim „ex ante” procjenama koje je odobrio Odbor za ocjenjivanje i praćenje projekta javne infrastrukture i energetske učinkovitosti 7.11.2014 i 29.8.2016 („ex ante procjena”), Ministarstvo financija Republike Litve, koje djeluje kao upravno tijelo, namijenilo je sredstva za provedbu Litavskog fonda s financijskom polugom („fond s financijskom polugom”). U kontekstu fonda s financijskom polugom, sklapanjem izmjene sporazuma o financiranju fonda fondova Jessica II za Litvu („Jessica II” ili Fund of Funds – „FoF”), koji je stupio na snagu 7.5.2015 (kako je izmijenjen 5.10.2016), između Ministarstva financija i Ministarstva okoliša Litve („Ministarstva”) i Europske investicijske banke („EIB”) („Sporazum o financiranju” ili Funding Agreement – „FA”), EIB je imenovan tijelom koje provodi financijski instrument („Financijski instrument”) u obliku jamstva u korist Republike Litve („Jamstvo”), u skladu s člankom 38. stavkom 4. točkom (b) podtočkom (i) Uredbe o zajedničkim odredbama („CPR”).</P><P>Relevantna pravila za primjenu financijskog instrumenta prvenstveno su propisana u CPR-u, Delegiranoj uredbi komisije (CDR), Provedbenoj uredbi Komisije i Uredbi o Europskom fondu za regionalni razvoj („ERDF”) i Uredbi o europskom socijalnom fondu („ESF”) (odnosno kako je utvrđeno u nastavku) i primjenjivim litavskim zakonima i propisima.</P><P>Cilj poziva na iskazivanje interesa odabir je prihvatljivih financijskih institucija u Litvi koje će postati financijski posrednici („Financijski posrednici”), koji će prema sporazumu o jamstvu („Sporazum o jamstvu”) primiti jamstvo koje financiraju Europski strukturni i investiciji fondovi („ESIF”). Jamstvo djelomično pokriva kreditni rizik povezan s novim portfeljom povlaštenih zajmova koje će odobravati financijski posrednici fizičkim i pravnim osobama koje su u vlasništvu objekata u stambenim zgradama („Krajnji primatelj”) ili upraviteljima zajedničkog vlasništva („Upravitelji zajedničkog vlasništva”) za obnovu stambenih zgrada u smislu energetske učinkovitosti („Projekti”) u skladu s pravnom osnovom Litve („Zajmovi za modernizaciju”).</P><P>Opis projekta s prilozima može se zatražiti slanjem e-pošte na adresu CS-procurement@eib.org pod naslovom „PC-1439 Lithuania Leveraged Fund — Request for documents” (PC-1439 Litavski fond s financijskom polugom — zahtjev za dokumente).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postupak prijave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prijedlozi trebaju biti dostavljeni poštom na engleskom jeziku na adresu navedenu u točki 1., strogo poštujući određene upute utvrđene u opisu projekta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opći opis postupka</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ovaj poziv na iskazivanje interesa ne predstavlja postupak javne nabave u smislu direktiva 2004/18/EZ ili 2014/24/EU.</P><P>Zainteresirane strane pozvane su dostaviti svoje prijedloge u skladu s pravilima iz ove obavijesti i opisa projekta.</P><P>Načela i metoda koji su primjenjivi na postupak ocjene, kao i faze postupaka ocjene, opisani su u opisu projekta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rok za podnošenje prijedloga</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>26.3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zaštita osobnih podataka</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Osobni podaci koje dostavite bit će obrađeni u skladu s Uredbom (EZ) br. 45/2001 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 18.12.2000 o zaštiti pojedinaca u vezi s obradom osobnih podataka u institucijama i tijelima Zajednice i o slobodnom kretanju takvih podataka u bilo kojim budućim zakonodavstvom o izmjenama ili stavljanju izvan snage predmetne uredbe. Informacije tražene u svrhu poziva na iskazivanje interesa potrebne su radi procjenjivanja prijedloga te će se koristiti isključivo u tu svrhu u nadležnosti Odjela za nabavu EIB-a (CS/IMP/PROCUR), u skladu s priručnikom za nabavu EIB-a, koji je odobrio Upravljački odbor EIB-a. Napominjemo da, kako bismo uzeli vaš prijedlog u obzir, može biti potrebno odgovoriti na neka ili sva pitanja u izjavi koju treba dati podnositelj prijave. Obvezna/neobvezna priroda ovih pitanja opisana je u opisu projekta. U svrhu procjene podnositelja prijave, osobnim podacima koje dostavite pristupit će članovi odbora za odabir i Uprava koja je zatražila poziv na iskazivanje interesa. Pristup tim podacima može se na zahtjev dati EIB-ovom Uredu glavnog službenika za sukladnost, pravnoj službi ili glavnom inspektoratu. Podaci uspješnog podnositelja prijave bit će zadržani tijekom cijelog trajanja ugovora, uz 2 dodatne godine u središnjem arhivu, osim ako navedeni podaci ne budu potrebni u kontekstu parničenja ili zahtjeva. Podaci neuspješnih podnositelja prijave bit će zadržani tijekom 4 godine, osim ako navedeni podaci ne budu potrebni u kontekstu parničenja ili zahtjeva. Imate pravo pristupiti svojim podacima te ih ispraviti ili ažurirati. Navedeno pravo možete ostvariti kontaktiranjem s voditeljem odjela CS/IMP/PROCUR (CS-procurement@eib.org). Imate i pravo obratiti se bilo kada Europskom nadzorniku za zaštitu podataka.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kriteriji isključenja, uvjeti sposobnosti i kriteriji za dodjelu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kriteriji isključenja, administrativni kriteriji i kriteriji za procjenu koji se primjenjuju za ovaj poziv opisani su u opisu projekta i njegovim prilozima.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum slanja obavijesti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>12.1.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum primitka u Uredu za publikacije</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>