<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="102770-2018"
            EDITION="2018047">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-105108-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180410</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>47</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180308</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 047-102770</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:102770-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>www.politi.dk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=206146&amp;B=RIGSPOLITIET</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="35740000">Battle simulators</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="DK">DANMARK</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="DK">DANMARK</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="DKK">1500000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180306</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180410 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="U">Public order and safety</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01B02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Дaния</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Копенхаген</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Симулатори на бойни действия</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kodaň</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Simulátory boje</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>København</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kampsimulatorer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Dänemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kopenhagen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kampfsimulatoren</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Δανία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Κοπεγχάγη</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Προσομοιωτές μάχης</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Denmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Battle simulators</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhague</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Simuladores de combate</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Taani</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kopenhaagen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Lahingusimulaatorid</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Tanska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kööpenhamina</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Taistelusimulaattorit</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Danemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhague</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Simulateurs de combat</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Danmhairg, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Cóbanhávan</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Battle simulators</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kopenhagen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Bojni simulatori</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Dánia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Koppenhága</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Harcszimulátorok</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Danimarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenaghen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Simulatori di combattimento</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Danija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kopenhaga</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Koviniai treniruokliai</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Dānija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kopenhāgena</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kaujas simulatori</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>id-Danimarka</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kopenħagen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Simulaturi tal-battalji</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Denemarken</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kopenhagen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Veldslagsimulatoren</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Dania</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kopenhaga</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Symulatory walki</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhaga</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Simuladores de combate</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Danemarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhaga</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Simulatoare de luptă</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kodaň</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Bojové simulátory</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Kopenhagen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Simulatorji za bitke</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Köpenhamn</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Stridssimulatorer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Rigspolitiet</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>601ef883-6910-475e-a6c4-a7666d870853</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Rigspolitiet</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>17143611</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>Polititorvet 14</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>København V</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1780</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Nadia Rasoulinia</CONTACT_POINT>
               <E_MAIL>NRA011@POLITI.DK</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.politi.dk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=206146&amp;B=RIGSPOLITIET</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=206146&amp;B=RIGSPOLITIET</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="MINISTRY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="PUBLIC_ORDER_AND_SAFETY"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Contract regarding the purchase of a shooting simulator for the Danish National Police (restricted procedure)</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="35740000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SUPPLIES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The Danish Police wish to purchase a shooting simulator including service, support and maintenance work. The shooting simulator will be used in the basic firearms education of new police school students.</P>
               <P>The purpose of the service, support and maintenance agreement is, to make sure that the Danish police school, has a fuly functional shooting simulator at all times.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="DKK">1500000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="35740000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>— The contract contains the right to purchase 1 shooting simulator including 4 years of service, support and maintenance agreement,</P>
                  <P>— the contracting authority have the right to purchase additional spare parts and to prolong the duration of the service, support and maintenance agreement with up to 2 years,</P>
                  <P>— the contract also includes the right to purchase 1 additional shooting simulator including a service, support and maintenance agreement, for 4 years,</P>
                  <P>— the Contract is not divided into lots. The contracting authority considers it necessary to offer 1 contract, because the shooting simulator and the additional Service, support and maintenance agreement and the additional accessories and equipment for the shooting simulator(s), must be delivered by the same supplier cf. the Danish Public Procurement Act section 49 (2) (udbudslovens § 49, stk. 2).</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="DKK">1500000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">48</DURATION>
               <RENEWAL/>
               <RENEWAL_DESCR>
                  <P>The contract duration is 4 years from the date of signature. The service, support and maintenance agreement(s) can be extended with 1 year plus 1 year.</P>
               </RENEWAL_DESCR>
               <NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>5</NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>The contracting authority will prequalify 5 applicants, provided that a sufficient number of suitable applications are received.</P>
                  <P>When selecting among suitable applicants, emphasis is placed on the applicant's experience of delivering services similar to the assignment given, based on the references submitted by the applicant.</P>
                  <P>In the selection of the applicants, it will be assessed as positive, that:</P>
                  <P>— The reference includes service, support and maintenance work,</P>
                  <P>— The other party of the contract is comparable to the contracting authority (e.g. police or military force),</P>
                  <P>— The contract has a high value.</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>The service, support and maintenance agreement can be extended with 1 year plus 1 year.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>The applicant must provide documentation of its economic and financial standing. The applicant must fill in the applicants equity for the last 3 accounting years (provided that the company has existed the whole period).</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>The applicants equity must be positive in the last 3 accounting years (provided that the company has existed the whole period).</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>The applicant must fill in the European single procurement document (ESPD) with description of the following information to document sufficient experience:</P>
               <P>A list of the principal deliveries, similar and most relevant to those referred to in Section II.1.4 of the contract Notice, carried out by the applicant in the past 3 years, calculated from the date of the application. Within this period, completed contracts and contracts in progress are of interest.</P>
               <P>By sufficient experiences is meant references, which can document experience with performing delivery of a similar contract.</P>
               <P>The description shall include following information:</P>
               <P>— description of the contract and the applicants obligation in this manner, and weather the contract was including service, support and maintenance work,</P>
               <P>— the contract price,</P>
               <P>— date of contract signing,</P>
               <P>— name of the customer.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>The applicant must be able to present at least 3 references on delivery of a shooting simulator.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_RESTRICTED/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-04-10</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>2018-04-23</DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DATE_TENDER_VALID>2018-11-22</DATE_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <EORDERING/>
            <EINVOICING/>
            <EPAYMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>When a applicant is based on the technical and professional ability (e.g. educational or professional qualifications, or professional experience) of other entities in relation to the performance of specific aspects of the works or services, the specific aspects of the works or services shall be performed by the entity on which the candidate or tenderer is based.</P>
               <P>If the applicant, applying for selection to tender, for this procurement, relies on the economic and financial standing of another entity, in accordance with the provisions of the European single procurement document, and clause 4.5 of the Tender conditions, the contracting authority requires, that the entity on which the applicant relies, is joint and several liable for any economic loss for the contracting authority, caused by the supplier, if the supplier is in breach of the contract and can not cover the claim.</P>
               <P>Joint and several liability has the effect that the entity, on which the applicant relies, must co-sign the contract.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Klagenævnet for Udbud</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Nævnenes Hus, Toldboden 2</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Viborg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>8800</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 35291000</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>klfu@naevneneshus.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>https://erhvervsstyrelsen.dk/klagevejledning-0</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Pursuant to Section 3 of the Danish Consolidation Act nº 593 of 2.6.2016 on the Complaints Board for Public Procurement (available at www.retsinformation.dk), the following time limits for filing a complaint apply:</P>
               <P>Complaints regarding a candidate not being pre-qualified must be filed with The Complaints Board for Public Procurement within 20 calendar days starting the day after the contracting authority has sent notification to the candidates involved, cf. § 7(1) of the Act on the Complaints Board for Public Procurement, provided that the notification includes a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P>
               <P>Complaints regarding public procurements and decisions subject to Chapter II or III of the Public Procurement Act, which does not concern a candidate not being invited to tender, must in accordance with § 7(2) of the Act on The Complaints Board for Public Procurement be filed with The Complaints Board for Public Procurement within:</P>
               <P>1. 45 calendar days after the contracting authority has published a contract award notice in the Official Journal of the European Union (with effect from the day following the publication date),</P>
               <P>2. 30 calendar days starting the day after the contracting authority has informed the tenderers in question, that the contracting authority has entered into a contract based on a framework agreement through reopening of competition or a dynamic purchasing system, provided that the notification includes a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision,</P>
               <P>3. 6 months starting the day after the contracting authority has sent notification to the candidates/tenderers involved that the contracting authority has entered into the framework agreement, cf. § 2(2) or § 171(4) of the Public Procurement Act, provided that the notification included a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision,</P>
               <P>4. 20 calendar days starting the day after the contracting authority has published a notice concerning his decision to uphold the contract, cf. § 185(2) of the Public Procurement Act.</P>
               <P>The complainant must inform the contracting authority of the complaint in writing at the latest simultaneously with the lodge of the complaint to The Complaints Board for Public Procurement stating whether the complaint has been lodged in the stand-still period, cf. § 6(4) of the Act on The Complaints Board for Public Procurement. If the complaint has not been lodged in the stand-still period, the complainant must also state whether it is requested that the appeal is granted delaying effect, cf. § 12(1) of the said Act.</P>
               <P>The e-mail of The Complaints Board for Public Procurement is stated in section VI.4.1.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Konkurrence- og Forbrugerstyrelsen</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Carl Jacobsens Vej 35</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Valby</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2500</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 41715000</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>kfst@kfst.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>http://www.kfst.dk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-06</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
