<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="103999-2018"
            EDITION="2018047">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-105632-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180614</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>47</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180308</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 047-103999</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:103999-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.england.nhs.uk/</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="85100000">Health services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKJ1">Berkshire, Buckinghamshire and Oxfordshire</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKJ1">Berkshire, Buckinghamshire and Oxfordshire</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <REF_NOTICE>
            <NO_DOC_OJS>2017/S 143-295470</NO_DOC_OJS>
         </REF_NOTICE>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180306</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="6">Body governed by public law</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="7">Contract award notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="H">Health</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C21</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Бристол</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги на здравеопазването</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zdravotnické zabezpečení</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tjenesteydelser inden for sundhedsvæsenet</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dienstleistungen des Gesundheitswesens</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Μπρίστολ</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υγειονομικές υπηρεσίες</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Health services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de salud</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tervishoiuteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Terveyspalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de santé</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Briostó</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Health services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge u području zdravstva</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Egészségügyi szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi sanitari</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristolis</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sveikatos priežiūros paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristole</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Veselības pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi tas-saħħa</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Gezondheidsdiensten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi ochrony zdrowia</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de saúde</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de sănătate</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zdravotnícke služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zdravstvene storitve</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Hälsovårdstjänster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">NHS Commissioning Board (NHS England South (South Central))</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F21_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F21" LG="EN">
         <NOTICE TYPE="AWARD_CONTRACT"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>NHS Commissioning Board (NHS England South (South Central))</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Jubilee House, Cowley Road</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bristol</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>OX4 2LH</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Phil Fear</CONTACT_POINT>
               <E_MAIL>p.fear@nhs.net</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKJ1"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.england.nhs.uk/</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/Home</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY_ADDITIONAL>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Thames Valley Police</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Headquarters, Oxford Road, Oxon, Kidlington</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bristol</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>OX5 1NZ</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Phil Fear</CONTACT_POINT>
               <E_MAIL>p.fear@nhs.net</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKJ1"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/Home</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY_ADDITIONAL>
            <JOINT_PROCUREMENT_INVOLVED/>
            <CENTRAL_PURCHASING/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="BODY_PUBLIC"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="HEALTH"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Procurement for the provision of Sexual Assault Referral Centre Services for Thames Valley</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>PR001921</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="85100000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>NHS England (South Central) and Thames Valley Police are seeking to jointly re-commission Sexual Assault Referral Centre (SARC) services in Thames Valley.</P>
               <P>The commissioners seek tender responses from providers who have the capability and capacity to undertake such a contract. This procurement is being carried out by NHS South, Central &amp; West Commissioning Support Unit (SCW) on behalf of the commissioners. The commissioner will be contracting for the services using the national NHS standard contract. Contracts will be for an initial term of 3 years and are planned to commence from 1.4.2018. The value of the service will be 2 341 428 GBP over 3 years. At the discretion of the commissioner, the contract may be extended for up to a further 24 months.</P>
               <P>NHS England (South Central) is responsible for commissioning and ensuring the provision of accessible, effective and appropriate SARC (Sexual Assault Referral Centre) services for victims of sexual violence.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKJ1"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Thames Valley.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The Thames Valley SARC will deliver the following services through the SARC provision:</P>
                  <P>— acute healthcare and support,</P>
                  <P>— comprehensive forensic medical examination,</P>
                  <P>— follow up services, which address the client’s medical, psychological and on-going needs,</P>
                  <P>— direct access to referral to Independent Sexual Violence Advisors (ISVAs),</P>
                  <P>— co-ordinating the smooth running of the SARC services and liaising with partner organisations to ensure the profile of the service is maintained.</P>
                  <P>SARC services should provide equitable access by individually tailored care packages based and comprehensive needs assessments, with a choice of action at every stage of clinical and non-clinical care and support, forensic examination and referral to appropriate services.</P>
                  <P>Thames Valley has a population of 2 340 000. The Police Force area covers the counties of Berkshire, Buckinghamshire and Oxfordshire and is a mixture of sparsely populated rural areas and densely populated urban areas.</P>
                  <P>Interested parties are invited to take part in an Invitation To Tender (ITT) process, based on the open procedure, and designed to identify the most economically advantageous tender and therefore determine the incoming provider.</P>
                  <P>Interested providers will be able to view the tender opportunity via the 'current tenders' list on in-tend.</P>
                  <P>https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/Home</P>
                  <P>Or you should be able to go directly to this particular tender opportunity by following the link below:</P>
                  <P>https://in-tendhost.co.uk/scwcsu/aspx/ProjectManage/446</P>
                  <P>In order to access the tender documentation you will need to “express an interest” and register on the system. Bidders are required to respond to the selection questionnaire &amp; ITT questions directly within In-Tend and attach any requested documents separately to the placeholders provided.</P>
                  <P>A prior information/market engagement notice was published in relation to this procurement in May 2017, seeking expressions of interest. Please note that this previous notice was an information gathering exercise rather than a call for competition in its own right. Although those who responded to that notice will be advised that this contract notice has been published, there will be no process exemptions or preferential treatment afforded to any parties who expressed an interest at that stage.</P>
                  <P>The Services are healthcare services within the meaning and scope of Annex XIV of Directive 2014/24/EU (“the Directive”) and Schedule 3 to the public contract Regulations 2015 (“the Regulations”). The tendering process will be conducted in accordance with the requirements and flexibilities provided by Articles 74 to 76 of the directive, and Regulations 74 to 76 of the regulations. The authority will run a transparent tender process, treating all bidders equally. For the avoidance of doubt, the Authority will not be bound by the regulations or the treaty on the functioning of the European Union or any other regulations or legislation except for the specific parts or circumstances that apply to the procurement of these services.</P>
                  <P>Neither the inclusion of a bidder selection stage, nor the use of any language or terms found in the Directive or Regulations, nor the description of the procedure voluntarily adopted by the authority (“Open”, “Restricted”, “Competitive Procedure with Negotiation”, “Competitive Dialogue” or any other description), nor any other indication, shall be taken to mean that the authority intends to hold itself bound by the directive or regulations, save by the provisions applicable to services coming within the scope of Annex XIV of the Directive / Schedule 3 of the Regulations. The services are healthcare services falling within Schedule 3 to the public contracts Regulations 2015 (“the Regulations”) which are not subject to the full regime of the regulations, but is instead governed by the “Light Touch Regime” contained within Chapter 3, Section 7 of the Regulations (Regulations 74 to 77).</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 143-295470</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <CONTRACT_NO>1</CONTRACT_NO>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Procurement for the provision of Sexual Assault Referral Centre Services for Thames Valley</P>
            </TITLE>
            <NO_AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <PROCUREMENT_UNSUCCESSFUL/>
            </NO_AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The Services are healthcare services within the meaning and scope of Annex XIV of Directive 2014/24/EU (“the Directive”) and Schedule 3 to the Public Contract Regulations 2015 (“the Regulations”). The tendering process will be conducted in accordance with the requirements and flexibilities provided by Articles 74 to 76 of the Directive, and Regulations 74 to 76 of the regulations. The authority will run a transparent tender process, treating all bidders equally. For the avoidance of doubt, the authority will not be bound by the regulations or the treaty on the functioning of the European Union or any other regulations or legislation except for the specific parts or circumstances that apply to the procurement of these services.</P>
               <P>Neither the inclusion of a bidder selection stage, nor the use of any language or terms found in the directive or regulations, nor the description of the procedure voluntarily adopted by the authority (“Open”, “Restricted”, “Competitive Procedure with Negotiation”, “Competitive Dialogue” or any other description), nor any other indication, shall be taken to mean that the authority intends to hold itself bound by the Directive or Regulations, save by the provisions applicable to services coming within the scope of Annex XIV of the Directive / Schedule 3 of the Regulations. The services are healthcare services falling within Schedule 3 to the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 ("the Regulations") which are not subject to the full regime of the Regulations, but is instead governed by the “Light Touch Regime” contained within Chapter 3, Section 7 of the Regulations (Regulations 74 to 77).</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>The contracting authority intends to voluntarily observe the award decision notices provisions and 10 days standstill period described in Regulation 86 of the 2015 Regulations. Unsuccessful tenderers will receive scores and reasons for the decision, including the characteristics and relative advantages of the winning bid and the reasons why the tenderer /application was unsuccessful. Deadline for lodging of appeals should be in accordance with Regulation 87 and Regulation 91 of the 2015 Regulations.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-06</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F21_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
