<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="141541-2018" EDITION="2018064"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-139567-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180614</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>64</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180331</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 064-141541</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141541-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="KZ"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="38000000">Laboratory, optical and precision equipments (excl. glasses)</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="38421110">Flowmeters</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="42131140">Pressure-reducing, control, check or safety valves</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="42961200">Scada or equivalent system</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="44163100">Pipes</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45232150">Works related to water-distribution pipelines</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45252120">Water-treatment plant construction work</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180327</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180614 15:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="3">Submission for one or more lots</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>BR505</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Kasakhstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - Renovering af vandbehandlingsplan og pumpestation til første løft</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Kasachstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - Sanierung der Wasseraufbereitungsanlage und der ersten Schöpfwerkpumpe</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Kazakhstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plan and First Lift Pumping Station</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Kazajistán</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Rehabilitación de planta de tratamiento de agua y primera estación de bombeo</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Kazakstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Vedenpuhdistamon ja ensivaiheen nostopumppausaseman kunnostustyöt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Kazakhstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Réhabilitation d’une installation de traitement des eaux et de la station de pompage principale</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Καζαχστάν</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - Αποκατάσταση σχεδίου επεξεργασίας νερού και πρώτου αντλιοστασίου</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Kazakstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - Riabilitazione del piano di trattamento delle acque e stazione di pompaggio di primo sollevamento</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Kazachstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - Renovatie van de waterbehandelingsinstallatie en het eerste pompstation</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Cazaquistão</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Reabilitação da instalação de tratamento de água e estação de bombagem elevatória principal</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Kazakstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Upprustning av planen avseende vattenrening och första lyftpumpstationen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Kazachstán</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Rekonstrukce úpravny vody a první přečerpávací stanice</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Kasahstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Veetöötlemisjaama ja esimese survekõrguse pumbajaama ümberehitamine</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Kazahsztán</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Vízkezelő üzem és elsőemeléses szivattyúállomás felújítása</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Kazachstanas</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - Vandens valymo plano atkūrimas ir pirmoji siurblinė</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Kazahstāna</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - Ūdens attīrīšanas iekārtas un pirmās sūkņu stacijas atjaunošana</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Kazakistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - Riabilitazzjoni ta' Pjan għat-Trattament tal-Ilma u l-Ewwel Stazzjon tal-Ippumpjar bil-Lift</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Kazachstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Remont oczyszczalni ścieków i pierwszej przepompowni</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Kazachstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Obnova čistiarne odpadových vôd a 1. čerpacej stanice</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Kazahstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Obnova čistilne naprave za vodo in črpalne postaje za prvi dvig</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Chasacstáin, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Athshlánú Phlean Cóireála Uisce agus Céadstáisiún Ardaithe Caidéalúcháin </TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Казахстан</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - Рехабилитация на пречиствателна станция за вода и първа подемна помпена станция</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Kazahstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Reabilitatea instalației de tratare a apelor și a stației de pompare First Lift</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Kazahstan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Sanacija plana za obradu vode i prve crpne stanice</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - Renovering af vandbehandlingsplan og pumpestation til første løft (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - Sanierung der Wasseraufbereitungsanlage und der ersten Schöpfwerkpumpe (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plan and First Lift Pumping Station (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Rehabilitación de planta de tratamiento de agua y primera estación de bombeo (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Vedenpuhdistamon ja ensivaiheen nostopumppausaseman kunnostustyöt (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Réhabilitation d’une installation de traitement des eaux et de la station de pompage principale (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - Αποκατάσταση σχεδίου επεξεργασίας νερού και πρώτου αντλιοστασίου (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - Riabilitazione del piano di trattamento delle acque e stazione di pompaggio di primo sollevamento (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - Renovatie van de waterbehandelingsinstallatie en het eerste pompstation (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Reabilitação da instalação de tratamento de água e estação de bombagem elevatória principal (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Upprustning av planen avseende vattenrening och första lyftpumpstationen (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Rekonstrukce úpravny vody a první přečerpávací stanice (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Veetöötlemisjaama ja esimese survekõrguse pumbajaama ümberehitamine (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Vízkezelő üzem és elsőemeléses szivattyúállomás felújítása (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - Vandens valymo plano atkūrimas ir pirmoji siurblinė (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - Ūdens attīrīšanas iekārtas un pirmās sūkņu stacijas atjaunošana (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - Riabilitazzjoni ta' Pjan għat-Trattament tal-Ilma u l-Ewwel Stazzjon tal-Ippumpjar bil-Lift (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Remont oczyszczalni ścieków i pierwszej przepompowni (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Obnova čistiarne odpadových vôd a 1. čerpacej stanice (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Obnova čistilne naprave za vodo in črpalne postaje za prvi dvig (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Athshlánú Phlean Cóireála Uisce agus Céadstáisiún Ardaithe Caidéalúcháin  (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - Рехабилитация на пречиствателна станция за вода и първа подемна помпена станция (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Reabilitatea instalației de tratare a apelor și a stației de pompare First Lift (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Sanacija plana za obradu vode i prve crpne stanice (KZ-Petropavlovsk)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9037-IFT-46955</P><P>Project name: Petropavlovsk Water</P><P>Country: Kazakhstan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 46955</P><P>Funding source: EBRD, Government of Kazakhstan</P><P>Type of contract: Supply and Installation</P><P>Type of notice: Project goods, works and services</P><P>Issue date: 27.3.2018</P><P>Closing date: 14.6.2018 at 15:00 Petropavlovsk (local time)</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was published on the EBRD website, Procurement Notices (www.ebrd.com) on 8.9.2016 and updated on 25.9.2017.</P><P>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su” (the Employer), has received a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of Petropavlovsk Water Project.</P><P>The Employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contracts to be funded from the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Lot 1: Rehabilitation of 1st Lift Pumping Station (PS1);</P><P>Lot 2: Rehabilitation of Water Treatment Plant (WTP).</P><P>The Contract comprises rehabilitation of existing PS1 and WTP Treatment Block nº 2 of the capacity of 50 000 m3/day including replacement of all mechanical and electrical equipment and refurbishment of civil structures. It is intended that PS1 would be equipped with new screens, submersible pumps with variable speed drives and new transformers. Rehabilitation of WTP covers rehabilitation of clarifiers, filters, filters backwash system including backwash reservoir and pumping station, chemical plant and refurbishment of treatment block building. The Contractor will be responsible for design and construction of the works. The anticipated time for completion for both lots is 365 days.</P><P>Tenders are invited for one or more lots. Each lot must be priced separately. Tenders for more than one lot may offer discounts and such discounts will be considered in the comparison of tenders.</P><P>The tenderers will be post qualified and the tenderer shall meet the requirements contained in the tender documents. The following are key minimum criteria:</P><P>a) average annual turnover as a contractor over the last 5 years not less than 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>b) access to, or has available, liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means sufficient to meet the construction cash flow for the contract, estimated as not less than 420 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1, 225 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2 and 645 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both lots;</P><P>c) the Tenderer shall have experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last five (5) years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least nine (9) months in each year;</P><P>d) the Tenderer shall have experience in participation as contractor or management contractor in at least two (2) contracts within the last five (5) years, each with a value of at least 1 400 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 1; 2 500 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for Lot 2; and 3 900 000 EUR equivalent when submitting a tender for both Lot 1 and Lot 2, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed Works;</P><P>e) the Tenderer, partner of JVCA or their sub-contractor for the design shall demonstrate successful experience in design of the Works of a nature and complexity comparable to the proposed contract;</P><P>f) the Tenderer should have or obtain prior to the Contract award all licenses to execute the Works on the territory of the Republic of Kazakhstan;</P><P>g) the Tenderer shall have quality assurance, environmental management and/or occupational health and safety management systems certified for compliance with ISO 9001, ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001 standards or shall submit his quality assurance / environmental management plans with the tender, to demonstrate the quality assurance procedures that would be applied during the Contract. These procedures in general should follow provisions of the above standards.</P><P>In the case of joint ventures, the lead partner shall meet not less than 60% and junior partners not less than 40% of all the qualifying criteria for general experience and financial position above.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from all countries. The proceeds of the Bank’s loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained upon request directed to the Employer at the address given below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 72 000 Kazakhstan tenge or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Payment of the fee shall be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>JSC “ALFA-BANK”</P><P>KZ 639470398990193912</P><P>KBE 17</P><P>BIN 031140004905</P><P>BIC HSBKKZKX</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier, however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the nonrefundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A 2 stage tender procedure will be adopted and will proceed as follows:</P><P>(a) the First Stage tender will consist of a technical proposal only, without any reference to prices, and a list of any deviations to the technical and commercial conditions set forth in the tender documents or any alternative technical solutions a tenderer wishes to offer, and a justification therefor, provided always that such deviations or alternative solutions do not change the basic objectives of the project. Following evaluation by the Employer of the First Stage tenders, the Employer will invite each tenderer who meets the qualification criteria and who has submitted a technically responsive tender to a clarification meeting. The proposals of all such tenderers will be reviewed at the meeting and all required amendments, additions, deletions and other adjustments will be noted and recorded in a Memorandum. Only qualified tenderers submitting a technically responsive and acceptable First Stage tender will be invited to submit a Second Stage tender.</P><P>(b) the Second Stage tender will consist of an updated technical tender incorporating all changes required by the Employer as recorded in the Memorandum to the clarification meeting or as necessary to reflect any amendments to the tender documents issued subsequent to submission of the First Stage tender; and the commercial tender.</P><P>First Stage tenders must be delivered to the address below on or before 15:00 (Local time) 14.6.2018 at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>All Second Stage tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security 13 300 000 KZT for Lot 1 and 7 200 000 KZT for Lot 2 or its equivalent in a convertible currency, and must be delivered to the address below on or before the time and date of the submission deadline specified in the Letter of Invitation to submit Second Stage tenders, at which time they will be opened in the presence of the tenderers’ representatives who wish to attend.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Yerzhan Tezekbaev</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>LLP “Kyzylzhar Su”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: 2 Kirovskiy Proyezd, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Petropavlovsk</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, the Republic of KAZAKHSTAN, Telephone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</PHONE><BLK_BTX>, Fax: </BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>+7 (7152) 61 82 17</BLK_BTX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>petropavlovsk.piu@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>