<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="141519-2018"
            EDITION="2018064">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-139671-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180525</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>64</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180331</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 064-141519</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:141519-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="73110000">Research services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="00">Not specified / Other</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="LU">LUXEMBOURG</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <REF_NOTICE>
            <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 057-125183</NO_DOC_OJS>
         </REF_NOTICE>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180327</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180525</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="2">Additional information</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="H">Health</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>AGC14</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>AG</INITIATOR>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Luxembourg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Udbudsprocedure nr. Chafea/2017/Health/01 vedrørende EU-dimensionen inden for forebyggelse af alkoholrelaterede skader som opfølgning på den standardiserede, europæiske alkoholundersøgelse (SEAS) og støtte til medlemsstaterne</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ausschreibung Nr. Chafea/2017/Health/01 bezüglich der Dimension der EU, Schäden in Verbindung mit Alkohol zu verhindern, die Standardisierte europäische Alkoholerhebung (SEAS) zu betreuen und die Mitgliedsstaaten zu unterstützen.</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Luxembourg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Call for tender no Chafea/2017/Health/01 concerning the EU dimension to prevent alcohol related harm, to follow-up the Standardised European Alcohol Survey (SEAS) and to support Member States</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Luxemburgo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxemburgo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Convocatoria de licitación n.º Chafea/2017/Health/01, relativa a la dimensión de la Unión Europea para prevenir los daños relacionados con el alcohol, hacer un seguimiento de la Encuesta Europea sobre Alcoholización (SEAS) y dar soporte a los Estados miembros</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tarjouspyyntö Chafea/2017/Health/01 – EU:n ulottuvuus alkoholiin liittyvien haittojen ehkäisemiseksi, standardoidun eurooppalaisen alkoholitutkimuksen (Standardised European Alcohol Survey, SEAS) jatkon varmistamiseksi ja jäsenvaltioiden tukemiseksi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Luxembourg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Appel d’offres no Chafea/2017/Health/01 concernant la dimension européenne de la prévention des dommages causés par l’alcool, pour assurer le suivi de l’Étude européenne normalisée sur l’alcool (SEAS) et apporter un soutien aux Etat-membres</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Λουξεμβούργο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Λουξεμβούργο</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Πρόσκληση υποβολής προσφορών αριθ. Chafea/2017/Health/01 σχετικά με τη διάσταση της ΕΕ για την πρόληψη των βλαβών που προκαλούνται από την κατανάλωση αλκοόλ, την παρακολούθηση της πρότυπης ευρωπαϊκής έρευνας για το αλκοόλ (SEAS) και την υποστήριξη των κρατών μελών</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Lussemburgo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Lussemburgo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Bando di gara no Chafea/2017/Health/01 riguardante la dimensione europea sulla prevenzione dei danni derivanti dall’alcol, dare seguito all’indagine europea standardizzata sull'alcool (SEAS) e sostenere gli Stati membri</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Oproep tot inschrijving nr. Chafea/2017/Health/01 met betrekking tot de EU-dimensie om de schadelijke gevolgen van alcohol te voorkomen, om het gestandaardiseerd Europees alcoholonderzoek (Standardised European Alcohol Survey - SEAS) op te volgen en om de lidstaten te ondersteunen.</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Luxemburgo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxemburgo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Anúncio para concurso nº Chafea/2017/Health/01 no que respeita à dimensão da UE na prevenção de danos relacionados com o álcool, para acompanhamento do Estudo Europeu Normalizado sobre o Álcool (SEAS) e apoio aos Estados-Membros</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Anbudsinfordran nr Chafea/2017/Health/01 avseende EU-dimensionen rörande förebyggande av alkoholrelaterade skador, att följa upp den standardiserade europeiska alkohol-bevakningen och att bistå medlemsstater</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Lucembursko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Lucemburk</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Výzva k podání nabídek č. Chafea/2017/Health/01, týkající se rozsahu EU v rámci prevence škod souvisejících s alkoholem, pokračování s evropským standardizovaným výzkumem o alkoholu a podpora členských států</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pakkumiskutse nr Chafea/2017/Health/01, mis käsitleb ELi mõõdet alkoholist põhjustatud kahjude ennetamisel, standardiseeritud Euroopa alkoholiuuringu (Standardised European Alcohol Survey, SEAS) järeluuringu läbiviimisel ja liikmesriikide toetamisel</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Chafea/2017/Health/01 sz. ajánlati felhívás az alkoholfogyasztással kapcsolatos ártalmak megelőzésének, az alkoholra irányuló standardizált felmérés (Standardised European Alkohol Survey - (SEAS)) nyomon követésének és a tagállamoknak nyújtott támogatás uniós dimenziójára vonatkozóan</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Liuksemburgas</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Liuksemburgas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Konkursas Nr. Chafea/2017/Health/01 dėl ES užmojo užkirsti kelią alkoholio daromai žalai, plėtoti Standartizuotą Europos alkoholio tyrimą (SEAS) ir remti valstybes nares</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Luksemburga</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luksemburga</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Uzaicinājums uz konkursu Chafea/2017/Health/01 saistībā ar ES dimensiju novērst alkohola radīto kaitējumu, pārraudzīt Standartizēto Eiropas alkohola apsekojumu (SEAS) un atbalstīt dalībvalstis</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>il-Lussemburgu</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Lussemburgu</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sejħa għall-offerti Nru Chafea/2017/Health/01 dwar id-dimensjoni tal-UE għall-prevenzjoni ta' ħsara relatata mal-alkoħol, bħala segwitu għas-Servej Standardizzat Ewropew dwar l-Alkoħol (SEAS) u bħala appoġġ għall-Istati Membri</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luksemburg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zaproszenie do składania ofert nr Chafea/ 2017/Health/01 dotyczące pomocy na poziomie UE w zapobieganiu szkodom powodowanym przez alkohol, w działaniach następczych w związku ze znormalizowanym europejskim badaniem ankietowym nad alkoholem (SEAS) i we wspieraniu państw członkowskich</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Luxembursko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Verejná výzva na predkladanie ponúk č. Chafea/2017/Health/01 týkajúca sa rozmeru EÚ s cieľom zabrániť škodám súvisiacim s požívaním alkoholu, nadviazať na Európsky štandardizovaný prieskum o alkohole (SEAS – Standardised European Alcohol Survey) a podporiť členské štáty</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Javni razpis št. Chafea/2017/Health/01 o razsežnosti EU za preprečevanje škode zaradi uživanja alkohola, spremljanje standardizirane evropske raziskave o alkoholu (SEAS) ter podporo državam članicam</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Lucsamburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Lucsamburg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Glao ar thairiscintí uimh Chafea/2017/Health/01 maidir le gné an AE chun díobháil ón alcól a chosc, chun leanúint ar aghaidh ón Suirbhé Caighdeánaithe Eorpach um Alcól (SEAS) agus chun tacú leis na Ballstáit</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Люксембург</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Люксембург</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Покана за участие в търг № Chafea/2017/Health/01 относно измерението на ЕС за предотвратяване на вредите от употребата на алкохол с цел предприемане на последващи действия в отговор на стандартизираното европейско проучване относно алкохола (SEAS) и подпомагане на държавите членки</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Licitația nr. Chafea/2017/Health/01 privind dimensiunea UE pentru prevenirea efectelor nocive ale alcoolului, urmărirea Sondajului European Standardizat privind Alcoolul (SEAS) și sprijinirea Statelor Membre</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Poziv na nadmetanje br. Chafea/2017/Health/01 koje se odnosi na dimenziju EU-a za sprečavanje štetnih posljedica alkohola, za praćenje standardiziranog europskog istraživanja o alkoholu (Standardised European Alcohol Survey – SEAS) i podršku državama članicama</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="DA">Forvaltningsorganet for Forbrugere, Sundhed, Landbrug og Fødevarer (CHAFEA), Health and Food Safety Unit, der handler ud fra de beføjelser, som det har fået pålagt af Kommissionen</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="DE">Exekutivagentur für Verbraucher, Gesundheit, Landwirtschaft und Lebensmittel (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, die im Rahmen der ihr seitens der Kommission übertragenen Befugnisse handelt</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Consumers, Health, Agriculture and Food Executive Agency (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, acting under power delegated to it by the Commission</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="ES">Agencia Ejecutiva de Consumidores, Salud, Agricultura y Alimentación (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, actuando en virtud de la facultad que le delegó la Comisión</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="FI">Kuluttaja-, terveys-, maatalous- ja elintarvikeasioiden toimeenpanovirasto (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, joka toimii komission sille antaman toimivallan nojalla</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="FR">Agence exécutive pour les consommateurs, la santé, l’agriculture et l’alimentation (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, agissant par délégation de pouvoir de la Commission</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="EL">Εκτελεστικός Οργανισμός για τους Καταναλωτές, την Υγεία, τη Γεωργία και τα Τρόφιμα (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, ενεργώντας υπό την εξουσία που του έχει ανατεθεί από την Επιτροπή</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="IT">Agenzia esecutiva per i consumatori, la salute, l’agricoltura e la sicurezza alimentare (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, che agisce in virtù dei poteri conferiti dalla Commissione</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="NL">Uitvoerend Agentschap voor consumenten, gezondheid, landbouw en voeding (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, acting under power delegated to it by the Commission</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="PT">Agência de Execução para os Consumidores, a Saúde, a Agricultura e a Alimentação (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, atuando sob o poder delegado à mesma pela Comissão</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="SV">Genomförandeorganet för konsument-, hälso-, jordbruks- och livsmedelsfrågor (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, som verkar under befogenhet som har delegerats till den av kommissionen</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="CS">Výkonná agentura pro spotřebitele, zdraví, zemědělství a potraviny (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, jednající z pravomoci jí svěřené Komisí</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="ET">Tarbija-, Tervise-, Põllumajandus- ja Toiduküsimuste Rakendusamet (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, kes tegutseb sellele komisjoni delegeeritud volituste piires</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="HU">Fogyasztó-, Egészség-, Élelmiszerügyi és Mezőgazdasági Végrehajtó Ügynökség (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, amely a Bizottság megbízásából jár el</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="LT">Vartotojų, sveikatos, žemės ūkio ir maisto programų vykdomoji agentūra (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, veikianti pagal Komisijos jai suteiktus įgaliojimus</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="LV">Patērētāju, veselības, lauksaimniecības un pārtikas izpildaģentūra (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit (darbojas saskaņā ar Komisijas piešķirtajām pilnvarām)</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="MT">L-Aġenzija Eżekuttiva għall-Konsumatur, is-Saħħa, l-Agrikoltura u l-Ikel (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, acting under power delegated to it by the Commission</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="PL">Agencja Wykonawcza ds. Konsumentów, Zdrowia, Rolnictwa i Żywności (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, acting under power delegated to it by the Commission</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="SK">Výkonná agentúra pre spotrebiteľov, zdravie, poľnohospodárstvo a potraviny (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, konajúc na základe právomoci, ktorú na ňu deleguje Komisia</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="SL">Izvajalska agencija za potrošnike, zdravje, kmetijstvo in hrano (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, ki deluje na podlagi pooblastila Komisije</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="GA">An Ghníomhaireacht Feidhmiúcháin um Thomhaltóirí, Sláinte, Talmhaíocht agus Bia (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, ag feidhmiú faoin gcumhacht arna tarmligean di ag an gCoimisiún</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="BG">Изпълнителна агенция за потребителите, здравеопазването, селското стопанство и храните (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, действаща по силата на делегираното ѝ от Комисията правомощие</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="RO">Agenția Executivă pentru Consumatori, Sănătate, Agricultură și Alimente (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, acționând în temeiul competențelor delegate acesteia de către Comisie</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="HR">Izvršna agencija za potrošače, zdravlje, poljoprivredu i hranu (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, djeluje temeljem ovlasti koju joj je dodijelila Komisija</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="DA">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Forvaltningsorganet for Forbrugere, Sundhed, Landbrug og Fødevarer (CHAFEA), Health and Food Safety Unit, der handler ud fra de beføjelser, som det har fået pålagt af Kommissionen</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Udbudsprocedure nr. Chafea/2017/Health/01 vedrørende EU-dimensionen inden for forebyggelse af alkoholrelaterede skader som opfølgning på den standardiserede, europæiske alkoholundersøgelse (SEAS) og støtte til medlemsstaterne</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Med henblik på at mindske alkoholrelaterede skader i EU har CHAFEA brug for regelmæssige tjenesteydelser for at støtte EU-medlemsstaternes handlinger på området. Dette udbud har til formål at følge op på den standardiserede, europæiske alkoholundersøgelse i 2018/2019 for at støtte medlemsstaternes kapacitetsopbygning på området for alkoholpolitik og forberede en pilotgennemførelse af kort alkoholintervention (ABI — Alcohol Brief Interventions).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Betingelser for åbning af bud</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="DE">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Exekutivagentur für Verbraucher, Gesundheit, Landwirtschaft und Lebensmittel (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, die im Rahmen der ihr seitens der Kommission übertragenen Befugnisse handelt</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Ausschreibung Nr. Chafea/2017/Health/01 bezüglich der Dimension der EU, Schäden in Verbindung mit Alkohol zu verhindern, die Standardisierte europäische Alkoholerhebung (SEAS) zu betreuen und die Mitgliedsstaaten zu unterstützen.</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Um die Schäden in Verbindung mit Alkohol innerhalb der EU zu reduzieren, muss Chafea regelmäßige Dienstleistungen zur Unterstützung der Maßnahmen der Mitgliedsstaaten in diesem Bereich erhalten. Diese Dienstleistung ruft dazu auf, die Standardisierte Europäische Alkoholerhebung in den Jahren 2018/2019 nachzubereiten, den Auf- und Ausbau der Leistungsfähigkeit der Mitgliedsstaaten im Bereich der Alkoholpolitik zu unterstützen und eine Pilot-Umsetzung der Akoholkurzinterventionen (Alcohol Brief Interventions (ABI)) vorzubereiten.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Bedingungen für die Öffnung der Angebote</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F14" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Consumers, Health, Agriculture and Food Executive Agency (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, acting under power delegated to it by the Commission</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Call for tender n<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> Chafea/2017/Health/01 concerning the EU dimension to prevent alcohol related harm, to follow-up the Standardised European Alcohol Survey (SEAS) and to support Member States</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>In order to reduce alcohol-related harm in the EU, Chafea needs to obtain regular services to support EU Member States actions in this field. This service calls to follow-up of the standardised European Alcohol Survey in 2018 /2019, to support the member states' capacity building in the area of alcohol policy, and to prepare a pilot implementation of alcohol brief interventions (ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Conditions for opening of tenders</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="ES">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agencia Ejecutiva de Consumidores, Salud, Agricultura y Alimentación (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, actuando en virtud de la facultad que le delegó la Comisión</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Convocatoria de licitación n.º Chafea/2017/Health/01, relativa a la dimensión de la Unión Europea para prevenir los daños relacionados con el alcohol, hacer un seguimiento de la Encuesta Europea sobre Alcoholización (SEAS) y dar soporte a los Estados miembros</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Para reducir los daños relacionados con el alcohol en la UE, Chafea requiere la prestación de servicios regulares que den soporte a las acciones de los Estados miembros de la Unión Europea en este ámbito. Este servicio pretende llevar a cabo un seguimiento de la Encuesta Europea de Alcohol Estandarizada en 2018-2019, a fin de dar soporte en el desarrollo de capacidades de los Estados miembros en el ámbito relativo a las políticas sobre alcohol, así como para preparar la ejecución piloto de un programa de Intervenciones Breves contra el Alcoholismo (ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Condiciones para la apertura de las ofertas</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="FI">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Kuluttaja-, terveys-, maatalous- ja elintarvikeasioiden toimeenpanovirasto (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, joka toimii komission sille antaman toimivallan nojalla</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Tarjouspyyntö Chafea/2017/Health/01 – EU:n ulottuvuus alkoholiin liittyvien haittojen ehkäisemiseksi, standardoidun eurooppalaisen alkoholitutkimuksen (Standardised European Alcohol Survey, SEAS) jatkon varmistamiseksi ja jäsenvaltioiden tukemiseksi</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Alkoholiin liittyvien haittojen vähentämiseksi EU:ssa kuluttaja-, terveys-, maatalous- ja elintarvikeasioiden toimeenpanovirasto tarvitsee säännöllisiä palveluja tukeakseen EU:n jäsenvaltioiden toimia tällä alalla. Tämän palvelun toteuttaminen edellyttää standardoidun eurooppalaisen alkoholitutkimuksen jatkamista 2018/2019 jäsenvaltioiden valmiuksien kehittämisen tukemiseksi alkoholipolitiikan alalla ja valmistelemaan alkoholiriippuvaisten lyhytneuvonnan (Alcohol Brief Interventions – ABI) pilottihankkeen täytäntöönpanoa.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Tarjousten avaamista koskevat ehdot</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="FR">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agence exécutive pour les consommateurs, la santé, l’agriculture et l’alimentation (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, agissant par délégation de pouvoir de la Commission</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Appel d’offres n<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> Chafea/2017/Health/01 concernant la dimension européenne de la prévention des dommages causés par l’alcool, pour assurer le suivi de l’Étude européenne normalisée sur l’alcool (SEAS) et apporter un soutien aux Etat-membres</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Afin de réduire les dommages causés par l’alcool dans l’UE, l’Agence exécutive pour les consommateurs, la santé, l’agriculture et l’alimentation a besoin d’obtenir des services régulier pour soutenir les actions des Etats-membres de l’UE dans ce domaine. Ce service demande un suivi de l’Étude européenne normalisée sur l’alcool en 2018-2019, afin de soutenir le renforcement des capacités des Etats-membres en matière de politique relative à l’alcool, et pour préparer une mise en œuvre pilote d’interventions brèves sur l’alcool (ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Modalités d'ouverture des offres</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="EL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Εκτελεστικός Οργανισμός για τους Καταναλωτές, την Υγεία, τη Γεωργία και τα Τρόφιμα (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, ενεργώντας υπό την εξουσία που του έχει ανατεθεί από την Επιτροπή</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Πρόσκληση υποβολής προσφορών αριθ. Chafea/2017/Health/01 σχετικά με τη διάσταση της ΕΕ για την πρόληψη των βλαβών που προκαλούνται από την κατανάλωση αλκοόλ, την παρακολούθηση της πρότυπης ευρωπαϊκής έρευνας για το αλκοόλ (SEAS) και την υποστήριξη των κρατών μελών</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Προκειμένου να μειωθούν οι βλάβες που προκαλούνται από την κατανάλωση αλκοόλ στην ΕΕ, ο CHAFEA πρέπει να λάβει τακτικές υπηρεσίες για να υποστηρίξει τις ενέργειες των κρατών μελών της ΕΕ στον τομέα αυτό. Η υπηρεσία αυτή ζητά την παρακολούθηση της πρότυπης ευρωπαϊκής έρευνας για το αλκοόλ το 2018/2019 για να υποστηρίξει την ανάπτυξη ικανοτήτων των κρατών μελών στον τομέα της πολιτικής για το αλκοόλ και να προετοιμάσει μια πιλοτική εφαρμογή σύντομων παρεμβάσεων για το αλκοόλ (ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Όροι αποσφράγισης των προσφορών</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="IT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agenzia esecutiva per i consumatori, la salute, l’agricoltura e la sicurezza alimentare (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, che agisce in virtù dei poteri conferiti dalla Commissione</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Bando di gara n<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> Chafea/2017/Health/01 riguardante la dimensione europea sulla prevenzione dei danni derivanti dall’alcol, dare seguito all’indagine europea standardizzata sull'alcool (SEAS) e sostenere gli Stati membri</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Al fine di ridurre i danni derivanti dall’alcol nell'UE, Chafea necessita di usufruire di servizi regolari a sostegno delle azioni degli Stati membri dell'UE in questo settore. Tale servizio richiede il follow-up dell'Indagine europea standardizzata sull'alcol nel 2018/2019, al fine di sostenere lo sviluppo delle capacità degli Stati membri nel settore della politica in materia di bevande alcoliche e preparare un'attuazione pilota di Brevi interventi nel settore degli alcolici (ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Modalità di apertura delle offerte</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="NL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Uitvoerend Agentschap voor consumenten, gezondheid, landbouw en voeding (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, acting under power delegated to it by the Commission</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Oproep tot inschrijving nr. Chafea/2017/Health/01 met betrekking tot de EU-dimensie om de schadelijke gevolgen van alcohol te voorkomen, om het gestandaardiseerd Europees alcoholonderzoek (Standardised European Alcohol Survey - SEAS) op te volgen en om de lidstaten te ondersteunen.</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Om de schadelijke gevolgen van alcohol te kunnen verminderen binnen de EU, heeft Chafea regelmatig toegang nodig tot diensten om acties van de EU-lidstaten te kunnen ondersteunen op dit gebied. Deze dienst verzoekt om opvolging van het gestandaardiseerd Europees alcoholonderzoek van 2018/2019, om ondersteuning van de capaciteitsversterking van de lidstaten rondom alcoholbeleid, en om de voorbereiding van een pilotimplementatie van kortdurende interventies inzake alcohol (Alcohol Brief Interventions - ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Omstandigheden waarin de inschrijvingen worden geopend:</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="PT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agência de Execução para os Consumidores, a Saúde, a Agricultura e a Alimentação (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, atuando sob o poder delegado à mesma pela Comissão</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Anúncio para concurso nº Chafea/2017/Health/01 no que respeita à dimensão da UE na prevenção de danos relacionados com o álcool, para acompanhamento do Estudo Europeu Normalizado sobre o Álcool (SEAS) e apoio aos Estados-Membros</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>De modo a reduzir os danos relacionados com o álcool na UE, a Chafea precisa obter serviços regulares para apoiar as ações dos Estados-Membros neste domínio. Este serviço requer o acompanhamento do Estudo Europeu Normalizado sobre o Álcool em 2018/2019, apoiar o desenvolvimento de capacidade dos Estados-Membros no domínio da política sobre o álcool e preparar um projeto de implementação das Intervenções Breves relacionadas com o Álcool.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Condições de abertura das propostas</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="SV">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Genomförandeorganet för konsument-, hälso-, jordbruks- och livsmedelsfrågor (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, som verkar under befogenhet som har delegerats till den av kommissionen</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Anbudsinfordran nr Chafea/2017/Health/01 avseende EU-dimensionen rörande förebyggande av alkoholrelaterade skador, att följa upp den standardiserade europeiska alkohol-bevakningen och att bistå medlemsstater</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>För att minska alkoholrelaterade skador i EU behöver Chafea erhålla regelbundna tjänster för att bistå EU:s medlemsstater i åtgärder inom detta område. Denna anbudsinfordran rör tjänster för att följa upp den standardiserade europeiska alkoholundersökningen 2018/2019, att bistå medlemsstaternas kapacitetsuppbyggnad inom området för alkoholpolitik och att förbereda en pilotimplementering för korta alkoholinterventioner.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Villkor för anbudsöppning</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="CS">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Výkonná agentura pro spotřebitele, zdraví, zemědělství a potraviny (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, jednající z pravomoci jí svěřené Komisí</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Výzva k podání nabídek č. Chafea/2017/Health/01, týkající se rozsahu EU v rámci prevence škod souvisejících s alkoholem, pokračování s evropským standardizovaným výzkumem o alkoholu a podpora členských států</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>V rámci snížení škod souvisejících s alkoholem v EU potřebuje agentura Chafea získat pravidelné služby na podporu členských států EU v této oblasti. Tato služba vyzývá k pokračování v evropském standardizovaném výzkumu o alkoholu v letech 2018/2019 s cílem podpořit budování kapacit členských států v oblasti politiky týkající se otázek alkoholu a přípravy pilotní realizace krátkých zásahů spojených s alkoholem (ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Podmínky pro otevírání nabídek</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="ET">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tarbija-, Tervise-, Põllumajandus- ja Toiduküsimuste Rakendusamet (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, kes tegutseb sellele komisjoni delegeeritud volituste piires</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Pakkumiskutse nr Chafea/2017/Health/01, mis käsitleb ELi mõõdet alkoholist põhjustatud kahjude ennetamisel, standardiseeritud Euroopa alkoholiuuringu (Standardised European Alcohol Survey, SEAS) järeluuringu läbiviimisel ja liikmesriikide toetamisel</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>ELis alkoholist põhjustatud kahjude vähendamiseks peab Chafea saama regulaarseid teenuseid, et toetada ELi liikmesriikide tegevusi selles valdkonnas. Kõnealune teenus kutsub üles viima 2018./2019. aastal läbi standardiseeritud Euroopa alkoholiuuringu järeluuringut, et toetada liikmesriikide suutlikkuse suurendamist alkoholipoliitika valdkonnas, ning valmistama ette alkoholi liigtarvitamisse lühisekkumiste (Alcohol Brief Interventions, ABI) katselist rakendamist.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Pakkumuste avamise tingimused</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="HU">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Fogyasztó-, Egészség-, Élelmiszerügyi és Mezőgazdasági Végrehajtó Ügynökség (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, amely a Bizottság megbízásából jár el</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Chafea/2017/Health/01 sz. ajánlati felhívás az alkoholfogyasztással kapcsolatos ártalmak megelőzésének, az alkoholra irányuló standardizált felmérés (Standardised European Alkohol Survey - (SEAS)) nyomon követésének és a tagállamoknak nyújtott támogatás uniós dimenziójára vonatkozóan</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Az alkoholfogyasztással kapcsolatos ártalmak csökkentése céljából az EU-ban a CHAFEA-nak rendszeres szolgáltatásokra van szüksége az EU-tagállamok e téren végzett tevékenységei támogatásához. Ez a szolgáltatás az alkoholra irányuló standardizált felmérés nyomon követésére 2018/2019 folyamán, a tagállamok felkészültségének fejlesztésére az alkoholpolitika terén és az alkoholfogyasztással kapcsolatos rövid időtartamú egészségügyi beavatkozások kísérleti megvalósítására irányul.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Az ajánlatok felbontásának feltételei</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="LT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Vartotojų, sveikatos, žemės ūkio ir maisto programų vykdomoji agentūra (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, veikianti pagal Komisijos jai suteiktus įgaliojimus</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Konkursas Nr. Chafea/2017/Health/01 dėl ES užmojo užkirsti kelią alkoholio daromai žalai, plėtoti Standartizuotą Europos alkoholio tyrimą (SEAS) ir remti valstybes nares</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Siekiant sumažinti alkoholio daromą žalą ES, Chafea siekia įsigyti reguliariai teikiamas paslaugas, kad remtų ES valstybių narių veiksmus šioje srityje. Šiomis paslaugomis raginama 2018 m. / 2019 m. plėtoti Standartizuotą Europos alkoholio tyrimą, remti valstybių narių gebėjimų stiprinimą alkoholio politikos formavimo srityje ir parengti bandomąjį skubių intervencijų dėl alkoholio vartojimo (ABI) vykdymą.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Vokų su pasiūlymais atplėšimo sąlygos</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="LV">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Patērētāju, veselības, lauksaimniecības un pārtikas izpildaģentūra (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit (darbojas saskaņā ar Komisijas piešķirtajām pilnvarām)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Uzaicinājums uz konkursu Chafea/2017/Health/01 saistībā ar ES dimensiju novērst alkohola radīto kaitējumu, pārraudzīt Standartizēto Eiropas alkohola apsekojumu (SEAS) un atbalstīt dalībvalstis</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Lai mazinātu alkohola radīto kaitējumu ES, Chafea nepieciešams saņemt regulārus pakalpojumus, lai atbalstītu ES dalībvalstu darbības šajā jomā. Pakalpojumu ietvaros jāpārrauga Standartizētais Eiropas alkohola apsekojums (Standardised European Alcohol Survey – SEAS) 2018./2019. gadam, jāatbalsta dalībvalstu spēju veidošana alkohola politikas jomā un jāsagatavo īslaicīgu iejaukšanās pasākumu alkohola jomā (Alcohol Brief Interventions – ABI) izmēģinājuma īstenošana.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Piedāvājumu atvēršanas nosacījumi</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="MT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>L-Aġenzija Eżekuttiva għall-Konsumatur, is-Saħħa, l-Agrikoltura u l-Ikel (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, acting under power delegated to it by the Commission</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Sejħa għall-offerti Nru Chafea/2017/Health/01 dwar id-dimensjoni tal-UE għall-prevenzjoni ta' ħsara relatata mal-alkoħol, bħala segwitu għas-Servej Standardizzat Ewropew dwar l-Alkoħol (SEAS) u bħala appoġġ għall-Istati Membri</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Sabiex titnaqqas il-ħsara relatata mal-alkoħol fl-UE, Chafea teħtieġ li tikseb servizzi regolari biex tagħti appoġġ lill-azzjonijiet tal-Istati Membri tal-UE f'dan il-qasam. Dan is-servizz jitlob segwitu għas-Servej Standardizzat Ewropew dwar l-Alkoħol fl-2018/2019, bħala appoġġ għall-bini ta' ħiliet tal-Istati Membri fil-qasam tal-politika dwar l-alkoħol, u biex titħejja implimentazzjoni pilota ta' Interventi Qosra minħabba l-Alkoħol (ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Il-kundizzjonijiet għall-ftuħ tal-offerti</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="PL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agencja Wykonawcza ds. Konsumentów, Zdrowia, Rolnictwa i Żywności (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, acting under power delegated to it by the Commission</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Zaproszenie do składania ofert nr Chafea/ 2017/Health/01 dotyczące pomocy na poziomie UE w zapobieganiu szkodom powodowanym przez alkohol, w działaniach następczych w związku ze znormalizowanym europejskim badaniem ankietowym nad alkoholem (SEAS) i we wspieraniu państw członkowskich</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>W celu ograniczenia szkodliwych skutków spożywania alkoholu w UE, CHAFEA musi pozyskać regularne usługi wspierające działania państw członkowskich UE w tej dziedzinie. W ramach tych usług należy podjąć działania następcze w związku ze znormalizowanym europejskim badaniem ankietowym nad alkoholem (Standardised European Alcohol Survey) na lata 2018/2019, aby wesprzeć budowanie zdolności państw członkowskich w dziedzinie polityki alkoholowej oraz aby przygotować pilotażowe wdrożenie interwencji dotyczących alkoholu (Alcohol Brief Interventions – ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Warunki otwarcia ofert</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="SK">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Výkonná agentúra pre spotrebiteľov, zdravie, poľnohospodárstvo a potraviny (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, konajúc na základe právomoci, ktorú na ňu deleguje Komisia</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Verejná výzva na predkladanie ponúk č. Chafea/2017/Health/01 týkajúca sa rozmeru EÚ s cieľom zabrániť škodám súvisiacim s požívaním alkoholu, nadviazať na Európsky štandardizovaný prieskum o alkohole (SEAS – Standardised European Alcohol Survey) a podporiť členské štáty</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>V záujme zníženia škôd súvisiacich s požívaním alkoholu v EÚ potrebuje Chafea získať pravidelné služby na podporu opatrení členských štátov EÚ v tejto oblasti. Táto služba si vyžaduje nadviazanie na Európsky štandardizovaný prieskum o alkohole v rokoch 2018/2019 s cieľom podporiť spôsobilosti členských štátov v oblasti politiky týkajúcej sa alkoholu a pripraviť pilotnú realizáciu krátkych zákrokov zameraných na alkohol (ABI – Alcohol Brief Interventions).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Podmienky otvárania obálok s ponukami</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="SL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Izvajalska agencija za potrošnike, zdravje, kmetijstvo in hrano (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, ki deluje na podlagi pooblastila Komisije</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Javni razpis št. Chafea/2017/Health/01 o razsežnosti EU za preprečevanje škode zaradi uživanja alkohola, spremljanje standardizirane evropske raziskave o alkoholu (SEAS) ter podporo državam članicam</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Da bi zmanjšali škodo zaradi uživanja alkohola v EU, je treba agenciji Chafea zagotoviti redne storitve, ki bodo podprle ukrepe držav članic EU na tem področju. Te storitve zajemajo spremljanje standardizirane evropske raziskave o alkoholu (Standardised European Alcohol Survey – SEAS) v letih 2018/2019, podporo pri krepitvi zmogljivosti držav članic na področju alkoholne politike ter pripravo na pilotno izvajanje kratkih intervencij za preprečevanje škodljive rabe alkohola.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Pogoji odpiranja ponudb</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="GA">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>An Ghníomhaireacht Feidhmiúcháin um Thomhaltóirí, Sláinte, Talmhaíocht agus Bia (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, ag feidhmiú faoin gcumhacht arna tarmligean di ag an gCoimisiún</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Glao ar thairiscintí uimh Chafea/2017/Health/01 maidir le gné an AE chun díobháil ón alcól a chosc, chun leanúint ar aghaidh ón Suirbhé Caighdeánaithe Eorpach um Alcól (SEAS) agus chun tacú leis na Ballstáit</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>D’fhonn an díobháil a bhaineann leis an alcól a laghdú san AE, teastaíonn ó CHAFEA seirbhísí rialta a fháil chun tacú le gníomhartha Bhallstáit an AE sa réimse sin. Glaoitear leis an tseirbhís sin mar bheart leantach don Suirbhé Caighdeánaithe Eorpach um Alcól sa bhliain 2018/2019, chun tacú le forbairt acmhainne na mballstát i réimse an bheartais alcóil, agus chun forfheidhmiú treorach na ngearr-idirghabhálacha alcóil (ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Coinníollacha maidir le tairiscintí a oscailt</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="BG">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Изпълнителна агенция за потребителите, здравеопазването, селското стопанство и храните (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, действаща по силата на делегираното ѝ от Комисията правомощие</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Покана за участие в търг № Chafea/2017/Health/01 относно измерението на ЕС за предотвратяване на вредите от употребата на алкохол с цел предприемане на последващи действия в отговор на стандартизираното европейско проучване относно алкохола (SEAS) и подпомагане на държавите членки</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>С цел намаляване на вредите от употребата на алкохол в ЕС CHAFEA се нуждае от редовни услуги в подкрепа на действията на държавите — членки на ЕС, в тази област. Тази услуга е необходима, за да се предприемат последващи действия в отговор на стандартизираното европейско проучване относно алкохола през 2018/2019 г., за да се подпомогне изграждането на капацитет на държавите членки в областта на политиката за алкохола и за да се подготвят условията за пилотното изпълнение на кратки интервенции в областта на употребата на алкохол (ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Условия за отваряне на офертите</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="RO">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Agenția Executivă pentru Consumatori, Sănătate, Agricultură și Alimente (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, acționând în temeiul competențelor delegate acesteia de către Comisie</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Licitația nr. Chafea/2017/Health/01 privind dimensiunea UE pentru prevenirea efectelor nocive ale alcoolului, urmărirea Sondajului European Standardizat privind Alcoolul (SEAS) și sprijinirea Statelor Membre</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Pentru a reduce efectele nocive ale alcoolului în UE, Chafea trebuie să obțină servicii regulate pentru a sprijini acțiunile statelor membre ale UE în acest domeniu. Acest serviciu vizează urmărirea Sondajului European Standardizat privind Alcoolul în 2018/2019, pentru a sprijini consolidarea capacităților statelor membre în domeniul politicii privind alcoolul și pentru a pregăti o implementare pilot a Intervențiilor scurte cu privire la alcool (ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Condiții de deschidere a ofertelor</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
      <F14_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F14" LG="HR">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Izvršna agencija za potrošače, zdravlje, poljoprivredu i hranu (Chafea), Health and Food Safety Unit, djeluje temeljem ovlasti koju joj je dodijelila Komisija</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2920</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Georgios Margetidis</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+352 4301-37228</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chafea-hp-tender@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="LU"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://ec.europa.eu/chafea/</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Poziv na nadmetanje br. Chafea/2017/Health/01 koje se odnosi na dimenziju EU-a za sprečavanje štetnih posljedica alkohola, za praćenje standardiziranog europskog istraživanja o alkoholu (Standardised European Alcohol Survey – SEAS) i podršku državama članicama</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Chafea/2017/Health/01</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73110000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Kako bi se smanjile štetne posljedice alkohola u EU-u, Chafea treba nabaviti redovite usluge za potporu aktivnostima država članica EU-a u ovom području. Ova služba poziva na praćenje standardiziranog europskog istraživanja o alkoholu 2018. i 2019. godine, kako bi se podržalo jačanje kapaciteta država članica u području politike alkohola i pripremila pilotska provedba kratkih intervencija u slučaju alkoholiziranosti (Alcohol Brief Interventions – ABI).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2018/S 057-125183</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
         <CHANGES>
            <CHANGE PUBLICATION="YES">
               <WHERE>
                  <SECTION>IV.2.7</SECTION>
                  <LABEL>Uvjeti za otvaranje ponuda</LABEL>
               </WHERE>
               <OLD_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-05-30</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </OLD_VALUE>
               <NEW_VALUE>
                  <DATE>2018-06-05</DATE>
                  <TIME>09:30</TIME>
               </NEW_VALUE>
            </CHANGE>
         </CHANGES>
      </F14_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
