<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="143591-2018" EDITION="2018064"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-146250-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180504</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>64</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180331</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 064-143591</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143591-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>https://www.mod.uk/DIO</IA_URL_GENERAL><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45235000">Construction work for airfields, runways and manoeuvring surfaces</ORIGINAL_CPV><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKM62">Inverness &amp; Nairn and Moray, Badenoch &amp; Strathspey</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS><VALUES_LIST><VALUES TYPE="GLOBAL"><RANGE_VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="GBP">50 000 000</VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="GBP">100 000 000</VALUE></RANGE_VALUE></VALUES></VALUES_LIST><REF_NOTICE><NO_DOC_OJS>2016/S 200-361451</NO_DOC_OJS></REF_NOTICE></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180329</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180504 16:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>01117</HEADING><DIRECTIVE VALUE="2009/81/EC"/></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Глазгоу</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Строителни и монтажни работи на самолетни писти, писти за излитане и кацане, стоянки за самолети</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Stavební úpravy přistávacích ploch, rozjezdových drah a manévrovacích ploch</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Arbejder i forbindelse med anlæg af start- og landingsbaner samt manøvrepladser</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bauarbeiten für Flugplätze, Start- und Landebahnen und Rollfelder</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Γλασκώβη</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Γενικές κατασκευαστικές εργασίες για αεροδρόμια, διαδρόμους προσγείωσης-απογείωσης και επιφάνειες ελιγμών</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Construction work for airfields, runways and manoeuvring surfaces</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Trabajos de construcción de aeródromos, pistas de despegue y aterrizaje y superficies de maniobra</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lennuväljade, stardi- ja maandumisradade ja manööverpindade ehitustöö</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lentokenttien, kiitoratojen ja liikennealueiden rakennustyöt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Travaux de construction de terrains d'aviation, de pistes d'envol et d'atterrissage et d'aires de manœuvre</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glaschú</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Construction work for airfields, runways and manoeuvring surfaces</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Građevinski radovi na uzletištima, uzletno-sletnim stazama i manevarskim površinama</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Repülőterek, futópályák és manőverezési felület építése</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lavori di costruzione per aerodromi, piste e superfici di manovra di campi d'aviazione</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Aerodromų, kilimo ir tūpimo takų bei manevravimo zonos statybos darbai</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glāsgova</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lidlauku, skrejceļu un manevrēšanas laukumu būvniecība</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Xogħol tal-kostruzzjoni għall-ajruporti, r-runways u l-uċuħ ta’ l-immanuvrar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bouwwerkzaamheden voor luchthavens, start- en landingsbanen en manoeuvreerplatforms</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Roboty budowlane w zakresie lotnisk, pasów startowych i placów manewrowych</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Construção de aeródromos, pistas de aeroportos e áreas de manobra</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lucrări de construcţii de aerodromuri, piste de decolare şi de aterizare şi suprafeţe de manevrare</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Stavebné práce na stavbe letísk, vzletových a pristávacích dráh a prevádzkových plôch</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Gradbena dela na letališčih, vzletno-pristajalnih stezah in površinah za manevriranje letal</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anläggningsarbete för flygfält, startbanor och manöverområde</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Defence Infrastructure Organisation (DIO)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><CONTRACT_DEFENCE CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="17" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE CTYPE="WORKS"><CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Defence Infrastructure Organisation (DIO)</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Room 1202-1221, Kentigern House, 65 Brown Street</ADDRESS><TOWN>Glasgow</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>G2 8EX</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><CONTACT_POINT>Karen Carter / Jessica Lucas — Commercial Team</CONTACT_POINT><ATTENTION>Karen Carter / Jessica Lucas - Commercial Team</ATTENTION><PHONE>+44 1412242674</PHONE><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>karen.carter676@mod.gov.uk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><URL_GENERAL>https://www.mod.uk/DIO</URL_GENERAL></INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><FURTHER_INFORMATION><IDEM/></FURTHER_INFORMATION><SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><IDEM/></SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO><IDEM/></TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO></NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY VALUE="MINISTRY"/><TYPE_OF_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF_NO/></PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><TITLE_CONTRACT><P>RAF Lossiemouth Development Programme (LDP): Aircraft/Airfield Operating Surfaces (AOS)</P></TITLE_CONTRACT><TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><TYPE_CONTRACT VALUE="WORKS"/><TYPE_WORK_CONTRACT><DESIGN_EXECUTION/></TYPE_WORK_CONTRACT></TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><LOCATION_NUTS><LOCATION><P>Inverness &amp; Nairn and Moray, Badenoch and Strathspey.</P></LOCATION><n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM62"/></LOCATION_NUTS><SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><P>Construction work for airfields, runways and manoeuvring surfaces. The LDP AOS infrastructure requirement effectively encapsulates the refurbishment of asphalt and concrete pavement and visual aids, equipment and associated infrastructure to the Taxiways, Aircraft Hard-Standing and Aircraft Servicing Platforms (Aprons/Dispersals), Main (05-23) and Secondary (10-28) Runways at RAF Lossiemouth to deliver suitable and compliant AOS infrastructure to enable existing defence capability and ensure its operational readiness to accommodate the introduction of the Maritime Patrol Aircraft (MPA) Fleet in 2020 and capability growth in the Typhoon Force, from 2019, in support of UK Defence initiatives.</P><P>Following Government and Industry best practice the Form of Contract will be an NEC, Engineering and Construction Contract (ECC) with Secondary Options and 'Z' Clause amendments. The proposed Pricing arrangement will be Main Option C — Target Cost Incentive Fee(TCIF) / Maximum Price Target Cost (MPTC) with an Activity Schedule.</P></SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><CPV><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="45235000"/></CPV_MAIN></CPV><SUBCONTRACTING><INDICATE_ANY_SHARE VALUE="YES"/><INDICATE_ANY_CHANGE VALUE="YES"/><SUBCONTRACT_AWARD_PART VALUE="NO"/><IDENTIFY_SUBCONTRACT VALUE="NO"/></SUBCONTRACTING><F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><DIV_INTO_LOT_NO/></F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><ACCEPTED_VARIANTS VALUE="YES"/></DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><QUANTITY_SCOPE><NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><TOTAL_QUANTITY_OR_SCOPE><P>The RAF Lossiemouth Development Programme (LDP) shapes the infrastructure requirement to deliver the work-strands announced in the Strategic Defence and Security Review (SDSR) 2015. SDSR 2015, confirmed an increase in the numbers and types of aircraft which will based at RAF Lossiemouth; the introduction into service of the Maritime Patrol Aircraft (MPA) Fleet and the generation of an additional Typhoon Front Line Squadron (FLS).</P><P>RAF Lossiemouth is a main operating base (MOB) for the Northern Typhoon assets, including the Quick Reaction Alert (Interceptor) North (QRA(I)N), which forms part of the National Defence Commitment. RAF Lossiemouth is a strategic air station providing interception capabilities for the immediate defence of UK airspace and from which operations are mounted globally. The infrastructure currently provides a base for operational squadrons flying, UK and International training exercises, operational deployments, and visiting aircraft together with an RAF Force Protection (FP) HQ, Regiment (Regt) Field Sqn and a Royal Auxiliary Air Force (RAuxAF) Regt. In addition to the airfield, the Station comprises a large number of operational, technical and domestic facilities together with supporting infrastructure. The site covers circa 4,6 km<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> ; the landscape is predominately coastal and flat, with the ground conditions generally comprising silty, sandy subsoils.</P><P>The Design and Construction works to be included within the scope of the LDP AOS requirement will be compliant with Military Aviation Authority (MAA) Regulatory Articles and Manual of Aerodrome Design and Safeguarding (MADS). The infrastructure works comprise, but are not limited to the following non-exhaustive list:</P><P>a) the refurbishment of pavement and visual aids, equipment and associated infrastructure to the Main (05-23) and Secondary (10-28) Runways to the requisite pavement classification number (PCN) level for continuous use;</P><P>b) removal and disposal of existing asphalt surface of the Main (05-23) and Secondary (10-28) Runways;</P><P>c) provision of compliant Taxiways, Aircraft Hard-Standing and Aircraft Surfacing Platforms (Aprons/Dispersals) and associated infrastructure to ensure continued safe access to the main and subsidiary runways;</P><P>d) re-provision of the 05 Threshold Loop;</P><P>e) the widening, strengthening and reconstruction of various pavement components including shoulders, taxiways and thresholds;</P><P>f) the replacement of Airfield Visual Aids — Aeronautical Ground Lighting (AGL) including associated circuitry;</P><P>g) the replacement of Approach Lighting, Threshold Wingbars together with associated Mast, Cables and Transformers;</P><P>h) the provision of Runway End Safety Areas (RESA);</P><P>i) Demolition, site clearance, earth works, civil works and associated utility infrastructure.</P><P>The integrity of the working environment and operational readiness of the Station are to be maintained at all times during the planning, construction and compliance period. MoD buildings will remain in an operational state during the full delivery of this contract.</P><P>Health and Safety is paramount to the delivery of this contract, as is the MoD Key Performance Indicators (KPI's) for Environmental Protection and Sustainability. All Contractors' personnel will need to be security cleared by MoD prior to the commencement of the works on site.</P><P>The following project dates are indicative, and provided for planning purposes only as they may be subject to change:</P><P>Issue of Invitation to Tender (ITT) — Summer/Autumn 2018.</P><P>Contract Award — Spring 2019.</P></TOTAL_QUANTITY_OR_SCOPE><COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY CURRENCY="GBP"><RANGE_VALUE_COST><LOW_VALUE FMTVAL="50000000">50 000 000</LOW_VALUE><HIGH_VALUE FMTVAL="100000000">100 000 000</HIGH_VALUE></RANGE_VALUE_COST></COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY></NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><NO_OPTIONS/><NO_RECURRENT_CONTRACT/></QUANTITY_SCOPE><PERIOD_WORK_DATE_STARTING><MONTHS>18</MONTHS></PERIOD_WORK_DATE_STARTING></OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><P>A Deed of Indemnity from a Parent Company or, as an alternative, a Bank / Insurance Bond will be required to guarantee due performance. Furthermore, the Authority reserves the right to seek an Indemnity, Guarantee of Bank/Insurance Bond if the supplier does not meet the required standard in respect of economic and financial standing. Further details will be provided in the Invitation to Tender (ITT) documentation.</P></DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><P>Conditions relating to financing and payment will be specified within the contractual documentation — NEC, ECC, Main Option C, Target Cost Incentive Fee (TCIF) / Maximum Price Target Cost (MPTC) pricing arrangement with an Activity Schedule, as amended.</P><P>The Authority's Contracting, Purchasing and Finance (CP and F) e-business tool will be used for payment under this contract. Candidates are deemed to have satisfied themselves that they will be able to operate CP and F through an RLI (Exostar) prior to making a request to participate.</P><P>Electronic Trading: Potential Suppliers must note the mandatory requirement for electronic trading using the Contracting, Purchasing and Finance (CP and F) electronic procurement tool. All payments for Contractor Deliverables under the Contract shall only be made via CP and F. you can find details on CP and F at https://ww.gov.uk/government/publications/mod-contracting-purchasing-and-finance-e-procurement-system</P></MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><LEGAL_FORM><P>If a group of economic operators submits a bid, the group must nominate a lead organisation to deal with the Authority. The Authority shall require the group to form a legal entity before entering into the Contract.</P><P>In the event of a joint venture or consortium submitting an acceptable offer it will be necessary for each member of the joint venture or consortium to sign an undertaking that each member will be jointly and severably responsible for the due performance of the contract.</P></LEGAL_FORM><EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS><P>The performance of this contract will be subject to the terms and conditions of the NEC ECC (Option C) as amended by the Authority.</P><P>The Authority reserves the right to amend any condition related to security of information to reflect any changes in national law or government policy. If any contract documents are accompanied by instructions on safeguarding classified information (e.g. a Security Aspects Letter), the Authority reserves the right to amend the terms of these instructions to reflect any changes in national law or government policy, whether in respect of the applicable protective marking scheme, specific protective markings given, the aspects to which any protective marking applies, or otherwise. The link below to the Gov.uk website provides information on the Government Security Classification.</P><P>https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/government-security-classifications</P></EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS></CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><P>The Authority will apply all the offences listed in Article 39(1) of Directive 2009/81/EC (implemented as Regulation 23(1) of the Defence and Security Public Contract Regulations (DSPCR) 2011 in the UK) and all of the professional misconducts listed at Article 39(2) of Directive 2009/81/EC (see also Regulation 23(2) in the DSPCR 2011) to the decision of whether a Candidate is eligible to be invited to tender.</P><P>A full list of the Regulation 23(1) and 23(2) criteria are at http://www.contracts.mod.uk/delta/project/reasonsForExclusion.html#dspr</P><P>Candidates will be required to sign a declaration confirming whether they do or do not have any of the listed criteria as part of the pre-qualification process.</P><P>Candidates who have been convicted of any of the offences under Article 39(1) are ineligible and will not be selected to bid, unless there are overriding requirements in the general interest (including defence and security factors) for doing so.</P><P>Candidates who are guilty of any of the offences, circumstances or misconduct under Article 39(2) may be excluded from being selected to bid at the discretion of the Authority.</P></ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>(a) Appropriate statements from the economic operator's bankers or where appropriate, evidence of relevant professional risk indemnity insurance;</P><P>(b) The presentation of balance-sheets or extracts from the balance-sheets, where publication of the balance-sheet is required under the law of the country in which the economic operator is established;</P><P>(c) where appropriate, a statement, covering the 3 previous financial years of the economic operator, of:</P><P>(i) the overall turnover of the business of the economic operator; and</P><P>(ii) where appropriate, the turnover in respect of the work, works, goods or services which are of a similar type to the subject matter of the contract.</P><P>In addition to submission III.2.2 requirements are further specified in the Pre-Qualification Questionnaire (PQQ) document.</P><P>A financial assessment will be undertaken on the suppliers financial status. An overall pass/fail judgement will be made after considering areas such as turnover, profit, net assets, liquidity, gearing and capacity. This assessment will include the Parent company where applicable. An independent financial assessment obtained from a reputable credit rating organisation will be utilised as part of this process.</P></EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION></F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI><T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>(a) in the case of a supply contract requiring the siting or installation of goods, a services contract or a works contract, the economic operator's technical ability, taking into account in particular that economic operator's skills, efficiency, experience and reliability;</P><P>(b) a list of works carried out over the past 5 years together with (unless the Contracting Authority specifies that the following certificate should be submitted direct to the contracting authority by the person certifying) certificates of satisfactory completion for the most important of those works indicating in each case:</P><P>(i) the value of the consideration received;</P><P>(ii)when and where the work or works were carried out; and</P><P>(iii)specifying whether they were carried out according to the rules of the trade or profession and properly completed.</P><P>(c) a statement of the principal goods sold or services provided by the supplier or the services provider in the past 5 years, or during a shorter period if necessary, and:</P><P>(i) the dates on which the goods were sold or the services provided;</P><P>(ii) the consideration received;</P><P>(iii) the identity of the person to whom the goods were sold or the service were provided;</P><P>(iv) any certificate issued or countersigned by that person confirming the details of the contract for those goods sold or services provided; and</P><P>(v) where:</P><P>(a) that person was not a contracting authorit; and</P><P>(b)the certificate referred to in sub-paragraph (c)(iv) is not available, any declaration by the economic operator attesting the details of the goods sold or services provided;</P><P>(d) a statement of the technicians or technical services available to the economic operator to:</P><P>(i) carry out the work under the contract; or</P><P>(ii) be involved in the production of goods or the provision of services under the contract, particularly those responsible for quality control, whether or not they are independent of the economic operator;</P><P>(e) a statement of the economic operator's:</P><P>(i) technical facilities;</P><P>(ii) measures for ensuring quality;</P><P>(iii) study and research facilities; and</P><P>(iv) internal rules regarding intellectual property;</P><P>(f) a check carried out by the Contracting Authority or on its behalf by a competent official body of the member State in which the economic operator is established:</P><P>(i) on the technical capacity of the economic operator; and</P><P>(ii) if relevant, on the economic operator's study and research facilities and quality control measures;</P><P>(g) in the case of works contracts, services contracts or supply contracts also covering siting and installation operations or services, the economic operator's educational and professional qualifications where the economic operator is an individual and:</P><P>(i) if any, those of the economic operator's managerial staff; and</P><P>(ii) those of one or more persons who would be responsible for providing the services or carrying out the work or works under the contract;</P><P>(h) the environmental management measures, that the economic operator is able to apply when performing the contract, but only where it is necessary for the performance of that contract</P><P>(i) a statement of the services provider's or contractor's average annual number of staff and managerial staff over the previous 3 years</P><P>(j) a description of the tools, material, technical equipment, staff numbers, know-how and sources of supply (with an indication of their geographical location when it is outside the territory of the EU) available to the economic operator to perform the contract, cope with any additional needs required by the Contracting Authority as a result of a crisis or carry out the maintenance, modernisation or adaptation of the goods covered by the contract</P><P>(k) any samples, descriptions and photographs of the goods to be purchased or hired under the contract and certification of the authenticity of such samples, descriptions or photographs</P><P>(l) certification by official quality control institutes or agencies of recognised competence, attesting that the goods to be purchased or hired under the contract conform to standards and technical specifications (within the meaning of regulation 12(1)) identified by the Contracting Authority;</P><P>(m) in the case of contracts involving, entailing or containing classified information, evidence of the ability to process, store and transmit such information at the level of protection required by the Contracting Authority;</P><P>(n) a certificate:</P><P>(i) attesting conformity to quality management systems standards based on the relevant European standard; and</P><P>(ii) from an independent accredited body established in any member State conforming to the European standards concerning accreditation and certification;</P><P>(o) any other evidence of conformity to quality management systems standards which are equivalent to the standards referred to in sub-paragraph (n)(i).</P><P>The Authority requires this information to evaluate technical and/or professional capability and this will be sought via the Pre-Qualification Questionnaire (PQQ) stage.</P></T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><T_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL><P>Shall be stated in the Pre-Qualification Questionnaire (PQQ).</P></T_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL></TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI></F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION></LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><PT_RESTRICTED/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED><OPE_MINIMUM_NUMBER>3</OPE_MINIMUM_NUMBER><OPE_MAXIMUM_NUMBER>6</OPE_MAXIMUM_NUMBER><OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA><P>Interested suppliers are required to complete the PQQ to provide information that allows the Authority to evaluate the supplier's capacity and capabilities against the selection criteria set out at Sections III.2.1), III.2.2) and III.2.3 of this Contract Notice.</P><P>The Authority will use the PQQ response to create a shortlist of tenderers who:</P><P>(1) are eligible to participate under Section III.2.1 of this Contract Notice;</P><P>(2) fulfil any minimum standards under Sections III.2.2) and III.2.3) of this Contract Notice; and</P><P>(3) best meet in terms of capacity and capability the selection criteria set out in Sections III.2.2) and III.2.3) of this Contract Notice.</P><P>Full details of the method for down selecting suitable candidates will be set out in the Help Text Box / instructions for the Dynamic PQQ.</P></OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA></MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><MOST_ECONOMICALLY_ADVANTAGEOUS_TENDER><CRITERIA_STATED_IN_OTHER_DOCUMENT/></MOST_ECONOMICALLY_ADVANTAGEOUS_TENDER></AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE><NO_USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION/></IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE></AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><P>DIOCB1/117</P></FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_EXISTS_F17><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_NOTICE_F17><PRIOR_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17 CHOICE="PRIOR_INFORMATION_NOTICE"/><NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2016/S 200-361451</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ><DATE_OJ><DAY>15</DAY><MONTH>10</MONTH><YEAR>2016</YEAR></DATE_OJ></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_NOTICE_F17><NO_OTHER_PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION/></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_EXISTS_F17></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17><CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><NO_PAYABLE_DOCUMENTS/></CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><DAY>04</DAY><MONTH>05</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>16:00</TIME></RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><LANGUAGE><LANGUAGE_EC VALUE="EN"/></LANGUAGE></ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE></PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/><RELATES_TO_EU_PROJECT_NO/><ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><P>Advertising Regime OJEU: This contract opportunity is published in the Official Journal of the European Union (OJEU), the MoD Defence Contracts Bulletin and www.contracts.mod.uk</P><P>Suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P><P>The information and/or documents for this opportunity are available on https://www.contracts.mod.uk/delta</P><P>You must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password. Please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P><P>Suppliers must log in, go to your Response Manager and add the following Access Code: Z83VKR5EYM. Please ensure you follow any instruction provided to you here.</P><P>The deadline for submitting your response(s) is 4.5.2018 16:00. Please ensure that you allow yourself plenty of time when responding to this invite prior to the closing date and time, especially if you have been asked to upload documents.</P><P>If you experience any difficulties please refer to the online Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ's) or the User Guides or contact the MOD DCO Helpdesk by emailing — support@contracts.mod.uk or call 0800 282 324.</P><P>Suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P><P>The information and/or documents for this opportunity are available on http://www.contracts.mod.uk</P><P>You must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password. Please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P><P>Suppliers must log in, go to your Response Manager and add the following Access Code: Z83VKR5EYM.</P><P>Please ensure you follow any instruction provided to you here.</P><P>The deadline for submitting your response(s) is detailed within this contract notice, you will also have visibility of the deadline date, once you have added the Access code via DCO as the opening and closing date is visible within the opportunity.</P><P>Please ensure that you allow yourself plenty of time when responding to this opportunity prior to the closing date and time, especially if you have been asked to upload documents.</P><P>If you experience any difficulties please refer to the online Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ's) or the User Guides or contact the MOD DCO Helpdesk by emailing support@contracts.mod.uk or Telephone 0800 282 324.</P><P>GO Reference: GO-2018329-DCB-12141863.</P></ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, DIO, Defence Infrastructure Organisation (DIO)</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><TOWN>Glasgow</TOWN><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE></PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE><DAY>29</DAY><MONTH>03</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR></NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE></CONTRACT_DEFENCE></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>