<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="143903-2018" EDITION="2018065"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-144246-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180517</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>65</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180404</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 065-143903</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:143903-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="RS"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71311210">Highways consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79415200">Design consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180329</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180517 10:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>BR102</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Serbien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Beograd</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - Projekt vedrørende vejrenovering og -sikkerhed</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Serbien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - Projekt zur Straßeninstandsetzung und Verkehrssicherheit</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrade</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrado</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Proyecto de seguridad y rehabilitación de carreteras</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - teiden kunnostusta ja turvallisuutta koskeva hanke</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Serbie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrade</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Projet de réhabilitation et de sécurité des routes</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Σερβία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Βελιγράδι</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - Σχέδιο αποκατάστασης και ασφάλειας οδών</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrado</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - Progetto riguardante il riattamento e la sicurezza stradali</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Servië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrado</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - Project voor herstel van wegen en verkeersveiligheid</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Sérvia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrado</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Projeto de segurança e reabilitação rodoviária</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Serbien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Projekt för vägupprustning och trafiksäkerhet</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Srbsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bělehrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt obnovy a bezpečnosti silnic</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - maanteede ümberehitust ja ohutust käsitlev projekt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Szerbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrád</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Úthelyreállítási és -biztonsági projekt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Serbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgradas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - Kelių remonto ir saugos projektas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Serbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrada</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - Ceļu atjaunošanas un drošības projekts</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>is-Serbja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - Progett ta' Riabilitazzjoni u Sigurtà tat-Toroq</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt dotyczący remontu i bezpieczeństwa dróg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Srbsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belehrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt obnovy a bezpečnosti ciest</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Srbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Beograd</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt za obnovo in varnost cest</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Seirbia, an t</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Béalgrád</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Tionscadal um Athshlánú agus um Shábháilteacht Bóithre</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Сърбия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Белград</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - Проект за реконструкция и безопасност на пътища</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Serbia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Belgrad</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Proiect privind reabilitarea și siguranța drumurilor</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Srbija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Beograd</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Projekt za obnovu i sigurnost cesta</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - Projekt vedrørende vejrenovering og -sikkerhed (RS-Beograd)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - Projekt zur Straßeninstandsetzung und Verkehrssicherheit (RS-Belgrad)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Proyecto de seguridad y rehabilitación de carreteras (RS-Belgrado)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - teiden kunnostusta ja turvallisuutta koskeva hanke (RS-Belgrad)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Projet de réhabilitation et de sécurité des routes (RS-Belgrade)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - Σχέδιο αποκατάστασης και ασφάλειας οδών (RS-Βελιγράδι)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - Progetto riguardante il riattamento e la sicurezza stradali (RS-Belgrado)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - Project voor herstel van wegen en verkeersveiligheid (RS-Belgrado)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Projeto de segurança e reabilitação rodoviária (RS-Belgrado)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Projekt för vägupprustning och trafiksäkerhet (RS-Belgrad)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt obnovy a bezpečnosti silnic (RS-Bělehrad)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - maanteede ümberehitust ja ohutust käsitlev projekt (RS-Belgrad)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Úthelyreállítási és -biztonsági projekt (RS-Belgrád)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - Kelių remonto ir saugos projektas (RS-Belgradas)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - Ceļu atjaunošanas un drošības projekts (RS-Belgrada)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - Progett ta' Riabilitazzjoni u Sigurtà tat-Toroq (RS-Belgrad)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt dotyczący remontu i bezpieczeństwa dróg (RS-Belgrad)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt obnovy a bezpečnosti ciest (RS-Belehrad)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt za obnovo in varnost cest (RS-Beograd)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Tionscadal um Athshlánú agus um Shábháilteacht Bóithre (RS-Béalgrád)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - Проект за реконструкция и безопасност на пътища (RS-Белград)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Proiect privind reabilitarea și siguranța drumurilor (RS-Belgrad)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Projekt za obnovu i sigurnost cesta (RS-Beograd)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR TENDERS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement Reference: 9043-IFT-44750</P><P>Project name: Road Rehabilitation and Safety Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Serbia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44750</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 29/03/2018</P><P>Closing date: 17.5.2018 10.00 a.m. local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice (7090-GPN-44750) for this project which was originally published in procurement notices on the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) website: 14.5.2013; updated (7705-GPN-44750) on 24.9.2014 and on 29.6.2016.</P><P>The public enterprise “Roads of Serbia” hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the bank towards the cost of road rehabilitation and safety project.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>— Hheavy maintenance of the state road IA3, Motorway Section: Border CRO/SER (Batrovci) - Kuzmin 1, Contract Ref. No. RRSP/RW-IA3BK/2017-07.</P><P>The contractor is expected to perform all Works from km 0+554.86 to km 22+196.11 left carriageway and from km 0+564.64 to km 22+229.16 right carriageway in accordance with the main design provided by the employer.</P><P>The civil works will consist of (but shall not be limited to) the following:</P><P>— Preliminary works which include removal of excessive vegetative material and waste, demolition of road elements on access roads (curbs and pavement), demolition and removal of elements of the damaged constructions, surface preparation of the existing pavement for application of new layers (milling of the existing pavement, repair of wide cracks, construction of leveling layers),</P><P>— Substructure works which include excavation of ditches, construction of stabilized shoulders, topsoiling of shoulders and other surfaces, and earth works on construction of asphalt access roads and bus stops,</P><P>— Superstructure works which include pavement construction on access roads; works on improvement of pavement (construction of bituminous bearing course, and construction of wearing asphalt concrete course), as well as placement of concrete curbs and construction of gutters,</P><P>— Works on structures (bridges) which include milling of the existing asphalt layer, construction or replacement of waterproofing, construction of asphalt layers (leveling course if needed, wearing course, asphalt layer on sidewalk), demolition and reconstruction of the curbs, repair or replacement of the bearing paths, repair or replacement of the expansion devices, repair of the protective layers, bridge drainage, repair of fences and guardrails, regulation of hydraulic watercourse profile in the bridge area and any other works if specified by the main design,</P><P>— Works on drainage system improvement which include cleaning and repair of elements of the existing culverts, culverts extension, construction of the new culverts in accordance with the main design, construction of drainage pipes, construction of concrete channel, construction of concrete pipes on access roads and approaches,</P><P>— Roadside arrangement and placement of traffic signalization and road furniture.</P><P>The works will be performed under traffic with a strong emphasis on maintaining safe conditions for both the flow of traffic and the works in progress.</P><P>Time for completion of works is 15 months.</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>Financial requirements</P><P>— Submission of audited balance sheets or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the employer, for the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016, as well as the forecast for 2017-2018, which shall demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderers financial position and its prospective long term profitability,</P><P>— minimum average annual construction turnover of 28 000 000 EUR equivalent, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years, i.e. 2012-2016,</P><P>— the tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>i) the following cash-flow requirement: min. EUR 5 800 000 equivalent, and</P><P>ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its concurrent commitments.</P><P>Experience requirements</P><P>— General experience - Experience under contracts in the role of contractor or management contractor for the last 5 years prior to the tender submission deadline, and with activity in at least 9 months in each year,</P><P>— Specific experience:</P><P>a) Participation as contractor, management contractor, or subcontractor, in at least 2 contracts within the last 5 years, each with a value of at least EUR 12 000 000 that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The similarity shall be based on the physical size, complexity, methods/technology or other characteristics as described in Section VI, employer’s requirements,</P><P>b) For the above or other contracts executed during the stipulated period under item (a), a minimum experience in the following key activities: Average annual production and laying of asphalt mixtures (asphalt concrete and bituminous base) not less than 65 000 tones /year in the last 3 years.</P><P>Above and all other qualification requirements related to the eligibility, litigation history, and technical capabilities including to the personnel and equipment are specified in the Section III. Evaluation and qualification criteria of the tender documents.</P><P>Tender documents may be obtained from 2.4.2018, from the office at the address below upon payment of non-refundable fee of EUR 200 (two hundred euros) or equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>EUR 200 (two hundred euros) payable by international tenderers.</P><P>FIELD 32A: Value DATE-EUR-AMOUNT</P><P>FIELD 50K: Ordering Customer</P><P>FIELD 56A (intermediary): DEUTDEFFXXX, Deutsche Bank AG., F/M, Taunusanlage 12, Germany</P><P>FIELD 57 A (acc. with bank): NBSRRSBGXXX, Narodna Banka SRBIJE (National Bank of Serbia-NBS), Beograd, Nemanjina 17, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 59 (beneficiary): /RS35840000000019179453, Public Enterprise Roads of Serbia, Bulevar Kralja Aleksandra BR.282, Beograd, Serbia</P><P>FIELD 70: Details of Payment</P><P>FIELD 71 A: OUR</P><P>Or</P><P>RSD 24 000 (twenty four thousand dinars) payable by tenderers from Republic of Serbia:</P><P>1 Primalac (Recipient): Javno preduzeće „Putevi Srbije“ (Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”)</P><P>2 Svrha uplate (Description of payment): Otkup tenderske dokumentacije za deonicu Batrovci - Kuzmin (Provision of Tender Document for Batrovci - Kuzmin section)</P><P>3 Račun primaoca (Account mode): 840-1189664-57</P><P>4 Broj modela (Payment mode): 97</P><P>5 Poziv na broj (odobrenje) (Reference number): 78-74232102</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will promptly be dispatched by courier; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery. In addition, if requested, the documents can be dispatched electronically after presentation by the prospective Tenderer of an appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>All tenderers must be accompanied by a tender security of 400 000 EUR or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 17.5.2018, 10:00 a.m. (local time), at which time they will be opened in the presence of those authorized tenderer's representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bul. kralja Aleksandra 282, 11000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Belgrade</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Serbia, </BLK_BTX><URL>www.putevi-srbije.rs</URL><BLK_BTX> — e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>office@putevi-srbije.rs</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules ate the Bank's Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from, and inspect and acquire the tender documents at, the following office:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Public Enterprise “Roads of Serbia”</P><P>Vlajkovićeva 19a street (sixth floor), Belgrade</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Contact Persons:</P><P>Mrs. Milena Vuksanović Petrović, (M.Ltt.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>Tel. +381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: milena.veselinovic@putevi-srbije.rs; vuksanovic.milena@gmail.com;</P><P>Mr. Nikola Veselinović, dipl-ing (Org.Sc.), Project Procurement Specialist</P><P>+381 11 3398 438</P><P>Fax. +381 11 3398 440</P><P>e-mail: nixona16@gmail.com</P><P>Date: 29.3.2018</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>