<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="053015-2018"
            EDITION="2018025">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-055607-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180309</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>25</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180206</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 025-053015</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:053015-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="FI"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.yle.fi</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://hanki.tarjouspalvelu.fi/hanki?id=141781&amp;tpk=3ab6d624-d1cf-4015-9cc9-cac34cc901e5</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="48900000">Miscellaneous software package and computer systems</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="72000000">IT services: consulting, software development, Internet and support</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="32000000">Radio, television, communication, telecommunication and related equipment</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="FI1B1">Helsinki-Uusimaa</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="FI1B1">Helsinki-Uusimaa</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180205</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180309 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="6">Body governed by public law</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="B">Competitive procedure with negotiation</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="8">Other</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01B02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Финлaндия</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Други софтуерни пакети и операционни системи</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Finsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Různé balíky programů a počítačové systémy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Finland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Diverse programpakker og computersystemer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Finnland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Diverse Softwarepakete und Computersysteme</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Φινλανδία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Διάφορα πακέτα λογισμικού και συστήματα ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Finland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Miscellaneous software package and computer systems</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Finlandia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Paquetes de software y sistemas informáticos diversos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Soome</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Mitmesugused tarkvarapaketid ja arvutisüsteemid</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Suomi</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Erilaiset ohjelmatuotteet ja tietokonejärjestelmät</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Finlande</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Logiciels et systèmes informatiques divers</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Fhionlainn, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Miscellaneous software package and computer systems</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Finska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Razni programski paketi i računalni sustavi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Finnország</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Különféle szoftvercsomagok és számítógépes rendszerek</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Finlandia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pacchetti software e sistemi informatici vari</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Suomija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Įvairūs programinės įrangos paketai ir kompiuterių sistemos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Somija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dažādas programmatūras pakotnes un datoru sistēmas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>il-Finlandja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pakketti tas-softwer varji u sistemi tal-kompjuter</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Finland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Diverse software en computersystemen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Finlandia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Różne pakiety oprogramowania i systemy komputerowe</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Finlândia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pacote de software e sistemas informáticos diversos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Finlanda</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Diverse pachete software şi sisteme informatice</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Fínsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Rôzne softvérové balíky a počítačové systémy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Finska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Razni programski paketi in računalniški sistemi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Finland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Yleisradio</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Diverse programvara och datorsystem</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Yleisradio Oy</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Yleisradio Oy</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>0215438-8</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>PL 76</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Yleisradio</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>00024</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="FI"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Marjatta Oravala</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+358 9014801</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>tarjoukset.yle@yle.fi</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="FI1B1"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.yle.fi</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://hanki.tarjouspalvelu.fi/hanki?id=141781&amp;tpk=3ab6d624-d1cf-4015-9cc9-cac34cc901e5</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://hanki.tarjouspalvelu.fi/hanki?id=141781&amp;tpk=3ab6d624-d1cf-4015-9cc9-cac34cc901e5</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="BODY_PUBLIC"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>Broadcasting</CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Media service order and management system</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>YLE20170038</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="48900000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SUPPLIES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Finnish broadcasting company, “Yle", invites you to take part in a tender competition of a media service order &amp; management system. Yle is looking for a new system to manage and operate various media services efficiently. Processes are going to be managed &amp; monitored end-to-end basis and degree of process automation is expected to increase. Flexible order management and process automation functionalities are the foundation for end-to-end process management. Planned primary processes to be supported are related to live video and audio signal reception, processing, routing, recording and transmission. Another to be supported process area is material ingest and export services. Procurement procedure will be a negotiated procedure.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="FI1B1"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Yle is procuring the following delivery and service combination:</P>
                  <P>— system/solution software for media service order &amp; management purposes,</P>
                  <P>— delivery project of the solution (phased approach),</P>
                  <P>— 3<FT TYPE="SUP">rd</FT> level continuous development and support services system expectations: With this tender competition Yle is looking for a new media service order &amp; management system for managing and operating various media services efficiently. The system is expected to provide complete order management and process management functionalities in as configurable and flexible manner as possible. In more detail, the system is going to be used for unifying order process for media services and utilizing the order information to establish operational efficiency and control. Through direct device control &amp; monitoring the degree of automation in end-to-end processes is planned to be significantly increased, which is one of the ultimate goals. But since full automation is unlikely, there is great need for user task management functionalities alongside process automation. Considering evolving technology and changing environment, one of the most important capability is the flexibility with device control and system integrations. The system is virtually expected to integrate to any system or technical device which has a communication interface. Yle is looking for a single off-the-shelf solution/platform which is highly modifiable &amp; configurable product as such. Since the system is planned to be operated 24/7 for the next 5-10 years, the usability, configurability and flexibility of a user interface is essential. Ease of use and general user experience is highly valued. Note, the system is expected to be used by Yle's internal and external customer and Yle's operators. Service expectations: In addition to the system/solution software platform, Yle is going to need 3rd level software support &amp; continuous development from the supplier. The chosen system supplier will take main responsibility of the project including planning, installation, configuration, training and system support. However, Yle and Yle’s local partners (e.g. 2nd level support &amp; development partner) are planned to be heavily involved in planning and implementation as well as in the continuous service. Procurement procedure will be a negotiated procedure: In the the first part of tender competition Yle will choose the suitable candidates, who may participate the procedure. Yle will select the candidates who meet the mandatory requirements set by Yle, and have the best rank according to the selection criteria described later in this invitation to participate. The deliverables and services that are included in this procurement as well as the scope of procurement are described in more detail in Appendix 1 — General Project Description. The general project description is meant to give a sufficient information of the requirements and expectations of Yle for the solution, delivery and services. Also the time frame of the project is described in Appendix 1. The preliminary call for tender, including more detailed descriptions &amp; requirements, will be available for the selected candidates. Candidate selection criterion is described in Appendix 1 and Appendix 2.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <DATE_START>2018-09-01</DATE_START>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NB_MIN_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>3</NB_MIN_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>6</NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>3-6 candidates are considered to be sufficiently competitive between the participants and negotiations can be conducted cost-effectively.</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>Optional services will be specified later in the negotiated procedure.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Yle will require the ESPD form to be completed by each candidate and their subcontractors, and each operator, if the proposal is made by a group of tenderers.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>The candidate shall be registered in the professional or trade register of its domicile country, if the candidate is obliged to register to these registers according to its domicile countries national law. The candidate shall also be registered in the prepayment register and the employer register in accordance with the act on prepayment of tax, and shall be registered as VAT-liable in the value added tax register in compliance with the value added tax act before the procurement decision is made, if the candidate is obliged to register to these registers according to its domicile countries national law. If the participant is a group, these requirements shall be met by all its members individually. If subcontractors are participating the delivery, they must meet these requirements individually. If requested, the candidate shall provide relevant certificates.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>The candidate's economic standing and financial solvency shall be sufficiently stable to provide the customer with the delivery's including the contract. Please see the requirements set in the ESPD form and below. If the candidate is a group, the requirements shall be met by all its members individually — except the required turn over, which can be met by summing together the turnovers of all the members of the group. If requested, the candidate shall provide relevant certificates.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Sufficient turn over: The candidate's turnover for the latest accounting period must be minimum 4 000 000 EUR. Sufficient credit rating: the candidate / member of a group / subcontractor participating the delivery must have a minimum credit rating (credit worthiness) A, according to credit rating system from AAA, the highest, to C, the lowest, rated by well known and established credit rating agency. If the candidates rating cannot be found, the candidate's situation will be evaluated through the last 3 audited financial statements and/or another similar statement. Sufficient risk indemnity insurance: The candidate must have a professional risk indemnity insurance policy with a minimum insured amount of EUR 4 000 000 EUR.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>Please see the requirements set in the ESPD form and below. Note: In addition to ESPD form, a candidate must give a detailed information of mandatory references using appendix 2. References. If requested, the candidate shall provide relevant certificates.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Sufficient level of experience: A candidate must have at least tree 3 references that fulfill requirements described in Appendix 2 — References. Tenderer shall fill in the ESPD form and give more detailed information about references and contact details to the Appendix 2 — References.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_COMPETITIVE_NEGOTIATION/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-03-09</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">6</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <EORDERING/>
            <EINVOICING/>
            <EPAYMENT/>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Markkinaoikeus</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Radanrakentajantie 5</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Helsinki</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>00520</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="FI"/>
               <PHONE>+358 295643300</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>markkinaoikeus@oikeus.fi</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+358 295643314</FAX>
               <URL>http://www.oikeus.fi/markkinaoikeus</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-05</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
