<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="192511-2018" EDITION="2018085"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-194449-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180601</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>85</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180503</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 085-192511</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192511-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.gov.uk/government/organisations/ministry-of-defence</IA_URL_GENERAL><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="80500000">Training services</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="80510000">Specialist training services</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="80600000">Training services in defence and security materials</ORIGINAL_CPV><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UK">UNITED KINGDOM</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS><VALUES_LIST><VALUES TYPE="GLOBAL"><RANGE_VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="GBP">45 000 000</VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="GBP">60 000 000</VALUE></RANGE_VALUE></VALUES><VALUES TYPE="GLOBAL"><RANGE_VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="GBP">45 000 000</VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="GBP">60 000 000</VALUE></RANGE_VALUE></VALUES></VALUES_LIST><REF_NOTICE><NO_DOC_OJS>2017/S 239-497167</NO_DOC_OJS></REF_NOTICE></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180430</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180601 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>01317</HEADING><DIRECTIVE VALUE="2009/81/EC"/></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Услуги по обучение</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Školení</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Uddannelsestilbud</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ausbildung</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Υπηρεσίες κατάρτισης</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Training services</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Servicios de formación</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Koolitusteenused</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ammattikoulutuspalvelut</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Services de formation</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Training services</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Usluge izobrazbe</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Képzési szolgáltatások</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Servizi di formazione</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Apmokymo paslaugos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Mācību pakalpojumi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Faċilitajjiet tat-taħriġ</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Opleidingsdiensten</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Usługi szkoleniowe</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Serviços de formação</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Servicii de formare</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Školiace (výcvikové) služby</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Storitve usposabljanja</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lisburn</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Utbildningstjänster</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C, Other</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><CONTRACT_DEFENCE CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="17" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE CTYPE="SERVICES"><CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C, Other</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Rm G6, Bldg 114, Thiepval Barracks</ADDRESS><TOWN>Lisburn</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>BFPO 801</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><PHONE>+44 2892266653</PHONE><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>ArmyComrcl-NI-Mailbox@mod.uk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><URL_GENERAL>http://www.gov.uk/government/organisations/ministry-of-defence</URL_GENERAL></INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><FURTHER_INFORMATION><IDEM/></FURTHER_INFORMATION><SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><IDEM/></SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO><IDEM/></TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO></NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY VALUE="MINISTRY"/><TYPE_OF_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF_NO/></PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><TITLE_CONTRACT><P>COEFOR Support (Project Thespis)</P></TITLE_CONTRACT><TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><TYPE_CONTRACT VALUE="SERVICES"/><SERVICE_CATEGORY_DEFENCE>20</SERVICE_CATEGORY_DEFENCE></TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><LOCATION_NUTS><LOCATION><P>United Kingdom</P></LOCATION><n2016:NUTS CODE="UK"/></LOCATION_NUTS><NOTICE_INVOLVES_DEFENCE VALUE="ESTABLISHMENT_FRAMEWORK_AGREEMENT"/><F17_FRAMEWORK><DURATION_FRAMEWORK_MONTH>36</DURATION_FRAMEWORK_MONTH><JUSTIFICATION/><TOTAL_ESTIMATED><COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY CURRENCY="GBP"><RANGE_VALUE_COST><LOW_VALUE FMTVAL="45000000">45 000 000</LOW_VALUE><HIGH_VALUE FMTVAL="60000000">60 000 000</HIGH_VALUE></RANGE_VALUE_COST></COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY></TOTAL_ESTIMATED></F17_FRAMEWORK><SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><P>Training services. Specialist training services. Training services in defence and security materials. Project Thespis will deliver the future Contemporary Operating Environment Force (COEFOR) capability to Support individual and collective Training. The capability shall provide training support services that are agile, responsive and capable of representing uniformed forces, governmental departments, NGOs, Demonstration Forces (DEMFOR), Opposing Forces (OPFOR), Subject Matter Experts (SME), private contracted forces, casualties including the breadth and depth of civilian population and institutions that will be consistent with the Conceptual Operating Environment SCENario (COESCEN) and Decisive Action Training Environment (DATE), augmented with conceptual language and cultural training to create realistic environments representing current and emerging threats.</P><P>COEFOR Support to training includes, but is not limited to:</P><P>— The physical manifestation of an operating environment to match the given scenario for the specified training establishment/training event.</P><P>— Representative uniformed forces ranging from allied through neutral and indigenous to opposing, such as military, paramilitary, police, OPFOR and DEMFOR and represent bodies across the full spectrum of the given scenario nationalities/geographical environment (government officials, military, civilians etc).</P><P>— Representation of the breadth and depth of a civilian population, including its customs, dress and tribal dynamics that will effectively represent the true complexities of communities, religions, tribes and the key personalities of the scenario.</P><P>— Provision of Casualty Simulation (CASSIM) to specific training scenarios that depict realistic clinical events. These clinical events will include all battle, disease and non-battle injuries present in contemporary operations, including, but not limited to, amputation simulation appropriate to ballistic/blast injury, gunshot wound injury, burn injuries, open fracture simulation and casualty make up depicting minor wounds.</P><P>— A wide range of role players in a dynamic, intelligent and flexible manner.</P><P>— Support to conceptual activity through interpreters (role play and real time), language and cultural training.</P><P>— Scenario Writers and pyrotechnic effects simulation.</P><P>— Provision of the logistics required to deliver training support to small, medium and large scale events, including, but not limited to, provision and management of feeding, transport to and from events, accommodation, clothing, props and equipment.</P></SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><CPV><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="80500000"/></CPV_MAIN><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="80510000"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="80600000"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL></CPV><SUBCONTRACTING><INDICATE_ANY_SHARE VALUE="YES"/><INDICATE_ANY_CHANGE VALUE="YES"/><SUBCONTRACT_AWARD_PART VALUE="NO"/><IDENTIFY_SUBCONTRACT VALUE="NO"/></SUBCONTRACTING><F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><DIV_INTO_LOT_NO/></F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><ACCEPTED_VARIANTS VALUE="NO"/></DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><QUANTITY_SCOPE><NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><TOTAL_QUANTITY_OR_SCOPE><P>COEFOR support to each training event will be delivered by a Service Provider (SP) who will draw upon an agile workforce of role players with a wide range of capabilities. Depicted scenarios will require role players to be dressed and equipped appropriately to meet the needs of the role and the environment. The SP will also provide appropriate replication of appropriate props to enhance the environment (eg. small enemy encampment, market stalls with replica products etc). Continuity of role players is highly desirable through the training progression. Service delivery will include, but not be limited to, the following:</P><P>— Representation of DEMFOR and OPFOR. The need is to expose trainees and those on professional development courses to appropriate field craft, skill at arms tactical procedures and leadership scenarios. To achieve these skills and gain an understanding around the use of Tactics, Techniques and Procedures (TTPs) at section, platoon and company level, a visual representation has been found to be the most effective enabler [OPFOR will be limited to Lt Role, commonly at Platoon level or less but not to exceed Company level in any one event].</P><P>— Representation of the Indigenous Population. FEs need to train throughout MST within an accurate indigenous population, which includes an accurate representation of indigenous key leaders and the insurgency network. The training environment needs to present a population that can replicate the language, culture, structures, frictions and dynamics of the given scenario of operation. FEs need to be able to practise analysing the population and determine how to influence it, to achieve tactical and operational success. Military Specific Training (MST) needs to have a population that can be interacted with, whilst operating with a representative Host Nation National Security Force (HNSF). Within field training (FT) the indigenous population/security forces will need to represent the operating principles within the scenario of the likely area of operation for future conflict.</P><P>— Representation of Simulated Casualties (CASSIM). The immediate medical treatment administered to an injured soldier at the Point Of Injury (POI) will determine that soldier's ultimate chance of survival. Critical to the success of the learning experience is working with personnel who have suffered the loss of limbs or experienced other traumas and the makeup artists who portray the effect for exercising troops through battlefield simulation training. Particular emphasis is given to Battlefield inoculation by allowing personnel to experience some of the injuries they may see on the battlefield. Through training, personnel may become more ready to deal with such scenarios on the battlefield thereby reducing the shock of being faced with trauma and limb-loss injuries. This high quality realistic casualty simulation allows soldiers to gain the vital experience of dealing with the stressful and extreme circumstances of immediate injury so that critical time is used to best effect to save life.</P><P>— Representation of the Host Nation National Security Forces (HN SF). The MST delivered by the collective training establishments at CT3 and CT4 places heavy emphasis on the preparation of FEs to advise and mentor the HNSF. This training is vital to ensure that the units are exposed to, and exercised in, the structures, procedures, practicalities, frictions and frustrations of fulfilling this role. At the higher end of capability, role players involved in constant engagement with UK FEs and complex decision making exercises will by necessity be agile, responsive and intelligent in their approach.</P><P>— Specific Capabilities. In addition to the five main capability categories (DemFor, OpFor, CASSIM, Indigenous Populace and HNSF) there are specific capabilities such as:</P><P>—— Cultural Advisors who provide a breadth and depth of cultural understanding of the operational environment,</P><P>—— Language Trainers who provide linguistic capabilities.</P><P>No business whatsoever is guaranteed under any resulting contract, indeed there is no guarantee that any contract will be put in place in relation to this notice. No compensation will be paid if a tender or resulting agreement is withdrawn for any reason. Bidders should take part in the process only on the basis that they fully understand and accept this position.</P></TOTAL_QUANTITY_OR_SCOPE><COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY CURRENCY="GBP"><RANGE_VALUE_COST><LOW_VALUE FMTVAL="45000000">45 000 000</LOW_VALUE><HIGH_VALUE FMTVAL="60000000">60 000 000</HIGH_VALUE></RANGE_VALUE_COST></COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY></NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><OPTIONS><OPTION_DESCRIPTION><P>2 x 1 (one) year extension options</P></OPTION_DESCRIPTION></OPTIONS></QUANTITY_SCOPE></OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><P>A Parent Company Guarantee and/or Performance Bond in a form to be provided by the MoD may be required. Details will be included in the Tender Documentation, if applicable.</P></DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><P>Potential Suppliers must note the mandatory requirement for electronic trading using the Contracting, Purchasing &amp; Finance (CP&amp;F) electronic trading tool. All payments for deliverables under the contract shall only be made via CP&amp;F. Details can be found at http://www.gov.uk/government/publications/mod-contracting-purchasing-and-finance-e-procurement-systems</P></MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><LEGAL_FORM><P>In the event of a group provider submitting an acceptable offer, the MoD reserves the right to require the group of bidders to take a legal form or require one bidder to take Prime Contractor responsibility or to require that each member of the group undertakes joint and severable liability for the performance of the agreement and any call-off made under it.</P></LEGAL_FORM><NO_EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS/></CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><P>The Authority will apply all the offences listed in Article 39(1) of Directive 2009/81/EC (implemented as Regulation 23(1) of the Defence and Security Public Contract Regulations (DSPCR) 2011 in the UK) and all of the professional misconducts listed at Article 39(2) of Directive 2009/81/EC (see also Regulation 23(2) in the DSPCR 2011) to the decision of whether a Candidate is eligible to be invited to tender.</P><P>A full list of the Regulation 23(1) and 23(2) criteria are at http://www.contracts.mod.uk/delta/project/reasonsForExclusion.html#dspr</P><P>Candidates will be required to sign a declaration confirming whether they do or do not have any of the listed criteria as part of the pre-qualification process.</P><P>Candidates who have been convicted of any of the offences under Article 39(1) are ineligible and will not be selected to bid, unless there are overriding requirements in the general interest (including defence and security factors) for doing so.</P><P>Candidates who are guilty of any of the offences, circumstances or misconduct under Article 39(2) may be excluded from being selected to bid at the discretion of the Authority.</P></ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION_SUBCONTRACTORS><P>As per above.</P></ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION_SUBCONTRACTORS></F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><SERVICES_CONTRACTS_SPECIFIC_CONDITIONS><NO_EXEC_SERVICE_RESERVED_PARTICULAR_PROFESSION/><REQUESTS_NAMES_PROFESSIONAL_QUALIFICATIONS VALUE="YES"/></SERVICES_CONTRACTS_SPECIFIC_CONDITIONS></LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><PT_RESTRICTED/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED><OPE_MINIMUM_NUMBER>1</OPE_MINIMUM_NUMBER><OPE_MAXIMUM_NUMBER>6</OPE_MAXIMUM_NUMBER><OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA><P>Potential suppliers are required to complete the Dynamic Pre-Qualification Questionnaire (DPQQ) linked to this notice.</P></OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA></MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><MOST_ECONOMICALLY_ADVANTAGEOUS_TENDER><CRITERIA_STATED_IN_OTHER_DOCUMENT/></MOST_ECONOMICALLY_ADVANTAGEOUS_TENDER></AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE><NO_USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION/></IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE></AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><P>ArmyHQ4/00087</P></FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_EXISTS_F17><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_NOTICE_F17><PRIOR_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17 CHOICE="PRIOR_INFORMATION_NOTICE"/><NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 239-497167</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ><DATE_OJ><DAY>13</DAY><MONTH>12</MONTH><YEAR>2017</YEAR></DATE_OJ></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_NOTICE_F17><NO_OTHER_PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION/></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_EXISTS_F17></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17><CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><NO_PAYABLE_DOCUMENTS/></CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><DAY>01</DAY><MONTH>06</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>12:00</TIME></RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><LANGUAGE><LANGUAGE_EC VALUE="EN"/></LANGUAGE></ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE></PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/><RELATES_TO_EU_PROJECT_NO/><ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><P>The contracting authority considers that this contract may be suitable for economic operators that are small or medium enterprises (SMEs). However, any selection of tenderers will be based solely on the criteria set out for the procurement.The Authority reserves the right to amend any condition related to security of information to reflect any changes in national law or government policy. If any contract documents are accompanied by instructions on safeguarding classified information (e.g. a Security Aspects Letter), the Authority reserves the right to amend the terms of these instructions to reflect any changes in national law or government policy, whether in respect of the applicable protective marking scheme, specific protective markings given, the aspects to which any protective marking applies, or otherwise. The link below to the Gov.uk website provides information on the Government Security Classification.</P><P>https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/government-security-classifications</P><P>Advertising Regime OJEU: This contract opportunity is published in the Official Journal of the European Union (OJEU),the MoD Defence Contracts Bulletin and www.contracts.mod.uk</P><P>The Authority intends to invite no more than 6 Economic Operators to tender for this requirement and will therefore conduct a pre-qualification exercise to assist in any down select. Only those Economic Operators who can demonstrate a sufficient level of economic and financial standing and technical or professional ability against the Authority's pre-qualification criteria may be invited to tender. Should more than 6 Economic Operators fulfil the selection criteria, the Authority reserves the right to conduct a further down selection. Full details on how to access the 'Dynamic' Pre-Qualification Questionnaire linked to this advert are contained in the final two paragraphs below. The Authority reserves the right to seek independent financial and market advice to validate information declared, or to assist in any pre-qualification evaluation.</P><P>Potential suppliers should note:</P><P>The Authority will require bidders to provide evidence that they hold a Firearms Dealers Licence as part of their tender submission.</P><P>Section 4 Part 1: Form D (Economic and Financial Standing). The Authority's preferred response is 4.2.1 (most recent 2 (two) years audited accounts). However, other means of establishing financial standing (serials 4.2.2 - 4.2.4) are acceptable provided they contain the requisite level of detail and are fully justified.</P><P>A Cyber Risk Assessment has been carried out for this requirement. The risk has been assessed as LOW, and the reference number is RAR-W3KQ8S5X. Potential suppliers should log on at the address below and complete a Supplier Assurance Questionnaire (SAQ), the results of which must be submitted along with the bidder's tender response.</P><P>https://supplier-cyber-protection.service.gov.uk</P><P>Guidance on how to access the Supplier Cyber Protection service can be found in the supporting documents linked to the DPQQ.</P><P>DOWN SELECT PROCESS.</P><P>Detailed in the DPQQ Evaluation Plan included in the supporting documentation.</P><P>Bidders should note that any ITT documents included in the supporting documentation are for information purposes only, at this stage.</P><P>Suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P><P>The information and/or documents for this opportunity are available on http://www.contracts.mod.uk</P><P>You must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password. Please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P><P>Suppliers must log in, go to your Response Manager and add the following Access Code: 9KEV9CM3B3.</P><P>Please ensure you follow any instruction provided to you here.</P><P>The deadline for submitting your response(s) is detailed within this contract notice, you will also have visibility of the deadline date, once you have added the Access code via DCO as the opening and closing date is visible within the opportunity.</P><P>Please ensure that you allow yourself plenty of time when responding to this opportunity prior to the closing date and time, especially if you have been asked to upload documents.</P><P>If you experience any difficulties please refer to the online Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ&#x92;s) or the User Guides or contact the MOD DCO Helpdesk by emailing support@contracts.mod.uk or Telephone 0800 282 324.</P><P>GO Reference: GO-2018430-DCB-12333923.</P></ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C, Other</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Rm G6, Bldg 114, Thiepval Barracks</ADDRESS><TOWN>Lisburn</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>BFPO 801</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE></PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE><DAY>30</DAY><MONTH>04</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR></NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE></CONTRACT_DEFENCE></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>