<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="133709-2018" EDITION="2018060"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-135955-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180515</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>60</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180327</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 060-133709</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:133709-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>http://forsvaret.dk/fmi</IA_URL_GENERAL><IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=201148&amp;B=KA</IA_URL_ETENDERING><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="34221000">Special-purpose mobile containers</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="44611500">Water tanks</ORIGINAL_CPV><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="DK032">Sydjylland</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS><VALUES_LIST><VALUES TYPE="GLOBAL"><RANGE_VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="DKK">40 000 000</VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="DKK">60 000 000</VALUE></RANGE_VALUE></VALUES><VALUES TYPE="GLOBAL"><RANGE_VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="DKK">40 000 000</VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="DKK">60 000 000</VALUE></RANGE_VALUE></VALUES></VALUES_LIST></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180323</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180515 13:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="4">Negotiated procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>01217</HEADING><DIRECTIVE VALUE="2009/81/EC"/></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Дaния</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Подвижни контейнери със специална употреба</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Mobilní kontejnery pro zvláštní účely</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Mobile containere til specielle formål</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Dänemark</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Fahrbare Großbehälter für besondere Zwecke</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Δανία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Κινητά εμπορευματοκιβώτια ειδικής χρήσης</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Denmark</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Special-purpose mobile containers</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Contenedores móviles para usos especiales</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Taani</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Eriotstarbelised teisaldatavad konteinerid</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Tanska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Erikoiskäyttöön tarkoitetut siirrettävät kontit</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Danemark</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Conteneurs mobiles à usage spécifique</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Danmhairg, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Special-purpose mobile containers</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Pokretni kontejneri za posebne namjene</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Dánia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Különleges célú mozgatható konténer</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Danimarca</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Container mobili speciali</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Danija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Specialios paskirties mobilūs konteineriai</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Dānija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Īpaša lietojuma pārvietojamie konteineri</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>id-Danimarka</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Kontenituri ambulanti għal skopijiet speċjali</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Denemarken</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Mobiele containers voor bijzondere doeleinden</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Dania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Cysterny samojezdne specjalnego zastosowania</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Contentores móveis para usos especiais</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Danemarca</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Containere mobile cu utilizare specială</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Špeciálne mobilné kontajnery</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Mobilni zabojniki za posebne namene</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Fraktcontainrar för särskilda ändamål</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Danish Defence Acquisition and Logistics Organization (DALO)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><CONTRACT_DEFENCE CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="17" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE CTYPE="SUPPLIES"><CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Danish Defence Acquisition and Logistics Organization (DALO)</OFFICIALNAME><NATIONALID>16287180</NATIONALID></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Lautrupbjerg 1-5</ADDRESS><TOWN>Ballerup</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>2750</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/><CONTACT_POINT>Danish Defence Acquisition and Logistics Organization</CONTACT_POINT><ATTENTION>Nikolaj Lysebjerg Hansen</ATTENTION><PHONE>+45 72307869</PHONE><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>niha@kammeradvokaten.dk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><URL_GENERAL>http://forsvaret.dk/fmi</URL_GENERAL><URL_INFORMATION>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=201148&amp;B=KA</URL_INFORMATION><URL_PARTICIPATE>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=201148&amp;B=KA</URL_PARTICIPATE></INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><FURTHER_INFORMATION><IDEM/></FURTHER_INFORMATION><SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><IDEM/></SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO><IDEM/></TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO></NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY VALUE="MINISTRY"/><TYPE_OF_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF_NO/></PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><TITLE_CONTRACT><P>Framework Agreement Regarding Supply of Water Tank Container Systems and Related Services</P></TITLE_CONTRACT><TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><TYPE_CONTRACT VALUE="SUPPLIES"/><TYPE_SUPPLIES_CONTRACT VALUE="PURCHASE"/></TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><LOCATION_NUTS><n2016:NUTS CODE="DK032"/></LOCATION_NUTS><NOTICE_INVOLVES_DEFENCE VALUE="ESTABLISHMENT_FRAMEWORK_AGREEMENT"/><F17_FRAMEWORK><SINGLE_OPERATOR/><DURATION_FRAMEWORK_MONTH>84</DURATION_FRAMEWORK_MONTH><TOTAL_ESTIMATED><COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY CURRENCY="DKK"><RANGE_VALUE_COST><LOW_VALUE FMTVAL="40000000">40 000 000</LOW_VALUE><HIGH_VALUE FMTVAL="60000000">60 000 000</HIGH_VALUE></RANGE_VALUE_COST></COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY></TOTAL_ESTIMATED></F17_FRAMEWORK><SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><P>Through a framework agreement, the Danish defence acquisition and logistics organization (DALO) is planning to purchase the most economically advantageous container systems (Water Tanks) for the Danish defence.</P><P>The Water tank container systems are intended to be used for multiple tasks related to storage and distribution of potable water. The Container systems will be based on either ISO 1CX containers or ISO 1CC containers.</P><P>The Water tank container systems are all mobile and shall be able to be deployed world-wide in a large variety of climatic conditions.</P><P>The carrier for the Water tank container systems is a tactical truck fitted with a hook lift system. The Water tank container systems shall be fully functional when placed on the ground and when mounted on a truck. The Water tank container system shall be able to be transported in rough terrain.</P><P>Some of the Water tank container systems shall be equipped with pumps. Some of the Water tank container systems shall be self-supported with the necessary power (engine). The Water tank container systems shall also be able to be supplied with power from external power sources.</P><P>The Water tank container systems shall be designed and equipped so all tasks can be performed in a secure and safe manner.</P><P>The Water tank container systems are intended to be used across the different services in the Danish defence both domestic and international and with short notice. The Container systems are through their lifetime intended to be continuously moved to locations where needed and will be used both in training as well as in national and international operations.</P><P>The framework agreement includes service and training (including maintenance, modifications and training of personnel) and delivery of spare parts and inventory.</P><P>Under the framework agreement the buyer will commit to purchase deliverables for a minimum amount within the first 2 years after commencement of the framework agreement. The amount is subject to negotiations but will at least be 20 000 000 DKK. Beyond this, the buyer shall not be obliged to purchase any minimum quantity of deliverables.</P></SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><CPV><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="34221000"/></CPV_MAIN><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="44611500"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL></CPV><SUBCONTRACTING><INDICATE_ANY_SHARE VALUE="NO"/><INDICATE_ANY_CHANGE VALUE="NO"/><SUBCONTRACT_AWARD_PART VALUE="NO"/><IDENTIFY_SUBCONTRACT VALUE="NO"/></SUBCONTRACTING><F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><DIV_INTO_LOT_NO/></F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><ACCEPTED_VARIANTS VALUE="NO"/></DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><QUANTITY_SCOPE><NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY CURRENCY="DKK"><RANGE_VALUE_COST><LOW_VALUE FMTVAL="40000000">40 000 000</LOW_VALUE><HIGH_VALUE FMTVAL="60000000">60 000 000</HIGH_VALUE></RANGE_VALUE_COST></COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY></NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><NO_OPTIONS/><NO_RECURRENT_CONTRACT/></QUANTITY_SCOPE><PERIOD_WORK_DATE_STARTING><MONTHS>084</MONTHS></PERIOD_WORK_DATE_STARTING></OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><P>Reference is made to the tender documents with regard to the payment terms. Invoicing must be done in accordance with the applicable Danish legislation on public payments. At present, this is Danish consolidation act. nº 798 of June 2007 which requires invoicing to be done electronically. Exact terms will be stated in the contract.</P></MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><LEGAL_FORM><P>No particular legal form is required. If the contract is awarded to a group of suppliers (e.g. a consortium) the participants are required to undertake joint and several liabilities and to appoint one supplier to represent the group.</P></LEGAL_FORM><EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS><P>The performance of the framework agreement must be conducted in careful consideration of social responsibility, as stated in the conventions that underpin the principles of the UN Global Compact, and as articulated in the OECD Guidelines for multinational companies. In accordance to ILO Convention 94 on labor clauses in public contracts and circular no. 9471 of 30.6.2014 the framework agreement contains a labour clause.</P></EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS></CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><P>When submitting the offers (but not the request for participation), the tenderers must submit a solemn declaration stating to which degree the tenderer has unpaid overdue debt in relation to tax, duties or social security contributions under Danish law or under the law of the country in which the tenderer is established. A template for the declaration will be provided with the tender documents, and the tenderer is encouraged — but not obliged — to use it.</P><P>Be advised, that DALO shall exclude a tenderer which has unpaid overdue debt of 100 000 DKK or more to public authorities in relation to tax, duties or social security contributions under Danish law or under the law of the country in which the tenderer is established.</P><P>However, DALO may not exclude a tenderer which has provided sufficient documentation that the tenderer is reliable. DALO will decide whether the documentation is sufficient, hence the tenderer is considered reliable, based on guidelines equal to the guidelines provided for in Section 138(1-4) of the Danish Act nº 1564 of 15.12.2015 – The Public Procurement Act.</P></ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>The candidate must provide the following information:</P><P>A statement of the candidate’s general yearly turnover for the last 3 financial years, and (2) the candidate’s equity at the end of the last financial year, if publication of annual reports is required under the law of the country in which the candidate is established, and to the extent such information is available. When groups of entities (e.g. consortiums), including temporary joint ventures, participate in the tender procedure together, the documentation must be provided for each of the participating entities. If the candidate relies on the economic and financial standing of another entity or entities (e.g. a parent or sister company or a sub supplier), the documentation must equally be provided for each entity or entities.</P></EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION></F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY_SUBCONTRACTORS><EAF_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL><P>1) The candidate must have had a general yearly turnover of at least 10 000 000 DKK in each of the last 3 financial years. If the turnover is not stated in said currency, DALO will calculate the turnover based on the official exchange rate on the date this notice was published.</P><P>2) The candidate must have had a positive equity at the end of the last financial year.</P><P>If the candidate is composed of a group of entities (e.g. consortium), including temporary joint ventures, the general yearly turnover/equity is calculated as the sum of all the participants’ general yearly turnover/equity.</P><P>If the candidate relies on the economic and financial standing of an entity or entities the general yearly turnover/equity will be calculated as the sum of the candidate’s general yearly turnover/equity and the entity’s or entities’ general yearly turnover/equity.</P></EAF_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL></F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY_SUBCONTRACTORS><TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI><T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>The candidate must provide a list of the most important similar deliveries (references), cf. section II.1.5) carried out within the past 5 years prior to the deadline for the request to participate.</P><P>Only the deliveries (references) performed at the time of the deadline for the request to participate will be considered when assessing which candidate has documented the most relevant previous deliveries, cf. section IV.1.2). If the delivery in question is ongoing, it is only the part of the delivery which has been performed and completed at the time of the deadline for the request to participate which will be included in the assessment of the delivery.</P><P>The list should preferably include a short description of each delivery. The description should include a clear indication of which specific parts the deliveries are similar to the supplies and services described in section II.1.5). The description should also include a description of the candidate’s part(s) in the performance of the deliveries.</P><P>The description should contain information on</P><P>i. the date of the deliveries,</P><P>ii. the size and value of the deliveries,</P><P>iii. the recipients of the deliveries (specific names/countries are preferred, but not necessary; if no country specific information is included the candidate is asked to provide as much generic information as possible about the delivery), and</P><P>iv. services and training provided in connection with the deliveries (if any).</P><P>When specifying the date for the deliveries the candidate should state the date of commencement and completion. If this is not possible, e.g. because the delivery in question is performed on an ongoing basis according to a framework agreement, the description of the deliveries should nonetheless contain information on how the date is set.</P><P>The list must contain a maximum of 5 previous deliveries, regardless of whether the candidate is one entity, composed of a group of entities (e.g. consortium), including temporary joint ventures, or relies on the technical and professional capacity of other entities. If the list contains more than 5 deliveries DALO will only consider the first 5 deliveries on the list. Deliveries beyond that will be disregarded.</P></T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION></TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI><TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI_SUBCONTRACTORS><T_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL/></TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI_SUBCONTRACTORS></F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><SERVICES_CONTRACTS_SPECIFIC_CONDITIONS><NO_EXEC_SERVICE_RESERVED_PARTICULAR_PROFESSION/><REQUESTS_NAMES_PROFESSIONAL_QUALIFICATIONS VALUE="NO"/></SERVICES_CONTRACTS_SPECIFIC_CONDITIONS></LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><PT_NEGOTIATED_CHOICE/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED><OPE_ENVISAGED_NUMBER>3</OPE_ENVISAGED_NUMBER><OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA><P>The limitation of candidates will be based on an evaluation of which candidates have documented the most relevant previous deliveries in comparison to the contract/purchases described in section II.1.5) above, in terms of the nature and quantity of the previous deliveries. The evaluation will be based on the list submitted by the candidates. Please note that any ambiguities and/or incomprehensibilities in the information submitted under III.2.3) may be regarded negatively in the evaluation when selecting the limited numbers of candidates.</P></OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA></MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED><REDUCTION_OF_THE_NUMBER VALUE="NO"/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><MOST_ECONOMICALLY_ADVANTAGEOUS_TENDER><CRITERIA_STATED_IN_OTHER_DOCUMENT/></MOST_ECONOMICALLY_ADVANTAGEOUS_TENDER></AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE><NO_USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION/></IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE></AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><P>7520467</P></FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17><NO_PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_EXISTS_F17/></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17><RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><DAY>15</DAY><MONTH>05</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>13:00</TIME></RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><LANGUAGE><LANGUAGE_EC VALUE="EN"/></LANGUAGE></ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE></PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/><RELATES_TO_EU_PROJECT_NO/><ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><P>This tender is conducted according to the negotiated procedure, cf. Directive 2009/81/EC of the European Parliament and the Council, article 26. The tenderers who will be invited to submit tenders will receive further practical information regarding the negotiated procedure in the Instructions to tenderers.</P><P>Candidates shall submit applications for prequalification using the electronic tender platform at http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=201148&amp;B=KAdk Applications for pre-qualification can only be submitted on the electronic tender platform. Applications for pre-qualification submitted by e-mail, ordinary mail etc. will not be considered.</P><P>Please note, that each candidate can only submit one request for participation. If the same legal entity is a part of or in any other way participates in several applications, e.g. submits its own application and at the same time participates in a consortium which also applies, the candidates shall ensure that the same legal entity’s participation does not provide for opportunity for mutual coordination of their applications and offers. DALO reserves the right to request the candidates to establish and reassure DALO that the same legal entity’s participation does not threaten the transparency and distort competition between the tenderers.</P><P>DALO reserves the right – but is not obliged – to use remedies equal to the remedies provided for in Section 159(5) of the Danish Act nº 1564 of 15.12.2015 on tender procedures if applications or tenders do not fulfil the formalities of the tender documents.</P><P>DALO have prepared a prequalification questionnaire which candidates are strongly encouraged to use when submitting their applications. The questionnaire contains questions, forms and templates for providing information etc. in accordance with the requirements in this Contract notice. However, it is emphasized that it is the sole responsibility of the candidate that the information provided fulfils the requirements.</P><P>The questionnaire is available on the electronic tender platform at http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=201148&amp;B=KA</P><P>According to the EU public procurement directives, a candidate may rely on the economic and financial standing and/or technical and/or professional capacity of other entities, regardless of the legal nature of the links with the entities. If a candidate wants to rely on other entities and wishes that the capacity of other entities is taken into account when DALO assesses the suitability of the candidate, the candidate must prove that the other entities will and shall put the relevant resources at the disposal of the candidate. A template for a declaration from the supporting entity to this effect is included in the pre-qualification questionnaire referred to above.</P></ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Klagenævnet for Udbud (The Complaints Board for Public Procurement)</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Toldboden 2</ADDRESS><TOWN>Viborg</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>8800</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>klfu@naevneneshus.dk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS><PHONE>+45 72405708</PHONE><URL>http://www.klfu.dk</URL></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><LODGING_OF_APPEALS><LODGING_OF_APPEALS_PRECISION><P>Pursuant to Section 3 of the Danish consolidation Act nº 593 of 2.6.2016 on the Complaints board for public procurement (available at www.retsinformation.dk), the following time limits for filing a complaint apply:</P><P>Complaints regarding a candidate not being pre-qualified must be filed with The Complaints board for public procurement within 20 calendar days starting the day after the Contracting Authority has sent notification to the candidates involved, provided that the notification includes a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P><P>Other complaints must be filed with the Complaints board for public procurement within:</P><P>1) 45 calendar days after the Contracting Authority has published a contract award notice in the Official Journal of the European Union (with effect from the day following the publication date).</P><P>2) 30 calendar days starting the day after the Contracting Authority has informed the tenderers in question, that the Contracting Authority has entered into a contract based on a framework agreement through reopening of competition or a dynamic purchasing system, provided that the notification includes a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P><P>3) 6 months starting the day after the Contracting Authority has sent notification to the candidates/tenderers involved that the Contracting Authority has entered into the framework agreement, provided that the notification included a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P><P>4) 20 calendar days starting the day after the Contracting Authority has published a notice concerning his decision to uphold the contract, cf. the principle in § 185(2) of the Danish act on Public procurement (act nº 1564 of 15.12.2015 – available at www.retsinformation.dk).</P><P>The complainant must inform the Contracting Authority of the complaint in writing at the latest simultaneously with the lodge of the complaint to the Complaints board for public procurement stating whether the complaint has been lodged in the stand-still period, cf. § 6(4) of the act on the Complaints board for public procurement. If the complaint has not been lodged in the stand-still period, the complainant must also state whether it is requested that the appeal is granted delaying effect, cf. § 12(1) of the said act.</P><P>The e-mail of the Complaints board for public procurement is stated in Section VI.4.1.</P><P>The Complaints board for public procurement’s own guidance note concerning complaints is available at the internet address stated in section VI.4.1.</P></LODGING_OF_APPEALS_PRECISION></LODGING_OF_APPEALS><LODGING_INFORMATION_FOR_SERVICE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Klagenævnet for udbud (The Danish Competition and Consumer Authority)</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Carl Jacobsens Vej 35</ADDRESS><TOWN>Valby</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>2500</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>kfst@kfst.dk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS><PHONE>+45 41715000</PHONE></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></LODGING_INFORMATION_FOR_SERVICE></PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE><DAY>23</DAY><MONTH>03</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR></NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE></CONTRACT_DEFENCE></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>