<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="169404-2018"
            EDITION="2018076">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-173301-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180524</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>76</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180419</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 076-169404</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:169404-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.scotland.gov.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://www.publictendersscotland.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79311000">Survey services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKM">SCOTLAND</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKM">SCOTLAND</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180417</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180524 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="6">Body governed by public law</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Глазгоу</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги, свързани с проучвания</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Průzkum služeb</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Rundspørger</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Umfragen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Γλασκώβη</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες ερευνών</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Survey services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de estudios</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Turu-uuringud</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kyselytutkimuspalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services d'études</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glaschú</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Survey services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge anketiranja</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Felmérési, közvélemény-kutatási szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di indagine</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Apklausų paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glāsgova</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Aptaujas pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' l-istħarriġ</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Uitvoeren van studies</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi w zakresie ankiet</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços relacionados com inquéritos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de studii</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Služby spojené s prieskumom</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve anketiranja</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Glasgow</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Undersökningar</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Scottish Government</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>96c2fe77-a386-4bcb-ac6e-4ba5478df63e</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Scottish Government</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Atlantic Quay, 150 Broomielaw</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Glasgow</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>G2 8LU</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Julia Kerr</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+44 1312443126</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>julia.kerr@gov.scot</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.scotland.gov.uk</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/search/Search_AuthProfile.aspx?ID=AA10482</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CENTRAL_PURCHASING/>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://www.publictendersscotland.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://www.publictendersscotland.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="BODY_PUBLIC"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Schools Adolescent Lifestyle Survey (SALSUS)</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>Case 387608</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79311000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Case 387608 Schools Adolescent Lifestyle Survey (SALSUS). A single supplier is required for the period 1.8.2018 to 31.7.2020.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Case 387608 Schools Adolescent Lifestyle Survey (SALSUS). A single service provider is required for the period 1.8.2018 to 31.7.2020.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Quality</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>75</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>25</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">24</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>Tenderer to provide information for optional services:</P>
                  <P>— themed topic reports,</P>
                  <P>— answering ad hoc requests,</P>
                  <P>— teaching packs,</P>
                  <P>— road show events.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Economic operators may be excluded from this competition if they are in any of the situations referred to in Regulation 58 of the Public Contracts (Scotland) Regulations 2015.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Statement for 4B.4:</P>
               <P>Bidders must demonstrate a Current Ratio of no less than 0,9. Current Ratio will be calculated as follows: Net current assets divided by net current liabilities.</P>
               <P>There must be no qualification or contra-indication from any evidence provided in support of the bidders economic and financial standing.</P>
               <P>Bidders who do not comply with the above financial requirements but are part of a Group, can provide a Parent Guarantee if the Parent company satisfies the financial requirements stipulated above.</P>
               <P>Statement for 4B.5:</P>
               <P>It is a requirement of this contract that bidders hold or can commit to obtain prior to the commencement of any subsequently awarded contract, the types of insurance indicated below.</P>
               <P>Employer's (Compulsory) Liability Insurance = 5 000 000 GBP.</P>
               <P>Public Liability Insurance = 2 000 000 GBP.</P>
               <P>Professional Indemnity Insurance = 2 000 000 GBP.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Statement for 4C.1.2:</P>
               <P>Bidders will be required to provide examples that demonstrate that they have the relevant experience to deliver the services.</P>
               <P>Please note: In PCS-T, responses to 4C.1.2 should be given as a clearly labelled attachment to this question.</P>
               <P>Statement for 4D.1.</P>
               <P>1. the Bidder must hold a UKAS (or equivalent) accredited independent third party certificate of compliance in accordance with BS EN ISO 9001 (or equivalent); or</P>
               <P>2. the Bidder must have the following:</P>
               <P>a. a documented policy regarding quality management. The policy must set out responsibilities for quality management demonstrating that the bidder has, and continues to implement, a quality management policy that is authorised by their Chief Executive, or equivalent, which is periodically reviewed at a senior management level. The policy must be relevant to the nature and scale of the work to be undertaken and set out responsibilities for quality management throughout the organisation;</P>
               <P>b. documented procedures for periodically reviewing, correcting and improving quality performance including processes for ensuring that the bidder’s quality management is effective in reducing / preventing incidents of substandard delivery. This must include the quality of output and general performance,</P>
               <P>c. a documented process for ensuring that quality management is effective in reducing / preventing incidents of substandard delivery. This must include the quality of output and general performance. The bidder must be able to provide copies of their organisation’s documentation procedures that meet current agreed good practice. These must include the arrangements for quality management throughout the bidder’s organisation. They must set out how the bidder’s organisation will carry out its policy, with a clear indication of how the arrangements are communicated to the workforce;</P>
               <P>d. documented arrangements for providing the bidder’s workforce with quality related training and information appropriate to the type of work for which this organisation is likely to bid. This will demonstrate that the organisation has in place, and implements, training arrangements to ensure that its workforce has sufficient skills and understanding to discharge their various responsibilities. These must include a programme of training that will keep the workforce up to date with required knowledge about quality related issues, including copies of job profiles; training manuals and records;</P>
               <P>e. documented arrangements that the organisation has a system for monitoring quality management procedures on an on-going basis. The bidder’s organisation must be able to provide evidence of systematic, periodic review and improvement of quality in respect of output and general performance;</P>
               <P>f. documented arrangements for ensuring that the bidders apply quality management measures that are appropriate to the work for which they are being engaged;</P>
               <P>g. a documented process demonstrating how the bidder deals with complaints. The bidder must be able to provide details of how their organisation maintains records of any complaints received and how corrective measures are carried out to prevent re-occurrence.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-05-24</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">6</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-05-24</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>ESPD will be scored on a pass / fail basis.</P>
               <P>Question Scoring Methodology for Award Criteria outlined in invitation to tender:</P>
               <P>0 — Unacceptable. Nil or inadequate response. Fails to demonstrate an ability to meet the requirement.</P>
               <P>1 — Poor. Response is partially relevant but generally poor. The response addresses some elements of the requirement but contains insufficient/limited detail or explanation to demonstrate how the requirement will be fulfilled.</P>
               <P>2 — Acceptable. Response is relevant and acceptable. The response addresses a broad understanding of the requirement but may lack details on how the requirement will be fulfilled in certain areas.</P>
               <P>3 — Good. Response is relevant and good. The response is sufficiently detailed to demonstrate a good understanding and provides details on how the requirements will be fulfilled.</P>
               <P>4 — Excellent. Response is completely relevant and excellent overall. The response is comprehensive, unambiguous and demonstrates a thorough understanding of the requirement and provides details of how the requirement will be met in full.</P>
               <P>Bidders must complete the ESPD (Scotland) to demonstrate adherence to the Exclusion and Selection Criteria for this procurement. If there are named subcontractors / technicians upon which the bidder will rely to meet the selection criteria, these named parties must complete and reattach the ESPD Supplier Response Form attached to ESPD Questions 2C.1.1 (Technicians) and 2D.1.2 (Subcontractors) on PCS-T. These parties must complete the first 3 sections of the ESPD form, as well as any part of the Section 4 selection criteria that the main bidder will rely upon the parties to fulfil. If parties have not yet been identified, this information may be required at a later date. Scottish Government reserves the right to request this information from relevant parties upon whom the main bidder will not rely to fulfil selection criteria.</P>
               <P>4C.10 Bidders will be required to confirm whether they intend to subcontract and if so, for what proportion of the contract.</P>
               <P>Note: The buyer is using PCS-Tender to carry out this procurement process. Please note this is a separate website and if you are not already registered, registration will be required.</P>
               <P>To access PCS-Tender, record your interest in this notice and access the tender documentation please visit https://www.publictendersscotland.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk and search for project Code 10687 under ITTs Open to All Suppliers. Please use the Search / Filter function, then select Project Code from the drop-down. Please note that once you have expressed interest in the ITT it will move to your My ITTs area.</P>
               <P>The buyer is using PCS-Tender to conduct this ITT exercise. The Project code is 10687</P>
               <P>For more information see: http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/info/InfoCentre.aspx?ID=2343</P>
               <P>(SC Ref:539375).</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Scottish Government</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Victoria Quay, Leith</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Edinburgh</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>EH6 6QQ</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1312447556</PHONE>
               <URL>http://www.scotland.gov.uk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-17</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
