<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="069085-2018" EDITION="2018032"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-064690-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180305</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>32</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180215</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 032-069085</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:069085-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="ET"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79111000">Legal advisory services</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="85300000">Social work and related services</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="85320000">Social services</ORIGINAL_CPV><REF_NOTICE><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 001-000041</NO_DOC_OJS></REF_NOTICE></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180209</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180305 17:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="2">Additional information</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="2">Submission for one lot only</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="Z">Not specified</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>AP3EA</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Etiopien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ICD - Teknisk bistand til støtte for GCCA+(Global Climate Change Alliance Plus)/integration af intelligent klimaplanlægning og metoder til gennemførelse af programmet for programmet for produktive sikkerhedsnet IV (PSNP4) i Etiopien</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Äthiopien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Technische Hilfe zur Unterstützung im Zusammenhang mit der Global Climate Change Alliance Plus GCCA+/Einbeziehung von Ansätzen intelligenter Planung und Umsetzung der Klimapolitik als Querschnittsaufgabe in das Programm für produktive Sicherheitsnetze IV (PSNP4) in Äthiopien</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Ethiopia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Ababa</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Technical Assistance to Support Global Climate Change Alliance Plus (GCCA+)/Mainstreaming of Climate Smart Planning and Implementation Approaches into the Productive Safety Net Program IV (PSNP4) in Ethiopia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Etiopía</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ICD - Asistencia técnica para prestar apoyo a la AMCC+/la integración de enfoques de planificación y ejecución inteligentes en el ámbito climático en el programa de redes de seguridad productivas IV (PSNP4) en Etiopía</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Etiopia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Tekninen tuki seuraavien tukemiseksi: maailmanlaajuinen ilmastonmuutosliittouma (GCCA+) / ilmaston kannalta älykkäiden suunnittelua ja toteutusta koskevien lähestymistapojen sisällyttäminen tuottavia turvaverkkoja koskevaan ohjelmaan IV (PSNP4) Etiopiassa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Éthiopie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis-Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ICD - Assistance technique en soutien à l'Alliance mondiale contre le changement climatique+ (AMCC+)/Intégration des approches de planification et de mise en œuvre intelligentes en matière de climat dans le programme de filet de sécurité productif IV (PSNP4) en Éthiopie</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Αιθιοπία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Αντίς Αμπέμπα</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Τεχνική βοήθεια για την συμμαχία για την αλλαγή του κλίματος του πλανήτη (GCCA+)/ενσωμάτωση έξυπνου σχεδιασμού για το κλίμα και προσεγγίσεις υλοποίησης στο πλαίσιο του προγράμματος δημιουργίας δικτύων ασφαλείας ελάχιστης παραγωγικότητας IV (PSNP4) στην Αιθιοπία</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Etiopia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Assistenza tecnica a sostegno dell'Alleanza mondiale contro il cambiamento climatico+ (GCCA+)/integrazione di approcci di pianificazione e attuazione intelligente in campo climatico nel programma Rete di sicurezza produttiva IV (PSNP4) in Etiopia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Ethiopië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Technische bijstand ter ondersteuning van het Wereldwijd bondgenootschap tegen klimaatverandering plus en het mainstreamen van slimme klimaatplannings- en uitvoeringsbenaderingen in het vierde programma inzake productieve vangnetten in Ethiopië</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Etiópia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Adis-Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ICD - Assistência técnica para apoiar a Aliança Global contra as Alterações Climáticas Mais (AGAC+) /integração de abordagens de implementação e planeamento inteligente em matéria de clima no programa da rede de segurança produtiva IV (PSNP4) na Etiópia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Etiopien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Finansieringsinstrumentet för utvecklingssamarbete - Tekniskt bistånd till stöd för den globala klimatförändringsalliansen+/integrering av metoder för klimatsmart planering och genomförande i programmet för produktivt skyddsnät IV (PSNP4) i Etiopien</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Etiopie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Technická pomoc na podporu globální aliance pro boj proti změně klimatu plus (GCCA+) / začlenění inteligentních přístupů týkajících se plánování a provádění v oblasti klimatu do programu sítě bezpečnosti produktivity IV (PSNP4) v Etiopii</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Etioopia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Tehniline abi, et toetada Etioopias kliimaga seotud aruka kavandamise ja rakendamise lähenemisviiside IV tootmisalase turvavõrkude programmiga (PSNP4) integreerimise peavoolustamist / ülemaailmset kliimamuutuste liitu (GCCA+)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Etiópia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addisz-Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Szakmai segítségnyújtás az éghajlatváltozás elleni globális szövetség (GCCA+) támogatásához / Az éghajlatváltozás intelligens tervezését és végrehajtását célzó megközelítéseknek a IV. Eredményes biztonsági háló programban (PSNP4) történő érvényesítése Etiópiában</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Etiopija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Adis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Techninė pagalba remti Pasaulinį kovos su klimato kaita aljansą+ (PKKKA+) / klimato pažangių planavimo ir įgyvendinimo principų įtraukimą į produktyvaus apsaugos tinklo programą IV (PSNP4) Etiopijoje</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Etiopija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Adisabeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ASI - Tehniskā palīdzība ar mērķi atbalstīt GCCA+ / klimata jomas pārdomātas plānošanas un ieviešanas pieeju integrēšanu Produktīvā drošības tīkla IV programmā (PSNP4) Etiopijā</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>l-Etjopja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Ababa</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>SKŻ - Għajnuna teknika biex tappoġġja lill-Global Climate Change Alliance Plus (GCCA+)/l-ippjanar intelliġenti mhux diskriminatorju dwar il-klima u l-approċċi ta' implimentazzjoni fil-Programm IV dwar ix-Xibka tas-Sigurtà Produttiva (PSNP4) fl-Etjopja</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Etiopia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Pomoc techniczna na potrzeby wsparcia światowego sojuszu na rzecz przeciwdziałania zmianom klimatycznym (GCCA+)/Włączenie podejść obejmujących inteligentne planowanie i wdrażanie w dziedzinie klimatu do programu sieci bezpieczeństwa produkcji IV (PSNP4) w Etiopii</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Etiópia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Technická pomoc na podporu Globálnej aliancie proti zmene klímy plus (GCCA+)/začlenenie inteligentných prístupov týkajúcich sa plánovania a vykonávania v oblasti klímy do Programu produktívnej záchrannej siete IV (PSNP4) v Etiópii</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Etiopija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Adis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Tehnična pomoč za podporo globalnega zavezništva o podnebnih spremembah+ (GCCA+)/vključitev pametnih pristopov načrtovanja in izvajanja na področju podnebja v program produktivnih varnostnih mrež IV (PSNP4) v Etiopiji</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Aetóip, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Ababa</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Cúnamh teicniúil chun tacú leis an gclár Comhaontas Domhanda um Athrú Aeráide+ (GCCA+)/Príomhshruthú na Pleanála Cliste i leith na hAeráide agus Cineálacha Cur Chuige um Chur chun Feidhme i gClár Líontáin Sábhála Tháirgiúil IV (PSNP4) san Aetóip</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Етиопия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Адис Абеба</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ИСР - Техническа помощ за подкрепа на Глобалния съюз за изменение на климата+ (GCCA+)/Насочване на съобразени с промените в климата подходи за планиране и прилагане в програмата за продуктивни безопасни мрежи IV (PSNP4) в Етиопия</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Etiopia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Addis Ababa</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ICD - Asistență tehnică pentru a susține Alianța mondială împotriva schimbărilor climatice (GCCA)/integrarea abordărilor inteligente de planificare și implementare privind clima în programul referitor la rețelele de siguranță productive IV (PSNP4) în Etiopia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Etiopija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Adis Abeba</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>DCI - Tehnička pomoć za podršku za Globalni savez za borbu protiv klimatskih promjena (GCCA+)/uključivanje pametnih pristupa planiranju i provedbi u području klime u Program proizvodne sigurnosne mreže IV (PSNP4) u Etiopiji</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den Europæiske Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">La Unión Europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan unioni</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Union européenne</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Unione europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europese Unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">União Europeia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska unionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Liit</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Az Európai Unió</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos Sąjunga</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Savienība</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">L-Unjoni Ewropea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Unia Europejska</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európska únia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska unija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An tAontas Eorpach</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейски съюз</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Uniunea Europeană</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska unija</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: ICD - Teknisk bistand til støtte for GCCA+(Global Climate Change Alliance Plus)/integration af intelligent klimaplanlægning og metoder til gennemførelse af programmet for programmet for produktive sikkerhedsnet IV (PSNP4) i Etiopien</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Berigtigelse</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement til Den Europæiske Unions Tidende, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den Europæiske Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, repræsenteret ved Europa-Kommissionen (Den Europæiske Unions delegation i Etiopien), for og på vegne af Etiopien, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>I stedet for:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Foreløbig udbudsdato 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Udvælgelseskriterier</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Ansøgeren har udført tjenesteydelser under mindst 1 kontrakt med et budget, der mindst svarer til denne kontrakts, på områderne for teknisk bistand og kapacitetsudvikling med henblik på gennemførelse af statslige multisektorielle programmer, der blev gennemført på et hvilket som helst tidspunkt i referenceperioden. Det vil sige, at projektet, til hvilket ansøgeren refererer, kan være påbegyndt eller fuldført på ethvert tidspunkt i løbet af den anførte periode, men ikke nødvendigvis skal være påbegyndt og fuldført i løbet af den periode eller være gennemført i løbet af perioden samlet set. Ansøgere/tilbudsgivere kan henvise til projekter fuldført i referenceperioden (men påbegyndt tidligere) eller projekter, der endnu ikke er fuldført. I forbindelse med det første tilfælde vil projektet blive taget i betragtning i sin helhed, hvis der er fremlagt korrekt dokumentation for udførelse (erklæring eller attest fra den enhed, der tildelte kontrakten, dokumentation for endelig betaling). I forbindelse med projekter, der endnu ikke er fuldført, vil udelukkende den del, der er fuldført med vellykket resultat i referenceperioden, men påbegyndt tidligere, blive taget i betragtning. Denne del skal dokumenteres (på samme vis som for fuldførte projekter) med angivelse af værdien. Hvis en ansøger/tilbudsgiver har gennemført projektet i et konsortium, skal den andel, som er vellykket udført af ansøgeren/tilbudsgiveren, klart fremgå af den skriftlige dokumentation sammen med en beskrivelse af arten af de udførte tjenesteydelser, hvis udvælgelseskriterierne vedrørende relevansen af erfaringen er blevet anvendt.</P><P>[...]</P><P>I tilfælde af at mere end 8 ansøgere opfylder ovennævnte kriterier for udvælgelse, vil de relative stærke og svage sider ved ansøgningerne blive gennemgået igen med henblik på at finde de 8 bedste ansøgere. De eneste faktorer, der vil blive taget i betragtning ved denne fornyede gennemgang, er:</P><P>— Antallet af projekter med relation til denne kontrakt,</P><P>— Værdien af projekter med relation til denne kontrakt,</P><P>— Antallet af projekter med relation til denne kontrakt og gennemført i Afrika syd for Sahara.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Sidste frist for modtagelse af ansøgninger</P><P>9.2.2018 (17:00), lokal tid i Østafrika.</P><P>Ansøgninger, der modtages af den ordregivende myndighed efter denne frist, vil ikke blive taget i betragtning.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Yderligere oplysninger</P><P>Eventuelle anmodninger om yderligere præciseringer skal sendes til Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu senest 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Læses:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Foreløbig udbudsdato 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Udvælgelseskriterier</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Ansøgeren har udført tjenesteydelser under mindst 3 kontrakter, der hver har et minimum kontraktbeløb på 3 000 000 EUR, på områderne for teknisk bistand og kapacitetsudvikling med henblik på gennemførelse af statslige multisektorielle programmer, der blev gennemført på et hvilket som helst tidspunkt i referenceperioden. Det vil sige, at projektet, til hvilket ansøgeren refererer, kan være påbegyndt eller fuldført på ethvert tidspunkt i løbet af den anførte periode, men ikke nødvendigvis skal være påbegyndt og fuldført i løbet af den periode eller være gennemført i løbet af perioden samlet set. Ansøgere/tilbudsgivere kan henvise til projekter fuldført i referenceperioden (men påbegyndt tidligere) eller projekter, der endnu ikke er fuldført. I forbindelse med det første tilfælde vil projektet blive taget i betragtning i sin helhed, hvis der er fremlagt korrekt dokumentation for udførelse (erklæring eller attest fra den enhed, der tildelte kontrakten, dokumentation for endelig betaling). I forbindelse med projekter, der endnu ikke er fuldført, vil udelukkende den del, der er fuldført med vellykket resultat i referenceperioden, men påbegyndt tidligere, blive taget i betragtning. Denne del skal dokumenteres (på samme vis som for fuldførte projekter) med angivelse af værdien. Hvis en ansøger/tilbudsgiver har gennemført projektet i et konsortium, skal den andel, som er vellykket udført af ansøgeren/tilbudsgiveren, klart fremgå af den skriftlige dokumentation sammen med en beskrivelse af arten af de udførte tjenesteydelser, hvis udvælgelseskriterierne vedrørende relevansen af erfaringen er blevet anvendt.</P><P>[...]</P><P>I tilfælde af at mere end 8 ansøgere opfylder ovennævnte kriterier for udvælgelse, vil de relative stærke og svage sider ved ansøgningerne blive gennemgået igen med henblik på at finde de 8 bedste ansøgere. De eneste faktorer, der vil blive taget i betragtning ved denne fornyede gennemgang, er:</P><P>— Først, antallet af projekter relateret til denne kontrakt/projekt, hver med en værdi højere end 1 000 000 EUR, og i tilfælde af resultatlighed mellem ansøgere</P><P>— Det samlede kumulative værdi af gennemførte projekter (selv hvis hver enkelte er på mindre end 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Sidste frist for modtagelse af ansøgninger</P><P>5.3.2018 (17:00), lokal tid i Addis Abeba.</P><P>Ansøgninger, der modtages af den ordregivende myndighed efter denne frist, vil ikke blive taget i betragtning.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Yderligere oplysninger</P><P>Eventuelle anmodninger om yderligere præciseringer skal sendes til Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu senest 19.2.2018</P><P>Bemærk venligst at alle præciseringer, der blev modtaget med den tidligere berigtigelse, og den, der skal være modtaget før den 19. februar, vil blive besvaret sammen.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alle andre bestemmelser og betingelser i udbudsbekendtgørelsen forbliver uændrede. Ovenstående ændringer og/eller berigtigelser vil være at betragte som en integreret del af udbudsbekendtgørelsen.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: DCI - Technische Hilfe zur Unterstützung im Zusammenhang mit der Global Climate Change Alliance Plus GCCA+/Einbeziehung von Ansätzen intelligenter Planung und Umsetzung der Klimapolitik als Querschnittsaufgabe in das Programm für produktive Sicherheitsnetze IV (PSNP4) in Äthiopien</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Berichtigung</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement zum Amtsblatt der Europäischen Union, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertreten durch die Europäische Kommission, im Auftrag und für Rechnung von Äthiopien, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Äthiopien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Anstatt:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Voraussichtlicher Zeitpunkt der Aufforderung zur Angebotsabgabe 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Auswahlkriterien</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Der Bewerber hat im Rahmen von mindestens einem Auftrag, dessen Budget mindestens dem dieses Auftrags entsprach, Dienstleistungen im Bereich technische Hilfe und Kapazitätenentwicklung zur Umsetzung von sektorübergreifenden, regierungsgeführten Programmen erbracht, die zu einem beliebigen Zeitpunkt während des Referenzzeitraums ausgeführt wurden. Das heißt, das vom Bewerber genannte Referenzprojekt kann zu jedem Zeitpunkt während des angegebenen Zeitraums begonnen oder abgeschlossen worden sein; es muss jedoch nicht zwingend in diesem Zeitraum begonnen und abgeschlossen und auch nicht während des gesamten Zeitraums durchgeführt worden sein. Bewerber/Bieter können sich auf im Referenzzeitraum abgeschlossene Projekte (die jedoch früher aufgenommen wurden) oder auf noch nicht abgeschlossene Projekte beziehen. Im ersten Fall wird das Projekt in seiner Gesamtheit berücksichtigt, sofern ordnungsgemäße Ausführungsnachweise vorgelegt werden (Erklärung oder Bescheinigung der Stelle, welche den Auftrag vergeben hat, Nachweis einer Abschlusszahlung). Bei laufenden Projekten wird nur der Teil berücksichtigt, der im Referenzzeitraum zufriedenstellend abgeschlossen wurde, auch wenn er früher begonnen wurde. Dieser Teil muss durch Nachweise belegt werden (ähnlich wie bei abgeschlossenen Projekten), aus denen auch der entsprechende Wert des Teils hervorgehen muss. Wenn ein Bewerber/Bieter das Projekt als Teil eines Konsortiums umgesetzt hat, muss der erfolgreich abgeschlossene Anteil des Bewerbers/Bieters deutlich aus den Nachweisen hervorgehen und mit einer Beschreibung der Art der Dienstleistungen versehen sein, sofern die Auswahlkriterien hinsichtlich der Relevanz der Erfahrung einbezogen wurden.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Falls mehr als 8 teilnahmeberechtigte Bewerber die vorgenannten Auswahlkriterien erfüllen, müssen die relativen Stärken und Schwächen der Bewerbungen dieser Bewerber erneut überprüft werden, um die acht besten Bewerber zu ermitteln. Die einzigen Faktoren, die bei dieser erneuten Überprüfung berücksichtigt werden, sind:</P><P>— Anzahl der auftragsrelevanten Projekte,</P><P>— Wert der auftragsrelevanten Projekte,</P><P>— Anzahl der auftragsrelevanten Projekte, die im subsaharischen Afrika durchgeführt wurden.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Schlusstermin für den Eingang der Bewerbungen</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00, Ortszeit Ostafrika.</P><P>Nach dieser Frist beim öffentlichen Auftraggeber eingehende Bewerbungen werden nicht berücksichtigt.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Sonstige Informationen</P><P>Anfragen bezüglich Erläuterungen sind bis spätestens 31.1.2018 an das folgende elektronische Postfach zu richten: Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>muss es heißen:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Voraussichtlicher Zeitpunkt der Aufforderung zur Angebotsabgabe 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Auswahlkriterien</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Der Bewerber hat im Rahmen von mindestens drei Aufträgen, dessen Budget mindestens einem Betrag von 3 000 000 EUR entsprach, Dienstleistungen im Bereich technische Hilfe und Kapazitätenentwicklung zur Umsetzung von sektorübergreifenden, regierungsgeführten Programmen erbracht, die zu einem beliebigen Zeitpunkt während des Referenzzeitraums ausgeführt wurden. Das heißt, das vom Bewerber genannte Referenzprojekt kann zu jedem Zeitpunkt während des angegebenen Zeitraums begonnen oder abgeschlossen worden sein; es muss jedoch nicht zwingend in diesem Zeitraum begonnen und abgeschlossen und auch nicht während des gesamten Zeitraums durchgeführt worden sein. Bewerber/Bieter können sich auf im Referenzzeitraum abgeschlossene Projekte (die jedoch früher aufgenommen wurden) oder auf noch nicht abgeschlossene Projekte beziehen. Im ersten Fall wird das Projekt in seiner Gesamtheit berücksichtigt, sofern ordnungsgemäße Ausführungsnachweise vorgelegt werden (Erklärung oder Bescheinigung der Stelle, welche den Auftrag vergeben hat, Nachweis einer Abschlusszahlung). Bei laufenden Projekten wird nur der Teil berücksichtigt, der im Referenzzeitraum zufriedenstellend abgeschlossen wurde, auch wenn er früher begonnen wurde. Dieser Teil muss durch Nachweise belegt werden (ähnlich wie bei abgeschlossenen Projekten), aus denen auch der entsprechende Wert des Teils hervorgehen muss. Wenn ein Bewerber/Bieter das Projekt als Teil eines Konsortiums umgesetzt hat, muss der erfolgreich abgeschlossene Anteil des Bewerbers/Bieters deutlich aus den Nachweisen hervorgehen und mit einer Beschreibung der Art der Dienstleistungen versehen sein, sofern die Auswahlkriterien hinsichtlich der Relevanz der Erfahrung einbezogen wurden.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Falls mehr als 8 teilnahmeberechtigte Bewerber die vorgenannten Auswahlkriterien erfüllen, müssen die relativen Stärken und Schwächen der Bewerbungen dieser Bewerber erneut überprüft werden, um die acht besten Bewerber zu ermitteln. Die einzigen Faktoren, die bei dieser erneuten Überprüfung berücksichtigt werden, sind:</P><P>— Erstens: Die Anzahl der auftragsrelevanten Projekte mit einem Wert von jeweils mindestens 1 000 000 EUR und im Falle einer identischen Bewertung der Bewerber</P><P>— der kumulierte Gesamtbetrag der umgesetzten Projekte (auch wenn der jeweilige Mindestwert unterhalb von 1 000 000 EUR liegt).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Schlusstermin für den Eingang der Bewerbungen</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00, Ortszeit Addis Abeba.</P><P>Nach dieser Frist beim öffentlichen Auftraggeber eingehende Bewerbungen werden nicht berücksichtigt.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Sonstige Informationen</P><P>Anfragen bezüglich Erläuterungen sind bis spätestens 19.2.2018 an das folgende elektronische Postfach zu richten: Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu.</P><P>Es wird darauf hingewiesen, dass die Rückfragen zu der früheren Berichtigung und die bis zum 19.2 einzureichenden Rückfragen gleichzeitig beantwortet werden.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alle anderen Daten und Bedingungen der Auftragsbekanntmachung bleiben unverändert. Die oben genannten Änderungen und/oder Berichtigungen der Auftragsbekanntmachung sind integraler Bestandteil derselben.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Ababa: DCI - Technical Assistance to Support Global Climate Change Alliance Plus (GCCA+)/Mainstreaming of Climate Smart Planning and Implementation Approaches into the Productive Safety Net Program IV (PSNP4) in Ethiopia</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Corrigendum</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement to the Official Journal of the European Union, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, represented by the European Commission (EU Delegation in Ethiopia) on behalf of and for the account of Ethiopia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Ababa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Ethiopia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Instead of:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Provisional date of invitation to tender 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Selection criteria</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>The candidate has provided services under at least one contract with a budget of at least that of this contract in the areas of technical assistance and capacity development for implementation of multi- sectoral government-led programs which were implemented at any moment during the reference period. This means that the project the candidate refers to could have been started or completed at any time during the indicated period but it does not necessarily have to be started and completed during that period, nor is it implemented during the entire period. Candidates/tenderers are allowed to refer either to projects completed within the reference period (although started earlier) or to projects not yet completed. In the first case the project will be considered in its whole if proper evidence of performance is provided (statement or certificate from the entity which awarded the contract, proof of final payment). In case of projects still ongoing only the portion satisfactorily completed during the reference period although started earlier will be taken into consideration. This portion will have to be supported by documentary evidence (similarly to projects completed) also detailing its value. If a candidate/tenderer has implemented the project in a consortium, the percentage that the candidate/tenderer has successfully completed must be clear from the documentary evidence, together with a description of the nature of the services provided if the selection criteria relating to the pertinence of the experience have been used.</P><P>[...]</P><P>If more than 8 eligible candidates meet the above selection criteria, the relative strengths and weaknesses of the applications of these candidates must be reexamined to identify the eight best candidates. The only factors which will be taken into consideration during this re-examination are:</P><P>— Number of projects related to this contract,</P><P>— Value of projects related to this contract,</P><P>— Number of projects related to this contract implemented in Sub-Saharan Africa.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Deadline for receipt of applications</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00hr East African Time.</P><P>Any application received by the contracting authority after this deadline will not be considered.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Additional information</P><P>Any request for clarification must be sent to Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu no later than 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Read:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Provisional date of invitation to tender 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Selection criteria</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>The candidate has provided services under at least three contracts with each having a minimum of 3 000 000 EUR contract amount in the areas of technical assistance and capacity development for implementation of multi- sectoral government-led programs which were implemented at any moment during the reference period. This means that the project the candidate refers to could have been started or completed at any time during the indicated period but it does not necessarily have to be started and completed during that period, nor is it implemented during the entire period. Candidates/tenderers are allowed to refer either to projects completed within the reference period (although started earlier) or to projects not yet completed. In the first case the project will be considered in its whole if proper evidence of performance is provided (statement or certificate from the entity which awarded the contract, proof of final payment). In case of projects still ongoing only the portion satisfactorily completed during the reference period although started earlier will be taken into consideration. This portion will have to be supported by documentary evidence (similarly to projects completed) also detailing its value. If a candidate/tenderer has implemented the project in a consortium, the percentage that the candidate/tenderer has successfully completed must be clear from the documentary evidence, together with a description of the nature of the services provided if the selection criteria relating to the pertinence of the experience have been used.</P><P>[...]</P><P>If more than 8 eligible candidates meet the above selection criteria, the relative strengths and weaknesses of the applications of these candidates must be reexamined to identify the eight best candidates. The only factors which will be taken into consideration during this re-examination are:</P><P>— First, the number of projects related to this contract/project with a value of more than 1 000 000 EUR each and in cases of similarities of scores between candidates,</P><P>—Total cumulative amount of implemented projects (even if each one is of less than 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Deadline for receipt of applications</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00hr Addis Ababa Time.</P><P>Any application received by the contracting authority after this deadline will not be considered.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Additional information</P><P>Any request for clarification must be sent to Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu no later than 19.2.2018</P><P>Please note all clarifications received with the previous corrigendum and the one to be received before the 19th of February will be replied together.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>All other terms and conditions of the contract notice remain unchanged. The above alterations and /or corrections to the contract notice are integral part of the contract notice.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: ICD - Asistencia técnica para prestar apoyo a la AMCC+/la integración de enfoques de planificación y ejecución inteligentes en el ámbito climático en el programa de redes de seguridad productivas IV (PSNP4) en Etiopía</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rectificativo</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplemento al Diario Oficial de la Unión Europea, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>La Unión Europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada por la Comisión Europea (Delegación de la UE en Etiopía), en nombre y por cuenta del Gobierno de Etiopía, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Adís Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopía.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>En lugar de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Fecha provisional de la invitación a licitar 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Criterios de selección</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>El candidato ha prestado servicios en el marco de al menos 1 contrato con un presupuesto al menos equivalente al del presente contrato en los ámbitos de la asistencia técnica y desarrollo de capacidades para la implementación de programas gubernamentales multisectoriales, implementados en cualquier momento durante el período de referencia. Esto significa que el proyecto al que el candidato se refiere pudo haberse iniciado o finalizado en cualquier momento durante el período indicado pero no tiene que haberse iniciado y finalizado necesariamente durante este, ni haberse ejecutado durante todo el período. Los candidatos/licitadores pueden utilizar como referencia proyectos que finalizaran dentro del período de referencia (aunque comenzaran antes) o proyectos que aún no hayan finalizado. En el primer caso, el proyecto se considerará en su conjunto si se presentan los documentos debidos que justifiquen su ejecución (declaración o certificado de la entidad a la que se adjudicó el contrato, una prueba de pago final, etc.). Respecto a los proyectos que aún estén en curso, solo se tendrá en consideración la parte que se haya finalizado de manera satisfactoria durante el período de referencia, aunque se haya empezado con anterioridad. Esta parte deberá ir acompañada de documentos justificativos (como para los proyectos finalizados) en los que se detalle el valor. Si el candidato/licitador ha realizado el proyecto como miembro de un consorcio, el porcentaje que el candidato/licitador ha realizado satisfactoriamente deberá estar claramente indicado en los documentos justificativos y se deberá incluir una descripción de la naturaleza de los servicios prestados en caso de que se apliquen los criterios de selección relativos a la pertinencia de la experiencia.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Si el número de candidaturas elegibles que satisfacen el conjunto de los criterios de selección es superior a 8, los méritos de las solicitudes de estos candidatos deberán ser reexaminados para identificar las 8 mejores candidaturas a la licitación. Los únicos elementos que se tendrán en cuenta en dicho reexamen son los siguientes:</P><P>— el número de proyectos relacionados con este contrato,</P><P>— el valor de los proyectos relacionados con este contrato,</P><P>— el número de proyectos relacionados con este contrato llevados a cabo en África subsahariana.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Plazo para la recepción de las solicitudes</P><P>9.2.2018 a las 17:00, hora de África Oriental.</P><P>No se tomará en consideración ninguna solicitud recibida por el órgano de contratación después de este plazo.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Información adicional</P><P>Cualquier duda debe enviarse a Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu antes del 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Léase:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Fecha provisional de la invitación a licitar 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Criterios de selección</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>El candidato ha prestado servicios en el marco de al menos 3 contratos con un presupuesto mínimo de 3 000 000 EUR en los ámbitos de la asistencia técnica y desarrollo de capacidades para la implementación de programas gubernamentales multisectoriales, implementados en cualquier momento durante el período de referencia. Esto significa que el proyecto al que el candidato se refiere pudo haberse iniciado o finalizado en cualquier momento durante el período indicado pero no tiene que haberse iniciado y finalizado necesariamente durante este, ni haberse ejecutado durante todo el período. Los candidatos/licitadores pueden utilizar como referencia proyectos que finalizaran dentro del período de referencia (aunque comenzaran antes) o proyectos que aún no hayan finalizado. En el primer caso, el proyecto se considerará en su conjunto si se presentan los documentos debidos que justifiquen su ejecución (declaración o certificado de la entidad a la que se adjudicó el contrato, una prueba de pago final, etc.). Respecto a los proyectos que aún estén en curso, solo se tendrá en consideración la parte que se haya finalizado de manera satisfactoria durante el período de referencia, aunque se haya empezado con anterioridad. Esta parte deberá ir acompañada de documentos justificativos (como para los proyectos finalizados) en los que se detalle el valor. Si el candidato/licitador ha realizado el proyecto como miembro de un consorcio, el porcentaje que el candidato/licitador ha realizado satisfactoriamente deberá estar claramente indicado en los documentos justificativos y se deberá incluir una descripción de la naturaleza de los servicios prestados en caso de que se apliquen los criterios de selección relativos a la pertinencia de la experiencia.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Si el número de candidaturas elegibles que satisfacen el conjunto de los criterios de selección es superior a 8, los méritos de las solicitudes de estos candidatos deberán ser reexaminados para identificar las 8 mejores candidaturas a la licitación. Los únicos elementos que se tendrán en cuenta en dicho reexamen son los siguientes:</P><P>— Primero, el número de proyectos relacionados con este contrato/proyecto con un valor de más de 1 000 000 EUR cada uno y en caso de similitud de puntuaciones entre los candidatos,</P><P>— Cantidad acumulada total de proyectos implementados (incluso si cada uno es inferior a 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Plazo para la recepción de las solicitudes</P><P>5.3.2018 a las 17:00, hora de Adís Abeba.</P><P>No se tomará en consideración ninguna solicitud recibida por el órgano de contratación después de este plazo.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Información adicional</P><P>Cualquier duda debe enviarse a Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu antes del 19.2.2018.</P><P>Tenga en cuenta que todas las aclaraciones recibidas con la rectificación anterior y la que se recibirá antes del 19 de febrero serán contestadas juntas.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>El resto de términos y condiciones del presente anuncio de contrato permanecen sin cambios. Las presentes modificaciones o correcciones del anuncio de contrato forman parte integral del mismo.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: DCI - Tekninen tuki seuraavien tukemiseksi: maailmanlaajuinen ilmastonmuutosliittouma (GCCA+) / ilmaston kannalta älykkäiden suunnittelua ja toteutusta koskevien lähestymistapojen sisällyttäminen tuottavia turvaverkkoja koskevaan ohjelmaan IV (PSNP4) Etiopiassa</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Oikaisuilmoitus</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Euroopan unionin virallisen lehden täydennysosa, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan unioni</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, jota edustaa Euroopan komissio (EU:n Etiopian-edustusto), Etiopian hallituksen puolesta, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Oikaistava tieto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Tarjouspyynnön alustava lähetysajankohta 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Valintaperusteet</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Hakija on toimittanut palveluja vähintään yhden sellaisen sopimuksen yhteydessä, jonka budjetti on ollut vähintään tämän sopimuksen budjettia vastaava ja joka on koskenut teknistä tukea ja valmiuksien kehittämistä monialaisten julkisen hallinnon ohjelmien toteuttamiseksi. Sopimus/sopimukset on toteutettu milloin tahansa viiteajanjakson aikana. Tämä merkitsee sitä, että hanke, johon hakija viittaa, on voitu aloittaa tai saattaa loppuun milloin tahansa kyseisenä ajanjaksona. Hanketta ei ole kuitenkaan tarvinnut välttämättä sekä aloittaa että saattaa loppuun kyseisenä ajanjaksona eikä toteuttamisen ole tarvinnut kestää koko ajanjakson ajan. Hakijat/tarjoajat voivat käyttää referensseinä hankkeita, jotka on saatettu loppuun viiteajanjaksona (vaikka ne on aloitettu aikaisemmin), tai hankkeita, joita ei ole vielä saatettu loppuun. Ensin mainitussa tapauksessa hanke otetaan huomioon kokonaisuudessaan, jos suorittamisesta toimitetaan kunnolliset todisteet (ilmoitus tai todistus sopimuksen tehneeltä taholta tai todiste loppumaksun suorittamisesta). Mikäli hankkeet ovat yhä käynnissä, huomioon otetaan ainoastaan viiteajanjaksona tyydyttävästi loppuun saatettu osuus, vaikka ne olisi aloitettu aiemmin. Tästä osuudesta on toimitettava asiakirjatodisteet (samalla lailla kuin loppuun saatettujen hankkeiden osalta), joista käy ilmi myös osuuden arvo. Jos hakija/tarjoaja on toteuttanut hankkeen konsortiossa, todistusasiakirjoista on selvästi käytävä ilmi hakijan/tarjoajan menestyksekkäästi päätökseen saattama prosenttiosuus sekä kuvaus toimitettujen palvelujen luonteesta, mikäli kokemuksen soveltuvuutta koskevia valintaperusteita on käytetty.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Jos yli 8 valintakelpoista hakijaa täyttää edellä mainitut valintaperusteet, näiden hakijoiden hakemusten suhteelliset vahvuudet ja heikkoudet arvioidaan uudelleen 8 parhaan hakijan valitsemiseksi. Tässä uudelleenarvioinnissa otetaan huomioon ainoastaan seuraavat tekijät:</P><P>— tähän sopimukseen liittyvien hankkeiden määrä,</P><P>— tähän sopimukseen liittyvien hankkeiden arvo,</P><P>— tähän sopimukseen liittyvien sellaisten hankkeiden lukumäärä, jotka on toteutettu Saharan eteläpuolisessa Afrikassa.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Hakemusten vastaanottamisen määräaika</P><P>9.2.2018 klo 17:00 Itä-Afrikan aikaa.</P><P>Hakemuksia, jotka hankintaviranomainen vastaanottaa tämän määräajan jälkeen, ei oteta huomioon.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Lisätiedot</P><P>Mahdolliset selvennyspyynnöt on lähetettävä osoitteella Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu viimeistään 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Oikaisu:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Tarjouspyynnön alustava lähetysajankohta 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Valintaperusteet</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Hakija on toimittanut palveluja vähintään 3 sellaisen sopimuksen yhteydessä, joista kunkin sopimusarvo on ollut vähintään 3 000 000 EUR ja jotka ovat koskeneet teknistä tukea ja valmiuksien kehittämistä monialaisten julkisen hallinnon ohjelmien toteuttamiseksi. Sopimukset on toteutettu milloin tahansa viiteajanjakson aikana. Tämä merkitsee sitä, että hanke, johon hakija viittaa, on voitu aloittaa tai saattaa loppuun milloin tahansa kyseisenä ajanjaksona. Hanketta ei ole kuitenkaan tarvinnut välttämättä sekä aloittaa että saattaa loppuun kyseisenä ajanjaksona eikä toteuttamisen ole tarvinnut kestää koko ajanjakson ajan. Hakijat/tarjoajat voivat käyttää referensseinä hankkeita, jotka on saatettu loppuun viiteajanjaksona (vaikka ne on aloitettu aikaisemmin), tai hankkeita, joita ei ole vielä saatettu loppuun. Ensin mainitussa tapauksessa hanke otetaan huomioon kokonaisuudessaan, jos suorittamisesta toimitetaan kunnolliset todisteet (ilmoitus tai todistus sopimuksen tehneeltä taholta tai todiste loppumaksun suorittamisesta). Mikäli hankkeet ovat yhä käynnissä, huomioon otetaan ainoastaan viiteajanjaksona tyydyttävästi loppuun saatettu osuus, vaikka ne olisi aloitettu aiemmin. Tästä osuudesta on toimitettava asiakirjatodisteet (samalla lailla kuin loppuun saatettujen hankkeiden osalta), joista käy ilmi myös osuuden arvo. Jos hakija/tarjoaja on toteuttanut hankkeen konsortiossa, todistusasiakirjoista on selvästi käytävä ilmi hakijan/tarjoajan menestyksekkäästi päätökseen saattama prosenttiosuus sekä kuvaus toimitettujen palvelujen luonteesta, mikäli kokemuksen soveltuvuutta koskevia valintaperusteita on käytetty.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Jos yli 8 valintakelpoista hakijaa täyttää edellä mainitut valintaperusteet, näiden hakijoiden hakemusten suhteelliset vahvuudet ja heikkoudet arvioidaan uudelleen 8 parhaan hakijan valitsemiseksi. Tässä uudelleenarvioinnissa otetaan huomioon ainoastaan seuraavat tekijät:</P><P>— ensin huomioon otetaan sellaisten tähän sopimukseen/hankkeeseen liittyvien hankkeiden määrä, joista kunkin arvo on yli 1 000 000 EUR, ja jos hakijat saavat saman määrän pisteitä,</P><P>— toteutettujen hankkeiden yhteenlaskettu kokonaisarvo (vaikka kunkin hankkeen arvo on alle 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Hakemusten vastaanottamisen määräaika</P><P>5.3.2018, klo 17:00, Addis Abeban aikaa.</P><P>Hakemuksia, jotka hankintaviranomainen vastaanottaa tämän määräajan jälkeen, ei oteta huomioon.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Lisätiedot</P><P>Mahdolliset selvennyspyynnöt on lähetettävä osoitteeseen Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu viimeistään 19.2.2018.</P><P>Huom. Kaikkiin aiempia oikaisuilmoituksia koskeviin selvennyspyyntöihin sekä 19.2. mennessä vastaanotettaviin selvennyspyyntöihin vastataan samanaikaisesti.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Kaikki muut hankintailmoituksen kohdat ja ehdot pysyvät muuttumattomina. Hankintailmoitukseen edellä tehdyt muutokset ja/tai korjaukset ovat olennainen osa hankintailmoitusta.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis-Abeba: ICD - Assistance technique en soutien à l'Alliance mondiale contre le changement climatique+ (AMCC+)/Intégration des approches de planification et de mise en œuvre intelligentes en matière de climat dans le programme de filet de sécurité productif IV (PSNP4) en Éthiopie</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rectificatif</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplément au Journal officiel de l'Union européenne, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Union européenne</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, représentée par la Commission européenne (EU Delegation in Ethiopia), agissant au nom et pour le compte du gouvernement d'Éthiopie </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis-Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Éthiopie.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Au lieu de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Date provisoire des appels d’offres: 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Critères de sélection</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Le candidat doit avoir fourni des services dans le cadre d'au moins un marché, d'un budget au minimum équivalent à celui du présent marché pour des services d'assistance technique et d’amélioration des capacités pour la mise en œuvre de programmes gouvernementaux multi-sectoriels ayant été mis en œuvre à tout moment au cours de la période de référence. Cela signifie que le projet auquel se réfère le candidat a pu être commencé ou finalisé à tout moment durant la période indiquée, mais pas nécessairement qu'il a dû être commencé et finalisé durant cette période, ni être mis en œuvre durant la période entière. Les candidats/soumissionnaires sont autorisés à citer des projets terminés au cours de la période de référence (bien que commencés plus tôt) ou des projets qui ne sont pas encore terminés. Dans le premier cas, le projet sera pris en considération dans sa globalité, pour autant que des preuves suffisantes soient fournies à l'appui de sa réalisation (déclaration ou attestation émanant du pouvoir adjudicateur, preuve du paiement final). En cas de projets toujours en cours, seule la partie terminée de manière satisfaisante au cours de la période de référence sera prise en considération, même si le projet a été commencé plus tôt. Des preuves documentaires devront être apportées à l'appui de la réalisation de cette partie (similaires à celles fournies pour les projets terminés), en détaillant également la valeur. Si un candidat/soumissionnaire a réalisé le projet en tant que membre d'un consortium, la part qu'il a menée à bien devra être clairement mentionnée dans les preuves documentaires. Celles-ci devront contenir une description de la nature des services fournis, lorsque les critères de sélection concernant la pertinence de l'expérience ont été appliqués.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Si plus de 8 candidats éligibles satisfont aux critères de sélection ci-dessus, il sera procédé à une réévaluation de leurs points forts et de leurs points faibles afin de déterminer les 8 meilleures candidatures. Lors de la réévaluation, seuls seront pris en compte les critères suivants :</P><P>— Le nombre de projets liés au présent marché,</P><P>— La valeur des projets liés au présent marché,</P><P>— Le nombre de projets dans des domaines en rapport avec le présent marché mis en œuvre en Afrique subsaharienne.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Date limite de réception des candidatures</P><P>Le 9.2.2018 à 17:00, heure d'Afrique orientale.</P><P>Toute candidature reçue par le pouvoir adjudicateur après cette date limite sera rejetée.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Renseignements complémentaires</P><P>Toute demande de renseignements doit être envoyée à l’adresse : Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu au plus tard le 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Lire:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Date provisoire des appels d’offres: 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Critères de sélection</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Le candidat doit avoir fourni des services dans le cadre d'au moins trois marchés, ayant chacun un minimum de 3 000 000 EUR de montant du marché pour des services d'assistance technique et d’amélioration des capacités pour la mise en œuvre de programmes gouvernementaux multi-sectoriels ayant été mis en œuvre à tout moment au cours de la période de référence. Cela signifie que le projet auquel se réfère le candidat a pu être commencé ou finalisé à tout moment durant la période indiquée, mais pas nécessairement qu'il a dû être commencé et finalisé durant cette période, ni être mis en œuvre durant la période entière. Les candidats/soumissionnaires sont autorisés à citer des projets terminés au cours de la période de référence (bien que commencés plus tôt) ou des projets qui ne sont pas encore terminés. Dans le premier cas, le projet sera pris en considération dans sa globalité, pour autant que des preuves suffisantes soient fournies à l'appui de sa réalisation (déclaration ou attestation émanant du pouvoir adjudicateur, preuve du paiement final). En cas de projets toujours en cours, seule la partie terminée de manière satisfaisante au cours de la période de référence sera prise en considération, même si le projet a été commencé plus tôt. Des preuves documentaires devront être apportées à l'appui de la réalisation de cette partie (similaires à celles fournies pour les projets terminés), en détaillant également la valeur. Si un candidat/soumissionnaire a réalisé le projet en tant que membre d'un consortium, la part qu'il a menée à bien devra être clairement mentionnée dans les preuves documentaires. Celles-ci devront contenir une description de la nature des services fournis, lorsque les critères de sélection concernant la pertinence de l'expérience ont été appliqués.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Si plus de 8 candidats éligibles satisfont aux critères de sélection ci-dessus, il sera procédé à une réévaluation de leurs points forts et de leurs points faibles afin de déterminer les 8 meilleures candidatures. Lors de la réévaluation, seuls seront pris en compte les critères suivants :</P><P>— Premièrement, le nombre de projets liés à ce contrat/projet d'une valeur de plus d’1 000 000 EUR chacun, et en cas de similitudes de scores entre candidats,</P><P>— Le montant cumulé total des projets mis en œuvre (même si chacun d'eux est inférieur à 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Date limite de réception des candidatures</P><P>Le 5.3.2018, 17:00, heure d'Addis-Abeba</P><P>Toute candidature reçue par le pouvoir adjudicateur après cette date limite sera rejetée.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Renseignements complémentaires</P><P>Toute demande de renseignements doit être envoyée à l’adresse : Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu au plus tard le 19.2.2018.</P><P>Veuillez noter que toutes les clarifications reçues avec le rectificatif précédent et celles qui seront reçues avant le 19 février seront publiées ensemble.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Toutes les autres conditions générales de l'avis de marché demeurent inchangées. Les modifications et/ou corrections ci-dessus font intégralement partie de l'avis de marché.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Αντίς Αμπέμπα: DCI - Τεχνική βοήθεια για την συμμαχία για την αλλαγή του κλίματος του πλανήτη (GCCA+)/ενσωμάτωση έξυπνου σχεδιασμού για το κλίμα και προσεγγίσεις υλοποίησης στο πλαίσιο του προγράμματος δημιουργίας δικτύων ασφαλείας ελάχιστης παραγωγικότητας IV (PSNP4) στην Αιθιοπία</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Διορθωτικό</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Συμπλήρωμα στην Επίσημη Εφημερίδα της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, εκπροσωπούμενη από την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή (Αντιπροσωπεία της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης στην Αιθιοπία) εξ ονόματος και για λογαριασμό της Αιθιοπίας, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Αντίς Αμπέμπα</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Αιθιοπία.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Αντί:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία αποστολής των προσκλήσεων υποβολής προσφορών 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Κριτήρια επιλογής</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Ο υποψήφιος έχει παράσχει υπηρεσίες στο πλαίσιο τουλάχιστον μιας σύμβασης με προϋπολογισμό τουλάχιστον ίσο με αυτόν της παρούσας σύμβασης στον τομέα της παροχής τεχνικής βοήθειας και αναπτυξιακής ικανότητας για την υλοποίηση πολυτομεακών κυβερνητικών προγραμμάτων τα οποία υλοποιήθηκαν οποιαδήποτε χρονική στιγμή κατά τη διάρκεια της περιόδου αναφοράς. Αυτό σημαίνει ότι το έργο στο οποίο αναφέρεται ο υποψήφιος μπορεί να έχει ξεκινήσει ή ολοκληρωθεί οποιαδήποτε χρονική στιγμή κατά τη διάρκεια της συγκεκριμένης περιόδου, αλλά δεν είναι απαραίτητο να έχει ξεκινήσει και ολοκληρωθεί κατά την εν λόγω περίοδο, ούτε να έχει εκτελεστεί κατά τη συνολική αναφερόμενη περίοδο. Οι υποψήφιοι/προσφέροντες μπορούν να αναφερθούν είτε σε σχέδια που έχουν ολοκληρωθεί εντός της περιόδου αναφοράς (παρόλο που έχουν ξεκινήσει νωρίτερα), είτε σε σχέδια που δεν έχουν ακόμα ολοκληρωθεί. Στην πρώτη περίπτωση, το σχέδιο θα ληφθεί υπόψη στο σύνολό του εάν παρασχεθούν κατάλληλα αποδεικτικά καλής εκτέλεσης (δήλωση ή πιστοποιητικό της οντότητας η οποία ανέθεσε τη σύμβαση, απόδειξη της τελικής πληρωμής). Στην περίπτωση σχεδίων που βρίσκονται σε εξέλιξη, θα ληφθεί υπόψη μόνο το τμήμα που έχει ολοκληρωθεί επιτυχώς κατά τη διάρκεια της περιόδου αναφοράς, παρόλο που έχουν ξεκινήσει νωρίτερα. Το εν λόγω τμήμα θα πρέπει να τεκμηριώνεται μέσω αποδεικτικών εγγράφων (παρομοίως με τα ολοκληρωμένα σχέδια) τα οποία αναφέρουν επίσης λεπτομερώς την αξία του. Εάν ένας υποψήφιος/προσφέρων έχει υλοποιήσει το σχέδιο στο πλαίσιο κοινοπραξίας, θα πρέπει να αναφέρεται σαφώς στα αποδεικτικά στοιχεία το ποσοστό που έχει ολοκληρώσει με επιτυχία ο υποψήφιος/προσφέρων, μαζί με περιγραφή της φύσης των υπηρεσιών που παρασχέθηκαν, σε περίπτωση που έχουν εφαρμοστεί τα κριτήρια επιλογής σχετικά με την καταλληλότητα της εμπειρίας.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Σε περίπτωση που περισσότεροι από 8 επιλέξιμοι υποψήφιοι πληρούν τα ως άνω κριτήρια επιλογής, θα επανεξετασθούν τα σχετικά πλεονεκτήματα και μειονεκτήματα των εν λόγω υποψηφιοτήτων για τον προσδιορισμό των οχτώ καλύτερων υποψηφίων. Οι μοναδικοί παράγοντες που θα ληφθούν υπόψη κατά την εν λόγω επανεξέταση είναι:</P><P>— Ο αριθμός των έργων σχετικών με τη σύμβαση,</P><P>— Η αξία των έργων σχετικών με τη σύμβαση,</P><P>— Ο αριθμός των έργων σχετικών με τη σύμβαση που έχουν υλοποιηθεί στην υποσαχάρια Αφρική.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Λήξη της προθεσμίας παραλαβής των υποψηφιοτήτων</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00 ώρα Ανατολικής Αφρικής.</P><P>Δεν θα ληφθούν υπόψη υποψηφιότητες που θα περιέλθουν εκπρόθεσμα στην αναθέτουσα αρχή.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες</P><P>Τυχόν αιτήματα για διευκρινίσεις πρέπει να αποστέλλονται στην Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu το αργότερο έως τις 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Διάβαζε:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία αποστολής των προσκλήσεων υποβολής προσφορών 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Κριτήρια επιλογής</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Ο υποψήφιος έχει παράσχει υπηρεσίες στο πλαίσιο τουλάχιστον τριών συμβάσεων με ελάχιστο ποσό σύμβασης 3 000 000 EUR στον τομέα της παροχής τεχνικής βοήθειας και και της ανάπτυξης ικανοτήτων για την υλοποίηση πολυτομεακών κυβερνητικών προγραμμάτων τα οποία υλοποιήθηκαν οποιαδήποτε χρονική στιγμή κατά τη διάρκεια της περιόδου αναφοράς. Αυτό σημαίνει ότι το έργο στο οποίο αναφέρεται ο υποψήφιος μπορεί να έχει ξεκινήσει ή ολοκληρωθεί οποιαδήποτε χρονική στιγμή κατά τη διάρκεια της συγκεκριμένης περιόδου, αλλά δεν είναι απαραίτητο να έχει ξεκινήσει και ολοκληρωθεί κατά την εν λόγω περίοδο, ούτε να έχει εκτελεστεί κατά τη συνολική αναφερόμενη περίοδο. Οι υποψήφιοι/προσφέροντες μπορούν να αναφερθούν είτε σε σχέδια που έχουν ολοκληρωθεί εντός της περιόδου αναφοράς (παρόλο που έχουν ξεκινήσει νωρίτερα), είτε σε σχέδια που δεν έχουν ακόμα ολοκληρωθεί. Στην πρώτη περίπτωση, το σχέδιο θα ληφθεί υπόψη στο σύνολό του εάν παρασχεθούν κατάλληλα αποδεικτικά καλής εκτέλεσης (δήλωση ή πιστοποιητικό της οντότητας η οποία ανέθεσε τη σύμβαση, απόδειξη της τελικής πληρωμής). Στην περίπτωση σχεδίων που βρίσκονται σε εξέλιξη, θα ληφθεί υπόψη μόνο το τμήμα που έχει ολοκληρωθεί επιτυχώς κατά τη διάρκεια της περιόδου αναφοράς, παρόλο που έχουν ξεκινήσει νωρίτερα. Το εν λόγω τμήμα θα πρέπει να τεκμηριώνεται μέσω αποδεικτικών εγγράφων (παρομοίως με τα ολοκληρωμένα σχέδια) τα οποία αναφέρουν επίσης λεπτομερώς την αξία του. Εάν ένας υποψήφιος/προσφέρων έχει υλοποιήσει το σχέδιο στο πλαίσιο κοινοπραξίας, θα πρέπει να αναφέρεται σαφώς στα αποδεικτικά στοιχεία το ποσοστό που έχει ολοκληρώσει με επιτυχία ο υποψήφιος/προσφέρων, μαζί με περιγραφή της φύσης των υπηρεσιών που παρασχέθηκαν, σε περίπτωση που έχουν εφαρμοστεί τα κριτήρια επιλογής σχετικά με την καταλληλότητα της εμπειρίας.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Σε περίπτωση που περισσότεροι από 8 επιλέξιμοι υποψήφιοι πληρούν τα ως άνω κριτήρια επιλογής, θα επανεξετασθούν τα σχετικά πλεονεκτήματα και μειονεκτήματα των εν λόγω υποψηφιοτήτων για τον προσδιορισμό των οχτώ καλύτερων υποψηφίων. Οι μοναδικοί παράγοντες που θα ληφθούν υπόψη κατά την εν λόγω επανεξέταση είναι:</P><P>— Πρώτον, ο αριθμός των σχεδίων που σχετίζονται με την παρούσα σύμβαση/σχέδιο αξίας άνω των 1 000 000 EUR το καθένα και σε περιπτώσεις ομοιότητας βαθμολογιών μεταξύ υποψηφίων,</P><P>— Συνολικό σωρευτικό ποσό υλοποιούμενων σχεδίων (ακόμη και αν καθένα από αυτά είναι μικρότερο από 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Λήξη της προθεσμίας παραλαβής των υποψηφιοτήτων</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00 ώρα Αντίς Αμπέμπα.</P><P>Δεν θα ληφθούν υπόψη υποψηφιότητες που θα περιέλθουν εκπρόθεσμα στην αναθέτουσα αρχή.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες</P><P>Τυχόν αιτήματα για διευκρινήσεις πρέπει να αποστέλλονται στην Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu το αργότερο έως τις 19.2.2018</P><P>Λάβετε υπόψη ότι όλες οι διευκρινίσεις που ελήφθησαν με το προηγούμενο διορθωτικό και αυτές που θα ληφθούν πριν από τις 19 Φεβρουαρίου θα απαντηθούν μαζί.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Όλοι οι λοιποί όροι και προϋποθέσεις της προκήρυξης σύμβασης παραμένουν αμετάβλητοι. Οι ανωτέρω τροποποιήσεις ή/και διορθώσεις στην προκήρυξη σύμβασης αποτελούν αναπόσπαστο τμήμα της προκήρυξης σύμβασης.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: DCI - Assistenza tecnica a sostegno dell'Alleanza mondiale contro il cambiamento climatico+ (GCCA+)/integrazione di approcci di pianificazione e attuazione intelligente in campo climatico nel programma Rete di sicurezza produttiva IV (PSNP4) in Etiopia</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rettifica</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplemento alla Gazzetta ufficiale dell'Unione europea, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unione europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, rappresentata dalla Commissione europea in nome e per conto del governo dell'Etiopia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>anziché:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Data prevista per il bando di gara 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Criteri di selezione</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Il candidato dovrà aver prestato servizi nell'ambito di almeno 1 contratto avente un bilancio pari almeno a quello del presente appalto, nei settori dell'assistenza tecnica e dello sviluppo di capacità per l'attuazione di programmi multisettoriali guidati dal governo, realizzato in qualsiasi momento durante il periodo di riferimento. Ciò significa che il progetto al quale il candidato si riferisce potrà essere stato avviato o ultimato in un qualsiasi momento nel corso del periodo indicato, ma non dovrà essere stato necessariamente avviato e ultimato durante tale periodo, né realizzato nel corso dell'intero periodo. I candidati/offerenti potranno fare riferimento a progetti completati entro il periodo di riferimento (anche se iniziati prima) o a progetti non ancora completati. Nel primo caso il progetto sarà considerato nel suo insieme se verrà fornita prova adeguata delle prestazioni (dichiarazione o certificato da parte dell'ente che ha aggiudicato l'appalto, prova del pagamento finale). In caso di progetti ancora in corso, sarà presa in considerazione soltanto la quota completata in modo soddisfacente nel corso del periodo di riferimento, anche se iniziata prima. Tale quota dovrà essere sostenuta da prove documentarie (analogamente ai progetti completati) che ne specifichino anche il valore. Qualora un candidato/offerente abbia realizzato il progetto in un consorzio, dai documenti probatori dovrà essere chiara la percentuale che ha completato con esito positivo, insieme a una descrizione della natura dei servizi prestati nel caso siano stati utilizzati i criteri di selezione relativi alla pertinenza dell'esperienza.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Qualora più di 8 candidati ammissibili soddisfino i criteri di selezione suindicati, tali candidature dovranno essere riesaminate valutandone i pregi e i difetti, al fine di individuare gli otto candidati migliori. Gli unici fattori che saranno presi in considerazione nella fase di riesame sono:</P><P>— Numero di progetti aventi relazione con il presente appalto,</P><P>— Valore dei progetti aventi relazione con il presente appalto,</P><P>— Numero di progetti aventi relazione con il presente appalto e realizzati nell'Africa sub-sahariana.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termine ultimo per la presentazione delle candidature</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00, ora dell'Africa orientale.</P><P>Le candidature pervenute all'ente appaltante dopo tale termine non verranno prese in considerazione.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Informazioni complementari</P><P>Eventuali domande di chiarimento dovranno essere inviate al seguente indirizzo e-mail: Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu entro e non oltre il 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>leggi:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Data prevista per il bando di gara 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Criteri di selezione</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Il candidato dovrà aver prestato servizi nell'ambito di almeno tre contratti ciascuno per un importo contrattuale minimo di 3 000 000 EUR, nei settori dell'assistenza tecnica e dello sviluppo della capacità per l'attuazione di programmi multisettoriali guidati dal governo, realizzati in qualsiasi momento durante il periodo di riferimento. Ciò significa che il progetto al quale il candidato si riferisce potrà essere stato avviato o ultimato in un qualsiasi momento nel corso del periodo indicato, ma non dovrà essere stato necessariamente avviato e ultimato durante tale periodo, né realizzato nel corso dell'intero periodo. I candidati/offerenti potranno fare riferimento a progetti completati entro il periodo di riferimento (anche se iniziati prima) o a progetti non ancora completati. Nel primo caso il progetto sarà considerato nel suo insieme se verrà fornita prova adeguata delle prestazioni (dichiarazione o certificato da parte dell'ente che ha aggiudicato l'appalto, prova del pagamento finale). In caso di progetti ancora in corso, sarà presa in considerazione soltanto la quota completata in modo soddisfacente nel corso del periodo di riferimento, anche se iniziata prima. Tale quota dovrà essere sostenuta da prove documentarie (analogamente ai progetti completati) che ne specifichino anche il valore. Qualora un candidato/offerente abbia realizzato il progetto in un consorzio, dai documenti probatori dovrà essere chiara la percentuale che ha completato con esito positivo, insieme a una descrizione della natura dei servizi prestati nel caso siano stati utilizzati i criteri di selezione relativi alla pertinenza dell'esperienza.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Qualora più di 8 candidati ammissibili soddisfino i criteri di selezione suindicati, tali candidature dovranno essere riesaminate valutandone i pregi e i difetti, al fine di individuare gli otto candidati migliori. Gli unici fattori che saranno presi in considerazione nella fase di riesame sono:</P><P>— In primo luogo, il numero di progetti relativi a questo contratto / progetto con un valore superiore a 1 000 000 EUR ciascuno e in caso di somiglianze tra i punteggi dei candidati,</P><P>—Importo cumulativo totale dei progetti attuati (anche se ciascuno è inferiore a 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termine ultimo per la presentazione delle candidature</P><P>5.3.2018, alle 17:00 ora di Addis Abeba.</P><P>Le candidature pervenute all'ente appaltante dopo tale termine non verranno prese in considerazione.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Informazioni complementari</P><P>Eventuali domande di chiarimento dovranno essere inviate al seguente indirizzo e-mail: Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu entro e non oltre il 19.2.2018</P><P>Si prega di notare che tutti i chiarimenti ricevuti con la rettifica precedente, e quelli da ricevere prima del 19 febbraio saranno risposti tutti insieme.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Tutte le altre condizioni del bando di gara rimangono immutate. Le summenzionate modifiche e/o correzioni al bando di gara sono parte integrante del bando di gara.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: DCI - Technische bijstand ter ondersteuning van het Wereldwijd bondgenootschap tegen klimaatverandering plus en het mainstreamen van slimme klimaatplannings- en uitvoeringsbenaderingen in het vierde programma inzake productieve vangnetten in Ethiopië</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rectificatie</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement op het Publicatieblad van de Europese Unie, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europese Unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertegenwoordigd door de Europese Commissie (Delegatie van de EU in Ethiopië), ten behoeve en voor rekening van Ethiopië, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Ethiopië.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>In plaats van:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Beoogde datum van de uitnodiging tot inschrijving: 10.3.2018.</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Selectiecriteria:</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>De gegadigde heeft diensten verleend in het kader van minstens 1 opdracht, met een begroting die minstens gelijk is aan die van onderhavige opdracht, op de gebieden van technische bijstand en capaciteitsontwikkeling voor de tenuitvoerlegging van multisectorale door de regering geleide programma's, die ten uitvoer is gelegd op een willekeurig moment tijdens de referentieperiode. Dit betekent dat het project waarnaar de gegadigde verwijst op een willekeurig moment tijdens de aangegeven periode kan zijn opgestart/voltooid, maar dat het niet noodzakelijk gedurende die periode moet zijn aangevat en voltooid, of dat de uitvoering ervan niet over de hele periode moet hebben gelopen. Gegadigden/inschrijvers mogen verwijzen naar projecten die binnen de referentieperiode zijn voltooid (hoewel ze eerder werden aangevat) of naar projecten die nog niet zijn voltooid. In het eerste geval zal rekening worden gehouden met het project als geheel indien gepaste bewijsstukken van de uitvoering worden verstrekt (een verklaring of certificaat van de entiteit die de opdracht gunde, bewijs van definitieve betaling). In het geval van nog lopende projecten zal enkel rekening worden gehouden met het deel dat naar behoren werd voltooid gedurende de referentieperiode (hoewel het eerder werd aangevat). Dit deel moet ondersteund worden door bewijsstukken (vergelijkbaar met deze voor voltooide projecten) die ook de waarde vermelden. Indien een gegadigde/inschrijver het project in een consortium ten uitvoer heeft gelegd, moet uit de bewijsstukken duidelijk blijken welk percentage de gegadigde/inschrijver met succes heeft voltooid, samen met een beschrijving van de aard van de verleende diensten indien de selectiecriteria met betrekking tot de relevantie van de ervaring zijn toegepast.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Indien meer dan 8 geschikte gegadigden aan de bovenvermelde selectiecriteria voldoen, moeten de relatieve sterke en zwakke punten van de aanvragen van deze gegadigden worden herbekeken teneinde de 8 beste gegadigden te identificeren. De enige factoren waarmee bij het herbekijken rekening wordt gehouden, zijn:</P><P>— het aantal projecten dat verband houdt met deze opdracht,</P><P>— de waarde van de projecten die verband houden met deze opdracht,</P><P>— het aantal projecten dat verband houdt met deze opdracht, uitgevoerd in Afrika bezuiden de Sahara.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Uiterste datum voor de ontvangst van de aanvragen:</P><P>9.2.2018 (17:00), Oost-Afrikaanse tijd.</P><P>Aanvragen die na deze uiterste datum door de aanbestedende dienst worden ontvangen, worden niet in behandeling genomen.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Nadere inlichtingen:</P><P>Verzoeken om verduidelijking moeten uiterlijk op 31.1.2018 worden verzonden naar Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Te lezen:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Beoogde datum van de uitnodiging tot inschrijving: 26.3.2018.</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Selectiecriteria:</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>De gegadigde heeft diensten verleend in het kader van minstens 3 opdrachten, elk met een minimale opdrachtwaarde van 3 000 000 EUR, op de gebieden van technische bijstand en capaciteitsontwikkeling voor de tenuitvoerlegging van multisectorale door de regering geleide programma's, die ten uitvoer zijn gelegd op een willekeurig moment tijdens de referentieperiode. Dit betekent dat het project waarnaar de gegadigde verwijst op een willekeurig moment tijdens de aangegeven periode kan zijn opgestart/voltooid, maar dat het niet noodzakelijk gedurende die periode moet zijn aangevat en voltooid, of dat de uitvoering ervan niet over de hele periode moet hebben gelopen. Gegadigden/inschrijvers mogen verwijzen naar projecten die binnen de referentieperiode zijn voltooid (hoewel ze eerder werden aangevat) of naar projecten die nog niet zijn voltooid. In het eerste geval zal rekening worden gehouden met het project als geheel indien gepaste bewijsstukken van de uitvoering worden verstrekt (een verklaring of certificaat van de entiteit die de opdracht gunde, bewijs van definitieve betaling). In het geval van nog lopende projecten zal enkel rekening worden gehouden met het deel dat naar behoren werd voltooid gedurende de referentieperiode (hoewel het eerder werd aangevat). Dit deel moet ondersteund worden door bewijsstukken (vergelijkbaar met deze voor voltooide projecten) die ook de waarde vermelden. Indien een gegadigde/inschrijver het project in een consortium ten uitvoer heeft gelegd, moet uit de bewijsstukken duidelijk blijken welk percentage de gegadigde/inschrijver met succes heeft voltooid, samen met een beschrijving van de aard van de verleende diensten indien de selectiecriteria met betrekking tot de relevantie van de ervaring zijn toegepast.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Indien meer dan 8 geschikte gegadigden aan de bovenvermelde selectiecriteria voldoen, moeten de relatieve sterke en zwakke punten van de aanvragen van deze gegadigden worden herbekeken teneinde de 8 beste gegadigden te identificeren. De enige factoren waarmee bij het herbekijken rekening wordt gehouden, zijn:</P><P>— ten eerste, het aantal projecten dat verband houdt met deze opdracht/dit project met een waarde van minstens 1 000 000 EUR per project, en in het geval van gelijke scores tussen de gegadigden:</P><P>— de totale cumulatieve waarde van de uitgevoerde projecten (zelfs indien deze een opdrachtwaarde hebben van minder dan 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Uiterste datum voor de ontvangst van de aanvragen:</P><P>5.3.2018 (17:00), tijd te Addis Abeba.</P><P>Aanvragen die na deze uiterste datum door de aanbestedende dienst worden ontvangen, worden niet in behandeling genomen.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Nadere inlichtingen:</P><P>Verzoeken om verduidelijking moeten uiterlijk op 19.2.2018 worden verzonden naar Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu</P><P>Gelieve op te merken dat alle verzoeken om verduidelijking die werden ontvangen na de vorige rectificatie en deze die vóór 19 februari zullen worden ontvangen tegelijk zullen worden beantwoord.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alle andere voorwaarden van de aankondiging van opdracht blijven ongewijzigd. De hiervoor vermelde wijzigingen en/of correcties aan de aankondiging van opdracht maken integraal deel uit van de aankondiging van opdracht.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Adis-Abeba: ICD - Assistência técnica para apoiar a Aliança Global contra as Alterações Climáticas Mais (AGAC+) /integração de abordagens de implementação e planeamento inteligente em matéria de clima no programa da rede de segurança produtiva IV (PSNP4) na Etiópia</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Retificativo</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplemento do Jornal Oficial da União Europeia, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>União Europeia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada pela Comissão Europeia (Delegação da UE na Etiópia), em nome e por conta da Etiópia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Adis-Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiópia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Em vez de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Data prevista do convite à apresentação de propostas 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Critérios de seleção</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>O candidato prestou serviços no âmbito de, pelo menos, um contrato, com um orçamento no mínimo equivalente ao do presente contrato, em matéria de assistência técnica e capacidade de desenvolvimento para a implementação de programas multi-setoriais liderados pelo governo, implementados em qualquer momento durante o período de referência. Isto significa que o projeto referido pelo candidato pode ter sido iniciado ou concluído em qualquer momento durante o período indicado, mas não deve ter sido, necessariamente, iniciado e concluído durante o período em questão, nem implementado durante a totalidade do período. Os candidatos/proponentes podem fazer referência a projetos concluídos no período de referência (embora iniciados anteriormente) ou a projetos ainda em curso. No primeiro caso, o projeto será considerado na sua totalidade se forem apresentados comprovativos de execução adequados (declaração ou certificado da entidade que adjudicou o contrato, comprovativo de pagamento final). No caso de projetos em curso, apenas a parte concluída com êxito durante o período de referência (embora iniciada anteriormente) será considerada. Esta parte deve ser devidamente comprovada por documentos comprovativos (semelhante aos projetos concluídos) com uma descrição do respetivo valor. Se um candidato/proponente implementou o projeto sob a forma de consórcio, a percentagem que o candidato/proponente concluiu com êxito deve ser claramente indicada nos documentos comprovativos, juntamente com uma descrição da natureza dos serviços prestados caso os critérios de seleção relativos à relevância da experiência tenham sido utilizados.</P><P>[...]</P><P>No caso de mais de 8 candidatos elegíveis preencherem os critérios de seleção, a solidez e a fraqueza relativas das candidaturas desses candidatos deverão ser reexaminadas com vista à identificação das oito melhores candidaturas para o concurso. Os únicos fatores que serão tomados em consideração durante esta reavaliação são:</P><P>— Número de projetos relacionados com o presente contrato,</P><P>— Valor dos projetos relacionados com o presente contrato,</P><P>— Número de projetos relacionados com o presente contrato implementados na África Subsariana.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Data-limite de receção das candidaturas</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00, hora da África Oriental.</P><P>As candidaturas recebidas pela entidade adjudicante após esta data-limite não serão tomadas em consideração.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Outras informações</P><P>Qualquer pedido de esclarecimentos deve ser enviado para Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu o mais tardar a 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Ler:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Data prevista do convite à apresentação de propostas 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Critérios de seleção</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>O candidato prestou serviços no âmbito de, pelo menos, três contratos, cada um com um montante mínimo de 3 000 000 EUR, em matéria de assistência técnica e capacidade de desenvolvimento para a implementação de programas multi-setoriais liderados pelo governo, implementados em qualquer momento durante o período de referência. Isto significa que o projeto referido pelo candidato pode ter sido iniciado ou concluído em qualquer momento durante o período indicado, mas não deve ter sido, necessariamente, iniciado e concluído durante o período em questão, nem implementado durante a totalidade do período. Os candidatos/proponentes podem fazer referência a projetos concluídos no período de referência (embora iniciados anteriormente) ou a projetos ainda em curso. No primeiro caso, o projeto será considerado na sua totalidade se forem apresentados comprovativos de execução adequados (declaração ou certificado da entidade que adjudicou o contrato, comprovativo de pagamento final). No caso de projetos em curso, apenas a parte concluída com êxito durante o período de referência (embora iniciada anteriormente) será considerada. Esta parte deve ser devidamente comprovada por documentos comprovativos (semelhante aos projetos concluídos) com uma descrição do respetivo valor. Se um candidato/proponente implementou o projeto sob a forma de consórcio, a percentagem que o candidato/proponente concluiu com êxito deve ser claramente indicada nos documentos comprovativos, juntamente com uma descrição da natureza dos serviços prestados caso os critérios de seleção relativos à relevância da experiência tenham sido utilizados.</P><P>[...]</P><P>No caso de mais de 8 candidatos elegíveis preencherem os critérios de seleção, a solidez e a fraqueza relativas das candidaturas desses candidatos deverão ser reexaminadas com vista à identificação das oito melhores candidaturas para o concurso. Os únicos fatores que serão tomados em consideração durante esta reavaliação são:</P><P>— Primeiro, o número de projetos relacionados com este contrato/projeto com um valor superior a 1 000 000 EUR cada e em casos de semelhanças entre as pontuações dos candidatos,</P><P>— Montante cumulativo total dos projetos implementados (mesmo se cada um for de valor inferior a 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Data-limite de receção das candidaturas</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00hr Hora de Adis-Abeba.</P><P>As candidaturas recebidas pela entidade adjudicante após esta data-limite não serão tomadas em consideração.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Outras informações</P><P>Qualquer pedido de esclarecimentos deve ser enviado para Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu o mais tardar a 19.2.2018</P><P>Note que todas as clarificações recebidas com o corretivo anterior e a que será recebida antes de 19 de Fevereiro serão respondidas em conjunto.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Todos os restantes pontos e condições do anúncio de concurso permanecem inalterados. As modificações e/ou correções supramencionadas ao anúncio de concurso são parte integrante do mesmo.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: Finansieringsinstrumentet för utvecklingssamarbete - Tekniskt bistånd till stöd för den globala klimatförändringsalliansen+/integrering av metoder för klimatsmart planering och genomförande i programmet för produktivt skyddsnät IV (PSNP4) i Etiopien</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Rättelse</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Tillägg till Europeiska unionens officiella tidning, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska unionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representerad av Europeiska kommissionen (EU-delegationen i Etiopien) till förmån för och på uppdrag av Etiopien, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>I stället för:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Preliminärt datum för anbudsinfordran 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Uttagningskriterier</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Den sökande ska ha tillhandahållit tjänster inom ramen för minst ett kontrakt med en budget som minst motsvarar den för detta kontrakt inom områdena tekniskt bistånd och kapacitetsutveckling för genomförande av sektorsövergripande samt statligt ledda program som ska ha genomförts vid någon tidpunkt under referensperioden. Detta innebär att det projekt som den sökande hänvisar till kan ha påbörjats eller slutförts när som helst under den angivna perioden, men det måste inte nödvändigtvis ha påbörjats och slutförts under denna period och inte heller genomförts under hela perioden. Sökande/anbudsgivare får hänvisa antingen till projekt som slutförts inom referensperioden (även om de påbörjats tidigare) eller till projekt som ännu inte slutförts. I det första fallet kommer projektet att beaktas i sin helhet om lämpligt bevis på utförande lämnas (intyg eller certifikat från den enhet som tilldelade kontraktet, bevis på slutbetalning). När det gäller projekt som fortfarande pågår kommer enbart den del som slutförts på ett tillfredsställande sätt under referensperioden (även om de påbörjats tidigare) att beaktas. Denna del ska stödjas av bevishandlingar (på ett liknande sätt som för slutförda projekt) som även anger dess värde. Om en sökande/anbudsgivare har genomfört projektet i ett konsortium ska det tydligt framgå av bevishandlingarna hur stor andel som den sökande/anbudsgivaren med gott resultat har slutfört, tillsammans med en beskrivning av de tillhandahållna tjänsternas slag, i de fall uttagningskriterierna med anknytning till erfarenhetens relevans har använts.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Om fler än 8 behöriga sökande uppfyller ovannämnda uttagningskriterier kommer dessa sökandes ansökningar att granskas på nytt vad avser relativa styrkor och svagheter, så att man får fram de åtta bästa sökande. De enda faktorer som kommer att beaktas vid denna nya granskning är följande:</P><P>— Antal projekt med anknytning till detta kontrakt,</P><P>— Värdet av projekten med anknytning till detta kontrakt,</P><P>— Antalet projekt med anknytning till detta kontrakt som genomförts i Afrika söder om Sahara.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Tidsfrist för mottagande av ansökningar</P><P>9.2.2018,17:00 lokal tid i östra Afrika.</P><P>Ansökningar som inkommer till den upphandlande myndigheten efter detta sista datum och klockslag kommer inte att beaktas.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Kompletterande information</P><P>Eventuell begäran om förtydligande ska skickas till Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu senast den 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Skall det stå:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Preliminärt datum för anbudsinfordran 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Uttagningskriterier</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Den sökande ska ha tillhandahållit tjänster inom ramen för minst tre kontrakt med en budget på vardera minst 3 000 000 EUR inom områdena tekniskt bistånd och kapacitetsutveckling för genomförande av sektorsövergripande samt statligt ledda program som ska ha genomförts vid någon tidpunkt under referensperioden. Detta innebär att det projekt som den sökande hänvisar till kan ha påbörjats eller slutförts när som helst under den angivna perioden, men det måste inte nödvändigtvis ha påbörjats och slutförts under denna period och inte heller genomförts under hela perioden. Sökande/anbudsgivare får hänvisa antingen till projekt som slutförts inom referensperioden (även om de påbörjats tidigare) eller till projekt som ännu inte slutförts. I det första fallet kommer projektet att beaktas i sin helhet om lämpligt bevis på utförande lämnas (intyg eller certifikat från den enhet som tilldelade kontraktet, bevis på slutbetalning). När det gäller projekt som fortfarande pågår kommer enbart den del som slutförts på ett tillfredsställande sätt under referensperioden (även om de påbörjats tidigare) att beaktas. Denna del ska stödjas av bevishandlingar (på ett liknande sätt som för slutförda projekt) som även anger dess värde. Om en sökande/anbudsgivare har genomfört projektet i ett konsortium ska det tydligt framgå av bevishandlingarna hur stor andel som den sökande/anbudsgivaren med gott resultat har slutfört, tillsammans med en beskrivning av de tillhandahållna tjänsternas slag, i de fall uttagningskriterierna med anknytning till erfarenhetens relevans har använts.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Om fler än 8 behöriga sökande uppfyller ovannämnda uttagningskriterier kommer dessa sökandes ansökningar att granskas på nytt vad avser relativa styrkor och svagheter, så att man får fram de åtta bästa sökande. De enda faktorer som kommer att beaktas vid denna nya granskning är följande:</P><P>— För det första, antalet projekt med anknytning till detta kontrakt/projekt med ett värde på mer än 1 000 000 EUR vardera och i fall av likheter i poäng mellan sökande,</P><P>— Totalt kumulativt belopp på genomförda projekt (även om varje projekt har ett lägre belopp än 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Tidsfrist för mottagande av ansökningar</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00 lokal tid i Addis Abeba.</P><P>Ansökningar som inkommer till den upphandlande myndigheten efter detta sista datum och klockslag kommer inte att beaktas.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Kompletterande information</P><P>Eventuell begäran om förtydligande ska skickas till Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu senast den 19.2.2018</P><P>Observera att alla förtydliganden som mottogs i den föregående rättelsen och den som kommer att mottas före den 19 februari kommer att besvaras tillsammans.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Alla andra förhållanden och villkor i meddelandet om upphandling förblir oförändrade. Ovannämnda ändringar och/eller rättelser av meddelandet om upphandling utgör en integrerad del av meddelandet om upphandling.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: DCI - Technická pomoc na podporu globální aliance pro boj proti změně klimatu plus (GCCA+) / začlenění inteligentních přístupů týkajících se plánování a provádění v oblasti klimatu do programu sítě bezpečnosti produktivity IV (PSNP4) v Etiopii</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Oprava</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatek k Úřednímu věstníku Evropské unie, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastoupená Evropskou komisí (delegací Evropské unie v Etiopii) jménem a ve prospěch Etiopie, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopie.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Namísto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Předběžné datum výzvy k účasti v nabídkovém řízení 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Kritéria pro výběr uchazečů</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Uchazeč poskytl služby v rámci alespoň 1 zakázky s rozpočtem alespoň ve výši rozpočtu této zakázky v oblasti poskytování technické pomoci a rozvoje kapacit pro provádění víceodvětvových vládních programů, které byly realizovány kdykoli během referenčního období. To znamená, že projekt, na který uchazeč odkazuje, mohl být započat nebo dokončen kdykoli v průběhu uvedené doby, ale nemusel být v průběhu této doby nutně započat a dokončen nebo realizován během celého tohoto období. Uchazeči / předkladatelé nabídek mohou odkazovat na projekty dokončené v rámci referenčního období (přestože byly zahájeny dříve) nebo na projekty, které ještě dokončené nejsou. V prvním případě bude projekt zohledněn jako celek, pokud je předložen vhodný důkaz o provedení (prohlášení nebo osvědčení od subjektu, který zakázku zadal, doklad o konečné platbě). V případě ještě probíhajících projektů bude zohledněn pouze podíl, který byl uspokojivě dokončen během referenčního období, i když byl započat dříve. Tento podíl bude muset být doložen listinným důkazem (podobně jako u dokončených projektů) rovněž s podrobným uvedením jeho hodnoty. Pokud uchazeč / předkladatel nabídky provedl projekt v rámci konsorcia, musí provedený procentuální podíl uchazeče / předkladatele nabídky na zakázce jasně vyplývat z dokladů spolu s popisem povahy poskytnutých služeb, za předpokladu, že byla uplatněna kritéria pro výběr týkající se vhodnosti těchto zkušeností.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Jestliže více než 8 oprávněných uchazečů splňuje výše uvedená výběrová kritéria, musí být k určení 8 nejlepších uchazečů znovu přezkoumány relativní klady a zápory přihlášek těchto uchazečů. Jediné faktory, které budou brány v úvahu během nového přezkoumání, jsou:</P><P>— počet projektů souvisejících s touto zakázkou,</P><P>— hodnota projektů souvisejících s touto zakázkou,</P><P>— počet projektů souvisejících s touto zakázkou, které byly realizovány v subsaharské Africe.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Konečná lhůta pro přijetí přihlášek</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00, východoafrický čas.</P><P>Jakákoli přihláška obdržená veřejným zadavatelem po této konečné lhůtě nebude brána v úvahu.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Další informace</P><P>Veškeré žádosti o objasnění musí být zaslány na e-mailovou adresu Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu nejpozději dne 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Čtěte:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Předběžné datum výzvy k účasti v nabídkovém řízení 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Kritéria pro výběr uchazečů</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Uchazeč poskytl služby v rámci alespoň 3 zakázek s rozpočtem každé alespoň ve výši 3 000 000 EUR v oblasti poskytování technické pomoci a rozvoje kapacit pro provádění víceodvětvových vládních programů, které byly realizovány kdykoli během referenčního období. To znamená, že projekt, na který uchazeč odkazuje, mohl být započat nebo dokončen kdykoli v průběhu uvedené doby, ale nemusel být v průběhu této doby nutně započat a dokončen nebo realizován během celého tohoto období. Uchazeči / předkladatelé nabídek mohou odkazovat na projekty dokončené v rámci referenčního období (přestože byly zahájeny dříve) nebo na projekty, které ještě dokončené nejsou. V prvním případě bude projekt zohledněn jako celek, pokud je předložen vhodný důkaz o provedení (prohlášení nebo osvědčení od subjektu, který zakázku zadal, doklad o konečné platbě). V případě ještě probíhajících projektů bude zohledněn pouze podíl, který byl uspokojivě dokončen během referenčního období, i když byl započat dříve. Tento podíl bude muset být doložen listinným důkazem (podobně jako u dokončených projektů) rovněž s podrobným uvedením jeho hodnoty. Pokud uchazeč / předkladatel nabídky provedl projekt v rámci konsorcia, musí provedený procentuální podíl uchazeče / předkladatele nabídky na zakázce jasně vyplývat z dokladů spolu s popisem povahy poskytnutých služeb, za předpokladu, že byla uplatněna kritéria pro výběr týkající se vhodnosti těchto zkušeností.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Jestliže více než 8 oprávněných uchazečů splňuje výše uvedená výběrová kritéria, musí být k určení 8 nejlepších uchazečů znovu přezkoumány relativní klady a zápory přihlášek těchto uchazečů. Jediné faktory, které budou brány v úvahu během nového přezkoumání, jsou:</P><P>– za prvé počet projektů týkajících se této zakázky/projektu s hodnotou více než 1 000 000 EUR u každé zakázky a v případě podobných výsledků mezi uchazeči,</P><P>– celková souhrnná hodnota realizovaných projektů (i v případě, že každý z nich má hodnotu nižší než 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Konečná lhůta pro přijetí přihlášek</P><P>5.3.2018 (17:00), místního času v Addis Abeba.</P><P>Jakákoli přihláška obdržená veřejným zadavatelem po této konečné lhůtě nebude brána v úvahu.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Další informace</P><P>Veškeré žádosti o objasnění musí být zaslány na e-mailovou adresu Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu nejpozději dne 19.2.2018</P><P>Upozorňujeme, že na všechna vysvětlení přijatá s předchozí opravou a ta, která budou přijata do 19. února, bude odpovězeno společně.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Další smluvní podmínky oznámení o zakázce zůstávají beze změn. Výše uvedené úpravy a/nebo opravy oznámení o zakázce jsou nedílnou součástí oznámení o zakázce.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: DCI - Tehniline abi, et toetada Etioopias kliimaga seotud aruka kavandamise ja rakendamise lähenemisviiside IV tootmisalase turvavõrkude programmiga (PSNP4) integreerimise peavoolustamist / ülemaailmset kliimamuutuste liitu (GCCA+)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Parandus</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Euroopa Liidu Teataja täiendus, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Liit</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, keda esindab Euroopa Komisjon (ELi delegatsioon Etioopias), Etioopia eest ja nimel, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etioopia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Enne:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Pakkumuskutse esialgne kuupäev: 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Valikukriteeriumid</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Kandidaat on osutanud teenuseid tehnilise abi ja suutlikkuse arendamise valdkonnas mitut sektorit hõlmavate valitsuse juhitud programmide rakendamiseks vähemalt ühe lepingu raames, milles lepingu eelarve on vähemalt võrdne käesoleva lepingu eelarvega ja mis täideti mis tahes ajal viiteperioodil. See tähendab, et kandidaadi viidatud projekt võidi algatada või lõpule viia mis tahes ajal osutatud perioodi jooksul, kuid seda ei pruugitud tingimata kogu ajavahemiku jooksul algatada ja lõpule viia. Kandidaadid/pakkujad võivad viidata nii viiteperioodil lõpule viidud (kuigi varem alustatud) projektidele kui ka veel lõpule viimata projektidele. Esimesel juhul võetakse arvesse kogu projekti, juhul kui täitmise kohta esitatakse nõuetekohased tõendusmaterjalid (lepingu sõlminud asutuse kinnitus või tunnistus, lõppmakse tõend). Projektide puhul, mida veel viiakse ellu, võetakse arvesse ainult viiteperioodil rahuldavalt täidetud (kuigi varem alustatud) osa. Seda osa tuleb tõendada dokumentaalse tõendusmaterjaliga (nagu lõpuleviidud projektide puhulgi), milles on kirjas ka selle osa maksumus. Kui kandidaat/pakkuja viis projekti ellu konsortsiumis, peab tõendavatest dokumentidest ilmnema kandidaadi/pakkuja edukalt lõpule viidud tööde osakaal protsentides, samuti tuleb esitada osutatud teenuste laadi kirjeldus, kui rakendatakse kogemuste asjakohasusega seotud valikukriteeriume.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Kui eespool sätestatud valikukriteeriumidele vastavate sobivate kandidaatide arv on suurem kui 8, tuleb nende kandidaatide taotluste suhtelised tugevad ja nõrgad küljed uuesti läbi vaadata, et kindlaks teha kaheksa parimat kandidaati. Teistkordsel läbivaatamisel arvestatakse üksnes järgmiseid tegureid:</P><P>— käesoleva lepinguga seotud projektide arv;</P><P>— käesoleva lepinguga seotud projektide väärtus;</P><P>— käesoleva lepinguga seotud selliste projektide arv, mis on viidud ellu Saharast lõunasse jäävas Aafrikas.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Taotluste laekumise tähtaeg</P><P>9.2.2018 kell 17:00 Ida-Aafrika aja järgi</P><P>Pärast nimetatud tähtaega avaliku sektori hankijale laekunud taotlused ei kuulu läbivaatamisele.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Lisateave</P><P>Kõik päringud täpsustava info saamiseks tuleb saata aadressil Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu hiljemalt 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Uus versioon:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Pakkumuskutse esialgne kuupäev: 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Valikukriteeriumid</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Kandidaat on osutanud teenuseid tehnilise abi ja suutlikkuse arendamise valdkonnas mitut sektorit hõlmavate valitsuse juhitud programmide rakendamiseks vähemalt kolme lepingu raames, millest iga lepingu lepingusumma on vähemalt 3 000 000 EUR ja mis täideti mis tahes ajal viiteperioodil. See tähendab, et kandidaadi viidatud projekt võidi algatada või lõpule viia mis tahes ajal osutatud perioodi jooksul, kuid seda ei pruugitud tingimata kogu ajavahemiku jooksul algatada ja lõpule viia. Kandidaadid/pakkujad võivad viidata nii viiteperioodil lõpule viidud (kuigi varem alustatud) projektidele kui ka veel lõpule viimata projektidele. Esimesel juhul võetakse arvesse kogu projekti, juhul kui täitmise kohta esitatakse nõuetekohased tõendusmaterjalid (lepingu sõlminud asutuse kinnitus või tunnistus, lõppmakse tõend). Projektide puhul, mida veel viiakse ellu, võetakse arvesse ainult viiteperioodil rahuldavalt täidetud (kuigi varem alustatud) osa. Seda osa tuleb tõendada dokumentaalse tõendusmaterjaliga (nagu lõpuleviidud projektide puhulgi), milles on kirjas ka selle osa maksumus. Kui kandidaat/pakkuja viis projekti ellu konsortsiumis, peab tõendavatest dokumentidest ilmnema kandidaadi/pakkuja edukalt lõpule viidud tööde osakaal protsentides, samuti tuleb esitada osutatud teenuste laadi kirjeldus, kui rakendatakse kogemuste asjakohasusega seotud valikukriteeriume.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Kui eespool sätestatud valikukriteeriumidele vastavate sobivate kandidaatide arv on suurem kui 8, tuleb nende kandidaatide taotluste suhtelised tugevad ja nõrgad küljed uuesti läbi vaadata, et kindlaks teha kaheksa parimat kandidaati. Teistkordsel läbivaatamisel arvestatakse üksnes järgmiseid tegureid:</P><P>— esimesena, käesoleva lepingu/projektiga seotud projektide arv, millest iga projekti väärtus oli suurem kui 1 000 000 EUR, ning kandidaatide poolt saavutatud tulemuste võrdsuse korral;</P><P>— täidetud projektide kumulatiivne kogusumma (isegi kui igaüks neist on väiksem kui 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Taotluste laekumise tähtaeg</P><P>5.3.2018 kell 17:00 Addis Abeba aja järgi.</P><P>Pärast nimetatud tähtaega avaliku sektori hankijale laekunud taotlused ei kuulu läbivaatamisele.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Lisateave</P><P>Kõik päringud täpsustava info saamiseks tuleb saata aadressil Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu hiljemalt 19.2.2018.</P><P>Arvestage palun seda, et kõik eelmise parandusega saadud selgitused ja see, mis saadakse enne 19. veebruari, saavad vastuse koos.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Kõik muud hanketeate tingimused jäävad muutmata. Hanketeate eespool nimetatud muudatused ja/või parandused on hanketeate lahutamatu osa.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addisz-Abeba: DCI - Szakmai segítségnyújtás az éghajlatváltozás elleni globális szövetség (GCCA+) támogatásához / Az éghajlatváltozás intelligens tervezését és végrehajtását célzó megközelítéseknek a IV. Eredményes biztonsági háló programban (PSNP4) történő érvényesítése Etiópiában</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Helyesbítés</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Kiegészítés az Európai Unió Hivatalos Lapjához, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Az Európai Unió</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, amelyet az Európai Bizottság (az EU Etiópiai Delegációja) képvisel, Etiópia nevében és megbízásából, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addisz-Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiópia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>A következő helyett:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Az ajánlattételi felhívás tervezett időpontja: 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Kiválasztási kritériumok</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>A jelentkező sikerrel teljesített szolgáltatásokat legalább egy olyan szerződés keretében, melynek költségvetése legalább megegyezett a jelen szerződés költségvetésével, amely több ágazatra kiterjedő, kormányzati programok végrehajtásával kapcsolatos szakmai segítségnyújtásra és felkészültségfejlesztésre irányult, és amelynek végrehajtására a referencia-időszak során került sor. Ez azt jelenti, hogy a jelentkező által hivatkozott projektet bármikor el lehetett kezdeni/be lehetett fejezni a jelzett időszak alatt, azonban a projektet nem kellett szükségszerűen elkezdeni és be is fejezni az adott időszak alatt, és a projektnek nem kellett a teljes időszak alatt tartania. A jelentkezők/ajánlattevők feltüntethetnek referenciaként a jelzett időszakon belül befejezett (de korábban elkezdett) vagy még be nem fejezett projekteket is. Az első esetben a projektet teljes egészében figyelembe veszik, amennyiben annak teljesítéséről rendelkezésre áll megfelelő igazolás (a szerződést odaítélő gazdasági szereplőtől származó nyilatkozat vagy igazolás, a végső kifizetést igazoló dokumentum). Még folyamatban lévő projektek esetében kizárólag a projektnek a referencia-időszak során megfelelően teljesített hányadát veszik figyelembe, annak ellenére, hogy végrehajtásuk korábban kezdődött. Az adott hányad teljesítését dokumentumokkal kell alátámasztani (a befejezett projektekhez hasonlóan), értékének részletes ismertetésével. Amennyiben a jelölt/pályázó a projektet konzorcium formájában teljesítette, az igazoló dokumentumokban világosan fel kell tüntetni a jelölt/pályázó által sikeresen teljesített hányadot, amelyhez a tapasztalat helytállóságára vonatkozó kiválasztási kritériumok alkalmazása esetében csatolni kell a biztosított szolgáltatások jellegének leírását.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Amennyiben a fenti kiválasztási kritériumoknak 8-nál több jogosult jelentkező felel meg, akkor a jelentkezők által benyújtott jelentkezések relatív erősségeinek és gyengeségeinek ismételt vizsgálata alapján történik meg a nyolc legjobb jelentkezés kiválasztása. Az ismételt vizsgálat során kizárólag a következő tényezőket veszik figyelembe:</P><P>— a szerződéshez kapcsolódó projektek száma,</P><P>— a szerződéshez kapcsolódó projektek értéke,</P><P>— a szerződéshez kapcsolódóan a szubszaharai Afrikában végrehajtott projektek száma.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. A jelentkezések beérkezésének határideje</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00, kelet-afrikai idő szerint.</P><P>A fenti határidő után beérkezett jelentkezéseket az ajánlatkérő figyelmen kívül hagyja.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. További információk</P><P>A felmerülő kérdéseket legkésőbb a 31.1.2018 dátumú napig kell elküldeni a Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu e-mail-címre.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Helyesen:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Az ajánlattételi felhívás tervezett időpontja: 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Kiválasztási kritériumok</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>A jelentkező sikerrel teljesített szolgáltatásokat legalább 3 olyan szerződés keretében, melyek értéke egyenként legalább 3 000 000 EUR volt, és amelyek több ágazatra kiterjedő, kormányzati programok végrehajtásával kapcsolatos szakmai segítségnyújtásra és felkészültségfejlesztésre irányultak, és amelyek végrehajtására a referencia-időszak során került sor. Ez azt jelenti, hogy a jelentkező által hivatkozott projektet bármikor el lehetett kezdeni/be lehetett fejezni a jelzett időszak alatt, azonban a projektet nem kellett szükségszerűen elkezdeni és be is fejezni az adott időszak alatt, és a projektnek nem kellett a teljes időszak alatt tartania. A jelentkezők/ajánlattevők feltüntethetnek referenciaként a jelzett időszakon belül befejezett (de korábban elkezdett) vagy még be nem fejezett projekteket is. Az első esetben a projektet teljes egészében figyelembe veszik, amennyiben annak teljesítéséről rendelkezésre áll megfelelő igazolás (a szerződést odaítélő gazdasági szereplőtől származó nyilatkozat vagy igazolás, a végső kifizetést igazoló dokumentum). Még folyamatban lévő projektek esetében kizárólag a projektnek a referencia-időszak során megfelelően teljesített hányadát veszik figyelembe, annak ellenére, hogy végrehajtásuk korábban kezdődött. Az adott hányad teljesítését dokumentumokkal kell alátámasztani (a befejezett projektekhez hasonlóan), értékének részletes ismertetésével. Amennyiben a jelölt/pályázó a projektet konzorcium formájában teljesítette, az igazoló dokumentumokban világosan fel kell tüntetni a jelölt/pályázó által sikeresen teljesített hányadot, amelyhez a tapasztalat helytállóságára vonatkozó kiválasztási kritériumok alkalmazása esetében csatolni kell a biztosított szolgáltatások jellegének leírását.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Amennyiben a fenti kiválasztási kritériumoknak 8-nál több jogosult jelentkező felel meg, akkor a jelentkezők által benyújtott jelentkezések relatív erősségeinek és gyengeségeinek ismételt vizsgálata alapján történik meg a nyolc legjobb jelentkezés kiválasztása. Az ismételt vizsgálat során kizárólag a következő tényezőket veszik figyelembe:</P><P>— elsőként a jelen szerződéshez/projekthez kapcsolódó, egyenként legalább 1 000 000 EUR értékű projektek számát, valamint a jelentkezők pontszámainak hasonlósága esetén,</P><P>— a megvalósított projektek teljes összesített értékét (akkor is, ha ezek értéke kevesebb, mint 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. A jelentkezések beérkezésének határideje</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00, addisz-abebai idő szerint.</P><P>A fenti határidő után beérkezett jelentkezéseket az ajánlatkérő figyelmen kívül hagyja.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. További információk</P><P>A felmerülő kérdéseket legkésőbb a 19.2.2018 dátumú napig kell elküldeni a Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu e-mail-címre.</P><P>Kérjük, vegyék figyelembe, hogy a korábbi helyesbítéskor beérkezett és a február 19. előtt beérkező kérdések egyszerre kerülnek megválaszolásra.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Az ajánlati felhívás többi feltétele változatlan marad. Az ajánlati felhívás fenti módosításai és/vagy javításai annak szerves részét képezik.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Adis Abeba: DCI - Techninė pagalba remti Pasaulinį kovos su klimato kaita aljansą+ (PKKKA+) / klimato pažangių planavimo ir įgyvendinimo principų įtraukimą į produktyvaus apsaugos tinklo programą IV (PSNP4) Etiopijoje</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Klaidų ištaisymas</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Europos Bendrijos Oficialiojo Leidinio priedas, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos Sąjunga</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, atstovaujama Europos Komisijos (ES delegacijos Etiopijoje), Etiopijos vyriausybės vardu ir jos naudai, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Adis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Vietoj:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Numatoma kvietimo pateikti pasiūlymus data 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Atrankos kriterijai</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Kandidatas teikė paslaugas bent pagal vieną sutartį, kurios biudžetas buvo bent toks, kaip šios sutarties, ir pagal kurią teikė techninę pagalbą bei pajėgumų plėtrą, įgyvendinant daugelio sektorių vyriausybines programas, kurios buvo įgyvendintos bet kuriuo metu per ataskaitinį laikotarpį. Tai reiškia, kad projektas, kurį nurodo kandidatas, turi būti pradėtas arba užbaigtas bet kuriuo metu per nurodytą laikotarpį, bet nebūtinai turi būti pradėtas ir užbaigtas per tą laikotarpį arba įgyvendintas per visą laikotarpį. Kandidatai ar konkurso dalyviai gali nurodyti arba per ataskaitinį laikotarpį užbaigtus projektus (nors buvo pradėti anksčiau), arba dar neužbaigtus projektus. Pirmuoju atveju projektas bus laikomas visapusišku, jeigu bus pateikti tinkami vykdymo įrodymai (subjekto, kuris paskyrė sutartį, pažyma ar pažymėjimas, galutinio apmokėjimo įrodymas). Jeigu projektai vis dar tebevykdomi, bus atsižvelgiama tik į patenkinamai per ataskaitinį laikotarpį užbaigtą dalį, nors buvo pradėta anksčiau. Ši dalis turės būti patvirtinta dokumentiniais įrodymais (panašiai į užbaigtus projektus), taip pat nurodant jos vertę. Jei kandidatas ir (arba) konkurso dalyvis įgyvendino projektą kaip konsorciumas, kandidato ir (arba) konkurso dalyvio sėkmingai įvykdytos dalies procentinė dalis turi būti aiškiai matoma tai įrodančiuose dokumentuose ir teiktų paslaugų aprašyme su sąlyga, kad tenkinami atrankos kriterijai patirties srityje.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Jei atrankos kriterijus tenkina daugiau kaip 8 teisę dalyvauti turintys kandidatai, dar kartą įvertinami kiekvieno kandidato paraiškos pranašumai bei trūkumai ir atrenkamos aštuonios geriausios konkurso paraiškos. Vieninteliai veiksniai, į kuriuos bus atsižvelgta pakartotinės peržiūros metu:</P><P>– su šia sutartimi susijusių projektų skaičius,</P><P>– su šia sutartimi susijusių projektų vertė,</P><P>– su šia sutartimi susijusių projektų, įgyvendintų Užsachario Afrikoje, skaičius.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Paraiškų priėmimo terminas</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00 Rytų Afrikos laiku.</P><P>Paraiškos, gautos pasibaigus šiam terminui, nebus svarstomos.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Papildoma informacija</P><P>Prašymai paaiškinti gali būti siunčiami adresu Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu iki 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Turi būti:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Numatoma kvietimo pateikti pasiūlymus data 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Atrankos kriterijai</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Kandidatas teikė paslaugas bent pagal tris sutartis, kurių kiekvienos suma buvo bent 3 000 000 EUR, pagal kurias teikė techninę pagalbą bei pajėgumų plėtrą, įgyvendinant daugelio sektorių vyriausybines programas, kurios buvo įgyvendintos bet kuriuo metu per ataskaitinį laikotarpį. Tai reiškia, kad projektas, kurį nurodo kandidatas, turi būti pradėtas arba užbaigtas bet kuriuo metu per nurodytą laikotarpį, bet nebūtinai turi būti pradėtas ir užbaigtas per tą laikotarpį arba įgyvendintas per visą laikotarpį. Kandidatai ar konkurso dalyviai gali nurodyti arba per ataskaitinį laikotarpį užbaigtus projektus (nors buvo pradėti anksčiau), arba dar neužbaigtus projektus. Pirmuoju atveju projektas bus laikomas visapusišku, jeigu bus pateikti tinkami vykdymo įrodymai (subjekto, kuris paskyrė sutartį, pažyma ar pažymėjimas, galutinio apmokėjimo įrodymas). Jeigu projektai vis dar tebevykdomi, bus atsižvelgiama tik į patenkinamai per ataskaitinį laikotarpį užbaigtą dalį, nors buvo pradėta anksčiau. Ši dalis turės būti patvirtinta dokumentiniais įrodymais (panašiai į užbaigtus projektus), taip pat nurodant jos vertę. Jei kandidatas ir (arba) konkurso dalyvis įgyvendino projektą kaip konsorciumas, kandidato ir (arba) konkurso dalyvio sėkmingai įvykdytos dalies procentinė dalis turi būti aiškiai matoma tai įrodančiuose dokumentuose ir teiktų paslaugų aprašyme su sąlyga, kad tenkinami atrankos kriterijai patirties srityje.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Jei atrankos kriterijus tenkina daugiau kaip 8 teisę dalyvauti turintys kandidatai, dar kartą įvertinami kiekvieno kandidato paraiškos pranašumai bei trūkumai ir atrenkamos aštuonios geriausios konkurso paraiškos. Vieninteliai veiksniai, į kuriuos bus atsižvelgta pakartotinės peržiūros metu:</P><P>— Pirma, projektų, susijusių su šia sutartimi (projektu), skaičius, kurių kiekvienos (-o) vertė buvo didesnė nei 1 000 000 EUR, o jei kandidatų balai bus panašūs,</P><P>— Bendra kaupiamoji įgyvendintų projektų vertė (net jei kiekvieno jų vertė atskirai būtų mažesnė nei 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Paraiškų priėmimo terminas</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00 Adis Abebos laiku.</P><P>Paraiškos, gautos pasibaigus šiam terminui, nebus svarstomos.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Papildoma informacija</P><P>Prašymai paaiškinti gali būti siunčiami adresu Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu iki 19.2.2018</P><P>Prašome atkreipti dėmesį, kad į visus paaiškinimus, gautus su ankstesniu klaidų ištaisymu, ir į tą, kurį gausite iki vasario 19 d., bus atsakyti kartu.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Visos kitos skelbimo apie pirkimą nuostatos ir sąlygos lieka nepakeistos. Pirmiau išvardyti skelbimo apie pirkimą pakeitimai ir (arba) pataisymai yra neatskiriama skelbimo apie pirkimą dalis.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Adisabeba: ASI - Tehniskā palīdzība ar mērķi atbalstīt GCCA+ / klimata jomas pārdomātas plānošanas un ieviešanas pieeju integrēšanu Produktīvā drošības tīkla IV programmā (PSNP4) Etiopijā</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Labojums</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Eiropas Savienības Oficiālā Vēstneša pielikums, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Savienība</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ko Etiopijas valdības vārdā un interesēs pārstāv Eiropas Komisija (ES delegācija Etiopijā), </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Adisabeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Šī teksta vietā:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Paredzamais konkursa izsludināšanas datums 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Atlases kritēriji</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Kandidāts ir sniedzis pakalpojumus vismaz viena līguma ietvaros ar tādu budžetu, kas ir vismaz tāds pats kā šim līgumam, tehniskās palīdzības jomā un spēju attīstības jomā, īstenojot daudznozaru valdības vadītas programmas, kuras tika īstenotas jebkurā brīdī atsauces periodā. Tas nozīmē, ka kandidāta minētais projekts var būt sākts vai pabeigts jebkurā brīdī norādītajā periodā, bet tam nav obligāti jābūt sāktam un pabeigtam šajā periodā, ne arī īstenotam visa perioda laikā. Kandidāti/pretendenti var norādīt vai nu projektus, kas ir pabeigti atsauces periodā (kaut arī tie ir sākti agrāk), vai arī projektus, kas vēl nav pabeigti. Pabeigtu projektu gadījumā tiks ņemts vērā viss projekts, ja tiks iesniegts pienācīgs izpildes pierādījums (paziņojums vai sertifikāts no personas, kas piešķīrusi līgumu, pierādījums par galīgo maksājumu). Ja projekti vēl joprojām tiek pildīti, tiks ņemta vērā tikai atsauces periodā apmierinoši izpildītā daļa (kaut arī tā sākta agrāk). Par šo daļu būs jāiesniedz dokumentārs pierādījums (tāpat kā pabeigtu projektu gadījumā), kurā jābūt norādītai arī tās vērtībai. Ja kandidāts/pretendents ir īstenojis projektu konsorcija sastāvā, jāiesniedz dokumentārs pierādījums, kurā skaidri norādīta kandidāta/pretendenta veiksmīgi izpildītā procentuālā daļa, kā arī nodrošināto pakalpojumu veida apraksts, ja izmantoti atlases kritēriji saistībā ar pieredzes piemērotību.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Ja iepriekš minētajiem atlases kritērijiem atbilst vairāk nekā 8 piemēroti kandidāti, atkārtoti jāizvērtē šo kandidātu iesniegto pieteikumu relatīvās priekšrocības un trūkumi, lai noteiktu 8 labākos kandidātus. Vienīgie faktori, kas tiks ņemti vērā, veicot šo atkārtoto izvērtēšanu, ir šādi:</P><P>— ar šo līgumu saistīto projektu skaits;</P><P>— ar šo līgumu saistīto projektu vērtība;</P><P>— Subsahāras Āfrikā īstenoto ar šo līgumu saistīto projektu skaits.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Pieteikumu saņemšanas termiņš</P><P>9.2.2018 (17:00) pēc Austrumāfrikas laika</P><P>Neviens pieteikums, ko līgumslēdzēja iestāde saņems pēc minētā termiņa, netiks izskatīts.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Papildu informācija</P><P>Skaidrojumu pieprasījumi jāsūta uz e-pasta adresi Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu ne vēlāk kā līdz 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Jābūt:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Paredzamais konkursa izsludināšanas datums: 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Atlases kritēriji</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Kandidāts ir sniedzis pakalpojumus vismaz 3 līgumu ietvaros ar budžetu vismaz 3 000 000 EUR apmērā (katram) tehniskās palīdzības jomā un spēju attīstības jomā, īstenojot daudznozaru valdības vadītas programmas, kuras tika īstenotas jebkurā brīdī atsauces periodā. Tas nozīmē, ka kandidāta minētais projekts var būt sākts vai pabeigts jebkurā brīdī norādītajā periodā, bet tam nav obligāti jābūt sāktam un pabeigtam šajā periodā, ne arī īstenotam visa perioda laikā. Kandidāti/pretendenti var norādīt vai nu projektus, kas ir pabeigti atsauces periodā (kaut arī tie ir sākti agrāk), vai arī projektus, kas vēl nav pabeigti. Pabeigtu projektu gadījumā tiks ņemts vērā viss projekts, ja tiks iesniegts pienācīgs izpildes pierādījums (paziņojums vai sertifikāts no personas, kas piešķīrusi līgumu, pierādījums par galīgo maksājumu). Ja projekti vēl joprojām tiek pildīti, tiks ņemta vērā tikai atsauces periodā apmierinoši izpildītā daļa (kaut arī tā sākta agrāk). Par šo daļu būs jāiesniedz dokumentārs pierādījums (tāpat kā pabeigtu projektu gadījumā), kurā jābūt norādītai arī tās vērtībai. Ja kandidāts/pretendents ir īstenojis projektu konsorcija sastāvā, jāiesniedz dokumentārs pierādījums, kurā skaidri norādīta kandidāta/pretendenta veiksmīgi izpildītā procentuālā daļa, kā arī nodrošināto pakalpojumu veida apraksts, ja izmantoti atlases kritēriji saistībā ar pieredzes piemērotību.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Ja iepriekš minētajiem atlases kritērijiem atbilst vairāk nekā 8 piemēroti kandidāti, atkārtoti jāizvērtē šo kandidātu iesniegto pieteikumu relatīvās priekšrocības un trūkumi, lai noteiktu 8 labākos kandidātus. Vienīgie faktori, kas tiks ņemti vērā, veicot šo atkārtoto izvērtēšanu, ir šādi:</P><P>— vispirms – ar šo līgumu/projektu saistīto projektu skaits, kuru vērtība pārsniedz 1 000 000 EUR (katram); ja kandidātiem ir līdzīgs rezultāts, tad</P><P>— kopējais īstenoto projektu apjoms (arī, ja katra projekta vērtība ir mazāka nekā 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Pieteikumu saņemšanas termiņš</P><P>5.3.2018 (17:00) pēc Adisabebas vietējā laika</P><P>Neviens pieteikums, ko līgumslēdzēja iestāde saņems pēc minētā termiņa, netiks izskatīts.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Papildu informācija</P><P>Skaidrojumu pieprasījumi jāsūta uz e-pasta adresi Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu ne vēlāk kā līdz 19.2.2018.</P><P>Lūdzam ņemt vērā, ka uz skaidrojumu pieprasījumiem, kas saņemti no iepriekšējā labojuma, un uz skaidrojumu pieprasījumiem, kas saņemti līdz 19. februārim, atbildes tiks sniegtas kopā.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Visi pārējie paziņojuma par līgumu noteikumi un nosacījumi paliek nemainīgi. Iepriekš minētās izmaiņas un/vai labojumi paziņojumā par līgumu ir neatņemama paziņojuma par līgumu daļa.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Ababa: SKŻ - Għajnuna teknika biex tappoġġja lill-Global Climate Change Alliance Plus (GCCA+)/l-ippjanar intelliġenti mhux diskriminatorju dwar il-klima u l-approċċi ta' implimentazzjoni fil-Programm IV dwar ix-Xibka tas-Sigurtà Produttiva (PSNP4) fl-Etjopja</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tiswija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement tal-Gurnal Ufficjali ta’ l-Unjoni Ewropea’, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>L-Unjoni Ewropea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, irrappreżentata mill-Kummissjoni Ewropea (Delegazzjoni tal-UE fl-Etjopja) , f'isem u għall-Etjopja, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Ababa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, l-Etjopja.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Minflok:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Id-data provviżorja tal-istedina għall-offerti 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Il-kriterji tal-għażla</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Il-kandidat ipprovda servizzi taħt mill-inqas kuntratt wieħed b'baġit ta' mill-inqas dak ta' dan il-kuntratt fl-oqsma ta' għajnuna teknika u l-iżvilupp ta' kapaċità għall-implimentazzjoni ta' programmi multisettorjali mmexxija mill-gvern, li kienu implimentati fi kwalunkwe ħin matul il-perijodu ta' referenza. Dan ifisser li l-proġett li jirreferi għalih il-kandidat seta' nbeda u tlesta f'kull waqt matul il-perijodu msemmi iżda mhux bilfors irid ikun inbeda u tlesta matul dak il-perijodu, u lanqas ma jrid ikun implimentat matul dak il-perijodu kollu. Il-kandidati/dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti jistgħu jirreferu għal kuntratti li tlestew matul il-perijodu ta' referenza (għalkemm ikunu nbdew qabel) jew għal proġetti li għadhom ma tlestewx. Fl-ewwel każ, il-proġett se jitqies kollu kemm hu jekk tingħata evidenza xierqa tat-twettiq tax-xogħol (stqarrija jew ċertifikat mingħand l-entità li tat il-kuntratt, prova tal-ħlas aħħari). F'każ ta' proġetti li għadhom għaddejjin, se titqies biss dik il-parti li tlestiet b'mod xieraq sad-data li tkun fil-perijodu ta' referenza minkejja li tkun bdiet qabel. Din il-parti se jkollha tiġi appoġġjata minn prova dokumentarja (bħal fi proġetti li tlestew) billi jingħata l-valur tagħha. Jekk kandidat/min qiegħed jitfa' l-offerta implimenta l-proġett bħala parti minn konsorzju, il-persentaġġ li l-kandidat/min qiegħed jitfa' l-offerta temm b'suċċess għandu joħroġ b'mod ċar mill-prova dokumentarja, flimkien ma' deskrizzjoni tat-tip ta' servizzi li ngħataw jekk intużaw il-kriterji tal-għażla marbuta mal-importanza tal-esperjenza.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Jekk ikun hemm iktar minn 8 kandidati li jilħqu l-kriterji tal-għażla msemmija hawn fuq, il-ħiliet u n-nuqqasijiet relattivi tal-applikazzjonijiet ta' dawn il-kandidati se jiġu eżaminati mill-ġdid biex jintgħażlu l-aqwa 8 kandidati. Matul din l-eżaminazzjoni mill-ġdid se jkunu meqjusa dawn il-fatturi biss:</P><P>— L-għadd ta' proġetti relatati ma' dan il-kuntratt,</P><P>— Il-valur ta' proġetti relatati ma' dan il-kuntratt,</P><P>— L-għadd ta' proġetti marbuta ma' dan il-kuntratt li kienu implimentati fl-Afrika sub-Saħarjana.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Id-data tal-għeluq għall-wasla tal-applikazzjonijiet</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00, Ħin tal-Afrika tal-Lvant.</P><P>Kwalunkwe applikazzjoni li tasal għand l-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt wara din id-data tal-għeluq mhix se titqies.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Tagħrif addizzjonali</P><P>Kull talba għal kjarifika għandha tintbagħat lil Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu mhux aktar tard mill-31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Aqra:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Id-data provviżorja tal-istedina għall-offerti 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Il-kriterji tal-għażla</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Il-kandidat ipprovda servizzi taħt mill-inqas 3 kuntratti, kull wieħed b'ammont ta' kuntratt ta' mhux inqas minn 3 000 000 EUR fl-oqsma ta' għajnuna teknika u l-iżvilupp ta' kapaċità għall-implimentazzjoni ta' programmi multisettorjali mmexxija mill-gvern, li kienu implimentati fi kwalunkwe ħin matul il-perijodu ta' referenza. Dan ifisser li l-proġett li jirreferi għalih il-kandidat seta' nbeda u tlesta f'kull waqt matul il-perijodu msemmi iżda mhux bilfors irid ikun inbeda u tlesta matul dak il-perijodu, u lanqas ma jrid ikun implimentat matul dak il-perijodu kollu. Il-kandidati/dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti jistgħu jirreferu għal kuntratti li tlestew matul il-perijodu ta' referenza (għalkemm ikunu nbdew qabel) jew għal proġetti li għadhom ma tlestewx. Fl-ewwel każ, il-proġett se jitqies kollu kemm hu jekk tingħata evidenza xierqa tat-twettiq tax-xogħol (stqarrija jew ċertifikat mingħand l-entità li tat il-kuntratt, prova tal-ħlas aħħari). F'każ ta' proġetti li għadhom għaddejjin, se titqies biss dik il-parti li tlestiet b'mod xieraq sad-data li tkun fil-perijodu ta' referenza minkejja li tkun bdiet qabel. Din il-parti se jkollha tiġi appoġġjata minn prova dokumentarja (bħal fi proġetti li tlestew) billi jingħata l-valur tagħha. Jekk kandidat/min qiegħed jitfa' l-offerta implimenta l-proġett bħala parti minn konsorzju, il-persentaġġ li l-kandidat/min qiegħed jitfa' l-offerta temm b'suċċess għandu joħroġ b'mod ċar mill-prova dokumentarja, flimkien ma' deskrizzjoni tat-tip ta' servizzi li ngħataw jekk intużaw il-kriterji tal-għażla marbuta mal-importanza tal-esperjenza.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Jekk ikun hemm iktar minn 8 kandidati li jilħqu l-kriterji tal-għażla msemmija hawn fuq, il-ħiliet u n-nuqqasijiet relattivi tal-applikazzjonijiet ta' dawn il-kandidati se jiġu eżaminati mill-ġdid biex jintgħażlu l-aqwa 8 kandidati. Matul din l-eżaminazzjoni mill-ġdid se jkunu meqjusa dawn il-fatturi biss:</P><P>— l-ewwel, in-numru ta' proġetti relatati ma' dan il-kuntratt/proġett b'valur ta' mhux aktar minn 1 000 000 EUR kull wieħed u f'każijiet ta' similaritajiet ta' punteġġi bejn kandidati,</P><P>—L ammont kumulattiv totali ta' proġetti implimentati (anke jekk kull wieħed ikun ta' anqas minn 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Id-data tal-għeluq għall-wasla tal-applikazzjonijiet</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00 Ħin ta' Addis Ababa.</P><P>Kwalunkwe applikazzjoni li tasal għand l-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt wara din id-data tal-għeluq mhix se titqies.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Tagħrif addizzjonali</P><P>Kull talba għal kjarifika għandha tintbagħat lil Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu mhux aktar tard mid-19.2.2018</P><P>Jekk jogħġbok innota li l-kjarifiki kollha rċevuti mat-tiswija preċedenti u dik li trid tiġi rċevuta qabel id-19 ta' Frar se jitwieġbu flimkien.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>It-termini u l-kundizzjonijiet l-oħrajn kollha tal-avviż ta' kuntratt jibqgħu ma jinbidlux. It-tibdiliet u/jew it-tiswijiet ta' hawn fuq għall-avviż ta' kuntratt huma parti integrali mill-avviż tal-kuntratt.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: DCI - Pomoc techniczna na potrzeby wsparcia światowego sojuszu na rzecz przeciwdziałania zmianom klimatycznym (GCCA+)/Włączenie podejść obejmujących inteligentne planowanie i wdrażanie w dziedzinie klimatu do programu sieci bezpieczeństwa produkcji IV (PSNP4) w Etiopii</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sprostowanie</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplement do Dziennika Urzędowego Unii Europejskiej, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unia Europejska</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentowana przez Komisję Europejską, w imieniu i na rzecz rządu Etiopii, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Zamiast:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Planowana data zaproszenia do składania ofert 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Kryteria wyboru</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Kandydat świadczył usługi w ramach przynajmniej jednego zamówienia, którego budżet był przynajmniej równy budżetowi niniejszego zamówienia, w obszarach dotyczących pomocy technicznej w rozwoju zarządzania w celu wdrożenia programów rządowych, które były realizowane w dowolnym czasie w okresie referencyjnym. Oznacza to, że projekt, na który powołuje się kandydat, mógł się rozpocząć lub zakończyć w dowolnym czasie we wskazanym okresie, lecz niekoniecznie musiał się i rozpocząć, i zakończyć w tym okresie ani trwać przez cały ten okres. Kandydaci/oferenci mogą powołać się na projekty zakończone w okresie referencyjnym (nawet jeśli rozpoczęły się wcześniej) bądź na projekty jeszcze nieukończone. W pierwszym przypadku zostanie uwzględniona całość projektu, jeżeli zostaną przedstawione odpowiednie dowody na jego realizację (oświadczenie lub zaświadczenie instytucji zamawiającej, dowód uiszczenia płatności końcowej). W przypadku projektów będących w toku realizacji brana pod uwagę będzie wyłącznie część projektu rozpoczęta wcześniej, lecz pomyślnie ukończona w okresie referencyjnym. Wymagane jest przedłożenie odpowiednich dowodów na realizację danych części (podobnie jak w przypadku projektów ukończonych), ze wskazaniem ich wartości. Jeżeli kandydat/oferent realizował projekt w ramach konsorcjum, informacje na temat określonej procentowo części pomyślnie zrealizowanej przez kandydata/oferenta muszą być wyraźnie podane w dokumentacji potwierdzającej, wraz z opisem charakteru świadczonych usług, jeżeli zastosowano kryteria wyboru dotyczące doświadczenia.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Jeżeli więcej niż 8 kwalifikujących się kandydatów spełnia powyższe kryteria wyboru, wnioski tych kandydatów muszą zostać ponownie zbadane pod kątem ich odpowiednich słabych i mocnych stron w celu wskazania 8 najlepszych kandydatów. Jedynymi kryteriami, które zostaną wzięte pod uwagę w trakcie tego ponownego badania, są:</P><P>— Liczba projektów związanych z niniejszym zamówieniem,</P><P>— Wartość projektów związanych z niniejszym zamówieniem,</P><P>— Liczba projektów związanych z niniejszym zamówieniem zrealizowanych w Afryce Subsaharyjskiej.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termin przyjmowania wniosków</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00 czasu wschodnioafrykańskiego</P><P>Wnioski otrzymane przez instytucję zamawiającą po upływie tego terminu nie będą rozpatrywane.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Informacje dodatkowe</P><P>Zapytania o wyjaśnienia należy przesłać na adres Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu najpóźniej do 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Powinno być:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Planowana data zaproszenia do składania ofert 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Kryteria wyboru</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Kandydat świadczył usługi w ramach przynajmniej trzech zamówień, każdego z budżetem w wysokości co najmniej 3 000 000 EUR, w obszarach dotyczących pomocy technicznej w rozwoju zarządzania w celu wdrożenia programów rządowych, które były realizowane w dowolnym czasie w okresie referencyjnym. Oznacza to, że projekt, na który powołuje się kandydat, mógł się rozpocząć lub zakończyć w dowolnym czasie we wskazanym okresie, lecz niekoniecznie musiał się i rozpocząć, i zakończyć w tym okresie ani trwać przez cały ten okres. Kandydaci/oferenci mogą powołać się na projekty zakończone w okresie referencyjnym (nawet jeśli rozpoczęły się wcześniej) bądź na projekty jeszcze nieukończone. W pierwszym przypadku zostanie uwzględniona całość projektu, jeżeli zostaną przedstawione odpowiednie dowody na jego realizację (oświadczenie lub zaświadczenie instytucji zamawiającej, dowód uiszczenia płatności końcowej). W przypadku projektów będących w toku realizacji brana pod uwagę będzie wyłącznie część projektu rozpoczęta wcześniej, lecz pomyślnie ukończona w okresie referencyjnym. Wymagane jest przedłożenie odpowiednich dowodów na realizację danych części (podobnie jak w przypadku projektów ukończonych), ze wskazaniem ich wartości. Jeżeli kandydat/oferent realizował projekt w ramach konsorcjum, informacje na temat określonej procentowo części pomyślnie zrealizowanej przez kandydata/oferenta muszą być wyraźnie podane w dokumentacji potwierdzającej, wraz z opisem charakteru świadczonych usług, jeżeli zastosowano kryteria wyboru dotyczące doświadczenia.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Jeżeli więcej niż 8 kwalifikujących się kandydatów spełnia powyższe kryteria wyboru, wnioski tych kandydatów muszą zostać ponownie zbadane pod kątem ich odpowiednich słabych i mocnych stron w celu wskazania 8 najlepszych kandydatów. Jedynymi kryteriami, które zostaną wzięte pod uwagę w trakcie tego ponownego badania, są:</P><P>– w pierwszej kolejności liczba projektów związanych z tym projektem o wartości większej niż 1 000 000 EUR każdy, a w przypadku zbieżności punktacji między kandydatami,</P><P>– łączna liczba zrealizowanych projektów (nawet jeśli każdy z nich miał wartość mniejszą niż 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termin przyjmowania wniosków</P><P>5.3.2018 (17:00) czasu miejscowego w Addis Abebie.</P><P>Wnioski otrzymane przez instytucję zamawiającą po upływie tego terminu nie będą rozpatrywane.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Informacje dodatkowe</P><P>Zapytania o wyjaśnienia należy przesłać na adres Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu do 19.2.2018.</P><P>Należy wziąć pod uwagę, że wszystkie objaśnienia otrzymane w związku z poprzednim sprostowaniem oraz otrzymane przed 19 lutego zostaną złożone razem.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Pozostałe warunki wymienione w ogłoszeniu o zamówieniu nie ulegają zmianie. Powyższe zmiany i/lub poprawki ogłoszenia o zamówieniu stanowią jego integralną część.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Abeba: DCI - Technická pomoc na podporu Globálnej aliancie proti zmene klímy plus (GCCA+)/začlenenie inteligentných prístupov týkajúcich sa plánovania a vykonávania v oblasti klímy do Programu produktívnej záchrannej siete IV (PSNP4) v Etiópii</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Korigendum</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Príloha k Úradnému vestníku Európskej únie, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európska únia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastúpená Európskou komisiou (Delegácia EÚ v Etiópii), v mene a záujme vlády Etiópie, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiópia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Namiesto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Predbežný dátum výzvy na predloženie ponúk 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Kritériá výberu</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Uchádzač poskytoval služby v rámci aspoň 1 obstarávania s rozpočtom aspoň na úrovni tohto obstarávania v oblasti odbornej pomoci a rozvoja spôsobilostí na realizáciu multisektorálnych vládnych programov, ktoré boli implementované kedykoľvek počas referenčného obdobia. To znamená, že projekt, ktorý uchádzač uvádza, sa mohol začať alebo mohol byť dokončený kedykoľvek počas uvedeného obdobia, nemusel sa však nevyhnutne začať ani byť dokončený počas tohto obdobia, ani nebol realizovaný počas celého obdobia. Uchádzači/záujemcovia môžu uviesť ako referencie projekty dokončené v rámci referenčného obdobia (aj keď sa začali skôr), ako aj projekty, ktoré ešte nie sú dokončené. V prvom prípade sa projekt zohľadní ako celok, ak bol poskytnutý náležitý dôkaz o vykonaní (vyhlásenie alebo osvedčenie zo strany subjektu, ktorý pridelil obstarávanie, dôkaz o konečnej úhrade). V prípade ešte prebiehajúcich projektov sa bude brať do úvahy iba podiel uspokojivo dokončený počas referenčného obdobia, hoci sa projekt začal už skôr. Tento podiel musí byť doložený dokumentárnym dôkazom (podobne ako v prípade dokončených projektov) taktiež s podrobným uvedením jeho hodnoty. Ak záujemca/uchádzač realizoval projekt v konzorciu, z dokumentárneho dôkazu musí byť jasný percentuálny podiel, ktorý záujemca/uchádzač úspešne dokončil, spolu s opisom povahy poskytnutých služieb, ak sa použili kritériá výberu týkajúce sa relevantnosti skúseností.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Ak počet spôsobilých uchádzačov, ktorí splnia uvedené kritériá výberu, presahuje 8, musia sa na určenie 8 najlepších uchádzačov opätovne preveriť relatívne výhody a nevýhody prihlášok týchto uchádzačov. Počas tohto opätovného preverenia sa budú brať do úvahy výhradne nasledujúce faktory:</P><P>— počet projektov súvisiacich s týmto obstarávaním,</P><P>— hodnota projektov súvisiacich s týmto obstarávaním,</P><P>— počet projektov súvisiacich s týmto obstarávaním, realizovaných v subsaharskej Afrike.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Konečný termín doručenia prihlášok</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00 hod. miestneho času vo východnej Afrike.</P><P>Prihlášky doručené obstarávateľovi po tomto termíne sa nebudú brať do úvahy.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Dodatočné informácie</P><P>Akékoľvek žiadosti o objasnenie je nutné zaslať na Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu najneskôr do 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Viď:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Predbežný dátum výzvy na predloženie ponúk 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Kritériá výberu</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Uchádzač poskytoval služby v rámci aspoň 3 obstarávaní, z ktorých každé malo zmluvnú hodnotu minimálne vo výške 3 000 000 EUR, v oblasti odbornej pomoci a rozvoja spôsobilostí na realizáciu multisektorálnych vládnych programov, ktoré boli realizované kedykoľvek počas referenčného obdobia. To znamená, že projekt, ktorý uchádzač uvádza, sa mohol začať alebo mohol byť dokončený kedykoľvek počas uvedeného obdobia, nemusel sa však nevyhnutne začať ani byť dokončený počas tohto obdobia, ani nebol realizovaný počas celého obdobia. Uchádzači/záujemcovia môžu uviesť ako referencie projekty dokončené v rámci referenčného obdobia (aj keď sa začali skôr), ako aj projekty, ktoré ešte nie sú dokončené. V prvom prípade sa projekt zohľadní ako celok, ak bol poskytnutý náležitý dôkaz o vykonaní (vyhlásenie alebo osvedčenie zo strany subjektu, ktorý pridelil obstarávanie, dôkaz o konečnej úhrade). V prípade ešte prebiehajúcich projektov sa bude brať do úvahy iba podiel uspokojivo dokončený počas referenčného obdobia, hoci sa projekt začal už skôr. Tento podiel musí byť doložený dokumentárnym dôkazom (podobne ako v prípade dokončených projektov) taktiež s podrobným uvedením jeho hodnoty. Ak záujemca/uchádzač realizoval projekt v konzorciu, z dokumentárneho dôkazu musí byť jasný percentuálny podiel, ktorý záujemca/uchádzač úspešne dokončil, spolu s opisom povahy poskytnutých služieb, ak sa použili kritériá výberu týkajúce sa relevantnosti skúseností.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Ak počet spôsobilých uchádzačov, ktorí splnia uvedené kritériá výberu, presahuje 8, musia sa na určenie 8 najlepších uchádzačov opätovne preveriť relatívne výhody a nevýhody prihlášok týchto uchádzačov. Počas tohto opätovného preverenia sa budú brať do úvahy výhradne nasledujúce faktory:</P><P>— po prvé, počet projektov súvisiacich s touto zmluvou/projektom, každý s hodnotou viac ako 1 000 000 EUR; a v prípade podobného bodového ohodnotenia kandidátov</P><P>— celková kumulatívna suma vykonaných projektov (aj v prípade, že každý z nich má hodnotu nižšiu ako 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Konečný termín doručenia prihlášok</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00 hod. miestneho času v Addis Abebe.</P><P>Prihlášky doručené obstarávateľovi po tomto termíne sa nebudú brať do úvahy.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Dodatočné informácie</P><P>Akékoľvek žiadosti o objasnenie je potrebné zaslať na adresu Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu najneskôr do 19.2.2018</P><P>Upozorňujeme, že všetky objasnenia obdržané s predchádzajúcim korigendom a tie, ktoré budú doručené pred 19.2., budú zodpovedané spoločne.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Všetky ostatné body a podmienky oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania zostanú nezmenené. Vyššie uvedené zmeny a/alebo úpravy v oznámení o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania tvoria neoddeliteľnú súčasť oznámenia.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Adis Abeba: DCI - Tehnična pomoč za podporo globalnega zavezništva o podnebnih spremembah+ (GCCA+)/vključitev pametnih pristopov načrtovanja in izvajanja na področju podnebja v program produktivnih varnostnih mrež IV (PSNP4) v Etiopiji</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Popravek</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatek k Uradnemu listu Evropske unije, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ki jo zastopa Evropska komisija (Delegacija EU v Etiopiji), v imenu in za račun Etiopije, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Adis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Namesto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Predvideni datum povabila k oddaji ponudb 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Merila za izbor</P><P>(3) [...]</P><P>Kandidat je zagotovil storitve v okviru vsaj 1 naročila s proračunom najmanj v višini proračuna tega naročila na področju tehnične pomoči in razvoja zmogljivosti za izvajanje večsektorskih vladnih programov, ki je bilo izvedeno kadar koli v referenčnem obdobju. To pomeni, da se je lahko projekt, na katerega se sklicuje kandidat, začel ali zaključil kadar koli v navedenem obdobju, vendar ni nujno, da se je začel in zaključil v tem obdobju ali izvajal v celotnem obdobju. Kandidati/ponudniki se lahko sklicujejo na projekte, ki so se zaključili v referenčnem obdobju (čeprav so se začeli prej), ali na projekte, ki še potekajo. V prvem primeru se bo projekt upošteval v celoti, če bodo predložena ustrezna dokazila o izvedbi (izjava ali potrdilo subjekta, ki je oddal naročilo, dokazilo o končnem plačilu). V primeru projektov, ki še potekajo, se bo upošteval le delež, ustrezno zaključen v referenčnem obdobju, četudi se je začel prej. Ta delež bo treba podpreti z dokumentarnimi dokazili (podobno kot za zaključene projekte), pri čemer je treba navesti tudi njegovo vrednost. Če je kandidat/ponudnik izvedel projekt v konzorciju, mora biti iz dokumentarnega dokazila razviden odstotni delež, ki ga je kandidat/ponudnik uspešno zaključil, skupaj z opisom vrste zagotovljenih storitev, če so bila uporabljena merila za izbor, ki se nanašajo na ustreznost izkušenj.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Če zgoraj navedena merila za izbor izpolnjuje več kot 8 upravičenih kandidatov, je treba prednosti in slabosti prijav teh kandidatov ponovno oceniti ter določiti 8 najboljših kandidatov. Pri ponovnem ocenjevanju se bodo upoštevali samo naslednji dejavniki:</P><P>— število projektov, povezanih s tem naročilom,</P><P>— vrednost projektov, povezanih s tem naročilom,</P><P>— število projektov, povezanih s tem naročilom in izvedenih v podsaharski Afriki.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Rok za sprejemanje prijav</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00 po vzhodnoafriškem času</P><P>Prijave, ki jih bo naročnik prejel po tem roku, ne bodo upoštevane.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Dodatne informacije</P><P>Kakršne koli zahtevke za pojasnila je treba poslati na naslov Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu najpozneje do 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Beri:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Predvideni datum povabila k oddaji ponudb 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Merila za izbor</P><P>(3) [...]</P><P>Kandidat je zagotovil storitve v okviru vsaj 3 naročil s proračunom posameznega najmanj v višini 3 000 000 EUR na področju tehnične pomoči in razvoja zmogljivosti za izvajanje večsektorskih vladnih programov, ki so bile izvedene kadar koli v referenčnem obdobju. To pomeni, da se je lahko projekt, na katerega se sklicuje kandidat, začel ali zaključil kadar koli v navedenem obdobju, vendar ni nujno, da se je začel in zaključil v tem obdobju ali izvajal v celotnem obdobju. Kandidati/ponudniki se lahko sklicujejo na projekte, ki so se zaključili v referenčnem obdobju (čeprav so se začeli prej), ali na projekte, ki še potekajo. V prvem primeru se bo projekt upošteval v celoti, če bodo predložena ustrezna dokazila o izvedbi (izjava ali potrdilo subjekta, ki je oddal naročilo, dokazilo o končnem plačilu). V primeru projektov, ki še potekajo, se bo upošteval le delež, ustrezno zaključen v referenčnem obdobju, četudi se je začel prej. Ta delež bo treba podpreti z dokumentarnimi dokazili (podobno kot za zaključene projekte), pri čemer je treba navesti tudi njegovo vrednost. Če je kandidat/ponudnik izvedel projekt v konzorciju, mora biti iz dokumentarnega dokazila razviden odstotni delež, ki ga je kandidat/ponudnik uspešno zaključil, skupaj z opisom vrste zagotovljenih storitev, če so bila uporabljena merila za izbor, ki se nanašajo na ustreznost izkušenj.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Če zgoraj navedena merila za izbor izpolnjuje več kot 8 upravičenih kandidatov, je treba prednosti in slabosti prijav teh kandidatov ponovno oceniti ter določiti 8 najboljših kandidatov. Pri ponovnem ocenjevanju se bodo upoštevali samo naslednji dejavniki:</P><P>— prvič, število projektov, povezanih s tem naročilom/projektom, z vrednostjo posameznega nad 1 000 000 EUR, v primeru podobnih rezultatov kandidatov pa še</P><P>— skupni znesek izvedenih projektov (tudi če znaša vrednost posameznih projektov manj kot 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Rok za sprejemanje prijav</P><P>5.3.2018 (17:00) po času v Adis Abebi.</P><P>Prijave, ki jih bo naročnik prejel po tem roku, ne bodo upoštevane.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Dodatne informacije</P><P>Zahtevke za pojasnila je treba poslati na naslov Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu najpozneje do 19.2.2018.</P><P>Upoštevajte, da bodo odgovori na zahtevke za pojasnila, prejete v zvezi s prejšnjim popravkom, in zahtevke, ki bodo predloženi do 19.2.2018, posredovani hkrati.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Vsi ostali formalni pogoji obvestila o naročilu ostanejo nespremenjeni. Zgornje spremembe in/ali popravki obvestila o naročilu so sestavni del obvestila o naročilu.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Ababa: DCI - Cúnamh teicniúil chun tacú leis an gclár Comhaontas Domhanda um Athrú Aeráide+ (GCCA+)/Príomhshruthú na Pleanála Cliste i leith na hAeráide agus Cineálacha Cur Chuige um Chur chun Feidhme i gClár Líontáin Sábhála Tháirgiúil IV (PSNP4) san Aetóip</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ceartúchán</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Forlíonaidh d'Iris Oifigiúil an Aontais Eorpaigh, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An tAontas Eorpach</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, arna ionadú ag an gCoimisiún Eorpach (Toscaireacht an AE san Aetóip) thar ceann agus chun cuntais na hAetóipe, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Ababa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Aetóip.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Seachas:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Dáta sealadach an chuiridh chun tairisceana 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Critéir roghnúcháin</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Sholáthair an t-iarrthóir seirbhísí faoi chonradh amháin ar a laghad agus buiséad i gceist leis ar chomhionann le buiséad an chonartha seo ar a laghad, a bhain i limistéir an chúnaimh theicniúil agus na forbartha acmhainní do chur chun feidhme clár ilearnálach faoi cheannas an rialtais a cuireadh i gcrích ag am ar bith i rith na tréimhse teistiméireachta. Ciallaíonn sé sin go mb’fhéidir go raibh an tionscadal dá dtagraíonn an t-iarrthóir tosaithe nó tugtha chun críche ag am ar bith le linn na tréimhse léirithe ach nach gá go raibh sé tionscanta agus tugtha chun críche le linn na tréimhse sin ná curtha i bhfeidhm le linn na tréimhse iomláine. Ceadaítear d'iarrthóirí/do thairgeoirí tagairt a dhéanamh do thionscadail a cuireadh i gcrích laistigh den tréimhse theistiméireachta (cé gur cuireadh tús leo roimhe sin) nó do thionscadail nach bhfuil curtha i gcrích go fóill. Sa chéad chás is amhlaidh a bhreithneofar an tionscadal ina iomláine má chuirtear fianaise cheart ar fheidhmíocht ar fáil (ráiteas nó teastas ón eintiteas a dhámh an conradh, cruthúnas ar íocaíocht deiridh). I gcás tionscadal atá fós ar siúl ní bhreithneofar ach an cion sin a cuireadh i gcrích go sásúil le linn na tréimhse tagartha cé gur cuireadh tús leo níos luaithe ná sin. Ní mór fianaise dhoiciméadach a sholáthar mar thaca leis an gcion sin (cosúil le tionscadail atá curtha i gcrích) lena mionsonraítear a luach freisin. Má chuir iarrthóir/tairgeoir an tionscadal i bhfeidhm mar chuid de chuibhreannas, ní foláir nó go bhfuil an céatadán a chuir an t-iarrthóir/tairgeoir i gcrích go rathúil soiléir ón bhfianaise dhoiciméadach, mar aon le cur síos ar chineál na seirbhísí a cuireadh ar fáil má baineadh úsáid as na critéir roghnúcháin a bhaineann le hábharthacht na taithí.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Má chomhlíonann níos mó ná 8 iarrthóirí incháilithe na critéir roghnúcháin thuas, ansin ní mór athscrúdú a dhéanamh ar láidreachtaí agus ar laigí coibhneasta iarratais na n-iarrthóirí sin d'fhonn an t-ochtar iarrthóirí is fearr a aithint. Ní bhreithneofar ach na fachtóirí seo a leanas agus iad sin amháin le linn an athscrúdaithe sin:</P><P>— Líon na dtionscadal a bhaineann leis an gconradh seo,</P><P>— Luach na dtionscadal a bhaineann leis an gconradh seo,</P><P>— Líon na dtionscadal a bhaineann leis an gconradh seo a feidhmíodh san Afraic fho-Shahárach.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Spriocdháta chun iarratais a fháil</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00 na hAfraice Thoir.</P><P>Ní bhreithneofar aon tairiscint a gheofar ag an údarás conarthachta tar éis an spriocdháta sin.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Faisnéis bhreise</P><P>Ní foláir aon iarratas ar shoiléiriú a sheoladh chuig Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu tráth nach déanaí an 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Léigh:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Dáta sealadach an chuiridh chun tairisceana 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Critéir roghnúcháin</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Sholáthair an t-iarrthóir seirbhísí faoi thrí chonradh ar a laghad agus íosmhéid conartha de 3 000 000 EUR i gceist le gach ceann díobh, i limistéir an chúnaimh theicniúil agus na forbartha acmhainní do chur chun feidhme clár ilearnálach faoi cheannas an rialtais a cuireadh i gcrích ag am ar bith i rith na tréimhse teistiméireachta. Ciallaíonn sé sin go mb’fhéidir go raibh an tionscadal dá dtagraíonn an t-iarrthóir tosaithe nó tugtha chun críche ag am ar bith le linn na tréimhse léirithe ach nach gá go raibh sé tionscanta agus tugtha chun críche le linn na tréimhse sin ná curtha i bhfeidhm le linn na tréimhse iomláine. Ceadaítear d'iarrthóirí/do thairgeoirí tagairt a dhéanamh do thionscadail a cuireadh i gcrích laistigh den tréimhse theistiméireachta (cé gur cuireadh tús leo roimhe sin) nó do thionscadail nach bhfuil curtha i gcrích go fóill. Sa chéad chás is amhlaidh a bhreithneofar an tionscadal ina iomláine má chuirtear fianaise cheart ar fheidhmíocht ar fáil (ráiteas nó teastas ón eintiteas a dhámh an conradh, cruthúnas ar íocaíocht deiridh). I gcás tionscadal atá fós ar siúl ní bhreithneofar ach an cion sin a cuireadh i gcrích go sásúil le linn na tréimhse tagartha cé gur cuireadh tús leo níos luaithe ná sin. Ní mór fianaise dhoiciméadach a sholáthar mar thaca leis an gcion sin (cosúil le tionscadail atá curtha i gcrích) lena mionsonraítear a luach freisin. Má chuir iarrthóir/tairgeoir an tionscadal i bhfeidhm mar chuid de chuibhreannas, ní foláir nó go bhfuil an céatadán a chuir an t-iarrthóir/tairgeoir i gcrích go rathúil soiléir ón bhfianaise dhoiciméadach, mar aon le cur síos ar chineál na seirbhísí a cuireadh ar fáil má baineadh úsáid as na critéir roghnúcháin a bhaineann le hábharthacht na taithí.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Má chomhlíonann níos mó ná 8 iarrthóirí incháilithe na critéir roghnúcháin thuas, ansin ní mór athscrúdú a dhéanamh ar láidreachtaí agus ar laigí coibhneasta iarratais na n-iarrthóirí sin d'fhonn an t-ochtar iarrthóirí is fearr a aithint. Ní bhreithneofar ach na fachtóirí seo a leanas agus iad sin amháin le linn an athscrúdaithe sin:</P><P>— Ar an gcéad dul síos, an líon tionscadal a bhaineann leis an gconradh/tionscadal seo de luach níos mó ná 1 000 000 EUR an ceann agus i gcásanna cosúlachtaí idir scóir na n-iarrthóirí,</P><P>— Méid carnach iomlán na dtionscadal a cuireadh chun feidhme (fiú sa chás gur níos lú ná 1 000 000 EUR gach ceann díobh).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Spriocdháta chun iarratais a fháil</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00 Am Addis Ababa.</P><P>Ní bhreithneofar aon tairiscint a gheofar ag an údarás conarthachta tar éis an spriocdháta sin.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Faisnéis bhreise</P><P>Ní foláir aon iarratas ar shoiléiriú a sheoladh chuig Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu tráth nach déanaí an 19.2.2018</P><P>Tabhair ar aird go dtabharfar comhfhreagra ar gach soiléiriú a fuarthas leis an gceartúchán roimhe seo agus ar an gceann atá le fáil roimh 19 Feabhra.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Níl athrú ar bith thairis sin ar théarmaí ná ar choinníollacha an fhógra chonartha. Is dlúthchuid den fhógra conartha iad na hathruithe nó na ceartúcháin thuas leis an bhfógra conartha.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Адис Абеба: ИСР - Техническа помощ за подкрепа на Глобалния съюз за изменение на климата+ (GCCA+)/Насочване на съобразени с промените в климата подходи за планиране и прилагане в програмата за продуктивни безопасни мрежи IV (PSNP4) в Етиопия</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Поправка</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Приложение към Официален вестник на Европейския съюз, 3.1.2018 г., 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейски съюз</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, представляван от Европейската комисия (Делегация на ЕС в Етиопия), от името и за сметка на Етиопия, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Адис Абеба</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Етиопия.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Вместо:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Прогнозна дата за покана за участие в търг — 10.3.2018 г.</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Критерии за подбор</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Кандидатът да е предоставил услуги по поне една поръчка, всяка с бюджет поне равен на бюджета на тази поръчка в областите на техническата помощ и разработването на капацитет за изпълнение на водени от правителството програми в няколко сектора, които са били осъществени в който и да е момент през референтния период. Това означава, че проектът, който кандидатът е посочил като референция, трябва да е започнат или да е завършен по всяко време през посочения период, но не трябва задължително да е започнат или завършен през този период, нито да е изпълняван през целия период. На кандидатите/оферентите е позволено да посочат като референция или завършени проекти в рамките на референтния период (дори и да са започнати по-рано) или проекти, които все още не са завършени. В първия случай проектът ще бъде разглеждан в неговото цяло, ако е представено подходящо доказателство за изпълнение (декларация или сертификат от субекта, който е възложил поръчката, доказателство за крайно плащане). В случай на проекти, които все още са в процес на изпълнение, само делът, задоволително приключен по време на референтния период, въпреки че е започнал по-рано, ще бъде взет под внимание. Този дял ще трябва да бъде подпомогнат чрез писмено доказателство (по подобен начин за завършени проекти), което също излага подробно неговата стойност. От писменото доказателство трябва да бъде ясно какъв е процентът, който кандидатът/оферентът е завършил успешно, ако кандидатът/оферентът е изпълнил проекта в консорциум, заедно с описание на естеството на предоставените услуги, ако са били използвани критериите за подбор, свързани с уместността на опита.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Ако повече от осем подходящи кандидати отговарят на горепосочените критерии за подбор, относителните силни и слаби страни в заявленията за участие на тези кандидати трябва да бъдат преразгледани, за да се определят осемте най-добри кандидати. Единствените фактори, които ще бъдат взети под внимание по време на това преразглеждане, са:</P><P>— Брой проекти, свързани с тази поръчка,</P><P>— Стойност на проектите, свързани с тази поръчка,</P><P>— Брой проекти, свързани с настоящата поръчка, изпълнени в Субсахарска Африка.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Краен срок за получаване на заявления за участие</P><P>9.2.2018 г., 17:00 ч., източноафриканско време.</P><P>Заявление, получено от възлагащия орган след този краен срок, няма да бъде разглеждано.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Допълнителна информация</P><P>Всяко искане за разяснение трябва да се изпрати до Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu не по-късно от 31.1.2018 г.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Да се чете:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Прогнозна дата за покана за участие в търг — 26.3.2018 г.</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Критерии за подбор</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Кандидатът да е предоставил услуги по поне три поръчки, всяка с минимална сума на договора 3 000 000 EUR в областите на техническата помощ и разработването на капацитет за изпълнение на водени от правителството програми в няколко сектора, които са били осъществени в който и да е момент през референтния период. Това означава, че проектът, който кандидатът е посочил като референция, трябва да е започнат или да е завършен по всяко време през посочения период, но не трябва задължително да е започнат или завършен през този период, нито да е изпълняван през целия период. На кандидатите/оферентите е позволено да посочат като референция или завършени проекти в рамките на референтния период (дори и да са започнати по-рано) или проекти, които все още не са завършени. В първия случай проектът ще бъде разглеждан в неговото цяло, ако е представено подходящо доказателство за изпълнение (декларация или сертификат от субекта, който е възложил поръчката, доказателство за крайно плащане). В случай на проекти, които все още са в процес на изпълнение, само делът, задоволително приключен по време на референтния период, въпреки че е започнал по-рано, ще бъде взет под внимание. Този дял ще трябва да бъде подпомогнат чрез писмено доказателство (по подобен начин за завършени проекти), което също излага подробно неговата стойност. От писменото доказателство трябва да бъде ясно какъв е процентът, който кандидатът/оферентът е завършил успешно, ако кандидатът/оферентът е изпълнил проекта в консорциум, заедно с описание на естеството на предоставените услуги, ако са били използвани критериите за подбор, свързани с уместността на опита.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Ако повече от осем подходящи кандидати отговарят на горепосочените критерии за подбор, относителните силни и слаби страни в заявленията за участие на тези кандидати трябва да бъдат преразгледани, за да се определят осемте най-добри кандидати. Единствените фактори, които ще бъдат взети под внимание по време на това преразглеждане, са:</P><P>— Първо, броят проекти, свързани с тази поръчка/проект, със стойност над 1 000 000 EUR всеки, а при сходни резултати между кандидатите,</P><P>— Обща сборна сума на изпълнените проекти (дори ако всеки един е по-малко от 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Краен срок за получаване на заявления за участие</P><P>5.3.2018 г., 17:00 ч., време в Адис Абеба.</P><P>Заявление, получено от възлагащия орган след този краен срок, няма да бъде разглеждано.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Допълнителна информация</P><P>Всяко искане за разяснение трябва да се изпрати до Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu не по-късно от 19.2.2018 г.</P><P>Моля, отбележете, че на всички пояснения, получени с предишната поправка и на тези, които ще бъдат получени до 19 февруари, ще се отговаря заедно.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Всички други срокове и условия на обявлението за поръчка остават непроменени. Горепосочените промени и/или поправки към обявлението за поръчка са неразделна част от него.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Addis Ababa: ICD - Asistență tehnică pentru a susține Alianța mondială împotriva schimbărilor climatice (GCCA)/integrarea abordărilor inteligente de planificare și implementare privind clima în programul referitor la rețelele de siguranță productive IV (PSNP4) în Etiopia</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Erată</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplimentul Jurnalului Oficial al Uniunii Europene, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Uniunea Europeană</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentată de Comisia Europeană (Delegația Uniunii europene în Etiopia), în numele și în favoarea Etiopiei, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Ababa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>În loc de:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Data prevăzută pentru invitația la licitație 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Criterii de selecție</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Candidatul a prestat servicii în baza a cel puțin un contract cu un buget cel puțin egal cu cel al acestui contract, vizând asistența tehnică și dezvoltarea capacității pentru punerea în aplicare a programelor multi-sectoriale conduse de guvern care au fost puse în aplicare în orice moment în perioada de referință. Aceasta înseamnă că proiectul menționat de candidat ar fi putut fi început sau finalizat în orice moment pe parcursul perioadei indicate, dar acesta nu trebuie să fi fost neapărat început și finalizat în respectiva perioadă sau implementat pe parcursul întregii perioade. Candidații/ofertanții pot să menționeze fie proiecte finalizate în perioada de referință (chiar dacă au fost începute mai devreme), fie proiecte încă nefinalizate. În primul caz, proiectul va fi luat în considerare în ansamblu dacă sunt furnizate dovezi corespunzătoare privind executarea acestuia (declarație sau certificat din partea entității care a atribuit contractul, dovada efectuării plății finale). În cazul proiectelor aflate în curs de executare, va fi luată în considerare numai partea finalizată în mod satisfăcător pe parcursul perioadei de referință, chiar dacă a fost începută mai devreme. Această parte va trebui să fie atestată prin documente justificative (similar cu proiectele finalizate), furnizând, de asemenea, detalii cu privire la valoarea acesteia. Dacă un candidat/ofertant a implementat proiectul în cadrul unui consorțiu, procentajul pe care candidatul/ofertantul l-a finalizat cu succes trebuie să fie clar specificat în documentele justificative, împreună cu o descriere a naturii serviciilor prestate în cazul în care au fost utilizate criteriile de selecție privind pertinența experienței.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Dacă mai mult de 8 dintre candidații eligibili îndeplinesc criteriile de selecție de mai sus, punctele forte și cele slabe ale candidaturilor acestora trebuie să fie reexaminate pentru a identifica cei mai buni opt candidați. Singurii factori care vor fi luați în considerare în timpul acestei reexaminări sunt:</P><P>— Numărul de proiecte vizate de acest contract,</P><P>— Valoarea proiectelor vizate de acest contract,</P><P>— Numărul de proiecte legate de acest contract care au fost implementate în Africa Subsahariană.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termenul-limită pentru primirea candidaturilor</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00 (ora Africii de Est).</P><P>Nu va fi luată în considerare nicio candidatură primită de autoritatea contractantă după acest termen-limită.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Informații suplimentare</P><P>Orice cerere de clarificare trebuie trimisă la Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu cel târziu până la 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>A se citi:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Data prevăzută pentru invitația la licitație 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Criterii de selecție</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Candidatul a prestat servicii în baza a cel puțin 3 contracte, fiecare cu un buget de cel puțin egal 3 000 000 EUR vizând asistența tehnică și dezvoltarea capacității pentru punerea în aplicare a programelor multi-sectoriale conduse de guvern care au fost puse în aplicare în orice moment în perioada de referință. Aceasta înseamnă că proiectul menționat de candidat ar fi putut fi început sau finalizat în orice moment pe parcursul perioadei indicate, dar acesta nu trebuie să fi fost neapărat început și finalizat în respectiva perioadă sau implementat pe parcursul întregii perioade. Candidații/ofertanții pot să menționeze fie proiecte finalizate în perioada de referință (chiar dacă au fost începute mai devreme), fie proiecte încă nefinalizate. În primul caz, proiectul va fi luat în considerare în ansamblu dacă sunt furnizate dovezi corespunzătoare privind executarea acestuia (declarație sau certificat din partea entității care a atribuit contractul, dovada efectuării plății finale). În cazul proiectelor aflate în curs de executare, va fi luată în considerare numai partea finalizată în mod satisfăcător pe parcursul perioadei de referință, chiar dacă a fost începută mai devreme. Această parte va trebui să fie atestată prin documente justificative (similar cu proiectele finalizate), furnizând, de asemenea, detalii cu privire la valoarea acesteia. Dacă un candidat/ofertant a implementat proiectul în cadrul unui consorțiu, procentajul pe care candidatul/ofertantul l-a finalizat cu succes trebuie să fie clar specificat în documentele justificative, împreună cu o descriere a naturii serviciilor prestate în cazul în care au fost utilizate criteriile de selecție privind pertinența experienței.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Dacă mai mult de 8 dintre candidații eligibili îndeplinesc criteriile de selecție de mai sus, punctele forte și cele slabe ale candidaturilor acestora trebuie să fie reexaminate pentru a identifica cei mai buni opt candidați. Singurii factori care vor fi luați în considerare în timpul acestei reexaminări sunt:</P><P>— În primul rând, numărul de proiecte legate de acest contract/proiect cu o valoare mai mare de 1 000 000 EUR fiecare și în cazurile scorurilor similare între candidați,</P><P>— Suma totală cumulată a proiectelor implementate (chiar dacă fiecare dintre ele este mai mică de 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Termenul-limită pentru primirea candidaturilor</P><P>5.3.2018, ora 17:00 (ora locală în Addis Ababa).</P><P>Nu va fi luată în considerare nicio candidatură primită de autoritatea contractantă după acest termen-limită.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Informații suplimentare</P><P>Orice cerere de clarificare trebuie trimisă la Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu cel târziu până la 19.2.2018</P><P>Vă rugăm să rețineți că toate clarificările primite cu erata anterioară și cea care va fi primită înainte de 19 februarie vor fi comunicate împreună.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Toți ceilalți termeni și toate celelalte condiții din anunțul de participare rămân neschimbate. Modificările și/sau rectificările de mai sus aduse anunțului de participare fac parte integrantă din acesta.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ET-Adis Abeba: DCI - Tehnička pomoć za podršku za Globalni savez za borbu protiv klimatskih promjena (GCCA+)/uključivanje pametnih pristupa planiranju i provedbi u području klime u Program proizvodne sigurnosne mreže IV (PSNP4) u Etiopiji</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ispravak</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatak Službenom listu Europske unije, 3.1.2018, 2018/S 001-000041)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, koju predstavlja Europska komisija (Delegacija EU-a u Etiopiji), u ime i za račun Etiopije, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Addis Abeba</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Etiopija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><CORREC><FOR_READ><FOR><INT_FOR>Umjesto:</INT_FOR><OLD QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Okvirni datum poziva na dostavu ponuda 10.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Uvjeti sposobnosti</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Natjecatelj je pružio usluge u sklopu barem jednog ugovora s proračunom barem jednakim proračunu ovog ugovora, u području tehničke pomoći i razvoja sposobnosti za provedbu višesektorskih programa koje vodi vlada, koji su provedeni u bilo kojem trenutku tijekom referentnog razdoblja. To znači da je projekt koji natjecatelj navodi mogao započeti ili završiti bilo kada u navedenom razdoblju, ali ne znači nužno da je započeo i bio dovršen u tom razdoblju ili da je provođen tijekom čitavog razdoblja. Natjecatelji/ponuditelji se smiju pozivati na projekte izvršene tijekom referentnog razdoblja (iako su započeti ranije) ili na projekte koji još nisu dovršeni. U slučaju projekata izvršenih tijekom referentnog razdoblja, projekt će se u potpunosti uzeti u obzir ako je dostavljen dokaz o izvršenju (izjava ili potvrda od subjekta s kojim je sklopljen ugovor, dokaz o konačnom plaćanju). U slučaju projekata koji i dalje traju, u obzir će se uzeti samo dio uredno izvršen tijekom referentnog razdoblja, iako je započet ranije. Za ovaj će se dio morati dostaviti dokumentacija s dokazima (slično izvršenim projektima) u kojoj se navodi njegova vrijednost. Ako je natjecatelj/ponuditelj proveo projekt u okviru konzorcija, postotak projekta koji je natjecatelj/ponuditelj uspješno dovršio mora biti jasno naveden u dokumentaciji s dokazima, kao i opis prirode pruženih usluga ako su korišteni uvjeti sposobnosti koji se odnose na značajnost iskustva.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Ako više od 8 prihvatljivih natjecatelja ispunjava navedene uvjete sposobnosti, moraju se ponovno pregledati relativne slabosti i snage prijava tih natjecatelja kako bi se utvrdilo 8 najboljih natjecatelja. Jedini čimbenici koji će se uzeti u obzir tijekom navedenog preispitivanja su:</P><P>— broj projekata povezanih s ovim ugovorom,</P><P>— vrijednost projekata povezanih s ovim ugovorom,</P><P>— broj projekata povezanih s ovim ugovorom koji su provedeni u subsaharskoj Africi.</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Rok za zaprimanje prijava</P><P>9.2.2018, 17:00, istočnoafričko vrijeme.</P><P>Prijave koje javni naručitelj zaprimi nakon isteka navedenog roka neće se razmatrati.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Dodatne informacije</P><P>Zahtjeve za pojašnjenje treba slati na adresu Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu najkasnije do 31.1.2018.</P></OLD></FOR><READ><INT_READ>Glasi:</INT_READ><NEW QUOTE="NO"><P>[...]</P><P>18. Okvirni datum poziva na dostavu ponuda 26.3.2018</P><P>[...]</P><P>21. Uvjeti sposobnosti</P><P>3) [...]</P><P>Natjecatelj je pružio usluge u sklopu barem 3 ugovora od kojih je svaki vrijednosti najmanje 3 000 000 EUR, u području tehničke pomoći i razvoja sposobnosti za provedbu višesektorskih programa koje vodi vlada, a koji su provedeni u bilo kojem trenutku tijekom referentnog razdoblja. To znači da je projekt koji natjecatelj navodi mogao započeti ili završiti bilo kada u navedenom razdoblju, ali ne znači nužno da je započeo i bio dovršen u tom razdoblju ili da je provođen tijekom čitavog razdoblja. Natjecatelji/ponuditelji se smiju pozivati na projekte izvršene tijekom referentnog razdoblja (iako su započeti ranije) ili na projekte koji još nisu dovršeni. U slučaju projekata izvršenih tijekom referentnog razdoblja, projekt će se u potpunosti uzeti u obzir ako je dostavljen dokaz o izvršenju (izjava ili potvrda od subjekta s kojim je sklopljen ugovor, dokaz o konačnom plaćanju). U slučaju projekata koji i dalje traju, u obzir će se uzeti samo dio uredno izvršen tijekom referentnog razdoblja, iako je započet ranije. Za ovaj će se dio morati dostaviti dokumentacija s dokazima (slično izvršenim projektima) u kojoj se navodi njegova vrijednost. Ako je natjecatelj/ponuditelj proveo projekt u okviru konzorcija, postotak projekta koji je natjecatelj/ponuditelj uspješno dovršio mora biti jasno naveden u dokumentaciji s dokazima, kao i opis prirode pruženih usluga ako su korišteni uvjeti sposobnosti koji se odnose na značajnost iskustva.</P><P>[...]</P><P>Ako više od 8 prihvatljivih natjecatelja ispunjava navedene uvjete sposobnosti, moraju se ponovno pregledati relativne slabosti i snage prijava tih natjecatelja kako bi se utvrdilo 8 najboljih natjecatelja. Jedini čimbenici koji će se uzeti u obzir tijekom navedenog preispitivanja su:</P><P>— kao prvo, broj projekata koji se odnosi na ovaj ugovor/projekt vrijednosti veće od 1 000 000 EUR po ugovoru/projektu u slučaju sličnosti rezultata između natjecatelja,</P><P>—ukupni kumulativni iznos provedenih projekata (čak i ako svaki vrijedi manje od 1 000 000 EUR).</P><P>[...]</P><P>23. Rok za zaprimanje prijava</P><P>5.3.2018, 17:00, vrijeme u Adis Abebi.</P><P>Prijave koje javni naručitelj zaprimi nakon isteka navedenog roka neće se razmatrati.</P><P>[...]</P><P>30. Dodatne informacije</P><P>Zahtjeve za pojašnjenje treba slati na adresu Delegation-Ethiopia-FCS@eeas.europa.eu najkasnije do 19.2.2018</P><P>Uzmite u obzir da će se na sve zahtjeve za pojašnjenja zaprimljene uz prethodni ispravak i one koji će biti zaprimljeni prije 19. veljače odgovoriti zajedno.</P></NEW></READ></FOR_READ></CORREC><P>Svi ostali uvjeti poziva na nadmetanje ostaju nepromijenjeni. Prethodno navedene izmjene i/ili ispravci poziva na nadmetanje čine sastavni dio poziva na nadmetanje.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>