<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="156259-2018"
            EDITION="2018070">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-157800-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180608</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>70</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180411</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 070-156259</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:156259-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="TR"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>www.ibb.gov.tr</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://ekap.kik.gov.tr/ekap/</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="34600000">Railway and tramway locomotives and rolling stock and associated parts</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="TR">TÜRKİYE</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="TR">TÜRKİYE</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180409</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180608 10:30</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="8">Other</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="8">Other</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>02F05</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>02</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/25/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Typция</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Истанбул</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Локомотиви и подвижен пътен състав за железници и трамваи и резервни части за тях</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Turecko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Železniční a tramvajové lokomotivy a kolejová vozidla a jejich díly</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Tyrkiet</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Lokomotiver og motorvogne samt rullende materiel og tilhørende dele</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>die Türkei</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Eisenbahn- und Straßenbahnlokomotiven und rollendes Material sowie zugehörige Teile</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Τουρκία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Κωνσταντινούπολη</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Μηχανές και τροχαίος εξοπλισμός σιδηροδρόμων και τροχιοδρόμων και μέρη τους</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Turkey</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Railway and tramway locomotives and rolling stock and associated parts</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Turquía</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Estambul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Locomotoras de ferrocarril y de tranvía, material móvil y sus partes</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Türgi</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Raudtee- ja trammivedurid ja veerem ning nendega seonduvad osad</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Turkki</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Junan ja raitiovaunun veturit ja muu liikkuva kalusto sekä niiden osat</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Turquie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Locomotives et matériel roulant de chemin de fer et de tramway et pièces détachées</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Tuirc, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Railway and tramway locomotives and rolling stock and associated parts</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Turska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Željezničke i tramvajske lokomotive i vagoni i pripadajući dijelovi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Törökország</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Isztambul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Vasúti mozdonyok és villamos-motorkocsik, gördülőállomány és ezek alkatrészei</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Turchia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Locomotive e materiale rotabile e parti associate ferrotranviarie</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Turkija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Geležinkelio ir tramvajaus lokomotyvai, riedmenys ir jungiamosios dalys</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Turcija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Stambula</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dzelzceļa vilcienu un tramvaju lokomotīves un ritošais sastāvs un saistītās detaļas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>it-Turkija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Lokomottivi u vaguni ambulanti tal-ferroviji u t-trammijiet, u l-partijiet assoċċjati</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Turkije</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Spoor- en tramlocomotieven, rollend materieel en onderdelen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Turcja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istambuł</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Lokomotywy kolejowe i tramwajowe oraz tabor kolejowy i podobne elementy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Turquia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istambul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Locomotivas e material circulante para vias férreas e respectivas peças</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Turcia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Locomotive şi materiale rulante feroviare şi piese</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Turecko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Železničné a električkové lokomotívy a vozňový park a súvisiace časti</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Turčija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tirna vozila in njihovi deli</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Turkiet</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Istanbul</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Järnvägs- och spårvägslok, rullande materiel samt tillhörande delar</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Istanbul Metropolitan Municipality Department of Rail Systems</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F05_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F05" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Istanbul Metropolitan Municipality Department of Rail Systems</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>İstanbul Büyükşehir Belediyesi Ek Hizmet Binası, Avrupa Yakası Raylı Sistem Müdürlüğü, Osmaniye Mah. Çobançeşme Koşuyolu Bulvarı No:5 Kat:2 34568 BAKIRKÖY/İSTANBUL</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Istanbul</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>34010</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="TR"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Istanbul Metropolitan Municipality, Department of Rail Systems, Directorate of European Side Rail Systems</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+90 2124494175</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>avruparaylisistem@ibb.gov.tr</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+90 2124494180</FAX>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="TR"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.ibb.gov.tr</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://ekap.kik.gov.tr/ekap/</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://ekap.kik.gov.tr/ekap/</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CE_ACTIVITY_OTHER>68 sets of (4-car) metro trains. 272 Metro Vehicles</CE_ACTIVITY_OTHER>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>68 sets of (4-car) metro trains. 272 Metro Vehicles</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>2018/144625</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="34600000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SUPPLIES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Procurement and commissioning of 272 metro vehicles for Kirazlı Halkalı railed public transportation System will be put out to tender with open tender procedure according to public tender act nº 4734 and Article nº 19.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="TR"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>İstanbul.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Delivery of the sets: Complete delivery of 272 vehicles shall be completed in 45 (forty-five) months. Delivery of sets shall start as of the 18th month after the work order date and shall be completed by the end of the 45th month. After the delivery of final set; 30 (thirty) days for field tests, 60 (sixty) days for trial and 90 days in total shall be allowed. The schedule of this delivery shall be designated by contractor so as to deliver 2 sets (8 vehicles) in each of the 18th, 19th, 20th, 21th, 22th, 23th, 24th, 25th and 26th months; 3 sets (12 vehicles) in each of the 27th, 28th, 29th, 30th, 31th, 32th, 33th, 34th, 35th, 36th, 37th and 38th months and 2 sets (8 vehicles) in each of the 39th, 40th, 41th, 42th, 43th, 44th and 45th months, in form of packages. It is compulsory for contractors to meet these conditions. Trial run will be carried out for the lines where the vehicles subject to this work will operate. As the vehicle delivery proceeds, in case of a line where vehicles subject to the work is completed and the delivery of the vehicles to be used in that line reach the sufficient number for the trial run to start, and if the administration demands so, trial run will start in the related line. In this case, duration of the trial run of the related line will take place in vehicle delivery period, however, it will not cause any changes on the duration of above-mentioned 60 (sixty) days of trial run period that will be used following the delivery of the last set and finalization of field tests. Following the work order date, the contractor will submit the detailed work program on vehicle test (factory and field tests) and trial runs to the approval of the administration within 60 (sixty) calendar days. Following the signing of the agreement, the contractor shall submit project plans detailing the descriptions of the design, procurement planning, production preparation, all tests and processes regarding the production and installation (equipment-vehicle-completed vehicle-field type /routine tests) to the approval of the administration.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">48</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>Documents concerning economic and financial capacity and the criteria applying to those documents:</P>
               <P>Documents to be obtained from banks:</P>
               <P>Banker’s reference letter, indicating unused cash credit, unused letter of guarantee or unrestricted deposited account in the amount offered by the tenderer on condition that it is no less than 10 %,</P>
               <P>These criteria may be fulfilled by adding the deposit and credit amounts or presenting more than one banker’s reference letter.</P>
               <P>The year-end balance sheet of the bidder for the year before the tender or equivalent documents:</P>
               <P>a— in accordance with the respective regulations, for bidders who have the legal obligation to publish their balance sheets, year-end balance sheets or parts of sheets showing necessary criteria have been met,</P>
               <P>b— in accordance with the respective regulations, for bidders who do not have the legal obligation to publish their balance sheets, year-end balance sheets or parts of sheets showing necessary criteria have been met or document in standard form regulated by certified public accountant or independent accountant and financial advisor showing that the criteria have been met.</P>
               <P>In the balance sheets or equivalent documents submitted;</P>
               <P>a) The current ratio (current assets /short term liabilities) must be minimum 0,75,</P>
               <P>b) The shareholders’ equity ratio (shareholders’ equity/ total assets) must be minimum 0,15,</P>
               <P>c) Short terms bank loans' ratio to the shareholders' equity must be lower than 0,50 and all three criteria must be met.</P>
               <P>Bidders that do not meet the aforementioned criteria in the previous year could submit documents on the last 2 years. In that case, it will be taken into account whether the criteria are met by the average monetary amount of the last 2 years.</P>
               <P>Documents stating the volume of the business:</P>
               <P>a) The income statement indicating the total turnover of the last year before the tender,</P>
               <P>b) Invoices issued during the year before the tender documenting completed sales and completed parts of the sales going on under commitment,</P>
               <P>Submitting one of these documents is sufficient.</P>
               <P>The amount of the total turnover shall be no less than 25 % of the price to be offered by bidder or the amount of sales for the finished works shall be no less than 15 % of the price to be offered by bidder. The bidder that fulfills either of these criteria and who submits document proving this shall be considered sufficient.</P>
               <P>Bidders that cannot fulfill those criteria 1 year before the tender takes place can also present the documents of the past 2 years. In this case whether the average of those two years is able to fulfill the criteria shall be taken into account.</P>
               <P>The bidders shall submit their bids for items of products as unit prices. At the end of the tender, a unit price contract will be signed with the willing bidder on the basis of the total amount determined by multiplying the unit price and work items.</P>
               <P>The proposal shall be submitted for the entire work in this tender.</P>
               <P>On condition that it is not less than %3 of the price they have offered, the bidders shall give a provisional bond in the amount they have set.</P>
               <P>The validity period of submitted proposals is 240 (two hundred forty) calendar days starting from the date of the tender.</P>
               <P>Consortiums cannot submit an offer to the tender.</P>
               <P>Other Matters:</P>
               <P>A statement shall be required from bidders whose bids are below the limit value according to Article 38 of the relevant law.</P>
               <P>Viewing and purchasing tender document:</P>
               <P>Tender document can be viewed at the premises of the administration and it can be purchased at the Directorate of European Side Rail Systems of Istanbul Metropolitan Municipality, located in Osmaniye Mah. Çobançeşme Koşuyolu Bulvarı No:5 Kat:2 Bakırköy /Istanbul on payment of 2.500 TRY (Turkish Lira).</P>
               <P>It is obligatory to purchase the tender document of those who will bid on the tender or to download it using e-signature via EKAP.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>Documents showing the work experience:</P>
               <P>Documents evidencing work experience, technological product experience document or production capacity report showing that the experience of the bidder regarding the work subject to that tender or similar work completed within the last five years under a contract not less than 10 % of the bid price.</P>
               <P>Preparation of the production capacity report:</P>
               <P>Bidders who wish to prove their work experience by presenting a capacity report shall submit the capacity report for a rail system (tram or light metro or metro) vehicle with an annual production quantity of 68 minimum.</P>
               <P>Works to be accepted as similar work in this tender:</P>
               <P>— Procurement of rail system vehicles (tram or light metro or metro) under a single contract shall be considered as similar work.</P>
               <P>In the work experience document, the bidder must specify that rail system vehicles corresponding to the amount in the work experience document have been delivered, put into commercial use and the administration has finalized its acceptance transactions.</P>
               <P>The most economically advantageous bid shall be determined on the basis of the bid price only.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <RULES_CRITERIA>
               <P>TWhile the tender is open to all domestic and foreign bidders, bidders who offer domestic product will be given a %15 (fifteen per cent) price advantage over the total tender.</P>
               <P>Bidders shall submit how they will meet the domestic contribution share of at least 51 % in all sets, including 1st and 9th train sets; domestic contribution share of at least 60 % in all sets, including 10th and 30th train sets and domestic contribution share of at least 70 % in all sets, including 31st and 68th train sets with which percentages in Annex-4: Metro vehicle percentage table of the technical specifications and by filling out Annex-6: Qualification Ratio – Equipment and /or service procurement list of the technical specifications alongside their bids. The bids of the bidders that failed to present a document showing mandatory minimum sufficiency rate conditions are met or presenting incomplete documents shall not be evaluated.</P>
            </RULES_CRITERIA>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-06-08</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>10:30</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="TR"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-06-08</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:30</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Detailed information can be reached via administrative specifications included in the tender document on EKAP.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Istanbul Metropolitan Municipality, Department of Tender</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Tender Hall at the Directorate of Tender Affairs of Istanbul Metropolitan Municipality, Osmaniye Mah. Çobançeşme Koşuyolu Bulvarı No:5 Kat:4 Bakırköy/İstanbul</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Istanbul</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>34010</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="TR"/>
               <PHONE>+90 2124494445</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>ihaleisleri@ibb.gov.tr</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+90 2124494463</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-04-09</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F05_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
