<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="118184-2018"
            EDITION="2018053">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-120018-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180330</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>53</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180316</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 053-118184</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:118184-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="FR"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.edf-energies-nouvelles.com</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://pha.edf.com</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="31121330">Wind turbine generators</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="FRD13">Orne</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="FR105">Hauts-de-Seine</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180314</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180330 14:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="4">Negotiated procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="N">Electricity</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01F05</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/25/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Фpaнция</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Париж</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Вятърни турбогенератори</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Francie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paříž</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Generátory využívající větrné turbíny</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Frankrig</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paris</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Vindturbinegeneratorer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Frankreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paris</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Windturbosätze</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Γαλλία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Παρίσι</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Στροβιλογεννήτριες αιολικής ενέργειας</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>France</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paris</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Wind turbine generators</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Francia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>París</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Generadores para turbinas eólicas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Prantsusmaa</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Pariis</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tuuleturbiinide generaatorid</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Ranska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Pariisi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tuuliturbiinien generaattorit</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>France</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paris</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Générateurs à turbines éoliennes</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Fhrainc, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Páras</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Wind turbine generators</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Francuska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Pariz</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Turbogeneratori na vjetar</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Franciaország</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Párizs</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Szélturbinás áramfejlesztők</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Francia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Parigi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Generatori a turbine eoliche</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Prancūzija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paryžius</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Vėjo turbinų generatoriai</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Francija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Parīze</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Vēja turbīnu ģeneratori</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Franza</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Pariġi</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ġeneraturi tat-turbini tar-riħ</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Frankrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Parijs</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Windturbinegeneratoren</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Francja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paryż</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Prądnice silników wiatrowych</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>França</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paris</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Geradores de turbinas eólicas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Franţa</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paris</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Generatoare cu turbine eoliene</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Francúzsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paríž</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Generátory veterných turbín</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Francija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Pariz</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Turbogeneratorji na veter</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Frankrike</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Paris</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Vindturbingeneratorer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">EDF Energies Nouvelles</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F05_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F05" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>EDF Energies Nouvelles</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Coeur défense tour B- 100 ésplanade du Général de Gaulle</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Paris la Défense Cedex</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>92932</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="FR"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Christopher Smith</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+33 140904818</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>christopher.smith@edf-en.com</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+33 140902311</FAX>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="FR105"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.edf-energies-nouvelles.com</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://pha.edf.com</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://pha.edf.com</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://pha.edf.com</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CE_ACTIVITY VALUE="ELECTRICITY"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Hauts Vaudois Turbine Supply and Installation Agreement</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>RFx_052950</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="31121330"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SUPPLIES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>This contract notice is for the “Les Hauts Vaudois” project currently under development in the Orne region in the North of France. The project consists of 11 wind turbines with an optimized case of 8 turbines.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="FRD13"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Commune of Montgaroult and Sentilly, in the Orne region of northern France.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>EDF Energies Nouvelles (“EDF EN”) is a leader in the production of renewable energy. The company develops, installs and operates green electricity power plants, mainly in Europe and North America, primarily for its own owner-operator account and for third parties. Futuren, an EDF EN subsidiary, have developed the Hauts Vaudois project in France and invited interest from the market for the design, manufacture, supply, installation, commissioning and servicing of onshore wind turbines. Due to the development nature of the project, interest is invited based on 2 possible scenarios as detailed below:</P>
                  <P>Base case.</P>
                  <P>— 9 turbines with a maximum hub height of 65 m, and a maximum tip height of 90 m,</P>
                  <P>— 2 turbines with a maximum hub height of 65 m, and a maximum tip height of 85 m,</P>
                  <P>— commercial operation date of 1.12.2019,</P>
                  <P>— maximum rotor diameter 60 m,</P>
                  <P>— the ability to generate electricity for a minimum of 25 years,</P>
                  <P>— a turbine warranty and servicing for the first 2 years of operation.</P>
                  <P>Upgraded case.</P>
                  <P>— 8 turbines with a maximum hub height of 65 m, and a maximum tip height of 105 m,</P>
                  <P>— commercial operation date of 1.12.2019,</P>
                  <P>— the ability to generate electricity for a minimum of 25 years,</P>
                  <P>— a turbine warranty and servicing for the first 2 years of operation.</P>
                  <P>Works shall be compliant with the employers’ requirements including health and safety provisions, project documentation and local norms and regulations from the relevant authorities.</P>
                  <P>For confidentiality reasons, the details of the requirements together with the procurement documents shall be accessed at https://pha.edf.com after the acceptance of a confidentiality agreement.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <DATE_START>2019-01-01</DATE_START>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>— An option to provide operation and maintenance servicing for years 1 to 5,</P>
                  <P>— An option to provide operation and maintenance servicing for years 6 to 10,</P>
                  <P>— An option to provide operation and maintenance servicing for years 11 to 15,</P>
                  <P>— An option to provide operation and maintenance servicing for years 16 to 20,</P>
                  <P>— An option to provide operation and maintenance servicing beyond year 20.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>Tenders or requests to participate must be submitted electronically through EDF's purchasing platform, called “Portail Achats”, accessible via this link: https://pha.edf.com In order to access the purchasing portal and to submit a tender or request to participate, the candidate must register in advance on the platform.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Information, formalities and documents to be submitted by the candidates to evaluate if the requirements are met.</P>
               <P>The required information shall include as a minimum the following information /documentation:</P>
               <P>— company's description /presentation,</P>
               <P>— corporate ownership and corporate structure details.</P>
               <P>(If the company is a subsidiary, the name of the parent company and ultimate parent company must be stated as well as the name of a French representative, if any.).</P>
               <P>— corporate headquarters details,</P>
               <P>— list of worldwide locations if any (subsidiaries, affiliates, joint ventures, distributors) specifying the type of functionality (manufacturing, service, sales),</P>
               <P>— an administration statement stamped and signed by the company that the work will be achieved by regular workers, according to the laws in force,</P>
               <P>— a sworn statement dated, stamped and signed by the Company stating that the candidate is not in one of the 4 situations cited in points 1) to 4) below (full text to be entirely transcribed in the sworn statement):</P>
               <P>1— Those candidates who have, within the last 5 years, been handed down a final sentence for one of the offences provided for in Articles 222-38, 222-40, 226-13, 313-1 to 313-3, 314-1 to 314-3, 324-1 to 324-6, 413-9 to 413-12, 421-1 to 421-2-3, subparagraph 2 of Article 421-5, Article 433-1, subparagraph two of Article 433-2,subparagraph eight of Article 434-9, subparagraph 2 of Article 434-9-1, Articles 435-3, 435-4, 435-9, 435-10, 441-1 to 441-7, 441-9, 445-1 and 450-1 of the French penal code, Article 1741 of the French general tax code and Articles L. 2339-2 to L. 2339-4, L. 2339-11-1 to L. 2339-11-3 of the French defense code and L.317-8 of the French interior security code.</P>
               <P>2— Those candidates who have, within the last 5 years, been handed down a sentence listed on report n<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> 2 of the criminal records bureau for the offences referred to in Articles L. 8221-1, L. 8221-3, L. 8221-5, L.8231-1, L.8241-1, L. 8251-1 and L 8251-2 of the French labour code.</P>
               <P>3— Those candidates subject to the compulsory liquidation proceedings provided for in Article L. 640-1 of the French commercial code, those individuals whose personal bankruptcy has been pronounced under Articles L.653-1 to L. 653-8 of the same code as well as those persons subject to equivalent proceedings under a foreign law jurisdiction. Candidates admitted to the compulsory reorganization proceedings laid down by Article L. 631-1 of the French commercial code or to equivalent proceedings under a foreign law jurisdiction must provide evidence that they have been authorized to continue their activities throughout the foreseeable term of execution of the contract.</P>
               <P>4— Those candidates who, on 31 December of the year prior to that during which the tender is launched, had not fulfilled their obligations in terms of tax and social security declarations or had not paid the tax and contributions payable on that date. However, the following shall be regarded as eligible candidates: those candidates who, on 31 December of the year prior to that during which the tender is launched, had not paid the various amounts due on that date or provided any guarantees, but who had, before the date of the launch of the tender and without any enforcement measures having been taken by the accountant or the agency responsible for collection, either paid the said amounts or provided guarantees deemed sufficient by the accountant or the agency responsible for collection. Individuals who are legal or de facto directors of a legal entity that does not satisfy the conditions provided for in this subparagraph may not personally tender for a contract.</P>
               <P>These conditions are applicable to the candidates and to each of the members of a group wishing to tender as a single candidate.</P>
               <P>The sworn statement shall be provided by the candidate, all the members of the consortium or joint venture, and also by the proposed subcontractors.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>Information and formalities necessary for evaluating if the requirements are met.</P>
               <P>The required information shall include as a minimum the following information /documentation:</P>
               <P>— the candidate or each member of the consortium or joint venture will have to give a presentation of its structure, its organization, and in case of subsidiary, will have to indicate the name of its parent company and the share of this one,</P>
               <P>— annual report of the last 3 financial years attesting to its financial sustainability,</P>
               <P>— total number of employees,</P>
               <P>— declaration dated, signed and stamped that the company neither filled or is involved in insolvency proceedings and that insolvency proceedings have not been refused for lack of assets,</P>
               <P>— rating of an independent rating agency, whose rating is based on relevant European standards or equivalent,</P>
               <P>— proof of valid liability insurance stating all the insurance policies and the sums insured (copy of insurance certificates to be provided if available),</P>
               <P>— the candidate or the members of the consortium or joint venture must have an annual turnover over the last 3 years equal to or greater than twice the estimated amount of the contract which is the subject of this notice,</P>
               <P>— if 50 % or more of the candidate or a member of the consortium or joint venture is owned by a third party company, or if this third party company owns 50 % or more of the votes, or if more than half of its members are on the board of directors of the member of the consortium or joint venture, then this parent company will have to provide all the necessary justifications for the evaluation of the economic and financial capacity.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>Information and formalities necessary to assess whether these requirements are fulfilled:</P>
               <P>I) Certifications</P>
               <P>1— the company or group must specify that it has a quality organization compliant with NF EN ISO 9001 standards or an equivalent standard to be justified by the company (attach a copy of the valid certificates),</P>
               <P>2— the company or group must have an ISO 14001 environmental management certification or an equivalent system to be justified by the company (attach a copy of the valid certificates),</P>
               <P>3— the company or group must have an OHSAS 18001 or MASE or VCA or ILOSH safety management certification or an equivalent system to be justified by the company (attach a copy of the valid certificates).</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <DEPOSIT_GUARANTEE_REQUIRED>
               <P>These conditions will include securities such as an advance payment bond, an on-demand performance bond, a parent company guarantee, a retention bond and will be detailed in the invitation to tender documentation.</P>
            </DEPOSIT_GUARANTEE_REQUIRED>
            <MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITION>
               <P>Payment will be made in accordance with French law.</P>
            </MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITION>
            <LEGAL_FORM>
               <P>The candidate may apply as joint venture or consortium (Group of Economic Operators or GEO), or single company,It shall submit:</P>
               <P>— a copy of the project of joint venture agreement (JV application) or,</P>
               <P>— a copy of the memorandum of understanding or the project of contract of consortium (consortium application),</P>
               <P>— a description of qualification and experience of subcontractors (or potential ones) to whom major parts of the works (design, hardware supply,installation...) are going to be subcontracted (single company application).</P>
               <P>A candidate who will submit an offer as member of a GEO, shall not submit an offer as single company or with another GEO. A candidate, who will submit an offer as a single company, shall not submit an offer as member of a GEO.</P>
               <P>If a GEO is awarded the contract, one of its members is appointed as representative. It coordinates the services of each member and represents them with EDF EN. Each member of the group is committed to the entire contract (“solidary” group).</P>
            </LEGAL_FORM>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_NEGOTIATED_WITH_PRIOR_CALL/>
            <REDUCTION_RECOURSE/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-03-30</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>14:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>2018-04-20</DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">6</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>EDF group's contract notices and /or tenders are published in the EDF Group Purchasing Portal (GPP). To access it, the candidate has to get registered and to access to the RFx.</P>
               <P>Any supplier can register on the Internet page: https://pha.edf.com To register, the supplier has to fill in a questionnaire. Fields followed by * are mandatory.</P>
               <P>An identification number is required:</P>
               <P>— for EU suppliers, the intra-community VAT number is mandatory,</P>
               <P>— ror suppliers outside European Union, the national identification number (or DUNS number) is mandatory.</P>
               <P>For French suppliers (except non-profit organizations), the SIRET number is also mandatory.</P>
               <P>Suppliers have to enter a main contact. By default, this contact will be registered as the administrator of the supplier's record.</P>
               <P>As soon as practical after receipt of any request for clarification through the EDF GPP, EDF EN shall respond through the GPP mailbox. Employer's response (including an explanation of the request but without identifying the source of the enquiry) may be sent, as the case may be, to all prospective candidates.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal de grande instance de Paris</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>4 boulevard du Palais</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Paris Cedex 01</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>75055</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="FR"/>
               <PHONE>+33 144325151</PHONE>
               <URL>http://www.ca-paris.justice.fr</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_MEDIATION_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal de grande instance de Paris</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Paris Cedex 01</TOWN>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="FR"/>
               <URL>www.tgi-nanterre.justice.fr</URL>
            </ADDRESS_MEDIATION_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal de grande instance de Paris</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Paris Cedex 01</TOWN>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="FR"/>
               <URL>www.tgi-nanterre.justice.fr</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-14</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F05_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
