<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="161069-2018" EDITION="2018073"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-158325-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180515</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>73</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180414</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 073-161069</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161069-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="TJ"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71310000">Consultative engineering and construction services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180409</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180515 14:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>BR605</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Tadsjikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - Rådgivningstjenester vedrørende hydraulisk modellering af vandforsynings- og kloaksystemer i byen Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Tadschikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - Beratungsdienste für die hydraulische Modellierung von Wasserversorgungs- und Abwasserentsorgungssystemen in der Stadt Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Tajikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Consultancy Services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Tayikistán</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Servicios de consultoría para la elaboración de modelos hidráulicos de suministro de agua y sistemas de alcantarillado para la ciudad de Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Tadžikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Konsultointipalvelut vesihuolto- ja viemäröintijärjestelmien hydraulista mallintamista varten Nurekin kaupungissa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Tadjikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Services de consultance pour la modélisation hydraulique des conduites d'eau et des réseaux d'assainissement dans la ville de Nourek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Τατζικιστάν</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - Συμβουλευτικές υπηρεσίες για υδραυλικά μοντέλα συστημάτων ύδρευσης και αποχέτευσης στην πόλη Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Tagikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - Servizi di consulenza per la modellazione idraulica dei sistemi di approvvigionamento idrico e fognario nella città di Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Tadzjikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - Adviesdiensten voor hydraulische modellering van watervoorzienings- en rioleringssystemen in de stad Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Tajiquistão</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Serviços de consultoria para modelação hidráulica de sistemas de abastecimento de água e esgotos na cidade de Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Tadzjikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Konsulttjänster avseende hydraulisk modellering av vattenförsörjning och avloppssystem i staden Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Tádžikistán</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Poradenské služby týkající se hydraulického modelování vodovodních a kanalizačních systémů ve městě Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Tadžikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Nõustamisteenused Nureki linna veevarustuse ja kanalisatsiooni süsteemide kohta</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Tádzsikisztán</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Tanácsadási szolgáltatások vízellátási és szennyvíz-elvezetési rendszerek hidraulikus modellezésére irányulóan Nurek városában</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Tadžikistanas</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - Konsultavimo paslaugos dėl Nureko miesto vandentiekio ir kanalizacijos sistemų hidraulinio modeliavimo</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Tadžikistāna</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - Konsultāciju pakalpojumi Nurekas pilsētas ūdensapgādes un kanalizācijas sistēmu hidrauliskajai modelēšanai</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>it-Taġikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - Servizzi ta' Konsulenza għall-immodellar idrawliku tal-provvista tal-ilma u s-sistemi ta' drenaġġ fil-Belt ta' Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Tadżykistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Usługi doradztwa w zakresie modelowania hydraulicznego systemów wodociągowo-kanalizacyjnych w mieście Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Tadžikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Poradenské služby pre hydraulické modelovanie systémov dodávky vody a kanalizačných systémov v meste Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Tadžikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Svetovalne storitve za hidravlično modeliranje vodovodnih in kanalizacijskih sistemov v mestu Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Táidsíceastáin, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Seirbhísí comhairleachta le haghaidh samhaltú hiodrálach a dhéanamh ar chórais soláthair uisce agus séarachais i gcathair Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Таджикистан</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - Консултантски услуги за хидравлично моделиране на системите за водоснабдяване и канализация в град Нурек</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Tadjikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Servicii de consultanță pentru modelarea hidraulică a sistemelor de alimentare cu apă și canalizare din orașul Nurek</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Tadžikistan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Nurek</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Usluge savjetovanja za hidrauličko modeliranje sustava vodoopskrbe i kanalizacije u gradu Nureku</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - Rådgivningstjenester vedrørende hydraulisk modellering af vandforsynings- og kloaksystemer i byen Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - Beratungsdienste für die hydraulische Modellierung von Wasserversorgungs- und Abwasserentsorgungssystemen in der Stadt Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Consultancy Services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Servicios de consultoría para la elaboración de modelos hidráulicos de suministro de agua y sistemas de alcantarillado para la ciudad de Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Konsultointipalvelut vesihuolto- ja viemäröintijärjestelmien hydraulista mallintamista varten Nurekin kaupungissa (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Services de consultance pour la modélisation hydraulique des conduites d'eau et des réseaux d'assainissement dans la ville de Nourek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - Συμβουλευτικές υπηρεσίες για υδραυλικά μοντέλα συστημάτων ύδρευσης και αποχέτευσης στην πόλη Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - Servizi di consulenza per la modellazione idraulica dei sistemi di approvvigionamento idrico e fognario nella città di Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - Adviesdiensten voor hydraulische modellering van watervoorzienings- en rioleringssystemen in de stad Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Serviços de consultoria para modelação hidráulica de sistemas de abastecimento de água e esgotos na cidade de Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Konsulttjänster avseende hydraulisk modellering av vattenförsörjning och avloppssystem i staden Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Poradenské služby týkající se hydraulického modelování vodovodních a kanalizačních systémů ve městě Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Nõustamisteenused Nureki linna veevarustuse ja kanalisatsiooni süsteemide kohta (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Tanácsadási szolgáltatások vízellátási és szennyvíz-elvezetési rendszerek hidraulikus modellezésére irányulóan Nurek városában (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - Konsultavimo paslaugos dėl Nureko miesto vandentiekio ir kanalizacijos sistemų hidraulinio modeliavimo (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - Konsultāciju pakalpojumi Nurekas pilsētas ūdensapgādes un kanalizācijas sistēmu hidrauliskajai modelēšanai (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - Servizzi ta' Konsulenza għall-immodellar idrawliku tal-provvista tal-ilma u s-sistemi ta' drenaġġ fil-Belt ta' Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Usługi doradztwa w zakresie modelowania hydraulicznego systemów wodociągowo-kanalizacyjnych w mieście Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Poradenské služby pre hydraulické modelovanie systémov dodávky vody a kanalizačných systémov v meste Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Svetovalne storitve za hidravlično modeliranje vodovodnih in kanalizacijskih sistemov v mestu Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Seirbhísí comhairleachta le haghaidh samhaltú hiodrálach a dhéanamh ar chórais soláthair uisce agus séarachais i gcathair Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - Консултантски услуги за хидравлично моделиране на системите за водоснабдяване и канализация в град Нурек (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Servicii de consultanță pentru modelarea hidraulică a sistemelor de alimentare cu apă și canalizare din orașul Nurek (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Usluge savjetovanja za hidrauličko modeliranje sustava vodoopskrbe i kanalizacije u gradu Nureku (TJ-Nurek)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>INVITATION FOR EXPRESSIONS OF INTEREST</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9054-EOI -47398</P><P>Project name: Nurek Water and Wastewater Project</P><P>Country: Tajikistan</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental infrastructure</P><P>Project ID: 47398</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for expressions of interest</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time</P><P>This invitation for expressions of interest follows the General procurement notice for this project published in procurement opportunities, on the EBRD’s website (www.ebrd.com) on 11.8.2017.</P><P>Project description:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>State enterprise ‘’Water and wastewater company”</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> of </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Nurek</TOWN><BLK_BTX> City (the “Client” or the “Company“), TAJIKISTAN</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT>,  is responsible for the provision of centralized water supply and sanitation services in the City of Nurek, Republic of Tajikistan. The European bank for reconstruction and development (the “EBRD”, or the “Bank”) provided the Company with financing, in the form of a loan and a grant, for implementation of the Nurek water and wastewater project (the “Project”).</P><P>Assignment description:</P><P>The Client intends to use part of the loan to procure the contract for the development of hydraulic models of the city water supply and sanitation systems (the "Assignment").</P><P>The assignment will include the following key tasks for the City water and wastewater systems:</P><P>a) Collection, evaluation and processing of the initial data including measurements and surveys, as necessary</P><P>b) Supply and installation of hydraulic modelling software and associated hardware</P><P>c) Development of an electronic map of the water supply and wastewater systems</P><P>d) Identification of the needs for network zoning, as well as for the increase/reduction of pressure in the systems, depending on the location of the customers</P><P>e) Provision of recommendations on the development of water supply and wastewater systems for short and long-term perspective, including identification of key parameters of new transmission mains and reservoirs</P><P>f) Conduct a non-destructive instrumental assessment of the physical state of the water main (D 900m, L 2.6 km)</P><P>Assignment start date and duration: it is anticipated that the Assignment will start in June 2018 and will have an overall duration of approximately 6 months.</P><P>Eligibility: Procurement will be open for all the Consultants except those restricted in the EBRD’s list of ineligible entities. The proceeds of the loan shall not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities or for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations and the Client’s Country prohibitions.</P><P>Procurement of the consultancy services will be conducted in accordance with the EBRD’s Procurement Policies and Rules.</P><P>Consultant profile:</P><P>Corporate services are required. The consultant should be a firm or a consortium of firms with substantive experience and knowledge of water and wastewater sector including:</P><P>a) Expertise and experience in implementation of electronic models and hydraulic simulation of water supply and wastewater systems,</P><P>b) Expertise and experience in performing similar work in countries with conditions comparable to Tajikistan</P><P>The Consultant's expert team is expected to include key experts as follows:</P><P>a. Expert Nº 1: Team leader/project manager with a degree in water and/or sanitation, or similar education, with preferably 10 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems and 5 years of experience as a project manager or the head of a group of experts in similar projects.</P><P>b. Expert Nº 2: Water and wastewater engineer with a degree in water and/or sanitation with preferably 5 years of total experience in designing and implementing of projects on analysis or assessment of water supply/wastewater systems.</P><P>c. Expert Nº 3: GIS specialist with a degree in Geo information systems or equivalent and with preferably 5 years of experience in the development of electronic maps and geodata management systems.</P><P>d. Expert Nº 4: Hydraulic engineer with a degree in Water supply and sanitation or IT and hydrology and with preferably 5 years of experience in the implementation of the projects on development of hydraulic models for engineering systems.</P><P>It is essential that the Consultant’s team contains key experts fluent in Russian or Tajik. If some of key experts do not speak Russian, the consultant should demonstrate that they arranged for high quality translation.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be awarded the contract, the information submitted should include the following</P><P>1. Company/group of firms' profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages).</P><P>2. Details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities and deliverables, objectives.</P><P>3. Proposed approach, work plan and methodology.</P><P>4. CVs of key experts who could carry out the Assignment detailing qualifications, experience in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity/client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives.</P><P>5. Completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc.</P><P>The expression of interest shall not exceed 30 pages (excluding CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet).</P><P>One original and one copy in English, 3 numbered copies in Russian and a CD containing an electronic version of the Expression of Interest in pdf format should be submitted in sealed envelope marked “Nurek water and wastewater project. Expression of interest – consultancy services for hydraulic modelling of water supply and sewerage systems in the City of Nurek” to the address below not later than the closing date and time, i.e. not later than 15.5.2018 at 14:00, local time.</P><P>Please note that a breach of this submission procedure may lead to exclusion of the selection process.</P><P>Address for the submission of expressions of interest:</P><P>Address: 27 Shotemur StreetTender Box Nº 2</P><P>City: Dushanbe</P><P>Postal Code: 734002</P><P>Country: Republic of Tajikistan,</P><P>Name – State Committee on Investment and State Property Management of the Republic of Tajikistan.</P><P>Further information may be obtained from:</P><P>Mr. Olim Cholboboev , Director of CRP “Nurek City Department for Management of Infrastructure Projects” , 18 Rudaki Ave, Nurek , Republic of TAJIKISTAN, Postal Code: 735300, Tel.: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 , Fax: (8-31-38) 2-46-53 . Email: grp-nurek-2015@mail.ru</P><P>Important notes:</P><P>1. The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only. The client will establish a shortlist of the consultants using the below listed evaluation criteria. Further, the client may request the simple quotations from the shortlisted companies. The shortlisted Consultant who would submit the most advantageous to the client quotation will be invited to negotiate the contract.</P><P>2. The evaluation criteria for the Expression of Interests are as follows:</P><P>(a) Firm’s structure, organization and capacity, and experience in delivering assignments in the locations similar to Tajikistan of a comparable nature, scale and complexity to the Assignment – 20 %</P><P>(c) Proposed approach to the assignment, work plan and methodology - 30 %</P><P>(d) Proposed team of key experts – 40 %</P><P>(e) Local participation and knowledge of Russian/Tajik language, remote support of the proposed software – 10 %</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>