<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="161050-2018" EDITION="2018073"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-152743-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20190405</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>73</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180414</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 073-161050</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:161050-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="TR"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="38000000">Laboratory, optical and precision equipments (excl. glasses)</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180405</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>AP201</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Tyrkiet</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ipa - Levering af laboratorieudstyr og lysfælder til bekæmpelse og forebyggelse af Lumpy Skin Disease (LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>die Türkei</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Lieferung von Laborausrüstung und Lichtfallen zur Kontrolle und Prävention von Hautknotenkrankheit (LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Turkey</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Supply of Laboratory Equipment and Light Traps for Control and Prevention of Lumpy Skin Disease (LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Turquía</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Suministro de equipo de laboratorio y trampas de luz para el control y la prevención de la dermatosis nodular contagiosa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Turkki</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Karjan kyhmynahkataudin (LSD – lumpy skin disease) valvontaan ja ehkäisyyn käytettävien laboratoriolaitteiden ja valopyydysten hankinta</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Turquie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IAP - Fourniture d’un équipement de laboratoire et des pièges à lumière pour le contrôle et la prévention de la dermatose nodulaire contagieuse</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Τουρκία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Άγκυρα</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Παροχή Εργαστηριακού Εξοπλισμού και Παγίδων Φωτισμού για τον Έλεγχο και την Πρόληψη της Οζώδους Δερματίτιδας (LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Turchia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Fornitura di attrezzature di laboratorio e di trappole luminose per il controllo e la prevenzione della dermatite nodulare contagiosa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Turkije</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Levering van laboratoriumuitrusting en lichtvallen voor de bestrijding en preventie van nodulaire dermatose</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Turquia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ancara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Fornecimento de equipamento de laboratório e armadilhas luminosas para controlo e prevenção da dermatite nodular contagiosa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Turkiet</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Tillhandahållande av laboratorieutrustning och mindre fällor för kontroll och förebyggande åtgärder avseende lumpy skin disease (LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Turecko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>NPP - Dodávka laboratorního vybavení a světelných propustí pro kontrolu a prevenci nodulární dermatitidy skotu (LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Türgi</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Laboriseadmete ja valguspüüniste tarne nodulaarse dermatiidi (LSD) tõrje ja ennetamise jaoks</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Törökország</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Laboratóriumi berendezések és fénycsapdák beszerzése a bőrcsomósodáskór elleni védelem és megelőzés érdekében</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Turkija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>PNPP - Laboratorijos įrangos ir šviesos gaudyklių, skirtų žvynelinės profilaktikai, tiekimas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Turcija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Laboratorijas aprīkojuma un gaismas slazdu piegāde nodulārā dermatīta (ND) kontrolei un novēršanai</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>it-Turkija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>SGħQD - Provvista ta' Tagħmir tal-Laboratorju u Nases tad-Dawl għall-Kontroll u l-Prevenzjoni tal-Marda tal-Infafet fil-Ġilda (LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Turcja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Dostawa sprzętu laboratoryjnego i pułapek świetlnych do kontroli guzowatej choroby skóry bydła (LSD) i do jej zapobiegania</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Turecko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Dodávka laboratórnych zariadení a svetelných lapačov na kontrolu a prevenciu nodulárnej dermatitídy</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Turčija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Dobava laboratorijske opreme in svetlobnih pasti za nadzor in preprečevanje vozličastega dermatitisa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Tuirc, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Soláthar Trealaimh Shaotharlainne agus Gaistí Solais do Rialáil agus Cosc Ghalar an Chraicinn Chnapánaigh (LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Typция</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Анкара</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ИПП - Доставка на лабораторно оборудване и леки капани за контрол и превенция на заразен нодуларен дерматит (LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Turcia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Furnizarea de echipamente de laborator și capcane luminoase pentru controlul și prevenirea dermatitei nodulare (Lumpy Skin Disease - LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Turska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ankara</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IPA - Nabava laboratorijske opreme i svjetlosnih klopki za kontrolu i prevenciju bolesti kvrgave kože (lumpy skin disease - LSD)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den centrale finans- og kontraktenhed (CFCU — Central Finance and Contracts Unit)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Zentrale Abteilung Finanzen und Verträge (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">Central Finance and Contracts Unit (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">Unidad Central de Finanzas y Contratos (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Rahoitus- ja sopimusasioiden keskusyksikkö (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Unité centrale de financement et de passation de contrats</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Κεντρική μονάδα χρηματοδότησης και ανάθεσης συμβάσεων (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Unità centrale per i finanziamenti e gli appalti (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Centrale eenheid Financiën en Contracten (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">Unidade Central de Finanças e Contratos (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Centrala finansierings- och upphandlingsenheten (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Ústřední finanční a kontraktační jednotka (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Rahastamise ja lepingute kesktalitus (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Központi Pénzügyi és Szerződéskötő Egység (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Centrinis finansų ir sutarčių skyrius (CFSS)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Centrālā finanšu un līgumu aģentūra (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">it-Taqsima Ċentrali tal-Finanzi u l-Kuntratti (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Centralna Jednostka Finansująco-Kontraktująca (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Centrálne finančné a zmluvné oddelenie (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Centralna enota za finance in javna naročila (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An Láraonad Airgeadais agus Conarthaí (CFCU - central finance and contracts unit)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Централно звено за финансиране и договориране (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Unitatea centrală pentru finanțe și contracte (CFCU)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Središnji odjel za financiranje i ugovaranje (Central Finance and Contracts Unit — CFCU)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: Ipa - Levering af laboratorieudstyr og lysfælder til bekæmpelse og forebyggelse af Lumpy Skin Disease (LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sted — Tyrkiet</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FORHÅNDSMEDDELELSE VEDRØRENDE VAREKONTRAKT</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udbudsreference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Offentlig.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programtitel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Det årlige handlingsprogram for Tyrkiet for 2015 inden for rammerne af instrumentet til førtiltrædelsesbistand (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA-budgetpost 22.02 03 02 i EU's almindelige budget (85 %) og nationalt bidrag (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den centrale finans- og kontraktenhed (CFCU — Central Finance and Contracts Unit)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Tyrkiet</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivelse af kontrakten</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kontrakten har til formål at kontrollere og forhindre LSD gennem fangstmetoder med lysfælder og styrkelsen af den virale diagnosekapacitet i ministeriet for fødevarer, landbrug og husdyrholds institutlaboratorier via laboratorieudstyr.</P><P>Genstanden for denne kontrakt er indkøb, levering, idriftsættelse, afprøvning, træning og garantitjenester for laboratorieudstyr og lysfælder til bekæmpelse og forebyggelse af LSD.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Anslået antal partier og deres titel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kun 1 parti: Laboratorieudstyr og lysfælder.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Foreløbig dato for offentliggørelse af udbudsbekendtgørelsen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juni 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yderligere oplysninger</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ikke relevant.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Retsgrundlag</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 236/2014 af 11.3.2014 angående fælles regler og procedurer for gennemførelsen af instrumenterne til finansiering af Unionens optræden udadtil og Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 231/2014 af 11.3.2014 om oprettelse af et instrument til førtiltrædelsesbistand (IPA II), EUT L 77, 15.3.2014, s. 11. — jf. bilag A2 i den praktiske vejledning.</P><P>Vær opmærksom på, at reglerne om adgang til EU's udbudsprocedurer for økonomiske aktører, der er etableret i tredjelande og for varer, der stammer fra tredjelande, efter Det Forenede Kongeriges udtræden af EU vil gælde for ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige og for alle ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere, der foreslår varer, der stammer fra Det Forenede Kongerige, afhængigt af resultatet af forhandlingerne. Hvis en sådan adgang ikke gives ved retlige bestemmelser, der er gældende på tidspunktet for kontrakttildelingen, vil ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige og ansøgere og tilbudsgivere, der foreslår varer, der stammer fra Det Forenede Kongerige, kunne blive udelukket fra udbudsproceduren.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Bemærkninger:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Der skal være en periode på mindst 30 kalenderdage mellem offentliggørelsen af denne forhåndsmeddelelse og offentliggørelsen af den tilsvarende udbudsbekendtgørelse.</P><P>Der kan ikke fremsendes ansøgninger eller anmodninger om oplysninger på nuværende tidspunkt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Lieferung von Laborausrüstung und Lichtfallen zur Kontrolle und Prävention von Hautknotenkrankheit (LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Standort - Türkei</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VORINFORMATION FÜR EINEN LIEFERAUFTRAG</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verfahren</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>offen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmbezeichnung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jährliches Aktionsprogramm für die Türkei für das Jahr 2015 im Rahmen des Instruments für Heranführungshilfe (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanzierung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA-Haushaltsposten 22.02 03 02 des Gesamthaushaltsplans der EU (85 %) und nationaler Beitrag (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Öffentlicher Auftraggeber</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Zentrale Abteilung Finanzen und Verträge (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Türkei</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Dieser Vertrag zielt darauf ab, LSD (Lumpy Skin Disease) zu kontrollieren und zu verhindern, indem Vektoren mit Lichtfallen eingefangen und die Virusdiagnosefähigkeit der Labore der Institute des Ministeriums für Ernährung, Landwirtschaft und Viehzucht mit Laborausrüstung verstärkt werden.</P><P>Gegenstand dieses Vertrages ist die Bereitstellung, Lieferung, Inbetriebnahme, Prüfung, Inspektion, Schulung und Garantieleistungen von Laborausrüstung und Lichtfallen zur Kontrolle und Prävention von LSD.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Voraussichtliche Losanzahl/-nummer/-bezeichnung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>nur 1 Los: Laborausrüstung und Lichtfallen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Geplanter Zeitpunkt für die Veröffentlichung der Auftragsbekanntmachung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juni 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sonstige Informationen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Entfällt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsgrundlage</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verordnung (EU) Nr. 236/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Festlegung gemeinsamer Vorschriften und Verfahren für die Anwendung der Instrumente der Union für die Finanzierung des auswärtigen Handelns und Verordnung (EU) Nr. 231/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Schaffung eines Instruments für Heranführungshilfe (IPA II), ABI L 77, 15.3.2014, S. 11. - Siehe Anhang A2 des „Handbuch“.</P><P>Es wird darauf hingewiesen, dass nach dem Austritt des Vereinigten Königreichs aus der EU, je nach dem Ergebnis der Verhandlungen, für Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich die Zugangsregeln zu EU-Beschaffungsverfahren für in Drittländern ansässige Wirtschaftsteilnehmer und für aus Drittländern stammende Waren gelten werden. Dies gilt auch für alle Bewerber oder Bieter, die Waren aus dem Vereinigten Königreich anbieten. Falls dieser Zugang gemäß den bei Auftragsvergabe geltenden Bestimmung nicht gewährt wird, können Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich sowie Bewerber oder Bieter, die aus dem Vereinigten Königreich stammende Waren anbieten, vom Beschaffungsverfahren ausgeschlossen werden.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Hinweise:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Es muss ein Zeitraum von mindestens 30 Kalendertagen zwischen der Veröffentlichung der Vorinformation und der Veröffentlichung der entsprechenden Auftragsbekanntmachung liegen.</P><P>Derzeit ist von der Einreichung von Bewerbungen oder weiteren Anfragen abzusehen.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Supply of Laboratory Equipment and Light Traps for Control and Prevention of Lumpy Skin Disease (LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Location - Turkey</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SUPPLY CONTRACT PRIOR INFORMATION NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publication reference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Open.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programme title</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Annual Action Programme for Turkey for the year 2015 under the Instrument for Pre-accession Assistance (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financing</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA budget item 22.02 03 02 of the general budget of the EU (85 %) and national contribution (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contracting authority</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Central Finance and Contracts Unit (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turkey</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contract description</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>This contract aims to control and prevent LSD through entrapping vectors with light traps and strengthening viral diagnosis capability of Institute Laboratories of Ministry of Food, Agriculture and Livestock with laboratory equipment.</P><P>The subject of this contract is the supply, delivery, commissioning, testing, inspection, training and warranty services of laboratory equipment and light traps for control and prevention of LSD.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicative number and titles of Lots</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 lot only: Laboratory equipment and light traps.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intended timing of publication of the contract notice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Additional information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Not Applicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal basis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulation (EU) N<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> 236/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 laying down common rules and procedures for the implementation of the Union's instruments for financing external action and Regulation (EU) No 231/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 establishing an Instrument for Pre-Accession Assistance (IPA II), OJ L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11 — See Annex A2 of the Practical Guide.</P><P>Please be aware that after the United Kingdom's withdrawal from the EU, the rules of access to EU procurement procedures of economic operators established in third countries and of goods originating from third countries will apply to candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom and to all candidates or tenderers proposing goods originating from the United Kingdom depending on the outcome of negotiations. In case such access is not provided by legal provisions in force at the time of the contract award, candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom, and candidates or tenderers proposing goods originating from the United Kingdom could be rejected from the procurement procedure.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarks:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>There must be a minimum period of 30 calendar days between the publication of this prior information notice and the publication of the corresponding contract notice.</P><P>No applications or requests for information should be sent at this stage.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Suministro de equipo de laboratorio y trampas de luz para el control y la prevención de la dermatosis nodular contagiosa</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lugar: Turquía</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNCIO DE PREVISIÓN DE CONTRATO DE SUMINISTROS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referencia de publicación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedimiento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Abierto.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Denominación del programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de acción anual para el año 2015 a favor de Turquía en el marco del Instrumento de Ayuda Preadhesión (IAP II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Partida presupuestaria 22.02 03 02 del IAP con cargo al presupuesto general de la Unión Europea (85 %) y a la contribución nacional (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de contratación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unidad Central de Finanzas y Contratos (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turquía</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Este contrato tiene el objetivo de controlar y prevenir la dermatosis nodular contagiosa atrapando los vectores de la enfermedad con trampas de luz y reforzando la capacidad de diagnóstico viral de los laboratorios del Ministerio de Alimentación, Agricultura y Ganadería con equipos de laboratorio.</P><P>El objeto de este contrato son los servicios de suministro, entrega, puesta en funcionamiento, prueba, inspección, formación y garantía de equipo de laboratorio y trampas de luz para el control y la prevención de la dermatosis nodular contagiosa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Número indicativo y títulos de los lotes</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 solo lote: equipo de laboratorio y trampas de luz.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha prevista de publicación del anuncio de contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Junio de 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información adicional</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>No aplicable.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fundamento jurídico</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Reglamento (UE) n.° 236/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establecen normas y procedimientos de ejecución comunes de los instrumentos de la Unión para la financiación de la acción exterior y Reglamento (UE) n.° 231/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establece un Instrumento de Ayuda Preadhesión (IAP II), DO L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11; véase el anexo A2 de la «Guía Práctica».</P><P>Téngase en cuenta que tras la salida del Reino Unido de la Unión Europea, las normas de acceso a los procedimientos de contratación de la Unión Europea de los operadores económicos establecidos en terceros países y de los bienes originarios de terceros países se aplicarán a los candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido y a todos los candidatos o licitadores que propongan productos originarios del Reino Unido, en función del resultado de las negociaciones. En caso de que dicho acceso no se prevea en las disposiciones jurídicas en vigor en el momento de la adjudicación del contrato, los candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido y los candidatos o licitadores que propongan productos originarios del Reino Unido podrían ser excluidos del procedimiento de licitación.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observaciones:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deben pasar al menos 30 días naturales desde la publicación de este anuncio de información previa hasta la publicación del correspondiente anuncio de licitación.</P><P>Por el momento, no deben enviarse solicitudes ni peticiones de información complementaria.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Karjan kyhmynahkataudin (LSD – lumpy skin disease) valvontaan ja ehkäisyyn käytettävien laboratoriolaitteiden ja valopyydysten hankinta</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sijainti – Turkki</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tavaranhankintasopimusta koskeva ennakkotietoilmoitus</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen viite</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menettely</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Avoin menettely.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ohjelman nimi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Turkkia koskeva vuotuinen toimintaohjelma vuodelle 2015 liittymistä valmistelevan tukivälineen (IPA II) yhteydessä</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahoitus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan unionin yleisen talousarvion IPA-budjettikohta 22.02 03 02 (85%) ja kansallinen rahoitusosuus (15%).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Rahoitus- ja sopimusasioiden keskusyksikkö (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turkki</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuksen kuvaus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tämän sopimuksen tarkoituksena on valvoa ja ehkäistä karjan kyhmynahkatautia (LSD – lumpy skin disease) pyydystämällä tautia välittäviä vektoreita valopyydyksillä sekä vahvistamalla elintarvike-, maatalous- ja karjanhoitoministeriön instituutin laboratorioiden virusdiagnostiikkavalmiuksia laboratoriolaittein.</P><P>Tämän sopimuksen piiriin kuuluu laboratoriolaitteistojen ja valopyydysten hankinta, toimitus, käyttöönotto, testaus, tarkastus sekä koulutus- ja takuupalvelut karjan kyhmynahkataudin valvontaa ja ehkäisyä varten.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Erien arvioitu lukumäärä ja nimet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Vain yksi erä: laboratoriolaitteet ja valopyydykset.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintailmoituksen ennakoitu julkaisemisajankohta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kesäkuu 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisätiedot</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ei ole.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oikeusperusta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) n:o 236/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, unionin ulkoisen toiminnan rahoitusvälineiden täytäntöönpanoa koskevista yhteisistä säännöistä ja menettelyistä sekä Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) n:o 231/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, liittymistä valmistelevan tukivälineen (IPA II) perustamisesta (EUVL L 77, 15.3.2014, s. 11) – katso EU:n ulkoisten toimien sopimusmenettelyjä koskevan käytännön oppaan liite A2.</P><P>Brittiläisten hakijoiden tai tarjoajien osalta on huomioitava, että Yhdistyneen kuningaskunnan EU:sta irtautumisen jälkeen kolmansiin maihin sijoittautuneisiin talouden toimijoihin sovellettavia EU:n hankintamenettelyihin osallistumista koskevia sääntöjä sovelletaan Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin oleviin hakijoihin tai tarjoajiin neuvottelujen tuloksesta riippuen. Mikäli sopimuksenteon hetkellä voimassa olevassa lainsäädännössä ei anneta lupaa tällaiseen osallistumiseen, Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin olevat hakijat tai tarjoajat voidaan hylätä hankintamenettelystä.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Huom.:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Tämän ennakkotietoilmoituksen ja vastaavan hankintailmoituksen julkaisemisen välillä on oltava vähintään 30 kalenteripäivää.</P><P>Hakemuksia tai lisätietopyyntöjä ei pidä lähettää tässä vaiheessa.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IAP - Fourniture d’un équipement de laboratoire et des pièges à lumière pour le contrôle et la prévention de la dermatose nodulaire contagieuse</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lieu - Turquie</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVIS DE PRÉINFORMATION RELATIF À UN MARCHÉ DE FOURNITURES</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Référence de la publication</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ouverte.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intitulé du programme</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programme d'action annuel en faveur de la Turquie au titre de l'instrument d'aide de préadhésion (IAP II) pour l'année 2015.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financement</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ligne 22.02 03 02 (IAP) du budget général de l'UE (85 %) et contribution nationale (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pouvoir adjudicateur</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unité centrale de financement et de passation de contrats</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turquie</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ce marché vise à contrôler et prévenir la dermatose nodulaire contagieuse via des vecteurs d’emprisonnement avec des pièges à lumière et à renforcer la capacité du diagnostique viral des laboratoires d’un institut du ministère de l'alimentation, de l'agriculture et de l'élevage par un équipement de laboratoire.</P><P>Ce marché porte sur les services de la fourniture, la livraison, la mise en service, l’essai, l’inspection, la formation et la garantie d’un équipement de laboratoire et des pièges à lumière pour le contrôle et la prévention de la dermatose nodulaire contagieuse.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nombre indicatif et intitulé des lots</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lot unique : Équipement de laboratoire et pièges à lumière.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date prévue de publication de l'avis de marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juin 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Renseignements complémentaires</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sans objet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base juridique</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Règlement (UE) N<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> 236/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 fixant les règles communes et les procédures de mise en œuvre des instruments de l'Union pour le financement de l'action extérieure et règlement (UE) n° 231/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 instituant un instrument d'aide de préadhésion (IAP II), JO L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11. — voir annexe A2 du « Guide pratique ».</P><P>Il convient de noter qu'à la suite du retrait du Royaume-Uni de l'UE, les règles d'accès aux procédures de passation des marchés de l'UE pour les opérateurs économiques établis dans des pays tiers et des marchandises en provenance des pays tiers s'appliqueront aux candidats ou aux soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni, et à tous les candidats ou soumissionnaires proposant des marchandises en provenance du Royaume-Uni, en fonction des résultats des négociations. Si les dispositions légales en vigueur au moment de l'attribution du contrat ne prévoient pas un tel accès, les candidats ou les soumissionnaires proposant des marchandises en provenance du Royaume-Uni pourraient être exclus de la procédure d'appel d'offres.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarques :</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Un délai minimal de 30 jours calendaires doit être respecté entre la publication du présent avis de pré-information et celle de l'avis de marché correspondant.</P><P>Aucune candidature ni demande de renseignements complémentaires ne sera envoyée à ce stade de la procédure.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Άγκυρα: IPA - Παροχή Εργαστηριακού Εξοπλισμού και Παγίδων Φωτισμού για τον Έλεγχο και την Πρόληψη της Οζώδους Δερματίτιδας (LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Τόπος - Τουρκία</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ΠΡΟΚΑΤΑΡΚΤΙΚΗ ΕΝΗΜΕΡΩΣΗ ΓΙΑ ΣΥΜΒΑΣΗ ΠΡΟΜΗΘΕΙΩΝ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αριθ. αναφοράς της δημοσίευσης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Διαδικασία</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ανοικτή.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τίτλος προγράμματος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ετήσιο πρόγραμμα δράσης για την Τουρκία για το έτος 2015 στο πλαίσιο του μηχανισμού προενταξιακής βοήθειας (ΜΠΒ II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Χρηματοδότηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κονδύλιο προϋπολογισμού ΜΠΒ 22.02 03 02 του γενικού προϋπολογισμού της ΕΕ (85 %) και εθνική συνεισφορά (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα αρχή</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Κεντρική μονάδα χρηματοδότησης και ανάθεσης συμβάσεων (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Άγκυρα</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Τουρκία.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Περιγραφή της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Η σύμβαση αυτή αποσκοπεί στον έλεγχο και την πρόληψη της οζώδους δερματίτιδας (LSD) μέσω της παγίδευσης φορέων με ελαφριές παγίδες και της ενίσχυσης της ικανότητας διάγνωσης των ιών από τα εργαστήρια του Ινστιτούτου του Υπουργείου Τροφίμων, Γεωργίας και Κτηνοτροφίας, με εργαστηριακό εξοπλισμό.</P><P>Το αντικείμενο της παρούσας σύμβασης είναι η παροχή, η παράδοση, η προετοιμασία για τη λειτουργία, η δοκιμή, η επιθεώρηση, η εκπαίδευση και οι υπηρεσίες εγγύησης εργαστηριακού εξοπλισμού και ελαφρών παγίδων για τον έλεγχο και την πρόληψη της οζώδους δερματίτιδας LSD).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ενδεικτικός αριθμός και τίτλοι παρτίδων</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 μόνον παρτίδα: Εργαστηριακός εξοπλισμός και ελαφριές παγίδες.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης της προκήρυξης σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ιούνιος 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Άνευ αντικειμένου.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Νομική βάση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 236/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τον καθορισμό κοινών κανόνων και διαδικασιών για την εφαρμογή των μηχανισμών χρηματοδότησης της εξωτερικής δράσης της Ένωσης και κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 231/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τη θέσπιση Μηχανισμού Προενταξιακής Βοήθειας (ΜΠΒ II), (ΕΕ L 77, 15.3.2014, σελ. 11). - βλέπε παράρτημα Α2 του «Πρακτικού Οδηγού»</P><P>Πρέπει να ληφθεί υπόψη ότι μετά την αποχώρηση του Ηνωμένου Βασιλείου από την ΕΕ, οι κανόνες πρόσβασης σε διαδικασίες διαγωνισμού της ΕΕ για οικονομικούς φορείς που είναι εγκατεστημένοι σε τρίτες χώρες και για αγαθά που προέρχονται από τρίτες χώρες θα ισχύουν για τους υποψήφιους ή προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο και σε όλους τους υποψηφίους ή προσφέροντες που προτείνουν αγαθά που προέρχονται από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο ανάλογα με το αποτέλεσμα των διαπραγματεύσεων. Σε περίπτωση που η πρόσβαση αυτή δεν παρέχεται από νομικές διατάξεις που ίσχυαν κατά τον χρόνο ανάθεσης της σύμβασης, οι υποψήφιοι ή οι προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο και οι υποψήφιοι ή οι προσφέροντες που προτείνουν αγαθά που προέρχονται από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο θα μπορούσαν να απορριφθούν από τη διαδικασία διαγωνισμού.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Παρατηρήσεις:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Μεταξύ της δημοσίευσης της παρούσας προκαταρκτικής ανακοίνωσης και της δημοσίευσης της αντίστοιχης προκήρυξης σύμβασης θα πρέπει να παρεμβληθεί χρονικό διάστημα τουλάχιστον 30 ημερολογιακών ημερών.</P><P>Κατά το παρόν στάδιο δεν πρέπει να αποστέλλονται υποψηφιότητες ή αιτήματα για παροχή πληροφοριών.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Fornitura di attrezzature di laboratorio e di trappole luminose per il controllo e la prevenzione della dermatite nodulare contagiosa</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ubicazione — Turchia</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avviso di preinformazione relativo a un appalto di forniture</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Riferimento della pubblicazione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>aperta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titolo del programma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programma d'azione annuale per la Turchia per l'anno 2015 nell'ambito dello strumento di assistenza preadesione (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanziamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Voce del bilancio IPA 22.02 03 02 del bilancio generale dell'Unione europea (85 %) e contributo nazionale (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ente appaltante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unità centrale per i finanziamenti e gli appalti (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turchia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il presente appalto si prefigge di controllare e prevenire la dermatite nodulare contagiosa intrappolando i vettori con trappole luminose e rafforzando la capacità di diagnosi virale dei laboratori dell'Istituto del Ministero dell'alimentazione, dell'agricoltura e dell'allevamento con attrezzature di laboratorio.</P><P>L’oggetto del presente appalto sono la fornitura, la consegna, la messa in servizio, il collaudo, l’ispezione, la formazione e i servizi di garanzia di apparecchiature di laboratorio e trappole luminose per il controllo e la prevenzione della dermatite nodulare contagiosa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numero indicativo e titoli dei lotti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Solo 1 lotto: attrezzature di laboratorio e trappole luminose.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista per la pubblicazione del bando di gara</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Giugno 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informazioni complementari</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Non applicabile.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base giuridica</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regolamento (UE) n. 236/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che stabilisce norme e procedure comuni per l'attuazione degli strumenti per il finanziamento dell'azione esterna dell'Unione e regolamento (UE) n. 231/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che istituisce uno strumento di assistenza preadesione (IPA II), GU L 77, 15.3.2014, pag. 11 — cfr. allegato A2 alla guida pratica.</P><P>Si prega di notare che, dopo il ritiro del Regno Unito dall'UE, ai candidati o offerenti del Regno Unito e a tutti i candidati o offerenti che propongono merci originarie del Regno Unito, si applicheranno le regole di accesso alle procedure d'appalto dell'UE per gli operatori economici stabiliti in paesi terzi e per le merci provenienti da paesi terzi, in funzione dell'esito dei negoziati. Nel caso in cui tale accesso non sia previsto dalle disposizioni giuridiche in vigore al momento dell'aggiudicazione dell'appalto, i candidati o gli offerenti del Regno Unito e i candidati o gli offerenti che propongono merci provenienti dal Regno Unito potrebbero essere respinti dalla procedura di aggiudicazione.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Osservazioni:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Dovrà intercorrere un periodo minimo di 30 giorni di calendario tra la pubblicazione dell'avviso di preinformazione e quella del corrispondente bando di gara.</P><P>Si prega di non inviare candidature o richieste di ulteriori informazioni durante questa fase della procedura.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Levering van laboratoriumuitrusting en lichtvallen voor de bestrijding en preventie van nodulaire dermatose</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Locatie - Turkije</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VOORAANKONDIGING VAN EEN LEVERINGSOPDRACHT</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referentie van de bekendmaking:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Openbaar.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titel van het programma:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jaarlijks actieprogramma voor Turkije voor het jaar 2015 in het kader van het instrument voor pretoetredingssteun (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiering:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA-begrotingspost 22.02 03 02 van de algemene begroting van de EU (85 %) en nationale bijdrage (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centrale eenheid Financiën en Contracten (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turkije.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschrijving van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Onderhavige opdracht is gericht op de bestrijding en preventie van nodulaire dermatose door het vangen van vectoren met lichtvallen en de versterking van de virale diagnosecapaciteit van de laboratoria van het instituut van het Ministerie van Voedingsmiddelen, Landbouw en Veestapel met laboratoriumuitrusting.</P><P>Het voorwerp van onderhavige opdracht is de levering, bezorging, inbedrijfstelling, tests en inspectie van de laboratoriumuitrusting en lichtvallen voor de bestrijding en preventie van nodulaire dermatose, alsook bijbehorende opleiding en garantiediensten.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicatief aantal en titels van percelen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Slechts 1 perceel: laboratoriumuitrusting en lichtvallen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beoogde datum voor bekendmaking van de aankondiging van opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juni 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nadere inlichtingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet van toepassing.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Juridische basis:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verordening (EU) nr. 236/2014 van het Europees Parlement en van de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van gemeenschappelijke voorschriften en procedures voor de tenuitvoerlegging van de instrumenten van de Unie ter financiering van extern optreden en Verordening (EU) nr. 231/2014 van het Europees Parlement en van de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van een instrument voor pretoetredingssteun (IPA II), PB L 77 van 15.3.2014, blz. 11 — zie bijlage A2 bij de praktische gids.</P><P>Gelieve op te merken dat na de terugtrekking van het Verenigd Koninkrijk uit de EU en afhankelijk van de uitkomst van de onderhandelingen, de regels voor toegang tot de EU-aanbestedingsprocedures voor ondernemers die zijn gevestigd in derde landen en voor goederen die komen uit derde landen zullen gelden voor gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk, en voor alle gegadigden of inschrijvers die goederen voorstellen die uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk komen. Indien dergelijke toegang niet is voorzien door de geldende wettelijke bepalingen op het tijdstip van de gunning van de opdracht, kunnen gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk en gegadigden of inschrijvers die goederen voorstellen die afkomstig zijn uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk worden geweigerd voor de aanbestedingsprocedure.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opmerkingen:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Er moet een minimumtermijn van 30 kalenderdagen liggen tussen de bekendmaking van deze vooraankondiging en de bekendmaking van de overeenstemmende aankondiging van een opdracht.</P><P>In dit stadium mogen er geen aanvragen of verzoeken om inlichtingen worden verzonden.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ancara: IPA - Fornecimento de equipamento de laboratório e armadilhas luminosas para controlo e prevenção da dermatite nodular contagiosa</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Localização - Turquia</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANÚNCIO DE PRÉ-INFORMAÇÃO RELATIVO A UM CONTRATO DE FORNECIMENTOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referência da publicação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Público.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Título do programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de ação anual para a Turquia para 2015, no âmbito do Instrumento de Assistência de Pré-Adesão (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rubrica orçamental do programa IPA 22.02 03 02 do orçamento geral da UE (85%) e contribuição nacional (15%).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unidade Central de Finanças e Contratos (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ancara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turquia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O presente contrato visa controlar e prevenir a dermatite nodular contagiosa através de vetores de aprisionamento com armadilhas luminosas e reforço da capacidade de diagnóstico viral dos laboratórios do Instituto do Ministério da Alimentação, Agricultura e Pecuária com equipamento de laboratório.</P><P>O objeto do presente contrato é o fornecimento, entrega, colocação em funcionamento, ensaio, inspeção, formação e serviços de garantia de equipamento de laboratório e armadilhas luminosas para o controlo e prevenção da dermatite nodular contagiosa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Número indicativo e designação dos lotes</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 lote unicamente: Equipamento para laboratório e armadilhas luminosas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista para a publicação do anúncio de concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Junho de 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Outras informações</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Não aplicável.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base jurídica</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulamento (UE) n.<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> 236/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que estabelece regras e procedimentos comuns para a execução dos instrumentos da União de financiamento da ação externa e Regulamento (UE) n.º 231/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que cria um instrumento de assistência de pré-adesão (IPA II), JO L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11 – Ver anexo A2 do «Guia Prático».</P><P>Importa notar que após a saída do Reino Unido da UE, as regras de acesso aos procedimentos de adjudicação de contratos da UE de operadores económicos estabelecidos em países terceiros e bens provenientes de países terceiros serão aplicadas aos candidatos ou proponentes de bens provenientes do Reino Unido consoante o resultado das negociações. Caso tal acesso não esteja previsto pelas disposições legais em vigor, os candidatos ou proponentes do Reino Unido e candidatos ou proponentes de bens provenientes do Reino Unido poderão ser excluídos do concurso.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observações:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deve ser respeitado um período mínimo de 30 dias de calendário entre a publicação do presente anúncio de informação prévia e a publicação do anúncio de concurso correspondente.</P><P>Não devem ser enviadas candidaturas ou efetuados pedidos de informação nesta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Tillhandahållande av laboratorieutrustning och mindre fällor för kontroll och förebyggande åtgärder avseende lumpy skin disease (LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Plats – Turkiet</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÖRHANDSMEDDELANDE AVSEENDE VARUKONTRAKT</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publikationsreferens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Förfarande</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Öppet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Namn på programmet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Årligt åtgärdsprogram för Turkiet för 2015 inom ramen för instrumentet för stöd inför anslutningen (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA-budgetrubrik 22.02 03 02 i EU:s allmänna budget (85 %) och nationellt bidrag (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centrala finansierings- och upphandlingsenheten (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turkiet</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivning av kontraktet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Detta kontrakt syftar till att kontrollera och förebygga LSD genom att fånga in vektorer med mindre fällor samt förstärka den diagnostiska kapaciteten avseende virus hos institutets laboratorier vid ministeriet för livsmedel, jordbruk och boskap med hjälp av laboratorieutrustning.</P><P>Syftet med kontraktet är tillhandahållande, leverans, idriftsättning, testning, inspektion, utbildning och garantitjänster avseende laboratorieutrustning och mindre fällor för kontroll och förebyggande åtgärder avseende LSD.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Preliminärt antal delar titlar på delarna</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Endast 1 del: Laboratorieutrustning och mindre fällor.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerat datum för publicering av meddelandet om upphandling</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juni 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kompletterande information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ej tillämplig.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rättslig grund</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 236/2014 av den 11.3.2014 om fastställande av gemensamma bestämmelser och förfaranden för genomförandet av unionens instrument för finansiering av yttre åtgärder samt Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 231/2014 av den 11.3.2014 om inrättande av ett instrument för stöd inför anslutningen (IPA II) - EUT L 77, 15.3.2014, s. 11 - se bilaga A2 i den praktiska handledningen.</P><P>Observera att efter det Förenade kungariket Storbritanniens utträde ur EU kommer reglerna för tillgång till EU:s upphandlingsförfaranden för ekonomiska aktörer, som är etablerade i tredjeländer och för varor som härrör från tredjeländer, att tillämpas på sökande eller anbudsgivare från det Förenade kungariket Storbritannien, och på alla sökande eller anbudsgivare som föreslår varor som härrör från det Förenade Kungariket Storbritannien, beroende på resultatet av förhandlingarna. Om sådan tillgång inte tillhandahålls av rättsliga bestämmelser, som gäller vid tidpunkten för kontraktstilldelningen, kan sökande eller anbudsgivare från det Förenade kungariket Storbritannien och alla sökande eller anbudsgivare som föreslår varor som härrör från det Förenade kungariket Storbritannien komma att uteslutas från upphandlingsförfarandet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Anmärkningar:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>En period på minst 30 kalenderdagar ska förflyta mellan publikationen av detta förhandsmeddelande och publikationen av motsvarande meddelande om upphandling.</P><P>Inga ansökningar eller begäranden av information ska skickas i detta skede.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: NPP - Dodávka laboratorního vybavení a světelných propustí pro kontrolu a prevenci nodulární dermatitidy skotu (LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokalita – Turecko</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>OZNÁMENÍ PŘEDBĚŽNÝCH INFORMACÍ O ZAKÁZCE NA DODÁVKY</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenční číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Otevřené.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Název programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Roční akční program pro Turecko pro rok 2015 v rámci nástroje předvstupní pomoci (NPP II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financování</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozpočtová položka NPP 22.02 03 02 souhrnného rozpočtu EU (85 %) a národní příspěvek (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veřejný zadavatel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ústřední finanční a kontraktační jednotka (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turecko</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popis zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cílem této zakázky je kontrola a prevence nodulární dermatitidy skotu zachycováním vektorů pomocí světelných propustí a posílením schopnosti virové diagnostiky Laboratorního institutu Ministerstva potravin, zemědělství a živočišné výroby pomocí laboratorního vybavení.</P><P>Předmětem této zakázky je dodávka, doručení, zprovoznění, testování, kontrola, školení a záruční servis laboratorního vybavení a světelných propustí pro kontrolu a prevenci nodulární dermatitidy skotu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Daný počet a názvy položek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pouze 1 položka: laboratorní zařízení a světelné propusti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zamýšlené datum zveřejnění oznámení o zakázce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>červen 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Další informace</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>nepoužije se.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právní základ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 236/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se stanoví společná pravidla a postupy pro provádění nástrojů Unie pro financování vnější činnosti, a nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 231/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se zřizuje nástroj předvstupní pomoci (NPP II), Úř. věst. L 77, 15.3.2014, s. 11 – viz příloha A2 „Praktického průvodce“.</P><P>Připomínáme, že po vystoupení Spojeného království z EU se na zájemce nebo uchazeče ze Spojeného království a na všechny uchazeče nebo zájemce předkládající zboží původem ze Spojeného království, v závislosti od výsledku jednání, budou uplatňovat pravidla přístupu k postupům výběrového řízení EU ze strany hospodářských subjektů se sídlem ve třetích zemích a pokud jde o zboží pocházející ze třetích zemí. V případě, že takový přístup není zabezpečen právními předpisy platnými v době zadání zakázky, mohli by být uchazeči nebo účastníci ze Spojeného království a uchazeči nebo zájemci předkládající zboží původem ze Spojeného království vyloučeni z výběrového řízení.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Mezi zveřejněním těchto předběžných informací o zakázce a zveřejněním odpovídajícího oznámení o zakázce musí uplynout minimálně 30 kalendářních dnů.</P><P>V této fázi nesmí být zasílány žádné přihlášky ani žádosti o informace.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Laboriseadmete ja valguspüüniste tarne nodulaarse dermatiidi (LSD) tõrje ja ennetamise jaoks</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Asukoht – Türgi</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tarnelepingu eelteade</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaldamise viide</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menetlus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Avatud.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmi pealkiri</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Türgi 2015. aasta tegevusprogramm ühinemiseelse abi rahastamisvahendi (IPA II) raames.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahastamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ELi üldeelarve IPA eelarvepunkt 22.02 03 02 (85 %) ja riiklik panus (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaliku sektori hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Rahastamise ja lepingute kesktalitus (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Türgi</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kõnealuse lepingu eesmärk on nodulaarse dermatiidi (Lumpy Skin Disease (LSD)) tõrje ja ennetamine nakkusesiirutajate valguspüünistega lõksu püüdmise ja ning toiduainete, põllumajanduse ja kariloomade ministeeriumi instituudi laborite viiruse diagnoosimise suutlikkuse tugevdamisega laboriseadmete tarne kaudu.</P><P>Kõnealuse lepingu ese on LSD tõrjeks ja ennetuseks mõeldud laboriseadmete ja valguspüüniste tarne, kättetoimetamine, käikulaskmine, testimine, kontrollimine, koolitus ja garantiiteenused.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Osade soovituslik arv ja nimetused</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ainult 1 osa:  laboriseadmed ja valguspüünised.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hanketeate avaldamise esialgne aeg</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Juuni 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisateave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ei kohaldata.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Õiguslik alus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 236/2014, milles sätestatakse liidu välistegevuse rahastamisvahendite rakendamise ühiseeskirjad ja menetlused, ning Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014 määrus (EL) nr 231/2014, millega luuakse ühinemiseelse abi rahastamisvahend (IPA II), (ELT L 77, 15.3.2014, lk 11) (vt praktilise juhendi lisa A2).</P><P>Palume tähele panna, et olenevalt läbirääkimiste tulemusest kehtivad pärast Ühendkuningriigi EList lahkumist Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaatidele või pakkujatele ja kõigile Ühendkuningriigist pärit tooteid pakkuvatele kandidaatidele või pakkujatele kolmandates riikides asutatud ettevõtjatele kehtivad ELi hankemenetlustele juurdepääsu käsitlevad eeskirjad. Juhul, kui selline juurdepääs ei ole tagatud lepingu sõlmimise ajal kehtivate õiguslike sätete kaudu, võidakse Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaadid või pakkujad ja Ühendkuningriigist pärit kaupu pakkuvad kandidaadid või pakkujad hankemenetlusest kõrvale jätta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Märkused</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Eelteate ja vastava hanketeate avaldamise vahele peab jääma vähemalt 30 kalendripäeva.</P><P>Taotlusi ega teabenõudeid ei või selles etapis veel saata.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Laboratóriumi berendezések és fénycsapdák beszerzése a bőrcsomósodáskór elleni védelem és megelőzés érdekében</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Helyszín: Törökország</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ÁRUBESZERZÉSRE IRÁNYULÓ ELŐZETES ÖSSZESÍTETT HIRDETMÉNY</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A közzététel hivatkozási száma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Eljárás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nyílt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A program címe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2015. évi cselekvési program Törökország számára az Előcsatlakozási Támogatási Eszköz (IPA II) keretében.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanszírozás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Az EU általános költségvetésének 22.02 03 02. számú IPA költségvetési tétele (85 %-ban) és nemzeti hozzájárulás (15 %-ban).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Központi Pénzügyi és Szerződéskötő Egység (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Törökország</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés meghatározása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A jelen szerződés célja a bőrcsomósodáskór elleni védelem és annak megelőzése a következők által: vektorok fénycsapdákkal történő elfogása, valamint az Élelmezésügyi, Mezőgazdasági és Állattenyésztési Minisztérium intézményi laboratóriumainak vírusok diagnosztizálására irányuló kapacitásának fejlesztése laboratóriumi berendezések segítségével.</P><P>A szerződés tárgya laboratóriumi berendezések és fénycsapdák beszerzése, leszállítása, üzembe helyezése, tesztelése, ellenőrzése, valamint a kapcsolódó képzési és garanciális szolgáltatások a bőrcsomósodáskór elleni védelem és annak megelőzése céljából.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A tételek várható száma és megnevezése</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A projekt 1 tételből áll: Laboratóriumi berendezések és fénycsapdák.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlati felhívás közzétételének tervezett időpontja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018. június.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>További információk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nem alkalmazható.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Jogalap</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A külső tevékenységek finanszírozását szabályozó uniós eszközök végrehajtására vonatkozó közös szabályok és eljárások megállapításáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű 236/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet, illetve az Előcsatlakozási Támogatási Eszköz (IPA II) létrehozásáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű 231/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet (HL L 77., 15.3.2014, 11. o.) – lásd a Gyakorlati útmutató A2 mellékletét.</P><P>Figyelembe kell venni, hogy az Egyesült Királyságnak az EU-ból való kilépése után az Egyesült Királyságból származó jelentkezőkre vagy ajánlattevőkre, valamint valamennyi olyan jelentkezőre és ajánlattevőre, akik az Egyesült Királyságból származó árukat kínálnak – a tárgyalások kimenetelétől függően – az EU közbeszerzési eljárásaihoz való hozzáférés tekintetében a harmadik országok gazdasági szereplőire és a harmadik országból származó árukra érvényes szabályok vonatkoznak. Amennyiben a részvételről nem rendelkezik hatályban lévő jogszabály, az Egyesült Királyságból származó ajánlattevők, valamint az Egyesült Királyságból származó árukat javasló jelentkezők vagy pályázók kizárásra kerülhetnek a közbeszerzési eljárásból.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Megjegyzések:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Legalább 30 naptári napnak kell eltelnie a jelen előzetes tájékoztató hirdetmény megjelenése és a vonatkozó ajánlati felhívás közzététele között.</P><P>Ezen időszak alatt jelentkezések benyújtásának, illetve információkérésnek nincs helye.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: PNPP - Laboratorijos įrangos ir šviesos gaudyklių, skirtų žvynelinės profilaktikai, tiekimas</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vieta – Turkija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IŠANKSTINIS INFORMACINIS SKELBIMAS APIE PREKIŲ PIRKIMO SUTARTĮ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nuoroda į publikaciją</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Atviras konkursas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programos pavadinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2015 m. metinė veiksmų programa, skirta Turkijai, pagal Pasirengimo narystei pagalbos priemonę (PNPP II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansavimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ES bendrojo biudžeto PNPP biudžeto išlaidų kategorija 22.02 03 02 (85 %) ir nacionalinis indėlis (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Perkančioji organizacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centrinis finansų ir sutarčių skyrius (CFSS)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turkija</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties apibūdinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Šios sutarties tikslas yra kontroliuoti žvynelinę ir užkirsti jai kelią užkrato pernešėjus sugaunant šviesos gaudyklėmis bei stiprinant Maisto, žemės ūkio ir gyvulininkystės ministerijos instituto laboratorijų gebėjimus virusų diagnostikos srityje teikiant laboratorinę įrangą.</P><P>Šios sutarties dalykas yra laboratorinės įrangos ir šviesos gaudyklių, skirtų žvynelinės kontrolei ir profilaktikai, tiekimas, pristatymas, perdavimas eksploatuoti, bandymai, patikrinimas, mokymai ir garantinės paslaugos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dalių skaičius ir pavadinimai</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tik 1 dalis: laboratorinė įranga ir šviesos gaudyklės.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatoma skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo data</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018 m. birželio mėn.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildoma informacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Netaikoma.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teisinis pagrindas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 236/2014, kuriuo nustatomos bendros Sąjungos išorės veiksmų finansavimo priemonių įgyvendinimo taisyklės ir procedūros, ir 11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 231/2014, kuriuo nustatoma Pasirengimo narystei paramos priemonė (PNPP II), OL L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11. (žr. Praktinio vadovo A2 priedą).</P><P>Atkreipkite dėmesį, kad Jungtinei Karalystei pasitraukus iš ES, ekonominės veiklos vykdytojų, įsisteigusių trečiosiose šalyse, ir trečiosiose šalyse pagamintų prekių prieigos prie ES pirkimo procedūrų taisyklės bus taikomos kandidatams arba konkurso dalyviams iš Jungtinės Karalystės bei visiems kandidatams arba konkurso dalyviams, siūlantiems prekes, pagamintas Jungtinėje Karalystėje, atsižvelgiant į derybų rezultatus. Jeigu tokia prieiga nebus suteikta galiojančiomis teisinėmis nuostatomis, kandidatai arba konkurso dalyviai iš Jungtinės Karalystės ir kandidatai arba konkurso dalyviai, siūlantys prekes, pagamintas Jungtinėje Karalystėje, gali būti pašalinti iš pirkimo procedūros.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Pastabos</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Nuo šio išankstinio informacinio skelbimo publikavimo iki atitinkamo skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo turi praeiti mažiausiai 30 kalendorinių dienų.</P><P>Šiuo etapu negalima siųsti paraiškų ar kreiptis dėl informacijos.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Laboratorijas aprīkojuma un gaismas slazdu piegāde nodulārā dermatīta (ND) kontrolei un novēršanai</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vieta – Turcija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IEPRIEKŠĒJS INFORMATĪVS PAZIŅOJUMS PAR PIEGĀŽU LĪGUMU</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsauce uz publikāciju</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Atklāta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmas nosaukums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2015. gada rīcības programma Turcijai Pirmspievienošanās palīdzības instrumenta (IPA II) ietvaros</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansējums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ES vispārējā budžeta IPA budžeta pozīcija 22.02 03 02 (85 %) un valsts ieguldījums (15 %)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centrālā finanšu un līgumu aģentūra (Central Finance and Contracts Unit – CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turcija</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Šī līguma mērķis ir kontrolēt un novērst ND, notverot slimības pārnēsātājus ar gaismas slazdiem un stiprinot Pārtikas, lauksaimniecības un lopkopības ministrijas institūta laboratoriju vīrusu diagnostikas spējas.</P><P>Šī līguma priekšmets ir ND kontrolei un novēršanai paredzēta laboratorijas aprīkojuma un gaismas slazdu sagāde, piegāde, nodošana ekspluatācijā, testēšana, pārbaude, lietotāju apmācība un garantijas pakalpojumi.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Provizoriskais daļu skaits un nosaukumi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tikai 1 daļa: laboratorijas aprīkojums un gaismas slazdi.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paziņojuma par līgumu paredzamais publicēšanas datums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018. gada jūnijs</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildu informācija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nav</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tiesiskais pamats</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 236/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko paredz kopīgus noteikumus un procedūras, lai īstenotu Savienības instrumentus ārējās darbības finansēšanai, un Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 231/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko izveido Pirmspievienošanās palīdzības instrumentu (IPA II) (OV L 77, 15.3.2014, 11. lpp.) – skatīt “Praktiskās rokasgrāmatas” A2 pielikumu.</P><P>Lūdzam ņemt vērā, ka pēc Apvienotās Karalistes izstāšanās no ES uz kandidātiem vai pretendentiem no Apvienotās Karalistes un kandidātiem vai pretendentiem, kuri piedāvā preces, kuru izcelsmes valsts ir Apvienotā Karaliste, atkarībā no sarunu iznākuma, attieksies noteikumi par trešo valstu uzņēmēju tiesībām piedalīties ES iepirkuma procedūrās un par precēm no trešām valstīm. Ja līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas brīdī spēkā esošajās tiesību normās šāda piekļuve nebūs paredzēta, kandidāti un pretendenti no Apvienotās Karalistes, kā arī kandidāti un pretendenti, kuri piedāvās preces no Apvienotās Karalistes, var tikt izslēgti no iepirkuma procedūras.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Piezīmes</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Starp šā iepriekšējā informatīvā paziņojuma un attiecīgā paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datumiem jāpaiet vismaz 30 kalendārajām dienām.</P><P>Šajā posmā nekādus pieteikumus vai informācijas pieprasījumus nesūtīt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: SGħQD - Provvista ta' Tagħmir tal-Laboratorju u Nases tad-Dawl għall-Kontroll u l-Prevenzjoni tal-Marda tal-Infafet fil-Ġilda (LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Il-post - it-Turkija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVIŻ TA' TAGĦRIF MINN QABEL DWAR KUNTRATT TA' PROVVISTI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-proċedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Miftuħa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-titlu tal-programm</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-programm annwali ta' azzjoni għat-Turkija għas-sena 2015 taħt l-Istrument għall-Assistenza ta' Qabel l-Adeżjoni (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-iffinanzjar</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-punt tal-baġit tal-IPA tat-22.02 03 02 tal-baġit ġenerali tal-UE (85 %) u l-kontribuzzjoni nazzjonali (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>it-Taqsima Ċentrali tal-Finanzi u l-Kuntratti (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, it-Turkija</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-deskrizzjoni tal-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Dan il-kuntratt għandu l-għan li jikkontrolla u jipprevjeni l-LSD permezz ta' vetturi li jaqbdu b'nases tad-dawl u t-tisħiħ tal-kapaċità tad-dijanjożi virali tal-Laboratorji tal-Istitut tal-Ministeru tal-Ikel, l-Agrikoltura u l-Bhejjem bit-tagħmir tal-laboratorju.</P><P>Is-suġġett ta' dan il-kuntratt huwa l-provvista, il-kunsinna, l-avvjament, l-ittestjar, l-ispezzjoni, it-taħriġ u s-servizzi ta' garanzija tat-tagħmir tal-laboratorju u tan-nases tad-dawl għall-kontroll u l-prevenzjoni tal-LSD.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>In-numru u t-titli indikattivi tal-Lottijiet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lott 1 biss: Tagħmir tal-laboratorju u nases tad-dawl.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Iż-żmien maħsub għall-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż dwar kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>f'Ġunju tal-2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif addizzjonali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mhux Applikabbli.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-bażi legali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 236/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi regoli u proċeduri komuni għall-implimentazzjoni tal-istrumenti tal-Unjoni għall-finanzjament tal-azzjoni esterna u r-Regolament (UE) Nru 231/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi Strument għall-Assistenza ta' Qabel l-Adeżjoni (IPA II), ĠU L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11. — Ara l-Anness A2 tal-Gwida Prattika.</P><P>Jekk jogħġbok kun af li wara l-irtirar tar-Renju Unit mill-UE, ir-regoli tal-aċċess għall-proċeduri ta' ksib tal-UE ta' operaturi ekonomiċi mwaqqfa f'pajjiżi terzi u ta' oġġetti li joriġinaw minn pajjiżi terzi se japplikaw għall-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit u għall-kandidati u dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti kollha li jipproponu oġġetti li joriġinaw mir-Renju Unit skont ir-riżultat tan-negozjati. F'każ li tali aċċess mhux ipprovdut minn dispożizzjonijiet legali fis-seħħ fil-ħin tal-għoti tal-kuntratt, il-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit, u kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti li jipproponu oġġetti li joriġinaw mir-Renju Unit jistgħu jiġu mwarrba mill-proċedura tal-ksib.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Kummenti:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Irid ikun hemm perijodu minimu ta' 30 jum kalendarju bejn il-pubblikazzjoni ta' dan l-avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel u l-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt li għandu x'jaqsam miegħu.</P><P>M'għandhomx jintbagħtu applikazzjonijiet jew talbiet għal tagħrif f'dan l-istadju.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Dostawa sprzętu laboratoryjnego i pułapek świetlnych do kontroli guzowatej choroby skóry bydła (LSD) i do jej zapobiegania</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokalizacja - Turcja</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Wstępne ogłoszenie informacyjne dotyczące zamówienia na dostawy</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numer referencyjny publikacji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Otwarta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nazwa programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Roczny program działania na rzecz Turcji na rok 2015 w ramach Instrumentu Pomocy Przedakcesyjnej (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansowanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Linia budżetowa IPA 22.02 03 02 budżetu ogólnego UE (85 %) oraz wkład krajowy (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Instytucja zamawiająca</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centralna Jednostka Finansująco-Kontraktująca (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turcja</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niniejsza umowa ma na celu kontrolę guzowatej choroby skóry bydła (LSD) jej zapobieganie poprzez zastosowanie pułapek świetlnych oraz wzmocnienie zdolności diagnostyki wirusowej w laboratoriach Instytutu Laboratoriów Ministerstwa Żywności, Rolnictwa i Zwierząt Gospodarskich z wyposażeniem laboratoryjnym.</P><P>Przedmiotem niniejszej umowy jest zapewnienie, dostawa, uruchomienie, testowanie, inspekcja, szkolenie i usługi gwarancyjne sprzętu laboratoryjnego i pułapek świetlnych do kontroli guzowatej choroby skóry bydła (LSD) i jej zapobiegania.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orientacyjna liczba i tytuły części</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tylko 1 część: sprzęt laboratoryjny i pułapki świetlne.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planowana data publikacji ogłoszenia o zamówieniu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>czerwiec 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacje dodatkowe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nie dotyczy.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Podstawa prawna</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 236/2014 z dnia 11.3.2014 ustanawiające wspólne zasady i procedury wdrażania unijnych instrumentów na rzecz finansowania działań zewnętrznych oraz rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 231/2014 z dnia 11.3.2014 ustanawiające Instrument Pomocy Przedakcesyjnej (IPA II), Dz. U. 77, 15.3.2014, s. 11 – zob. załącznik A2 do „Praktycznego przewodnika”.</P><P>Należy pamiętać, że po wystąpieniu Zjednoczonego Królestwa z Unii Europejskiej do kandydatów lub oferentów ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa oraz do wszystkich kandydatów lub oferentów oferujących towary pochodzące ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa – zależnie od wyniku negocjacji – mogą mieć zastosowanie zasady dostępu do unijnych procedur zamówień publicznych dla podmiotów gospodarczych z państw trzecich oraz względem towarów pochodzących z państw trzecich. W sytuacji gdy przepisy prawa obowiązujące w chwili udzielenia zamówienia nie będą przewidywać takiego dostępu, kandydaci lub oferenci ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa oraz kandydaci i oferenci oferujący towary pochodzące ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa mogą zostać wykluczeni z postępowania o udzielenie zamówienia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Uwagi:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Między publikacją niniejszego wstępnego ogłoszenia informacyjnego a publikacją odpowiedniego ogłoszenia o zamówieniu musi upłynąć co najmniej 30 dni kalendarzowych.</P><P>Na tym etapie nie należy przesyłać wniosków ani zapytań o informacje.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Dodávka laboratórnych zariadení a svetelných lapačov na kontrolu a prevenciu nodulárnej dermatitídy</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Miesto – Turecko</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDBEŽNÉ OZNÁMENIE O VYHLÁSENÍ VEREJNÉHO OBSTARÁVANIA TOVAROV</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčné číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Konanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verejná súťaž.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Názov programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ročný akčný program pre Turecko na rok 2015 v rámci nástroja predvstupovej pomoci (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zdroj financovania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozpočtová položka IPA 22.02 03 02 všeobecného rozpočtu EÚ (85 %) a národné spolufinancovanie (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verejný obstarávateľ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centrálne finančné a zmluvné oddelenie (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turecko</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cieľom tejto zmluvy je kontrolovať nodulárnu dermatitídu a predchádzať jej prostredníctvom odchytu prenášačov svetelnými pascami a posilňovaním spôsobilosti vírusovej diagnostiky laboratórií ústavov ministerstva potravinárstva, poľnohospodárstva a živočíšnej výroby za pomoci laboratórnych zariadení.</P><P>Predmetom tohto obstarávania je dodávka, doručenie, uvedenie do prevádzky, testovanie, kontrola, školenie a záručné služby týkajúce sa laboratórneho vybavenia a svetelných pascí na kontrolu a prevenciu nodulárnej dermatitídy.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predpokladaný počet a názvy častí</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Len 1 časť: laboratórne vybavenie a svetelné pasce.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plánovaný dátum zverejnenia oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Jún 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatočné informácie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Neuplatniteľné.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právny základ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 236/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovujú spoločné pravidlá a postupy pre vykonávanie nástrojov Únie na financovanie vonkajšej činnosti, a nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 231/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj predvstupovej pomoci (IPA II), Ú. v. EÚ L 77, 15.3.2014, s. 11 – pozri prílohu A2 praktickej príručky.</P><P>Upozorňujeme, že po vystúpení Spojeného kráľovstva z EÚ sa budú pravidlá prístupu hospodárskych subjektov z tretích krajín k verejným obstarávaniam EÚ a pravidlá o tovare pochádzajúcom z tretích krajín uplatňovať na všetkých uchádzačov alebo záujemcov ponúkajúcich tovar zo Spojeného kráľovstva, a to v závislosti od výsledku rokovaní. V prípade, že sa takýto prístup nezabezpečí ustanoveniami platnými v čase pridelenia zákazky, záujemcovia alebo uchádzači zo Spojeného kráľovstva, ako aj záujemcovia alebo uchádzači ponúkajúci tovar zo Spojeného kráľovstva by mohli byť vylúčení z obstarávacieho konania.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Medzi uverejnením predbežného oznámenia a uverejnením príslušného oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania musí uplynúť minimálne 30 kalendárnych dní.</P><P>V tomto období sa nemajú zasielať žiadne prihlášky ani žiadosti o informácie.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Dobava laboratorijske opreme in svetlobnih pasti za nadzor in preprečevanje vozličastega dermatitisa</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokacija – Turčija</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDHODNO INFORMATIVNO OBVESTILO O NAROČILU BLAGA</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčna številka dokumenta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postopek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Odprti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Letni akcijski program za Turčijo za leto 2015 v okviru instrumenta za predpristopno pomoč (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proračunska postavka IPA 22.02 03 02 splošnega proračuna EU (85 %) in nacionalno sofinanciranje (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Centralna enota za finance in javna naročila (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turčija</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>To naročilo zajema nadzor in preprečevanje vozličastega dermatitisa z zajemanjem vektorjev s svetlobnimi pastmi in krepitvijo zmogljivosti diagnosticiranja virusov v laboratorijih inštitutov Ministrstva za živila, kmetijstvo in živinorejo z laboratorijsko opremo.</P><P>Naročilo zajema dobavo, dostavo, zagon, preskušanje, pregledovanje, usposabljanje in garancijske storitve v zvezi z laboratorijsko opremo in svetlobnimi pastmi za nadzor in preprečevanje vozličastega dermatitisa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Okvirno število in naslovi sklopov</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Samo 1 sklop: laboratorijska oprema in svetlobne pasti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predvideni datum objave obvestila o naročilu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Junij 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ni navedeno.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravna podlaga</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uredba (EU) št. 236/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o določitvi skupnih pravil in postopkov za izvajanje instrumentov Unije za financiranje zunanjega delovanja in Uredba (EU) št. 231/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o vzpostavitvi instrumenta za predpristopno pomoč (IPA II), UL L 77, 15.3.2014, str. 11 – glejte Prilogo A2 k Praktičnemu vodiču.</P><P>Upoštevajte, da se bodo po izstopu Združenega kraljestva iz EU za kandidate ali ponudnike iz Združenega kraljestva in za vse kandidate ali ponudnike, ki ponujajo blago, ki izvira iz Združenega kraljestva, uporabljala pravila o dostopu do razpisnih postopkov EU, ki veljajo za gospodarske subjekte, ustanovljene v tretjih državah, in za blago, ki izvira iz tretjih držav, odvisno od rezultata pogajanj. V primeru, da v času oddaje naročila veljavne pravne določbe ne zagotavljajo tovrstnega dostopa, se lahko kandidatom ali ponudnikom iz Združenega kraljestva ter kandidatom ali ponudnikom, ki ponujajo blago, ki izvira iz Združenega kraljestva, sodelovanje v razpisnem postopku zavrne.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opombe:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Med objavo tega predhodnega informativnega obvestila in objavo ustreznega obvestila o naročilu mora preteči vsaj 30 koledarskih dni.</P><P>V tej fazi ne pošiljajte prijav ali zahtevkov za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Soláthar Trealaimh Shaotharlainne agus Gaistí Solais do Rialáil agus Cosc Ghalar an Chraicinn Chnapánaigh (LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Láthair - an Tuirc</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÓGRA RÉAMHAISNÉISE MAIDIR LE CONRADH SOLÁTHAIR</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nós imeachta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Oscailte.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teideal an chláir</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>An Clár Gníomhaíochta Bliantúil don Tuirc le haghaidh na bliana 2015 faoin Ionstraim um Chúnamh Réamhaontachais (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Maoiniú</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mír bhuiséid IPA 22.02 03 02 de bhuiséad ginearálta an AE (85 %) agus an cion tairbhe náisiúnta (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás conarthach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An Láraonad Airgeadais agus Conarthaí (CFCU - central finance and contracts unit)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Tuirc</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ar an gconradh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Is í aidhm an chonartha LSD a rialáil agus a chosc ach veicteoirí a sháinniú le gaistí solais agus cumas diagnóise víreasaí Institiúidí Saotharlainne na hAireachta Bia, Talmhaíochta agus Beostoic le trealamh saotharlainne a neartú.</P><P>Is é ábhar an chonartha seo soláthar, seachadadh, coimisiúnú, tástáil, imscrúdú, oiliúint agus seirbhísí baránta an trealaimh shaotharlainne agus na ngaistí solais do rialáil agus cosc LSD. </P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uimhir tháscach agus teidil na mbeart</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 bheart amháin: Trealamh saotharlainne agus gaistí solais.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>An sprioc atá beartaithe d'fhoilsiú an fhógra conartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Meitheamh 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis bhreise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Neamhbhainteach.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bunús dlí</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 236/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 ina leagtar síos rialacha agus nósanna imeachta comhchoiteanna le haghaidh cur chun feidhme ionstraimí an Aontais chun an ghníomhaíocht sheachtrach a mhaoiniú; agus Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 231/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 lena mbunaítear Ionstraim um Chúnamh Réamhaontachais (IPA II), IO L 77, 15.3.2014, lch. 11 — Féach Iarscríbhinn A2 den Treoir Phraiticiúil.</P><P>Tabhair faoi deara go gcuirfear na rialacha um rochtain ar nósanna imeachta soláthair an AE ag oibreoirí eacnamaíocha atá bunaithe i dtríú tíortha agus ag earraí ar tríú tíortha a ndéanta i bhfeidhm le hiarrthóirí nó tairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe agus le gach iarrthóir nó tairgeoir a mholann earraí arb í an Ríocht Aontaithe tír a ndéanta tar éis don Ríocht Aontaithe tarraingt siar ón AE, ag brath ar thorthaí na hidirbheartaíochta. Sa chás nach gcuirfear a leithéid de rochtain ar fáil trí fhorálacha dlíthiúla a bheidh i bhfeidhm nuair a dhámhfar an conradh, d'fhéadfaí diúltú d’iarrthóirí nó do thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe agus d’iarrthóirí nó do thairgeoirí a mholann earraí arb í an Ríocht Aontaithe tír a ndéanta ón nós imeachta soláthair.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Nótaí:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Ní mór tréimhse 30 lá féilire ar a laghad a bheith idir foilsiú an fhógra réamhaisnéise seo agus foilsiú an fhógra conartha chomhfhreagraigh.</P><P>Níor cheart aon iarratais ná iarrataí ar fhaisnéis a sheoladh faoi láthair.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Анкара: ИПП - Доставка на лабораторно оборудване и леки капани за контрол и превенция на заразен нодуларен дерматит (LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Местоположение — Турция</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ОБЯВЛЕНИЕ ЗА ПРЕДВАРИТЕЛНА ИНФОРМАЦИЯ ЗА ПОРЪЧКА ЗА ДОСТАВКА</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Референтен номер на публикация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Процедура</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Открита.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Заглавие на програма</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Годишна програма за действие за Турция за 2015 година по Инструмента за предприсъединителна помощ (ИПП II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Финансиране</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Бюджетна позиция на ИПП 22.02 03 02 от общия бюджет на ЕС (85 %) и национално участие (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Централно звено за финансиране и договориране (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Анкара</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Турция</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Описание на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Поръчката цели да контролира и предотвратява LSD чрез хващане на преносителите с леки капани и подсилване на капацитета за диагностика на вируса в лабораториите на института към Министерството на храните, селското стопанство и животновъдството чрез лабораторно оборудване.</P><P>Обектът на тази поръчка са придобиването, доставката, въвеждането в експлоатация, изпитването, обучението и гаранционните услуги за лабораторно оборудване и леки капани за контрол и превенция на LSD.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Брой и заглавия на обособени позиции</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Само 1 обособена позиция: Лабораторно оборудване и леки капани.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Очакван срок за публикуване на обявлението за поръчка</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>юни 2018 г.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Допълнителна информация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Не е приложимо.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Правно основание</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Регламент (ЕС) № 236/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за определяне на общи правила и процедури за изпълнението на инструментите на Съюза за финансиране на външната дейност и Регламент (ЕС) № 231/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за създаване на Инструмент за предприсъединителна помощ (ИПП II), ОB L 77, 15.3.2014 г., стр. 11 — вж. приложение A2 от Практическото ръководство.</P><P>Имайте предвид, че след оттеглянето на Обединеното кралство от ЕС правилата за достъп на икономически оператори до процедури за обществени поръчки на ЕС, установени в трети държави, и за стоки, чийто произход е от трети държави, ще се прилагат за кандидати или оференти от Обединеното кралство, и за всички кандидати или оференти, които предлагат стоки, чийто произход е от Обединеното кралство, в зависимост от резултата от преговорите. В случай че такъв достъп не е предвиден в действащите правни разпоредби, които са в сила по време на възлагането на поръчката, кандидатите или оферентите от Обединеното кралство, и кандидатите или оферентите, които предлагат стоки, чийто произход е от Обединеното кралство, могат да бъдат отхвърлени от процедурата за обществена поръчка.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Забележки:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Трябва да има минимален период от 30 календарни дни между публикуването на това обявление за предварителна информация и публикуването на съответното обявление за поръчка.</P><P>На този етап не трябва да се изпращат никакви молби или искания за информация.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Furnizarea de echipamente de laborator și capcane luminoase pentru controlul și prevenirea dermatitei nodulare (Lumpy Skin Disease - LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Locație – Turcia</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNȚ DE INTENȚIE PRIVIND UN CONTRACT DE ACHIZIȚII PUBLICE DE BUNURI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referința publicației</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedură</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Deschisă.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titlul programului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programul anual de acțiune pentru Turcia pentru anul 2015, în baza Instrumentului de asistență pentru preaderare (IPA II).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanțare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Articolul bugetar IPA 22.02 03 02 din bugetul general al UE (85%) și contribuție națională (15%).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea contractantă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unitatea centrală pentru finanțe și contracte (CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turcia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Acest contract vizează controlul și prevenirea LSD prin prinderea vectorilor cu capcane luminoase și consolidarea capacității de diagnosticare virale a Laboratoarelor Institutului din cadrul Ministerului Alimentației, Agriculturii și Zootehniei cu echipamente de laborator.</P><P>Obiectul acestui contract îl reprezintă serviciile de furnizare, livrare, punere în funcțiune, testare, inspecție, formare și garanție pentru echipamentele de laborator și capcanele luminoase pentru controlul și prevenirea LSD.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numărul indicativ și titlurile loturilor</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 singur lot: Echipamente de laborator și capcane luminoase.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevăzută de publicare a anunțului de participare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Iunie 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informații suplimentare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nu se aplică.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Temeiul juridic</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulamentul (UE) nr. 236/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de stabilire a normelor și procedurilor comune pentru punerea în aplicare a instrumentelor Uniunii pentru finanțarea acțiunii externe și Regulamentul (UE) nr. 231/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de instituire a unui instrument de asistență pentru preaderare (IPA II) JO L 77, 15.3.2014, p. 11 – a se vedea Anexa A2 la „Ghidul practic”.</P><P>A se avea în vedere că, după retragerea Regatului Unit din UE, normele de acces al operatorilor economici stabiliți în țări terțe la procedurile de achiziții publice ale UE și a bunurilor originare din țări terțe se vor aplica ofertanților sau candidaților din Regatul Unit și tuturor candidaților sau ofertanților care propun mărfuri originare din Regatul Unit în funcție de rezultatul negocierilor. În cazul în care accesul nu este prevăzut de dispozițiile juridice în vigoare la momentul atribuirii contractului, candidații sau ofertanții din Regatul Unit și candidații sau ofertanții care propun mărfuri originare din Regatul Unit, ar putea fi respinși de la procedura de achiziții publice.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observații:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Trebuie respectată o perioadă de minimum 30 de zile calendaristice între publicarea prezentului anunț de intenție și publicarea anunțului de participare corespunzător.</P><P>În această etapă nu se acceptă candidaturi sau cereri de informații.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>TR-Ankara: IPA - Nabava laboratorijske opreme i svjetlosnih klopki za kontrolu i prevenciju bolesti kvrgave kože (lumpy skin disease - LSD)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokacija – Turska</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Prethodna informacijska obavijest za ugovor o nabavi robe</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uputa na objavu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139620/IH/SUP/TR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postupak</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Otvoreni.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Godišnji akcijski program za Tursku u okviru Instrumenta pretpristupne pomoći (IPA II) za 2015.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IPA proračunska stavka 22.02 03 02 općeg proračuna EU-a (85 %) i nacionalni doprinos (15 %).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Središnji odjel za financiranje i ugovaranje (Central Finance and Contracts Unit — CFCU)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Ankara</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Turska</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cilj je ovog ugovora kontrola i prevencija bolesti kvrgave kože hvatanjem vektora svjetlosnim klopkama i jačanje kapaciteta za viralnu dijagnostiku laboratorija instituta Ministarstva hrane, poljoprivrede i stočarstva pomoću laboratorijske opreme.</P><P>Predmet ovog ugovora su usluge nabave, isporuke, puštanja u pogon, ispitivanja, inspekcije, osposobljavanja i jamstava laboratorijske opreme i svjetlosnih klopki radi kontrole i prevencije bolesti kvrgave kože.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Broj i nazivi grupa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Samo 1 grupa: laboratorijska oprema i svjetlosne klopke.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predviđeni datum objave poziva na nadmetanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>lipanj 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nije primjenjivo.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravni temelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uredba (EU) br. 236/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o utvrđivanju zajedničkih pravila i postupaka za provedbu instrumenata Unije za financiranje vanjskog djelovanja i Uredba (EU) br. 231/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014. o uspostavi Instrumenta pretpristupne pomoći (IPA II), SL L 77, 15.3.2014., str. 11. – vidjeti Prilog A2 Praktičnom vodiču.</P><P>Napominjemo da će se nakon izlaska Ujedinjene Kraljevine iz EU-a pravila pristupa postupcima javne nabave EU-a za gospodarske subjekte koji su osnovani u trećim zemljama i robu koja potječe iz trećih zemalja primjenjivati na natjecatelje ili ponuditelje iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine i sve natjecatelje ili ponuditelje koji nude robu koja potječe iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine ovisno o rezultatima pregovora. U slučaju da pristup nije omogućen putem pravnih odredbi koje su na snazi u vrijeme sklapanja ugovora, natjecatelji ili ponuditelji iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine i natjecatelji ili ponuditelji koji nude robu koja potječe iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine mogu biti odbijeni iz postupka javne nabave.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Napomene:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Između objave ove prethodne informacijske obavijesti i objave odgovarajućeg poziva na nadmetanje mora proći najmanje 30 kalendarskih dana.</P><P>U toj se fazi ne smiju slati prijave ili zahtjevi za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>