<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="063146-2018"
            EDITION="2018029">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-063902-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180312</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>29</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180210</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 029-063146</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:063146-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>www.hertfordshire.gov.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://www.supplyhertfordshire.uk</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="77314000">Grounds maintenance services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKH23">Hertfordshire</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKH23">Hertfordshire</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">8000000</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180208</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180312 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="3">Regional or local authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги по поддържане на други зелени площи</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Služby při údržbě pozemků</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Vedligeholdelse af arealer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Grundstückspflege</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες συντήρησης οικοπέδων</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Grounds maintenance services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de mantenimiento de terrenos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Maa-alade hooldusteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Maa-alueiden hoito</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services d'entretien de terrains</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Grounds maintenance services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge održavanja terena</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Rétfenntartási szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di manutenzione terreni</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Aikštelių priežiūros paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laukumu kopšanas pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi tal-manutenzjoni ta' l-artijiet</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Onderhoud van terreinen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi utrzymania gruntów</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de manutenção de terrenos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de întreţinere a terenurilor</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Údržba pozemkov</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve vzdrževanja zemljišč</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Hertford</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Markskötsel</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Hertfordshire County Council</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Hertfordshire County Council</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Pegs Lane</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Hertford</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>SG13 8DE</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Strategic Procurement Group</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+44 1707292464</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>chris.notley@hertfordshire.gov.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKH23"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.hertfordshire.gov.uk</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>www.supplyhertfordshire.uk</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>http://www.supplyhertfordshire.uk</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>http://www.supplyhertfordshire.uk</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="REGIONAL_AUTHORITY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>HCC Feb 2018  —  The Provision of a Grounds Maintenance Framework for Hertfordshire County Council</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>HCC1709937</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="77314000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Hertfordshire County Council (the ‘Council’) is currently out to procurement for the provision of a Grounds Framework Service. Further information in regards to this opportunity can be found in II.2.4) ‘Description of the Procurement’ field (OJEU Contract Notice refers). Organisations wishing to take part in this project are invited to "express interest" which will give access to the full procurement documents in the e-tendering system. Please see VI.3) Additional information for further information. Any questions relating to this procurement must be made via the correspondence area in the e-Tendering system, in accordance with the procurement documents and can be addressed to the main contact as shown in the details above.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">8000000</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="77314000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKH23"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Hertfordshire Business Services (hereinafter referred to as "HBS") the trading organisation of Hertfordshire County Council (hereinafter referred to as "the Council") is advertising its requirement to appoint competent and cost effective organisations to be part of its Grounds Maintenance Framework Agreement to provide general grounds maintenance services to sites throughout the County. This Contract will be utilised by all departments of the Council including establishments such as Schools, Fire Stations, Disused Sites, Day Centres, Libraries etc. It may also be used for works outside of the Council as requested by our partners and customers (this may be outside the geographical area of Hertfordshire in some cases). The estimated total value of the Framework Agreement is stated in II.1.5) of this notice and is for the initial term inclusive of the approximate value for extensions, together with the Call-Off Contracts and their possible durations. It is anticipated that the term of the Call-Off Contracts awarded under this Framework Agreement could be up to seven (7) years. For the avoidance of doubt, the estimated annual value of the Contract will be approximately between 1 500 000 and 2 000 000 GBP. The Framework Agreement will be awarded for a fixed period of four (4) years Please note that the contract requirements will be subject to available financial resources, supplier performance and flexibility to meet changing demands. There will be no form of exclusivity or volume that is guaranteed under the resultant Framework Agreement and the Council will be entitled to enter into other contracts and arrangements with other suppliers for the provision of any, or all, of the requirements which are the same as, or similar to those specified under the established Framework Agreement. Organisations should be aware that due to the nature of the Services provided, any Framework Agreement formed as a result of this procurement process shall be executed as a deed. Organisations should seek independent legal advice on the implications of this prior to submitting their bid, where appropriate. Please Note the TUPE Staffing Information for this procurement will be provided at each Call-Off off where applicable. Due to the requirements of the Service carried out, the Council will not be splitting this Framework into Lots Please Note The TUPE Staffing Information for this procurement will be provided along with other documentation at each Call-Off for this procurement. TUPE related information must be treated as protected data in accordance with the requirements of the Data Protection Act 1998 and must be kept confidential. By clicking on the View Details button and accessing the documentation for this procurement, Tenderers agree:</P>
                  <P>a) To undertake to treat the information as confidential and commercially sensitive at all times and take all reasonable steps to prevent any inadvertent disclosure to any third party;</P>
                  <P>b) That under no circumstances will any of the information be disclosed by your organisation or your personnel to any third party without the Council’s prior consent in writing;</P>
                  <P>c) That the information supplied will be stored securely and destroyed or returned to the Council, after your Organisation’s bid has been submitted or you decide not to proceed with a tender submission;</P>
                  <P>d) That you will indemnify the Council for any losses, arising from your breach or breach by any of your personnel of these confidentiality requirements specified above and data protection requirements in relation to TUPE Staffing Information;</P>
                  <P>e) The requirements above apply whether the supplier uploads a tender response to this procurement or not.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">8000000</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">48</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <FRAMEWORK>
               <SEVERAL_OPERATORS/>
               <NB_PARTICIPANTS>8</NB_PARTICIPANTS>
               <JUSTIFICATION>N/A</JUSTIFICATION>
            </FRAMEWORK>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-03-12</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">6</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-03-12</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Please note Hertfordshire County Council has worked closely with its districts and partners to create a joint procurement portal called supply Hertfordshire. This portal provides an e-Tendering system which is run by In-Tend. To access this procurement opportunity please visit www.supplyhertfordshire.uk and follow the on-screen guidance. In accordance with Regulation 53 of The Public Contracts Regulations 2015, the Council's procurement documents are available within the e-Tendering system. This is a one stage procurement process. Therefore, if you wish to be considered as a tenderer you must complete and submit a tender by the specified closing date and time. Tender submissions cannot be uploaded after this return deadline. If you are experiencing problems In-Tend offer a help section which includes a dedicated UK support desk which can be contacted via email: support@in-tend.com or Telephone: +44 1144070065 for any website/technical questions, Monday to Friday, 8:30-17:30. The Council reserves the right at any time to cease the procurement process and not award a Framework Agreement or to award only part of the opportunity described in this notice. If the Council takes up this right, then they will not be responsible for or pay the expenses or losses, which may be incurred by any organisation or tenderer as a result. The Council undertakes to hold confidential any information provided in the proposal submitted, subject to the Council's obligations under the law including the Freedom of Information Act 2000. If the organisation considers that any of the information submitted in the proposal should not be disclosed because of its sensitivity then this should be stated with the reason for considering it sensitive. The Council will then endeavour to consult with the applicant about such sensitive information when considering any request received under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 before replying to such a request. The Council reserves the right to carry out additional financial checks on all organisations bidding for this opportunity at any time during the procurement process. This is to ensure that they continue to meet the Council's requirements and remain financially viable to fulfil the requirements under the Framework Agreement.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>N/A</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>N/A</TOWN>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>The Contracting Authority will incorporate a minimum 10 calendar day (when using electronic means) standstill period at the point information on the award of the Framework Agreement is communicated to tenderers. This period allows unsuccessful tenderers to challenge the decision to award a Framework Agreement before a contract is executed/signed (as appropriate). The Public Contracts Regulations 2015 (‘Regulations’) provide for aggrieved parties who have been harmed or at risk of harm by a breach of the rules to take action in the High Court (England, Wales and Northern Ireland). Any such action must be brought promptly and within the time limits as defined in the above regulations. Where a Framework Agreement has not been entered into the court may order the setting aside of the award decision or order the contracting authority to amend any document and may award damages. If the Framework Agreement has been entered into the court has the options to award damages and/or to shorten or order the Framework Agreement ineffective.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>High Court, Royal Courts of Justice</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>The Strand</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Hertford</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>WC2A 2LL</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-08</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
