<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="063225-2018"
            EDITION="2018029">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-062606-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180313</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>29</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180210</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 029-063225</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:063225-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DE"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.fms-wm.de</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://www.fms-wm.de/en/tenders</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="72268000">Software supply services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="72263000">Software implementation services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="DE21H">München, Landkreis</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="DE212">München, Kreisfreie Stadt</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="EUR">250000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180208</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180313 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="8">Other</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="B">Competitive procedure with negotiation</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="F">Economic and financial affairs</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Гepмaния</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Мюнхен</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги по доставка на софтуерни продукти</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Německo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Mnichov</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dodávka programového vybavení</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Tyskland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Levering af programmel</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Deutschland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Bereitstellung von Software</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Γερμανία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Μόναχο</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες προμήθειας λογισμικού</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Germany</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Software supply services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Alemania</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Múnich</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de suministro de software</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Saksamaa</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tarkvara tarnimisteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Saksa</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ohjelmiston toimituspalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Allemagne</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de fourniture de logiciels</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ghearmáin, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Software supply services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Njemačka</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge dobave programske podrške</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Németország</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Szoftverellátási szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Germania</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Monaco di Baviera</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di fornitura di software</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Vokietija, VFR</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Miunchenas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Programinės įrangos tiekimo paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Vācija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Minhene</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Programmatūras piegādes pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>il-Ġermanja</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi tal-forniment tas-software</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Duitsland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Leveren van software</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Niemcy</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Monachium</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi dostawy oprogramowania</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Alemanha</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Munique</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de fornecimento de software</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Germania</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de furnizare de software</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Nemecko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Mníchov</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dodávky softvéru</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Nemčija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve oskrbe s programsko opremo</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Tyskland</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tillhandahållande av programvara</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">FMS Wertmanagement AöR</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>FMS Wertmanagement AöR</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Prinzregentenstraße 56</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>München</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>80538</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DE"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Pia Spranz</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+49 899547627232</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>ausschreibung@fms-wm.de</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+49 8995476277232</FAX>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DE212"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.fms-wm.de</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>http://www.fms-wm.de/en/tenders</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE_OTHER>Öffentlicher Auftraggeber nach §99 Nr.2 GWB</CA_TYPE_OTHER>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="ECONOMIC_AND_FINANCIAL_AFFAIRS"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Market Data Management Software Solution</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="72268000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The contracting authority intends to implement a market data management software solution for the management and administration of market data licences, vendors / services, users and costs including reporting of use, users, costs, invoicing, actuals, forecasts, budgets.</P>
               <P>The system shall support all tasks related to the daily business of a market data manager at the contracting authority.</P>
               <P>The main goal is to have and maintain complete transparency of the market data landscape. The main functions needed are reporting, admin/controlling, management of market data licenses / contracts and costs.</P>
               <P>The system, while being a web-based, hosted solution, has to meet modern security standards. It is expected that the implementation / initial filling of the database be performed by the vendor of the product.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">250000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72268000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72263000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DE21H"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>FMS Wertmanagement Service GmbH.</P>
                  <P>Freisinger Str. 11,</P>
                  <P>85716 Unterschleißheim,</P>
                  <P>Germany.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>FMS Wertmanagement AöR (hereinafter: "FMS-WM") is an organizationally and economically independent institution under public law with partial legal capacity within the Financial Market Stabilization Authority (FMSA) in Germany.</P>
                  <P>As of 1.10.2010, FMS-WM assumed risk positions and non-strategic divisions from Hypo Real Estate Holding AG and its direct and indirect subsidiaries and SPEs in Germany and abroad (collectively the HRE group) for the purpose of ultimately stabilizing the HRE group and the financial market and will settle these in accordance with economic principles.</P>
                  <P>FMS Wertmanagement Service GmbH (FMS-SG), a wholly-owned subsidiary of FMS-WM, operates as a service provider for FMS-WM for its portfolio and the associated refinancing resources.</P>
                  <P>These include the three segments:</P>
                  <P>— Asset Management,</P>
                  <P>— Finance, and,</P>
                  <P>— Risk and Operations.</P>
                  <P>It is a specialist financial servicing company with about 350 employees in three locations:</P>
                  <P>— Munich,</P>
                  <P>— Dublin, and,</P>
                  <P>— New York.</P>
                  <P>FMS-SG provides services in connection with loans, bonds, and derivatives in the sectors real estate, infrastructure and project finance, public finance, asset finance and structured products. The services provided for FMS-WM comprise credit analysis and review, asset restructuring, workout management, detailed portfolio reporting, payment collection and arrears monitoring.</P>
                  <P>FMS-SG assumed management of the portfolio of FMS-WM on 1.10.2013. One of its branches is at the Dublin location from where it performs a part of the servicing.</P>
                  <P>The present invitation to tender is organized by FMS-WM on behalf of FMS Group.</P>
                  <P>FMS-WM intends to implement a market data management software solution for the management and administration of market data licenses, vendors / services, users and costs including reporting of use, users, costs, invoicing, actuals, forecasts, budgets etc. The system shall support all tasks related to the daily Business of a market data Manager at the contracting authority.</P>
                  <P>The main goal is to have and maintain complete transparency of all market data services, users etc. (market data landscape). The main functions needed are reporting and admin / controlling functions such as invoice reconciliation for various departments and purposes. With respect to reporting it is expected that a wide range of standardized reports is available as well as the ability for power users to customize reports to their needs.</P>
                  <P>Finally, the market data management software solution has to ensure an easy and transparent management of market data licenses / contracts and costs. The system, while being a web-based, hosted solution, has to meet modern security standards. It is expected that the implementation / initial filling of the database be performed by the vendor of the product.</P>
                  <P>The required market data management software solution has to meet as a minimum the technical specification according to Procurement document B (“Technical specification”), freely available on:</P>
                  <P>— http://www.fms-wm.de/en/tenders.</P>
                  <P>The mandatory services listed in Procurement document B (“Technical specification”) will become part of the contract as a minimum specification.</P>
                  <P>For detailed information on the contract award procedure please refer to the procurement documents which are freely available at the following link:</P>
                  <P>— http://www.fms-wm.de/en/tenders and to figure III.1.1) to III.1.3) of this European-wide notice.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="EUR">250000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">36</DURATION>
               <RENEWAL/>
               <RENEWAL_DESCR>
                  <P>The minimum term of the contract will be 3 years with a yearly option for termination after 3 years.</P>
               </RENEWAL_DESCR>
               <NB_MIN_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>3</NB_MIN_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>5</NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>The first step of the contract Award procedure consists in an application of participation. Interested parties need to fill out the procurement documents indicated in this notice and in the tender documents which are freely available at the following link:</P>
                  <P>— http://www.fms-wm.de/en/tenders</P>
                  <P>FMS-WM will then choose from the applicants those who will receive a request for quotation. These companies will be invited to submit a fist offer which constitutes the basis for negotiations. However, the contracting authority reserves the right to award the contract on the basis of the first round of offers, without entering into negotiations (§ 17, para. 11 VgV).</P>
                  <P>The contracting authority will review the applications according to § 56 and 57 VgV after they have been received and opened. The rating is performed in accordance with the suitability criteria presented in Section III.1.1), III.1.2) and III.1.3) of this notice and the required declarations and documents submitted by the applicant. The submission of the requested declarations and supporting documents is mandatory.</P>
                  <P>The suitability will be checked according to the formal requirements and the compliance with the minimum criteria. Applications that do not comply with the requirements and minimum criteria will be excluded from the award procedure.</P>
                  <P>If more than three applicants have submitted all mandatory documents and declarations and fulfill the minimum criteria and are therefore qualified as suitable, the contracting authority may determine the best-qualified applicants according to additional criteria.</P>
                  <P>The criteria are the total net revenue of the applicant generated by the offered market data management software solution in the financial years 2016, 2015 and 2014 and the references in the financial services industry where the specific market data management software solution of the applicant has been implemented.</P>
                  <P>The criteria for differentiating rating of suitability are evaluated in accordance with the following method:</P>
                  <P>— each criterion (revenue, reference quality) is rated individually per applicant with valuation points:</P>
                  <P>— — 10: Very good,</P>
                  <P>— — 7: Good,</P>
                  <P>— — 3: Satisfactory, and,</P>
                  <P>— — 0: Not satisfactory.</P>
                  <P>— each criterion carries a weight of 50% of total rating.</P>
                  <P>The revenue over the financial years 2016, 2015, 2014) will be rated for each year according to revenue spans:</P>
                  <P>— &gt; EUR 5 000 000,00 - 10p,</P>
                  <P>— EUR 1 000 000,00 - EUR 4 999 000,00 - 7p,</P>
                  <P>— EUR 501 000 - EUR 999 000 - 5p,</P>
                  <P>— &lt;/= EUR 500 000 - 0p.</P>
                  <P>The individually achieved performance points will be added together.</P>
                  <P>The reference quality will be evaluated according to the degree of comparability to the scope of this tender and the industry relevance:</P>
                  <P>— completely comparable - 10p,</P>
                  <P>— nearly comparable - 7p,</P>
                  <P>— partially comparable - 5p,</P>
                  <P>— not comparable - 0p.</P>
                  <P>For every individual reference, max. 10 performance points can be achieved. The individually achieved performance points will be added together. The weighted performance points will be added for each applicant and a ranking will be determined.</P>
                  <P>A minimum of 3 (three) applicants and a maximum of 5 (five) applicants with the highest score in performance points will be asked to submit an offer (step 2 - Request for quotation).</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>Additional optional requirements will be specified during, the contract award procedure (step 2: Request for quotation, please refer to section 3.4).</P>
                  <P>The optional requirements concern the following topics:</P>
                  <P>— “Reporting”,</P>
                  <P>— “Invoicing / Accounting / Cost allocation”,</P>
                  <P>— “Contracts, Analytics and Interfaces”,</P>
                  <P>— “Support”,</P>
                  <P>— “Product properties”, and,</P>
                  <P>— “Initial Filling/Implementation”:</P>
                  <P>Reporting capabilities:</P>
                  <P>— the range of standard reports and the ability to set up customized reports.</P>
                  <P>Ability to manage budgets and invoices:</P>
                  <P>— ability to create budgets based on underlying contract criteria (e.g. incorporating price increases) and to create reports comparing budgeted and historical figures,</P>
                  <P>— the capability to automatically reconcile invoices and to create a list of on-going contract obligations.</P>
                  <P>Interfaces:</P>
                  <P>— availability of interfaces on different levels, access to different entitlement systems and vendor invoice/customer portals.</P>
                  <P>Support:</P>
                  <P>— reliability of the system and quality of the help desk and error handling.</P>
                  <P>General Product Properties:</P>
                  <P>— availability of calendar functions (e.g. contract/invoice calendar) and the ability to manage diverse kinds of licenses and contracts,</P>
                  <P>— the opportunity to include further data in customized fields and the ability to set filters in the software solution.</P>
                  <P>Initial Filling / Implementation:</P>
                  <P>— Project Management to effect a high-quality implementation including initial data filling and concrete conceptualization of the implementation.</P>
                  <P>For detailed information please refer to the procurement documents which are freely available in the internet link http://www.fms-wm.de/en/tenders.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>The contract will be awarded to a reliable, capable and expert (suitable) company, (cf. § 122 GWB). The criteria for expertise, capability, and reliability must be proven by submitting the following declarations and documents.</P>
               <P>The submission of the requested declarations and supporting documents is mandatory. Failure to provide them will, subject to an optional subsequent request by the contracting authority, result in exclusion from the award procedure.</P>
               <P>The following declarations and supporting documents must be submitted:</P>
               <P>— Written Application Cover Letter,</P>
               <P>— information about the applicant and, if applicable, the consortium of applicants: information on the company or the companies participating in the consortium of applicants (name, legal form, address, contact person),</P>
               <P>— in the case of a consortium of applicants: Self-Declaration by the members of the consortium on the power of representation of the consortium and joint liability (where applicable),</P>
               <P>— in the case that the applicant and, if relevant, the consortium of applicants, would like to engage subcontractors - Self-declaration if and for which services subcontractors or other third parties would be contracted. In this case, the application for participation must contain indications concerning the subcontractors or third parties and their scope of services. In addition, a letter of intent of the subcontractor or third party must be submitted (where applicable),</P>
               <P>— self-declaration on reliability and independence and on the absence of grounds for exclusion refere to §§ 123, 124 GWB. In the case of sub-contraction, the sub-contractors must also submit this declaration,</P>
               <P>— self-declaration on data protection and self-declaration on conflicting interests,</P>
               <P>— self-declaration on the fulfillment of the mandatory services listed in Procurement document B: “Technical Specification”.</P>
               <P>— current certificate of commercial registration (Germany) or equivalent documentation (other countries) (please provide a copy of the document),</P>
               <P>— Procurement Document D - Non-disclosure Agreement.</P>
               <P>— — a complete list of the documents to be submitted with the application for participation can be found in the overview of documents/supporting document list to be submitted (see Procurement document C - “Form sheets” Form C0), freely available at the following link: http://www.fms-wm.de/en/tenders. This list also contains the documents to be submitted by consortia of applicants.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>Self-declaration on the total net revenue of the applicant in the field of the scope of this awarding procedure in the financial years 2016, 2015, 2014.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Minimum requirement:</P>
               <P>— the total net revenue of the applicant generated by the offered market data management software solution needs to be at least 500 000,00 EUR for each financial year in the financial years 2016, 2015, 2014,</P>
               <P>— revenues indicated by each individual member of a consortium will be consolidated.</P>
               <P>Revenues of subcontractors or other third companies will only be counted if a letter of intent of the respective subcontractor or other third company is submitted.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>— certification of the applicant in accordance with ISO 27001 (IT Security Standard and Procedures). In case of a consortium of applicants, the certification of at least 2 members of the consortium is mandatory in order to minimise the risk resulting from the departure of one applicant leaving the consortium (please provide copy of the certification documents),</P>
               <P>— self-declaration on company references in the financial services industry running the market data management software solution of the applicant and the respective net revenue put into effect with these reference clients in the financial years 2016 and 2015.</P>
               <P>A maximum of 5 references is allowed. If more than 5 references are provided, the first 5 references in sequence will be taken into account. The references and respective revenues indicated by each individual member of a consortium will be consolidated.</P>
               <P>Clients of subcontractors or other third companies will only be counted if a letter of intent of the respective subcontractor or other third company is submitted.</P>
               <P>Reference clients may be contacted by the contracting authority in the course of the awarding procedure.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>Minimum requirement:</P>
               <P>— at least one (1) reference in the financial services industry where the market data management software solution of the applicant has been implemented,</P>
               <P>— the net revenue with each single reference client needs to amount to at least 250 000,00 EUR for each of the financial years 2016 and 2015.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_COMPETITIVE_NEGOTIATION/>
            <REDUCTION_RECOURSE/>
            <RIGHT_CONTRACT_INITIAL_TENDERS/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-03-13</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>2018-03-20</DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DATE_TENDER_VALID>2018-08-31</DATE_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <EORDERING/>
            <EINVOICING/>
            <EPAYMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>For a complete List of formal requirements please refer to the procurement documents (Procurement Document A - Procedural conditions) which are available for free download on the Homepage of the FMS-WM at the following link:</P>
               <P>— http://www.fms-wm.de/en/tenders</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Bundeskartellamt | Vergabekammer des Bundes</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Villemomblerstraße 76</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bonn</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>53123</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DE"/>
               <PHONE>+49 22894990</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>vk@bundeskartellamt.bund.de</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+49 2289499163</FAX>
               <URL>http://www.bundeskartellamt.de</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>The contracting authority refers, in particular, to § 160 para. 3, no. 1 GWB.</P>
               <P>Under this act, an application for review is only admissible if that application is made within 10 (ten) calendar days after becoming aware of the violation of public procurement provisions during the award procedure.</P>
               <P>Breaches that become apparent from the EU Notice or the procurement documents must, at the latest, be indicated to the contracting authority by the end of the period for the submission of a tender or application specified in the notice (§ 160 para. 3, no. 2 and 3 GWB).</P>
               <P>If the contracting authority gives notice that it is unwilling to redress the complaint, the application for a review proceeding may be submitted in writing to the public procurement tribunal only within 15 (fifteen) calendar days of receipt of such notice (§ 160 para. 3, no. 4 GWB) - in this context the date of receipt of the application for a review proceeding by the public procurement tribunal will be decisive in determining whether the time limit has been observed.</P>
               <P>The contracting authority understands that the award criteria open leeway in terms of the assessment exercised by the contracting authority. However, the assessment will be exercised to the best knowledge and belief, in an impartial, transparent and non-discriminatory way. The contracting authority considers the selected criteria, their description, including the requirements for the content of the applications and the related notes on the assessment method as compliant with the public procurement law, also in light of recent cases regarding the requirements of the tender evaluation (in particular the Higher Regional Court of Dusseldorf decision of 21.10.2015 (VII-Verg 28/14) and the decision of 16.12.2015 (VII-Verg 25/15)). We point out that there is a duty of reprimand notice following § 160 para. 3 GWB.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Bundeskartellamt | Vergabekammer des Bundes</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Villemomblerstraße 76</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bonn</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>53123</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DE"/>
               <PHONE>+49 22894990</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>vk@bundeskartellamt.bund.de</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+49 2289499163</FAX>
               <URL>http://www.bundeskartellamt.de</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-08</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
