<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="030343-2018"
            EDITION="2018015">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-030638-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180328</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>15</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180123</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 015-030343</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:030343-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>www.contracts.mod.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>www.contracts.mod.uk</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="80650000">Training and simulation in aircrafts, missiles and spacecrafts</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKJ14">Oxfordshire</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKK15">Wiltshire CC</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">150000</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180119</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180328 10:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01B02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Тренировка и симулация със самолети, ракети и космически кораби</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Školení a simulace v oblasti letadel, raket a kosmických lodí</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Uddannelse og simulering — luftfartøjer, missiler og rumfartøjer</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Schulung und Simulation für Luftfahrzeuge, Raketen und Raumfahrzeuge</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Επιμόρφωση και προσομοίωση σε αεροσκάφη, πυραύλους και διαστημόπλοια</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Training and simulation in aircrafts, missiles and spacecrafts</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Formación y simulación en materia de aeronaves, misiles y naves espaciales</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sõjaväe õhusõidukite, rakettide ja kosmosesõidukite alane koolitus ja simulatsioonid</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ilma-aluksiin, ohjuksiin ja avaruusaluksiin liittyvä koulutus ja simulointi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Formation et simulation dans le domaines des aéronefs, des missiles et des spationefs militaires</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Training and simulation in aircrafts, missiles and spacecrafts</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Izobrazba i simulacija u području letjelica, raketa i svemirskih letjelica</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Repülőgépekkel, rakétákkal és űrhajókkal kapcsolatos képzés és szimulációs gyakorlat</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Formazione e simulazione in materia di velivoli militari, missili e velivoli spaziali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Mokymo naudotis karo orlaiviais, raketomis, erdvėlaiviais ir imitavimo paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Mācības un simulācija gaisa kuģu, raķešu un kosmosa kuģu jomā</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Taħriġ u simulazzjoni fl-ajruplani, il-missilli u l-vetturi spazjali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Opleiding en simulatie met lucht- en ruimtevaartuigen en raketten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Szkolenie i symulacja w zakresie samolotów, rakiet (pocisków rakietowych) i statków kosmicznych</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Formação e simulação em aeronaves, mísseis e naves espaciais militares</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Formare profesională şi simulare în domeniul aeronavelor militare, al proiectilelor şi al navelor spaţiale</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Školenia a simulácie v oblasti lietadiel, rakiet a vesmírnych lodí</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usposabljanje in simulacije na zrakoplovih, raketah in vesoljskih plovilih</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>High Wycombe</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Utbildning och simulering: luftfartyg, robotar och rymdfarkoster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C,</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C,</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Nimrod Building, 3 Site, RAF High Wycombe</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>High Wycombe</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>HP14 4UE</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <E_MAIL>simon.bratchell643@mod.gov.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK15"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.contracts.mod.uk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>www.contracts.mod.uk</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="MINISTRY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Provision of Advanced Rigging Services to the Robson Parachute Centre</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>ACT/04613</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="80650000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SUPPLIES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Provision of Advanced Rigger Services to the Robson Parachute Centre Weston on the Green (RPC(W)) to cover period 1 May 2018 to 30 September 2020 with a further 2 x 1-year options, 1 October 2020 to 30 September 2021 and 1 October 2021 to 30 September 2022.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">150000</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKJ14"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Oxfordshire</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Force Development and Adventurous Training (AT) is one of the cornerstones of personal and professional development within the Armed Forces with parachuting being one of the recognized AT activities. With an RAF member currently unable to support AT parachute rigging activities at the Robson Parachuting Centre Weston on the Green (RPC(W)), the service of an Advanced Rigger will be required. These services will have to be conducted in accordance with the relevant regulations, these being; the British Parachute Association (BPA) and the Civil Aviation Authority (CAA).</P>
                  <P>The parachute season will cover the period from February to mid-December annually.</P>
                  <P>Requirement.</P>
                  <P>The requirement is for a contract to include the core period commencing 1 May 2018 to 30 September 2020, with a further 2 x 1-year options, 1 October 2020 to 30 September 2021 and 1 October 2021 to 30 September 2022. The contract services required will comprise:</P>
                  <P>(RPC(W).</P>
                  <P>— provision for a full-time Advanced Rigger required for an average of 37 hours per week,</P>
                  <P>— the Rigger must hold a BPA Advanced Rigger qualification and additional qualifications, either as a CSI or AFFI are highly desirable,</P>
                  <P>— the Advanced Rigger will need to temporarily support the delivery of JSAT activity at alternative locations for up to 4 weeks at a time, these locations may not be limited to within the UK but would be limited to Europe and could include Germany, Spain, and Cyprus. When contract employees are required to work away from RPC (W) in support of the contracting activity, food and accommodation will be paid for or provided by the Authority - this will be the same standard as received by military staff,</P>
                  <P>— the Advanced Rigger will be expected to assist with instruction and participate in staff training as a CSI/AFFI and coach in a relevant discipline.</P>
                  <P>Cyber Security:</P>
                  <P>The Cyber Essentials DCPP (Defence Cyber Protection Partnership) internet-based Cyber Security Model Risk Assessment has been completed by the RAF User (the Customer), thus the Cyber Risk of this requirement is classified as Very Low. If your company is subsequently invited to tender then your tender must include the completion of the ‘Supplier Assurance Questionnaire’ via the internet based DCPP Cyber Security Model online link:</P>
                  <P>— https://suppliercyberprotection.service.xgov.uk/.</P>
                  <P>This is to demonstrate a supplier’s compliance with the required cyber risk level.</P>
                  <P>More information will be published with regards to this process, the evaluation criteria and how to access the information/website once the tender documentation is live and you have been invited to tender.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">150000</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DATE_START>2018-05-01</DATE_START>
               <DATE_END>2020-09-30</DATE_END>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NB_MIN_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>2</NB_MIN_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>6</NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>The Authority will use the PQQ response to create a shortlist of Tenders who are eligible to participate; fulfill any minimum economic, financial, professional and technical standards, and best meet in terms of capacity and capability the selection criteria set out in this PQQ. Full details of the method of choosing the Tenders are set out in the PQQ.</P>
                  <P>It is the intention to down select to between approximately 2 and 6 highest scoring suppliers who will be invited to Tender, providing they meet the overall percentage pass mark of 60 %, do not score any lower than 2 points and receive a pass in any pass/fail questions within the PQQ. If the supplier scores below 2 in any of the questions or receives a fail in a pass/fail question then they will automatically fail the evaluation and will not be invited to participate any further.</P>
                  <P>Suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P>
                  <P>The information and/or documents for this opportunity are available on www.contracts.mod.uk.</P>
                  <P>— you must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password.</P>
                  <P>— please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P>
                  <P>— suppliers must log in, go to the Response Manager and add the following Access Code: D57M76U98M.</P>
                  <P>— please ensure you follow any instruction provided to you.</P>
                  <P>— the deadline for submitting your responses is 19 February 2018, 10:00.</P>
                  <P>— please ensure that you allow yourself plenty of time when responding to this invite prior to the closing date and time, especially if you have been asked to upload documents.</P>
                  <P>If you experience any difficulties please refer to the online Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ's) or the User Guides or contact the MOD DCO Helpdesk by:</P>
                  <P>— email: support@contracts.mod.uk</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>2 x 1-year options, 1 October 2020 to 30 September 2021 and 1 October 2021 to 30 September 2022</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>As detailed in the DPQQ (Dynamic Pre-Qualification Questionnaire.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>As stated in the PQQ.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>The estimated annual contract value is £35,000. If the estimated annual contract value is greater than 40 % of the supplier’s turnover, the Authority reserves the right to exclude the supplier from being selected to tender except where the supplier provides, to the satisfaction of the Authority, evidence showing it has sufficient economic and financial capability, e.g. such evidence should include, either:</P>
               <P>1) the last 2 years of certified audited accounts or</P>
               <P>2) a statement of overall turnover, an indemnity, guarantee or bank bond.</P>
               <P>A financial assessment will be undertaken on the supplier’s financial status. An overall pass/fail judgment will be made after considering areas such as turnover, profit, net assets, liquidity, gearing, and capacity.</P>
               <P>This assessment will include the Parent company where applicable.</P>
               <P>An independent financial assessment obtained from a reputable credit rating organization could be utilized as part of this process.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Electronic Trading:</P>
               <P>Potential suppliers must note the mandatory requirement for electronic trading using the Contracting, Purchasing, and Finance (CP&amp;F) electronic procurement tool.</P>
               <P>All payments for Contractor Deliverables under the Contract shall only be made via CP&amp;F. You can find details on CP&amp;F at:</P>
               <P>— https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/mod-contracting-purchasing-and-finance-e-procurement-system.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_RESTRICTED/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-03-28</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">3</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <EINVOICING/>
            <EPAYMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The contracting authority considers that this contract may be suitable for economic operators that are small or medium enterprises (SMEs). However, any selection of tenderers will be based solely on the criteria set out for the procurement.</P>
               <P>The Authority reserves the right to amend any condition related to security of information to reflect any changes in national law or government policy. If any contract documents are accompanied by instructions on safeguarding classified information (e.g. a Security Aspects Letter), the Authority reserves the right to amend the terms of these instructions to reflect any changes in national law or government policy, whether in respect of the applicable protective marking scheme, specific protective markings given, the aspects to which any protective marking applies, or otherwise.</P>
               <P>The link below to the Gov.uk website provides information on the Government Security Classification:</P>
               <P>— https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/government-security-classifications</P>
               <P>Advertising Regime OJEU:</P>
               <P>— this contract opportunity is published in the Official Journal of the European Union (OJEU), the MoD Defence Contracts Bulletin and www.contracts.mod.uk.</P>
               <P>— suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P>
               <P>— the information and/or documents for this opportunity are available on:</P>
               <P>— — http://www.contracts.mod.uk</P>
               <P>— — you must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password.</P>
               <P>— — please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P>
               <P>— suppliers must log in, go to your Response Manager and add the following Access Code: D57M76U98M.</P>
               <P>— please ensure you follow any instruction provided to you here.</P>
               <P>— — the deadline for submitting your responses is detailed within this contract notice, you will also have visibility of the deadline date, once you have added the Access code via DCO as the opening and closing date is visible within the opportunity.</P>
               <P>Please ensure that you allow yourself plenty of time when responding to this opportunity prior to the closing date and time, especially if you have been asked to upload documents.</P>
               <P>— — if you experience any difficulties please refer to the online Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ&#x92;s) or the User Guides or contact the MOD DCO Helpdesk by:</P>
               <P>— — — email: support@contracts.mod.uk,</P>
               <P>— — — telephone: 0800 282 324.</P>
               <P>GO Reference: GO-2018119-DCB-11756215.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, C&amp;C,</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Nimrod Building, No. 3 Site, RAF High Wycombe</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>High Wycombe</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>HP14 4UE</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1494494356</PHONE>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-01-19</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
