<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="030739-2018"
            EDITION="2018015">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-030967-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180223</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>15</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180123</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 015-030739</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:030739-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.guilsborough.northants.sch.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://www.litmuspartnership.co.uk/project/guilsborough_academy</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="55524000">School catering services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKF2">Leicestershire, Rutland and Northamptonshire</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKF2">Leicestershire, Rutland and Northamptonshire</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">1480000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180119</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180223 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="6">Body governed by public law</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="L">Education</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Приготвяне и доставяне на храна за ученически столове и бюфети</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Zabezpečování pohostinských služeb pro školy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Catering til skoler</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Verpflegungsdienste für Schulen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες τροφοδοσίας σχολείων με έτοιμα γεύματα</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>School catering services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de suministro de comidas para escuelas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kooli toitlustusteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kouluateriapalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Service traiteur pour écoles</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>School catering services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge dostavljanja pripremljene hrane (catering) u škole</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Iskolai élelmezési szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di ristorazione scolastica</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pagaminto valgio tiekimo mokykloms paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Skolas ēdināšanas pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi tal-preżentazzjoni ta’ l-ikel għall-iskejjel</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Catering voor scholen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi dostarczania posiłków do szkół</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de fornecimento de refeições (catering) a escolas</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de catering pentru şcoli</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Služby hromadného stravovania pre školy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve priprave in dostave hrane za šole</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Guilsborough</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Skolbespisning</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Guilsborough Academy</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Guilsborough Academy</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>West Haddon Road</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Guilsborough</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>NN6 8QE</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 1276-673880</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>pqq@litmuspartnership.co.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKF2"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.guilsborough.northants.sch.uk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>http://www.litmuspartnership.co.uk/project/guilsborough_academy</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="BODY_PUBLIC"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="EDUCATION"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Guilsborough Academy — Tender for Catering Services</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="55524000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The successful supplier will be required to provide catering services at Guilsborough Academy.</P>
               <P>Guilsborough Academy is a secondary school situated in the rural village of Guilsborough on the Northamptonshire/Leicestershire border. The school converted to academy status in 2011 and formed a Multi Academy Trust with Naseby Church of England Primary Academy in 2014. We believe that learning should be enjoyable and challenging. This belief, combined with the excellent teaching skills and commitment of our staff and the enthusiasm and hard work of our students, lies at the heart of our success.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">1480000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKF2"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Guilsborough Academy.</P>
                  <P>Northamptonshire.</P>
                  <P>United Kingdom.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The tender project is seeking to appoint a supplier whose initiative and innovation will be welcomed for the provision of service within the existing facilities for the 1338 students on roll and 134 teaching and support staff, with a focus on exciting new food concepts to satisfy a wide range of pupil tastes and dietary requirements. The client would wish the successful supplier to review the current range of services offered and make recommendations accordingly.</P>
                  <P>The contract being tendered is for 3 years in duration from 1 August 2018 to 31 July 2021 and will operate as a guaranteed performance contract, with the successful supplier offering the client a guaranteed return/cost per annum for the provision of catering services. Sovereignty of the cash tariff is to remain with the client for the duration of this contract.</P>
                  <P>The academic year is based on a calendar of 195 days. Five days are to be used for staff professional development which means that school will be open to receive students for the legal minimum of 190 days.</P>
                  <P>The contract offered covers the scope for the provision of all school catering services, which currently includes morning break, lunch, all hospitality and free issue requirements. Free school meals and hospitality will be charged based on consumption, with free meals at a margin and hospitality at net food cost.</P>
                  <P>Whilst the client prioritises value for money as a key objective of the competitive tender process, the governing body is not obliged to accept the lowest price.</P>
                  <P>The client expects the successful supplier to enable the continued development of catering through the provision of an innovative, healthy food service, with fresh, seasonal, locally sourced ingredients being prepared on-site. The client expects the successful supplier to evidence, through their bid, how they shall support and complement its values and support the principles of Every Child Matters.</P>
                  <P>The client believes that success should be celebrated and that pupils should enjoy their time at school; if lessons are stimulating and challenging, then students will love learning. Much time, therefore, is spent reviewing and planning schemes of work to ensure that they are differentiated to meet the needs of all students. As a result, the client is very enthusiastic regarding work experience and apprenticeship proposals and would welcome the input of the successful supplier.</P>
                  <P>As a school who are continually seeking ways to improve and develop the ethos and environment for students and staff, to give them the facilities they deserve and need to meet the challenges of the 21st Century, any consideration regarding inward capital investment as part of the supplier’s tender submission would be welcomed. The client would wish for the supplier to look at making this investment within the existing dining area.</P>
                  <P>Please be advised that:</P>
                  <P>1) This contract will be let on a 3 + 2 years basis;</P>
                  <P>2) There are currently 11 staff employed to deliver the catering service;</P>
                  <P>3) There are no current catering staff in the LGPS;</P>
                  <P>4) The catering service is currently contracted to Chartwells who are part of the Compass Group;</P>
                  <P>5) Guilsborough Academy is part of a Multi-Academy Trust of 2 schools at this present time; however, the number of schools in the Trust may increase. Although this tender process is for Guilsborough Academy, any other schools in the Trust (whether currently in the Trust or that may join over the course of the contract being let) may join this contract at the Trust’s discretion;</P>
                  <P>6) Please be advised that the client will only accept bids with a guaranteed return to the school per annum.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">1480000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DATE_START>2018-08-01</DATE_START>
               <DATE_END>2023-07-31</DATE_END>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NB_MIN_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>5</NB_MIN_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>10</NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>A minimum of 5 suppliers and a maximum of 10 suppliers will be taken forward to the tender stage of the process. Where less than 5 suppliers meet the minimum standards, only those that meet the minimum standards will be taken through to the tender stage. Where more than 5 suppliers meet the minimum standard, those suppliers with the highest scores will proceed to the tender stage.</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_RESTRICTED/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-02-23</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>2018-04-06</DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Interest in the selection process should be expressed via email only to pqq@litmuspartnership.co.uk clearly stating within this email which contract/notice you are referring to. Please also provide, as a minimum, a contact name, full company postal address and telephone number.</P>
               <P>The Selection Questionnaire and associated documents can be obtained at: http://www.litmuspartnership.co.uk/project/guilsborough_academy</P>
               <P>The closing date for receipt of the Selection Questionnaire is 23.2.2018 (12:00). Suppliers are required to ensure that documents are obtained and returned to The Litmus Partnership Limited, by email to pqq@litmuspartnership.co.uk by the above closing date and time.</P>
               <P>Documents in respect of economic/financial standing (where indicated in the Selection Questionnaire) shall be returned to The Litmus Partnership Limited, by email to pqq@litmuspartnership.co.uk by the above closing date and time.</P>
               <P>It will be the supplier's responsibility to obtain any necessary documents in order to submit a response by the closing date and time.</P>
               <P>The contracting authority reserves the right not to award any or part of the contract which is the subject of this contract notice and reserves the right to terminate the procurement process at any time.</P>
               <P>The contracting authority will not be liable for any costs incurred by those expressing an interest in tendering for this contract opportunity.</P>
               <P>The contracting authority will consider variant bids, evaluating them (so far as the variant or the evaluation of the variant is in the opinion of the contracting authority practicable) on the same basis as a conforming bid, but shall not be obliged to accept any such bid in preference to a conforming bid even if the variant bid scores more highly. No variant will be considered unless the bidder simultaneously submits a conforming bid.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Guilsborough Academy</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Guilsborough</TOWN>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-01-19</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
