<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="030715-2018"
            EDITION="2018015">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-030924-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20190119</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>15</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180123</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 015-030715</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:030715-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>www.networkrail.co.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="73000000">Research and development services and related consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UK">UNITED KINGDOM</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UK">UNITED KINGDOM</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">7000000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180119</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="8">Other</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="8">Other</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C01</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Лондон</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Научни изследвания и експериментални разработки и свързаните с тях консултантски услуги</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londýn</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Výzkum a vývoj a související služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Forsknings- og udviklingsvirksomhed og hermed beslægtet konsulentvirksomhed</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Forschungs- und Entwicklungsdienste und zugehörige Beratung</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Λονδίνο</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες έρευνας και ανάπτυξης, καθώς και συναφείς υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Research and development services and related consultancy services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londres</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de investigación y desarrollo y servicios de consultoría conexos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Uurimis- ja arendusteenused ja seonduvad nõustamisteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Lontoo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tutkimus- ja kehityspalvelut ja niihin liittyvät konsulttipalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londres</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de recherche et développement et services de conseil connexes</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londain</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Research and development services and related consultancy services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge na području istraživanja i razvoja i s tim povezane usluge savjetovanja</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Kutatási és fejlesztési szolgáltatások és kapcsolódó tanácsadói szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londra</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di ricerca e sviluppo nonché servizi di consulenza affini</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londonas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Mokslinių tyrimų ir taikomosios veiklos paslaugos bei su jomis susijusios konsultacinės paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londona</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pētniecības un izstrādes pakalpojumi un saistītie konsultāciju pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londra</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' riċerka u żvilupp u servizzi relatati mal-konsulenza</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Onderzoek en ontwikkeling, en aanverwante adviezen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londyn</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi badawcze i eksperymentalno-rozwojowe oraz pokrewne usługi doradcze</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londres</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de investigação e desenvolvimento e serviços de consultoria conexos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londra</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de cercetare şi de dezvoltare şi servicii conexe de consultanţă</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londýn</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Výskum a vývoj a súvisiace poradenské služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve na področju raziskav in razvoja ter s tem povezane svetovalne storitve</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>FoU-tjänster samt tillhörande konsulttjänster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Network Rail Infrastructure Limited</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F01_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F01" LG="EN">
         <NOTICE TYPE="PRI_ONLY"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Network Rail Infrastructure Limited</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>1 Eversholt Street, London</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>London</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>NW1 2DN</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Patrick Benjuya</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+44 7515621206</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>patrick.benjuya@networkrai.co.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UK"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.networkrail.co.uk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE_OTHER>Railway Infrastructure Operator</CA_TYPE_OTHER>
            <CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>Transport</CA_ACTIVITY_OTHER>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>The formation of a Digital Railway Joint Development Group (JDG)</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="73000000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>DRP seeks to build a Joint Development Group (JDG) - a community of suppliers with a range and breadth of skills, capabilities, and competencies that are called upon to support digital railway project development activities.</P>
               <P>A lead delivery partner will be required to manage and operate the JDG and their primary objective will be to connect the right capability from the supplier community to work with the Digital Railway project teams on particular problem statements and other project development activities. This procurement is the lead delivery partner role only.</P>
               <P>It should be noted that the majority of the estimated value described herein is likely to materialize through the work of the community of suppliers in the resources and capabilities provided to the DRP in working through project development activities.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">7000000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UK"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>NR offices, London (and others)/Supplier's own office.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Having considered various procurement options and reference models, DRP seeks to appoint a lead delivery partner who will manage and operate the JDG. In practical terms this means engaging, as necessary, a community of suppliers to collaboratively work alongside project teams on early stage digital railway project deliverables.</P>
                  <P>NR intends to publish an OJEU Notice in Quarter 1 2018 to seek interested suppliers in tendering for the delivery partner opportunity. Interested suppliers will be requested to submit their expression of interest by responding to a PQQ which will be issued at the same time and as part of the OJEU Notice.</P>
                  <P>Publication of the OJEU notice will be supported with supplier engagement sessions to support a transparent and consistent understanding of required outcomes, strategic approach to delivery and the supplier selection process.</P>
                  <P>The PQQ process will follow the NR corporate pre-qualification criteria and will place emphasis on supplier’s experience and the ability to provide the professional services required in establishing an appropriate mechanism for managing and appointing specialist services and resources from the supplier community to work on DR problem statements/early GRIP deliverables to successful outcomes.</P>
                  <P>The aim of the PQQ evaluation will be to establish an ITT list of 4 potential delivery partners; subject to supply market appetite and capability.</P>
                  <P>An ITT will be issued to short-listed suppliers. Included will be standard DR contractual documents as well as evaluation details based on declared criteria, weightings and evaluation methodologies.</P>
                  <P>Negotiation Stage – this step in the process will benchmark all major bid elements and provide appropriate feedback to bidders.</P>
                  <P>This will enable clarification of any incorrect assumptions and give suppliers the opportunity to update bids in the light of such clarification. All suppliers will be treated equally and given all the required information to formulate their bids in a transparent manner, ensuring full OJEU compliance and demonstrating optimum value for money.</P>
                  <P>Appointment Stage - a preferred supply/delivery partner will be selected.</P>
                  <P>All suppliers will be informed of the decision in the normal manner.</P>
                  <P>NB - Total estimated value (notional estimate) c£7,000,000, is for a lead delivery partner over a 5 year period (this procurement is for the appointment of the lead delivery partner to undertake the core management of the Joint Development Group).</P>
                  <P>Total value through the proposed JDG arrangement is estimated at c£35,000,000 over 5 years. However, this value includes all the services expected to be procured by the JDG (via the supplier community and the delivery partner) of which only the above notional estimate will be awarded to the lead delivery partner.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>We would like to create a single point of contact with each interested organization for all JDG related matters.</P>
                  <P>Should you wish to participate in this procurement, please email your intent to jointdevelopmentgroup@networkrail.co.uk, and include the relevant contact details.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>2018-03-30</DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>DRP has undertaken a study to develop the concept of a Joint Development Group (JDG) to help meet digital railway deployment needs. The JDG will be an open and collaborative model whereby a community of suppliers, managed by a lead delivery partner is called upon to support, in general, digital railway problem statements.</P>
               <P>To efficiently operate this model the JDG will create a single contracting mechanism with equal terms and conditions for the entire supplier community. In practice, this means each individual supplier will engage under the same contract terms with the lead delivery partner. This will allow the JDG to efficiently unlock the right skills, capabilities, and competencies from the community of suppliers to work with the digital railway project teams. Whilst we are measuring interest to join the supplier community, this procurement is specifically concerned with appointing a lead delivery partner and not, at this point in time, engagement with the downstream supplier community.</P>
               <P>Role of the Lead Delivery Partner:</P>
               <P>— the lead delivery partner will manage the operations of the JDG and will occupy many of the positions within the JDG core management team. Thus, the capability required from a lead delivery partner will predominately be enabling functions like the commercial, finance, resourcing, and planning.</P>
               <P>— depending on the final capability requirements, the lead delivery partner may also need a level of technical competence, the exact remit is still under development. However, most importantly, the core management team has the critical task of connecting resources from the supplier community and appointing the relevant supplier to work with Digital Railway project teams.</P>
               <P>Supplier Community:</P>
               <P>— this communication is for the appointment of a lead delivery partner however the JDG also needs a community of suppliers to effectively operate.</P>
               <P>— if suppliers do not wish to compete for the lead delivery partner role, they are still encouraged to join the supplier community. Equally, if a supplier wishes to compete for the lead delivery partner role their organization can also still join the supplier community; one is not precluded from the other.</P>
               <P>— DRP will be engaging with suppliers in early 2018 to help define the uniform terms and conditions of membership. See the draft proposed Supply Chain Engagement timeline below.</P>
               <P>The proposed supplier engagement timeline for the lead delivery partner procurement is as described below:</P>
               <P>— the procurement for the delivery partner will be completed through an OJEU process and the contract duration will include the time from contract award through to the remainder of Control Period 5 and for all of Control Period 6.</P>
               <P>— the form of contract will likely be a Network Rail 3 services contract with bespoke terms and conditions as may be required.</P>
               <P>Supply Chain Engagement Timeline:</P>
               <P>— in making the proposed JDG model a success DRP requires the endorsement and buy-in from suppliers and the rail industry to be successful. Whilst a reference operating model exists, DRP would like to test this with the supplier community and ensure the final model has been developed collaboratively, transparently and to best advantage DRP and its industry partners.</P>
               <P>— DRP will be running a series of workshops to support this objective prior to calling for competition.</P>
               <P>Indicative Supplier Engagement dates:</P>
               <P>—  31/01/18: Teleconference Briefing:</P>
               <P>Purpose: To inform suppliers of the JDG implementation plan, field initial questions and capture any comments or concerns for inclusion/discussion in future workshops.</P>
               <P>— 07/02/18: Operating Model Workshop:</P>
               <P>Purpose: To work through the operating model, address known challenges or concerns and agree to possible solutions with suppliers.</P>
               <P>— 14/02/18: Procurement and Commercial Workshop (Provisional):</P>
               <P>Purpose: To agree, the engagement principles, discuss terms and conditions and work through the contractual mechanism likely to be used between the lead delivery partner and community of suppliers.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-01-19</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F01_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
