<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="129471-2018" EDITION="2018059"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-120285-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20190314</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>59</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180324</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 059-129471</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129471-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>FR</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="70000000">Real estate services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180314</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>EC301</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Informationsmeddelelse rettet mod ejendomsmarkedet — flerårige prognoser for Europa-Kommissionens ejendomsbehov i Bruxelles (2020-2024) og prospektering af det lokale marked</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bekanntmachung einer Information für den Immobilienmarkt — Schätzung des mehrjährigen Gebäudebedarfs der Europäischen Kommission in Brüssel für die Jahre 2020 bis 2024 und Akquisition des örtlichen Marktes</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussels</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Information notice for the property market - Forecasts of multiannual property requirements for the years 2020 to 2024 for the European Commission in Brussels and prospecting of the local market</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anuncio de información destinado al mercado inmobiliario; previsión de las necesidades inmobiliarias plurianuales correspondientes al período de 2020-2024 para la Comisión Europea en Bruselas y prospección del mercado local</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Kiinteistömarkkinoille osoitettu tiedonanto – monivuotiset ennakkoarviot (vuodet 2020–2024) Euroopan komission Brysselin kiinteistötarpeista sekä paikallinen kiinteistömarkkinakartoitus</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Belgique</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Avis d'information à l'attention du marché immobilier — Prévisions des besoins immobiliers pluriannuels pour les années 2020 à 2024 pour la Commission européenne à Bruxelles et prospection du marché local</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Βέλγιο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ενημερωτική κοινοποίηση υπόψη της αγοράς ακινήτων — Προβλέψεις πολυετών αναγκών στον τομέα των ακινήτων για τα έτη 2020 έως 2024 για την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή στις Βρυξέλλες και διερεύνηση της τοπικής αγοράς</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Belgio</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Avviso di informazione rivolto al mercato immobiliare — previsioni delle esigenze immobiliari pluriennali della Commissione europea a Bruxelles per gli anni dal 2020 al 2024 e indagine sul mercato locale</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>België</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Kennisgeving van informatie voor de vastgoedmarkt — Raming van de meerjarige vastgoedbehoeften voor de jaren 2020-2024 voor de Europese Commissie in Brussel en prospectie van de lokale markt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anúncio de informação à atenção do mercado imobiliário — Previsões das necessidades imobiliárias plurianuais para o período de 2020-2024 para a Comissão Europeia em Bruxelas e prospeção do mercado local</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Meddelande med information till fastighetsmarknaden – prognos för Europeiska kommissionens fleråriga fastighetsbehov i Bryssel och undersökning av den lokala marknaden (2020–2024)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Belgie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Oznámení určené trhu s nemovitostmi – Předběžné oznámení o víceleté potřebě služeb v oblasti nemovitostí v letech 2020 až 2024, které budou poskytovány Evropské komisi v Bruselu, včetně průzkumu místního trhu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Kinnisvaraturule suunatud teade – mitmeaastased prognoosid Euroopa Komisjoni kinnisvaranõudluse kohta Brüsselis (2020–2024) ja kohaliku turu uurimine</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüsszel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tájékoztató felhívás az ingatlanpiac számára – többéves előrejelzések az Európai Bizottság brüsszeli ingatlanok iránti igényei kapcsán (2020–2024), valamint a helyi piac felmérése</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Briuselis</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Informacinis pranešimas dėl nekilnojamojo turto rinkos – Europos Komisijos Briuselyje daugiametės nekilnojamojo turto poreikių prognozės nuo 2020 iki 2024 m. ir vietos rinkos žvalgymas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Beļģija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brisele</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Informatīvs paziņojums nekustamā īpašuma tirgum – daudzgadu prognozes (2020.–2024. gadam) par Eiropas Komisijas ar nekustamo īpašumu saistītajām vajadzībām Briselē un vietējā tirgus izpēte</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Belġju</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussell</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Avviż ta' tagħrif għall-attenzjoni tas-suq tal-proprjetà — tbassir multiannwali għal ħtiġijiet tal-proprjetà tal-Kummissjoni Ewropea fi Brussell (mill-2020 sal-2024) u l-istħarriġ tas-suq lokali</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruksela</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ogłoszenie informacyjne skierowane do sektora nieruchomości — szacunki dotyczące wieloletnich potrzeb lokalowych Komisji Europejskiej w Brukseli w latach 2020–2024 oraz rozpoznanie rynku lokalnego</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Belgicko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Informačné oznámenie do pozornosti trhu s nehnuteľnosťami – Prognózy viacročných potrieb Európskej komisie týkajúcich sa nehnuteľností v Bruseli na obdobie rokov 2020 – 2024 a prieskum miestneho trhu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselj</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Informativno obvestilo v vednost trgu nepremičnin – Večletne napovedi potreb Evropske komisije po nepremičninah v Bruslju za leta 2020–2024 in povpraševanje za lokalni nepremičninski trg</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Bheilg, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Fógra faisnéise don mhargadh maoine - Réamhaisnéisí de riachtanais mhaoine ilbhliantúla do na blianta 2020 chuig 2024 don Choimisiún Eorpach sa Bhruiséil agus cuardach sa mhargadh áitiúil</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бeлгия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Брюксел</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Информационно обявление на вниманието на пазара за недвижима собственост – многогодишна прогноза за изискванията за собственост на Европейската комисия в Брюксел (2020–2024) и проучване на местния пазар</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anunț de informare în atenția pieței imobiliare – Previziuni multianuale privind necesitățile imobiliare ale Comisiei Europene în Bruxelles pentru perioada 2020 - 2024 și prospectarea pieței locale</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Informacijska obavijest na pažnju tržištu nekretnina — višegodišnje prognoze potreba za nekretninama u razdoblju od 2020. do 2024. za Europsku komisiju u Bruxellesu te predviđanja lokalnog tržišta</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Europa-Kommissionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Kommission</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Commission</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">Comisión Europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan komissio</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Commission européenne</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Commissione europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europese Commissie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">Comissão Europeia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska kommissionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská komise</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Komisjon</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Európai Bizottság</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos Komisija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Komisija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">Il-Kummissjoni Ewropea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Komisja Europejska</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európska komisia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska komisija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An Coimisiún Eorpach</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейска комисия</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Comisia Europeană</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska komisija</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Informationsmeddelelse rettet mod ejendomsmarkedet — flerårige prognoser for Europa-Kommissionens ejendomsbehov i Bruxelles (2020-2024) og prospektering af det lokale marked</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Den ansvarlige afdeling ved Europa-Kommissionen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europa-Kommissionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 — 09/P001, cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien. E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Websted: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Almindelige oplysninger:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>I overensstemmelse med Kommissionens meddelelse KOM(2007) 501 af 5.9.2007 er formålet med denne meddelelse at oplyse aktører på ejendomsmarkedet samt andre interesserede parter om prognoserne for Europa-Kommissionens ejendomsbehov i Bruxelles og at indsamle informationer om projekter og fast ejendom på et afgrænset område.</P><P>Ønskede bygninger</P><P>For at imødekomme sit behov for kontorfaciliteter i tidshorisonten 2020-2024 leder Europa-Kommissionen efter kontorarealer i Bruxelles, der er beliggende, enten</P><P>— højst 700 m fra aksen på strækningen mellem metrostationen Mérode og metrostationen Arts-Loi og mellem metrostationen Arts-Loi og metrostationen De Brouckère,</P><P>— eller højst 700 m fra aksen mellem metrostationen Arts-Loi og metrostationen Rogier,</P><P>— eller højst 700 m fra aksen mellem metrostationen Delta og metrostationen Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>For at erstatte saneringsklare bygninger eller bygninger, hvis lejekontrakt snart udløber, skal det ønskede areal uden kælder være på mellem 80 000 m{^&gt;2&lt;^} og 150 000 m{^&gt;2&lt;^} for perioden 2020-2024. De faktiske behov afhænger blandt andet af resultatet af igangværende eller fremtidige forhandlinger angående fornyelse af kontrakter, der udløber i de kommende år for en vis række bygninger, der bruges af Kommissionens tjenester.</P><P>De bygninger, der kan imødekomme disse behov, skal hver have et overjordisk bruttoareal på mindst 10 000 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}. Bygningerne skal helt og udelukkende bruges af Kommissionens tjenester og/eller af andre tjenester</P><P>ved de europæiske institutioner og fællesskabsorganer. Der er tale om brugsretsaftaler og/eller senere købsaftaler.</P><P>De ønskede bygninger skal helst være færdige eller blive færdige i den nærmeste fremtid. Der kan dog foreslås projekter, som i givet fald kan prospekteres på et senere tidspunkt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Målet for ejendomssøgningen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Søgningens formål er at indsamle forslag til kontorbygninger, der kan imødekomme Kommissionens behov inden for det område, der beskrives i punkt 2 ovenfor.</P><P>Til dette formål bedes ejere eller disses bemyndigede repræsentanter om at udfylde forslagsskemaet i delen »kontrakter og offentlige indkøb — Bekendtgørelse om ejendomssøgning» på webstedet anført i punkt 1.</P><P>Det garanteres, at de modtagne informationer bliver behandlet med fortrolighed. Forslagsskemaerne bliver dernæst lagret i en beskyttet database, hvortil kun godkendte ansatte ved Europa-Kommissionen har adgang.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Anvendelse af de indsamlede informationer</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De indsamlede informationer, der lagres i databasen, bliver anvendt af Kommissionen til at udpege de bygninger, der kan imødekomme dens behov for kontorarealer.</P><P>OIB-kontoret henvender sig derefter til ejerne af de udpegede bygninger for at opnå detaljerede oplysninger om bygningens stand og kapaciteter samt de mere præcise finansielle vilkår.</P><P>Hvis Kommissionen på baggrund af de detaljerede oplysninger vurderer, at de relevante bygninger faktisk kan imødekomme dens behov, kan en procedure med forhandling igangsættes med ejeren eller ejerne af de udpegede bygninger i overenstemmelse med artikel 134 i forordning (EU, Euratom) nr. 1268/2012 om gennemførelsesbestemmelserne til forordning (EU, Euratom) nr. 966/2012.</P><P>Denne bekendtgørelse er på ingen måde bindende for Kommissionen, hvad angår kontrakttildelingsprocedurer.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indgivelse af forslagsskemaer</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De underskrevne og daterede forslagsskemaer skal indgives af ejerne eller af disses bemyndigede repræsentanter inden (30 arbejdsdage efter bekendtgørelsen) kl. 16.30.</P><P>Oplysningerne skal fremsendes på 1 af følgende måder:</P><P>— enten pr. post, som rekommanderet forsendelse, i hvilket tilfælde poststemplets dato er gyldig, til følgende adresse: Europa-Kommissionen, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgien,</P><P>— eller ved aflevering (personligt eller ved en repræsentant for ansøgeren eller pr. kurertjeneste) til følgende adresse: Europa-Kommissionen, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgien. Denne afdeling er åben 8.00-16.30 mandag til torsdag og 8.00-16.00 fredag, undtagen på Kommissionens fridage.</P><P>For leveringer med kurer vil den gyldige afsendelsesdato være datoen på kurerens følgeseddel. Vedrørende leveringer, der sker personligt eller via en hvilken som helst repræsentant, vil leveringen af forslaget i dette tilfælde blive bekræftet ved udstedelsen af en dateret kvittering, underskrevet af den tjenestemand i Kommissionens centrale posttjeneste, som har modtaget dokumenterne.</P><P>Under alle omstændigheder skal ejeren eller dennes repræsentant overholde følgende formaliteter:</P><P>— forslagsskemaet skal sendes i to kuverter,</P><P>— begge kuverter skal forsegles,</P><P>— den inderste kuvert skal foruden adressen på den relevante afdeling mærkes med «avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles«, «fiche de prospection de (navnet på ejeren eller dennes repræsentant)«, »à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courrier«,</P><P>— selvlukkende kuverter skal forsegles med tape, hvorpå afsenderen skal sætte sin underskrift,</P><P>— hvis ejeren eller dennes repræsentant ønsker at bede om yderligere oplysninger før datoen for indgivelse af forslagene, skal anmodningen sendes udelukkende per e-mail til den adresse, der er anført i punkt 1 ovenfor. Forslagsstillere opfordres endvidere til jævnligt at besøge webstedet anført i punkt 1, da det er her, stillede spørgsmål og Kommissionens svar løbende offentliggøres.</P><P>— sidste frist for indsendelse af spørgsmål er (10 arbejdsdage før tidsfristen) kl. 16.00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: Bekanntmachung einer Information für den Immobilienmarkt — Schätzung des mehrjährigen Gebäudebedarfs der Europäischen Kommission in Brüssel für die Jahre 2020 bis 2024 und Akquisition des örtlichen Marktes</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zuständige Abteilung der Europäischen Kommission:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Kommission</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Immobilienverwaltung, Büro: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien, E-Mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Website </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Allgemeine Informationen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Gemäß der Mitteilung der Kommission vom 5.9.2007 (KOM(2007) 501) soll diese Bekanntmachung die Akteure des Immobilienmarktes und alle sonstigen interessierten Parteien über den geschätzten Gebäudebedarf der Europäischen Kommission in Brüssel informieren sowie Informationen über Projekte und Immobilien in einem bestimmten Umkreis einholen.</P><P>Gesuchte Immobilien</P><P>Um den Bedürfnissen nach Büroräumen für den Zeitraum 2020-2024 gerecht zu werden, ist die Europäische Kommission auf der Suche nach Bürofläche in Brüssel in folgender Lage,</P><P>— höchstens 700 Meter von der Achse zwischen den Metrostationen Mérode und Arts-Loi sowie zwischen den Metrostationen Arts-Loi und De Brouckère,</P><P>— oder höchstens 700 Meter von der Achse zwischen den Metrostationen Arts-Loi und Rogier</P><P>— oder höchstens 700 Meter von der Achse zwischen den Metrostationen Delta und Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Die gesuchte oberirdische Nutzungsfläche zur Ersetzung von Immobilien am Ende ihres Lebenszyklus oder deren Mietvertrag ausläuft umfasst während des Zeitraums 2020-2024 zwischen 80 000 m <FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> und 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Die tatsächlichen Bedürfnisse hängen besonders vom Ergebnis der laufenden oder noch zu führenden Verhandlungen hinsichtlich der Erneuerung der in den nächsten Jahren auslaufenden Konventionen für eine bestimmte Anzahl Immobilien ab, die für Dienstleistungen der Kommission genutzt werden.</P><P>Die gesuchten Gebäude, die diese Zwecke erfüllen, müssen jeweils eine oberirdische Bruttofläche von mindestens 10 000 m <FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> haben. Sie sollen primär vollständig und ausschließlich mit Dienstleistungen der Kommission und/oder anderer</P><P>Europäischer Institutionen oder Organisationen der Gemeinschaft besetzt sein.. Die vorgeschlagenen Verträge sind Nießbrauchverträge und/oder begrenzte Kaufverträge.</P><P>Die in Frage kommenden Gebäude wurden bevorzugt bereits erworben oder werden dies in Zukunft sein. Projekte können dennoch vorgeschlagen werden für den Fall einer späteren Akquisition.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zweck der Erwerbung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Zweck der Akquisition ist die Sammlung von Vorschlägen von Bürogebäuden, die den Bedürfnissen der Kommission in den in Punkt 2 oben genannten Umfängen entsprechen können.</P><P>Zu diesem Zweck sind die Eigentümer oder ihre Vertreter eingeladen, das Akquisitionsformular in der Sektion „Verträge und Beschaffungen - Bekanntmachung der Immobiliensuche“ auf der in Punkt 1 genannten Internetseite auszufüllen.</P><P>Die Vertraulichkeit der erhaltenen Informationen ist gewährleistet. Die Akquisitionsformulare werden in einer gesicherten Datenbank archiviert, zu der nur ordnungsgemäß ermächtigte statutorische Bedienstete der Europäischen Kommission Zugang haben.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verwendung der gesammelten Informationen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Die gesammelten und in der Datenbank archivierten Informationen werden von der Kommission genutzt, um die Gebäude zu identifizieren, die ihre Bedürfnisse hinsichtlich der Oberfläche erfüllen können.</P><P>Für die ausgewählten Gebäude tritt das OIB an die Eigentümer heran, um detaillierte Informationen hinsichtlich des Zustandes und die Kapazitäten des betreffenden Gebäudes sowie die anvisierten finanziellen Bedingungen zu erhalten.</P><P>Wenn auf Grundlage der detaillierten Informationen die Kommission befindet, dass die in Frage kommenden Immobilien effektiv den Bedürfnissen entsprechen können, kann ein Verhandlungsverfahren mit dem/den Eigentümer(n) der betreffenden Immobilien eingeleitet werden, entsprechend Artikel 134 der Verordnung (EU, Euratom) Nr. 1268/2012 über die Anwendungsbestimmungen für die Verordnung Nr. 966/2012.</P><P>Die vorliegende Bekanntmachung begründet jedoch keinerlei Verpflichtung seitens der Kommission im Hinblick auf ihre Auftragsvergabeverfahren.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Versendung der Akquisitionsformulare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Die unterschriebenen und datierten Akquisitionsformulare müssen von den Eigentümern oder ihren ordnungsgemäß beauftragten Vertretern vor dem (30 Tage vor Veröffentlichungsdatum) 16:30 versendet werden.</P><P>Die Informationen können gemäß nachfolgenden Bestimmungen wahlweise wie folgt eingereicht werden:</P><P>— entweder per Einschreiben auf dem Postweg (es gilt das Datum des Poststempels) an folgende Anschrift: Europäische Kommission, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1,— avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgien,</P><P>— oder durch Abgabe (persönlich oder durch einen Bevollmächtigten des Bewerbers, einschließlich Kurierdiensten) bei folgender Anschrift: Europäische Kommission, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1,— avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgien. Diese Dienststelle ist montags bis donnerstags von 8:00 bis 16:30 und freitags von 8:00 bis 16:00 geöffnet und an bei der Kommission geltenden Feiertagen geschlossen.</P><P>Bei Abgabe durch einen Kurierdienst ist das Absendedatum auf dem Beleg des Kurierdienstes maßgeblich. Im Falle der Abgabe durch den Bewerber persönlich oder durch einen seiner Bevollmächtigten wird die Abgabe der Antwort durch eine datierte und von dem Beamten der zentralen Posteingangsstelle der Kommission, dem die Unterlagen übergeben wurden, unterzeichnete Empfangsbestätigung bescheinigt.</P><P>In allen Fällen sind seitens des Eigentümers oder seines Vertreters ebenfalls folgende Modalitäten zu respektieren:</P><P>— das Akquisitionsformular muss in einem doppeltem Umschlag eingereicht werden.</P><P>— Beide Umschläge müssen verschlossen werden.</P><P>— zusätzlich zu der empfangenden Dienststelle muss der innere Umschlag die Referenz „Bekanntmachung über eine Immobiliensuche zur Befriedigung der Bedürfnisse der Europäischen Kommission bei Büroräumen in Brüssel“, „Akquisitionsformular von (Name des Eigentümers oder seines Vertreters“, „nicht vom Postdienst zu öffnen“ tragen.</P><P>Werden selbstklebende Umschläge benutzt, sind sie mit Klebeband zu verschließen und der Absender muss quer über dieses Klebeband unterschreiben.</P><P>— möchten der Eigentümer oder sein Vertreter vor Einreichung der Vorschläge weitere Informationen erhalten, so ist das Gesuch ausschließlich per E-Mail an die weiter oben unter Punkt 1 angegebene Adresse zu richten. Die Bieter werden dementsprechend aufgefordert, die unter Ziffer 1 angegebene Website regelmäßig zu besuchen, auf der die gestellten Fragen und die Antworten der Kommission veröffentlicht werden.</P><P>— Einsendeschluss für die Fragen ist (10 Arbeitstage vor Schlussdatum) 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussels: Information notice for the property market - Forecasts of multiannual property requirements for the years 2020 to 2024 for the European Commission in Brussels and prospecting of the local market</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>European Commission department responsible</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Commission</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>General information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>In accordance with the Commission Communication of 5.9.2007 [COM(2007)501], this notice is intended to inform property market participants and any other interested parties about the European Commission's forecast of property needs in Brussels, and to collect information on projects and properties within a defined perimeter.</P><P>Properties sought</P><P>To meet its office space needs by 2020-2024, the European Commission is looking for office space in Brussels, located either,</P><P>— 700 metres maximum from the axis of the segments between the Mérode metro station and the Arts-Loi metro station, and between the Arts-Loi metro station and the De Brouckère metro station,</P><P>— or 700 metres maximum from the axis of the metro line between Arts-Loi metro station and Rogier station,</P><P>— or 700 metres maximum from the axis of the metro line between Delta metro station and Hermann-Debroux station.</P><P>The total aboveground area required to replace properties at the end of their life cycle, or whose lease expires, is between 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> and 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> during the period 2020-2024. The actual requirements will depend in particular on the outcome of the negotiations under way or to be conducted for the renewal of agreements which will expire in the coming years for a number of properties occupied by Commission departments.</P><P>The buildings required to meet these needs must each have a gross floor area of at least 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. They should preferably be entirely and exclusively occupied by the Commission and/or the departments of other</P><P>European institutions or Community bodies. The proposed contracts will be usufruct and/or forward purchase contracts</P><P>The buildings in question should preferably be completed or nearing future completion. However, projects may be proposed in order to serve as part of a subsequent prospective study, if necessary.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Purposes of prospecting</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The purpose of prospecting is to collect proposals for office properties that can meet the Commission's needs in the areas indicated in point 2 above.</P><P>To this end, owners or their representatives are invited to complete the prospecting form available in the section “Contracts and public procurement - Property prospecting notice” on the website indicated in point 1.</P><P>Confidentiality of the information received is guaranteed. The prospecting files will then be archived in a secure database to which only duly authorised European Commission officials will have access.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Use of collected information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The information collected and stored in the database will be used by the Commission to identify buildings that can meet its office space needs.</P><P>For the properties identified, the OIB will approach the owners to obtain detailed information on the condition and capacity of the building concerned, as well as the contemplated financial conditions.</P><P>If, on the basis of this detailed information, the Commission considers that the properties in question can effectively meet its needs, a negotiated procedure would be launched with the owner(s) of the properties concerned, in accordance with the provisions of Article 134 of Regulation (EU, Euratom) Nº 1268/2012 on the rules of application for Regulation (EU, Euratom) Nº 966/2012.</P><P>This publication does not, however, constitute a commitment on the part of the Commission in its procurement procedures.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Submission of prospecting forms</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The signed and dated prospecting forms must be sent by the owners or their duly authorised representatives, before 16:30 on the (30 working days after publication date).</P><P>Information must be sent using one of the following methods:</P><P>— registered post, as evidenced by the postmark, to the following address: European Commission, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgium,</P><P>— delivery (in person or by any party representing the candidate, or by courier) to the following address: European Commission, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgium. This department is open 8:00–16:30, Monday to Thursday and 8:00–16:00 on Fridays, except for Commission holidays.</P><P>For deliveries by courier, the valid date of dispatch will be the date on the courier's delivery note. For deliveries made in person or by any representative, delivery of the response will, in this case, be confirmed by a receipt dated and signed by the official from the Commission's Central Mail Department who takes delivery of the documents.</P><P>In all cases, the owner or his representative must also respect the following conditions:</P><P>— the prospecting form must be presented in a double envelope,</P><P>— both envelopes must be sealed,</P><P>— the inner envelope must bear, in addition to the name of the department to which it is addressed, the reference “avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles”, “fiche de prospection de (name of owner or his representative)”, “à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courier”,</P><P>— self-adhesive envelopes must be sealed with adhesive tape through which the sender's signature must be affixed,</P><P>— if the owner or its representative wishes to obtain additional information before the date of the proposals’ submission, it must send its request, by e-mail only, to the e-mail address indicated above in point 1. Proposers are also invited to consult the website indicated in point 1, on a regular basis, where questions put to the Commission and the replies will be published,</P><P>— the deadline for sending questions is 16:00 on the (10 working days before the closing date).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselas: Anuncio de información destinado al mercado inmobiliario; previsión de las necesidades inmobiliarias plurianuales correspondientes al período de 2020-2024 para la Comisión Europea en Bruselas y prospección del mercado local</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Departamento responsable de la Comisión Europea</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Comisión Europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica, Correo electrónico: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Sitio Web: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información general:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De conformidad con la comunicación de la Comisión de 5.9.2007 [COM(2007)501], el presente anuncio se destina a informar a los agentes del mercado inmobiliario, así como a todas las partes interesadas, sobre la previsión de las necesidades inmobiliarias de la Comisión Europea en Bruselas y a recopilar información sobre bienes inmobiliarios y propiedades dentro de un área definida.</P><P>Inmuebles buscados</P><P>A fin de cumplir con los requisitos de espacio en las oficinas de cara al periodo 2020-2024, la Comisión Europea está buscando superficies de oficinas en Bruselas, ubicadas</P><P>— a una distancia máxima de 700 metros del eje de los segmentos entre la estación de metro Mérode y la estación de metro Arts-Loi y entre la estación de metro Arts-Loi y la estación de metro De Brouckère,</P><P>— o a una distancia máxima de 700 metros del eje de la línea de metro entre la estación de metro Arts-Loi y la estación de Rogier,</P><P>— o a una distancia máxima de 700 metros del eje de la línea de metro entre la estación de metro Delta y la estación Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>La superficie de suelo total buscada para reemplazar los edificios que se encuentran al final de su ciclo de vida o cuyo contrato de alquiler está a punto de expirar, está comprendida entre 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> y 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> durante el período 2020-2024. Los requisitos reales dependerán, en particular, del resultado de las negociaciones en curso o de la renovación de los acuerdos que expirarán en los próximos años para un determinado número de edificios ocupados por los servicios de la Comisión.</P><P>Los edificios destinados a satisfacer estas necesidades deben tener una superficie bruta de al menos 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Preferiblemente estarán total y exclusivamente ocupados por los servicios de la Comisión y/o servicios de otras</P><P>instituciones europeas u organismos comunitarios. Los contratos propuestos serán de usufructo y/o contratos de compra a plazo.</P><P>Los edificios en cuestión deberán encontrarse, preferentemente, en estado finalizado o a punto de completarse. Sin embargo, podrán proponerse proyectos para su uso, según sea el caso, en un potencial contexto futuro.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Propósitos de la prospección</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El objetivo de la prospección es recopilar propuestas de edificios de oficinas que puedan satisfacer las necesidades de la Comisión en el marco de los condicionantes indicados en el punto 2 anterior.</P><P>Para ello, se invita a los propietarios o sus representantes a completar la hoja de prospectos disponible en el apartado «Contratos y contratación pública — Aviso de prospección de bienes inmuebles» del sitio web indicado en el punto 1.</P><P>La confidencialidad de la información recibida está garantizada. Las hojas de prospección se archivarán en una base de datos segura que solo será accesible para el personal de la Comisión Europea autorizado legalmente.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uso de las informaciones recogidas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>La información recopilada y archivada en la base de datos será utilizada por la Comisión para identificar edificios que puedan satisfacer las necesidades de habilitación de espacios para oficinas.</P><P>Cuando se identifique un edificio, la OIB contactará con los propietarios para obtener información detallada sobre las condiciones y capacidades del edificio involucrado, así como sobre las condiciones financieras previstas.</P><P>Si, sobre la base de esta información detallada, la Comisión considera que los edificios en cuestión pueden cubrir efectivamente sus necesidades, podría iniciarse un procedimiento negociado con el propietario o los propietarios de los edificios implicados, de conformidad con las disposiciones del artículo 134 del Reglamento Delegado (UE) n.º 1268/2012 sobre las normas de desarrollo del Reglamento (UE, Euratom) n.º 966/2012.</P><P>La presente publicación no constituye, de forma alguna, un compromiso para la Comisión en el ámbito de los procedimientos de adjudicación de contratos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entrega de hojas de prospección</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Los propietarios o sus representantes debidamente autorizados deberán presentar las hojas de prospección, firmadas y fechadas, antes del (30 días hábiles después de la fecha de publicación) a las 16:30.</P><P>Las informaciones deberán entregarse según las modalidades siguientes, a discreción:</P><P>— bien por correo certificado, dando fe el matasellos, a la dirección siguiente: Comisión Europea, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Bélgica,</P><P>— bien entregándolas (directamente o por un representante del candidato, incluyendo los servicios de mensajería) en la siguiente dirección: Comisión Europea, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles Bélgica. Este servicio está abierto de 8:00 a 16:30 de lunes a jueves y de 8:00 a 16:00 el viernes; cerrado los días festivos de la Comisión.</P><P>En el caso de entrega por servicio de mensajería, la fecha de envío indicada en la minuta de la empresa de mensajería dará fe. En el caso de una entrega directa o por un mandatario, el depósito de la respuesta se efectuará con acuse de recibo fechado y firmado por el funcionario del servicio central de recepción del correo de la Comisión a quien se hayan entregado los documentos.</P><P>En todos los casos, el propietario o su representante deberá igualmente respetar las siguientes condiciones:</P><P>— la hoja de prospección se presentará en un sobre doble,</P><P>— los 2 sobres deberán estar cerrados,</P><P>— el sobre interior deberá llevar, además de la indicación del servicio receptor, la referencia «avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles» (aviso de prospección de edificios para cubrir las necesidades de la Comisión Europea de habilitar un espacio para oficinas en Bruselas), « «fiche de prospection de (nom du propriétaire ou son représentant)» [Hoja de prospección de (nombre de propietario o su representante)] , «à ne pas ouvrir par le service du couurier» (El servicio de correos no deberá abrir este sobre),</P><P>— en caso de utilizar sobres autoadhesivos, se cerrarán con la ayuda de cinta adhesiva sobre la que se estampará la firma del remitente,</P><P>— si el propietario o su representante desea obtener información adicional antes de la fecha de presentación de propuestas, deberá enviar su solicitud únicamente por correo electrónico a la dirección de correo electrónico indicada en el punto 1 anterior. Además, se invita a los licitadores a consultar de forma regular el sitio web indicado en el punto 1, donde se publicarán periódicamente las cuestiones presentadas y las respuestas de la Comisión,</P><P>— la fecha límite para enviar preguntas es el (10 días hábiles antes de la fecha de cierre) a las 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: Kiinteistömarkkinoille osoitettu tiedonanto – monivuotiset ennakkoarviot (vuodet 2020–2024) Euroopan komission Brysselin kiinteistötarpeista sekä paikallinen kiinteistömarkkinakartoitus</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vastaava Euroopan komission osasto:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan komissio</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia, sähköpostiosoite: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Verkkosivusto: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yleiset tiedot:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Komission tiedonannon KOM(2007)501 (annettu 5.9.2007) mukaisesti tämän ilmoituksen tarkoituksena on tiedottaa kiinteistömarkkinoilla työskenteleville henkilöille ja muille kiinnostuneille osapuolille Euroopan komission Brysselin kiinteistötarpeita koskevasta ennakkoarviosta sekä kerätä tietoja lähistön hankkeista ja kiinteistöistä rajatulla säteellä.</P><P>Etsityt kiinteistöt:</P><P>Vastatakseen toimistotilantarpeeseensa vuosia 2020-2024 silmällä pitäen Euroopan komissio etsii toimistotilaa Brysselistä. Tilojen tulisi sijaita</P><P>— korkeintaan 700 metriä Méroden metroaseman ja Arts-Loin metroaseman sekä Arts-Loin metroaseman ja De Brouckèren metroaseman yhdistävien osuuksien muodostamalta akselilta,</P><P>— tai korkeintaan 700 metriä Arts-Loin metroaseman ja Rogierin aseman välisen metrolinjan akselilta,</P><P>— tai korkeintaan 700 metriä Deltan metroaseman ja Hermann-Debroux'n aseman välisen metrolinjan akselilta.</P><P>Haettu kokonaislattiapinta-ala, joka tarvitaan korvaamaan elinkaarensa loppuun tulleita kiinteistöjä tai kiinteistöjä, joiden vuokrasopimus erääntyy, on 80 000 m{^&gt;2&lt;^} ja 150 000 m{^&gt;2&lt;^} välillä ajanjaksona 2020–2024. Tosiasialliset tarpeet riippuvat tiettyjen komission toimistojen käytössä olevien kiinteistöjen osalta erityisesti käynnissä olevien ja myöhemmin lähivuosina erääntyvien sopimusten uusimisesta käytävien neuvottelujen tuloksesta.</P><P>Kunkin näitä tarpeita varten haetun kiinteistökohteen maanpäällisen lattiapinta-alan tulee olla vähintään 10 000 m{^&gt;2&lt;^}. Kiinteistökohteiden tulisi mieluiten olla kokonaan ja ainoastaan komission ja/tai muiden EU:n toimielinten tai yhteisön muiden elinten käytössä.</P><P> Ehdotetut sopimustyypit ovat käyttöoikeussopimukset ja/tai ostaminen maksuerissä.</P><P>Kyseeseen tulevien rakennusten tulisi olla mieluiten valmiita tai valmistumassa lähiaikoina. Hankkeita voidaan kuitenkin ehdottaa tarvittaessa tulevaa mahdollista tarvetta täyttämään.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kiinteistömarkkinakartoituksen tavoitteet:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tämän kartoituksen tarkoituksena on kerätä toimistokiinteistöehdotuksia, jotka voisivat vastata komission tarpeisiin yllä kohdassa 2 mainituilla alueilla.</P><P>Tämän vuoksi kiinteistöjen omistajia tai heidän valtuuttamiaan henkilöitä pyydetään täyttämään kartoituslipuke, joka on saatavilla kohdassa 1 mainitun verkkosivuston otsikon ”sopimukset ja julkiset kauppatarjoukset – ilmoitus kiinteistökartoituksesta” (contrats et marchés publics — Avis de prospection immobilière) alla.</P><P>Vastaanotettujen tietojen luottamuksellisuus taataan. Kartoituslipukkeet arkistoidaan tämän jälkeen turvatietokantaan, johon on pääsy vain Euroopan komission asianmukaisesti valtuuttamilla virallisilla toimenhaltijoilla.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kerättyjen tietojen käyttö:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Komissio käyttää kerättyjä ja tietokantaan arkistoituja tietoja sellaisten kiinteistöjen löytämiseksi, jotka voisivat täyttää sen toimistopinta-alatarpeita.</P><P>Infrastruktuuri- ja logistiikkatoimisto lähestyy omistajia näin löydettyjen kiinteistöjen osalta saadakseen tarkempia tietoja kyseisen rakennuksen kunnosta ja valmiuksista sekä suunnitelluista rahallisista ehdoista.</P><P>Mikäli komissio katsoo näiden yksityiskohtaisten tietojen perusteella, että kyseiset kiinteistöt voivat tosiasiallisesti tyydyttää sen tarpeet, se voi käynnistää neuvottelumenettelyn kyseisten kiinteistöjen omistajan (omistajien) kanssa varainhoitoasetuksen, komission delegoitu asetus (EU) n:o 1268/2012, soveltamissääntöjen, Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU, Euratom) n:o 966/2012, artiklan 134 määräysten mukaisesti.</P><P>Tämä ilmoitus ei missään tapauksessa sido komissiota sen sopimuksentekomenettelyissä.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kartoituslipukkeiden jättäminen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Omistajien tai heidän asiamukaisesti valtuutettujen edustajiensa tulee jättää allekirjoitetut ja päivätyt kartoituslipukkeet ennen päivää, joka on 30 päivää tämän ilmoituksen julkaisupäivästä, viimeistään klo 16:30.</P><P>Tiedot on lähetettävä toisella seuraavista tavoista:</P><P>— postitse kirjattuna kirjeenä (mistä postileima on osoituksena) seuraavaan osoitteeseen: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgia,</P><P>— tai tuomalla henkilökohtaisesti tai hakijan edustajan, esimerkiksi kuljetuspalvelun, välityksellä seuraavaan osoitteeseen: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgia. Yksikkö on auki maanantaista torstaihin klo 8:00–16:30 ja perjantaisin klo 8:00–16:00 komission vapaapäiviä lukuun ottamatta.</P><P>Lähetin välityksellä toimitettujen hakemusten osalta voimassa oleva lähetyspäivä on lähetin antamaan rahtikirjaan merkitty päivä. Henkilökohtaisesti tai hakijan edustajan välityksellä tuotujen hakemusten jättämisestä annetaan todistukseksi asiakirjat vastaanottaneen komission keskuspostiosaston virkailijan päiväämä ja allekirjoittama kuittaus.</P><P>Joka tapauksessa omistajan tai hänen edustajansa tulee myös noudattaa seuraavia muodollisuuksia:</P><P>— kartoituslipuke tulee panna kahden kirjekuoren sisälle,</P><P>— molemmat kuoret on suljettava,</P><P>— sisemmässä kuoressa vastaanottavan viranomaisen ilmoittavan rivin yläpuolella tulee olla merkinnät ”avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles”, ”fiche de prospection de (omistajan tai hänen edustajansa nimi)”, ”à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courrier”,</P><P>— tarrakirjekuoret on suljettava tarraläppien yli asetetulla teipillä ja varustettava lähettäjän allekirjoituksella teippien poikki,</P><P>— mikäli omistaja tai hänen edustajansa haluaa saada lisätietoja ennen ehdotusten jättöpäivää, hänen tulee osoittaa pyyntönsä yksinomaisesti sähköpostilla yllä kohdassa 1 mainittuun sähköpostiosoitteeseen. Ehdotuksen tekijöitä suositellaan käymään säännöllisesti tämän ilmoituksen kohdassa 1 mainitulla verkkosivustolla, jossa julkaistaan säännöllisesti kysymyksiä ja komission niihin antamia vastauksia,</P><P>— viimeinen päivä kysymysten lähettämiseksi on 10 työpäivää ennen ehdotusten viimeistä jättöpäivää klo 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Avis d'information à l'attention du marché immobilier — Prévisions des besoins immobiliers pluriannuels pour les années 2020 à 2024 pour la Commission européenne à Bruxelles et prospection du marché local</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Département responsable de la Commission européenne</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Commission européenne</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, B-1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgique, Courriel: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Site web: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informations générales:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Conformément à la communication de la Commission du 5.9.2007 [COM(2007)501], le présent avis est destiné à informer les acteurs du marché immobilier, ainsi que toute autre partie intéressée sur la prévision des besoins immobiliers de la Commission européenne à Bruxelles et à recueillir les informations sur les projets et biens immobiliers dans un périmètre défini.</P><P>Immeubles recherchés</P><P>Afin de répondre à ses besoins d'espaces de bureaux à l'horizon de 2020-2024, la Commission européenne est à la recherche de surfaces de bureaux à Bruxelles, situées soit,</P><P>— à 700 mètres maximum de l’axe des segments entre la station de métro Mérode et la station de métro Arts-Loi et entre la station de métro Arts-Loi et la station de métro De Brouckère,</P><P>— ou à 700 mètres maximum de l’axe de la ligne métro entre la station de métro Arts-Loi et la station Rogier,</P><P>— ou à 700 mètres maximum de l'axe de la ligne métro entre la station de métro Delta et la station Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>La superficie hors sol totale recherchée, afin de remplacer des immeubles en fin de cycle de vie ou dont le contrat de bail arrive à échéance, est comprise entre 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> et 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> durant la période 2020-2024. Les besoins effectifs seront fonction notamment du résultat des négociations en cours ou à mener pour le renouvellement de conventions qui arrivent à échéance, dans les prochaines années, pour un certain nombre d'immeubles occupés par les services de la Commission.</P><P>Les bâtiments recherchés pour satisfaire ces besoins doivent avoir chacun une surface brute d'au moins 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> hors sol. Ils auront, de préférence, vocation à être entièrement et exclusivement occupés par les services de la Commission et/ou les services d'autres</P><P>Institutions européennes ou d'organismes communautaires. Les contrats proposés seront des contrats d'usufruit et/ou d'achat à terme</P><P>Les bâtiments en question devront, de préférence, être achevés ou en voie d'achèvement futur. Des projets pourront toutefois être proposés afin de servir, le cas échéant, dans le cadre d'une prospective ultérieure.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finalités de la prospection</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>La prospection a pour finalité de collecter les propositions d'immeubles de bureaux pouvant répondre aux besoins de la Commission, dans les périmètres indiqués au point 2 ci-dessus.</P><P>À cette fin, les propriétaires ou leurs mandataires sont invités à compléter la fiche de prospection disponible dans la section «contrats et marchés publics — Avis de prospection immobilière» du site internet renseigné au point 1.</P><P>La confidentialité des informations reçues est garantie. Les fiches de prospection seront ensuite archivées dans une base de données sécurisée à laquelle n'auront accès que des agents statutaires de la Commission européenne dûment habilités.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Utilisation des informations collectées</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les informations collectées et archivées dans la base de données seront exploitées par la Commission pour identifier les bâtiments pouvant satisfaire ses besoins en surface de bureaux.</P><P>Pour les immeubles identifiés, l'OIB se rapprochera des propriétaires afin d'obtenir des informations détaillées sur l'état et les capacités du bâtiment concerné ainsi que les conditions financières envisagées.</P><P>Si sur la base de ces informations détaillées, la Commission considère que les immeubles en question peuvent effectivement satisfaire ses besoins, une procédure négociée pourrait être lancée avec le(les) propriétaires des immeubles concernés, conformément aux dispositions de l'article 134 du règlement (EU, Euratom) nº 1268/2012 relatif aux règles d’application du règlement (EU, Euratom) n<FT TYPE="SUP">o</FT> 966/2012.</P><P>La présente publication ne constitue toutefois en aucun cas un engagement pour la Commission dans le cadre de ses procédures de passation de marchés.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Remise des fiches de prospection</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les fiches de prospection signées et datées doivent être transmises par les propriétaires ou leurs représentants dûment mandatés, avant le (30 jours ouvrables après date de publication) 16:30.</P><P>Les informations doivent être transmises selon les modalités suivantes, au choix:</P><P>— soit par la poste, par envoi recommandé, le cachet de la poste faisant foi, à l’adresse suivante: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, B-1140 Bruxelles,</P><P>— soit par dépôt (directement ou par tout mandataire du candidat ou par messagerie), à l’adresse suivante: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — avenue du Bourget 1, B-1140 Bruxelles. Ce service est ouvert de 8:00 à 16:30 du lundi au jeudi et de 8:00 à 16:00 le vendredi, sauf jours fériés de la Commission.</P><P>Dans le cas d’un dépôt par messagerie, la date d’envoi sur le bordereau de la messagerie fait foi. Dans le cas d’un dépôt directement ou par tout mandataire, le dépôt de la réponse est établi au moyen d’un reçu daté, signé par le fonctionnaire du service central de réception du courrier de la Commission à qui les documents ont été remis.</P><P>Dans tous les cas de figure, le propriétaire ou son représentant devra également respecter les modalités suivantes:</P><P>— la fiche de prospection doit être présentée sous double enveloppe,</P><P>— les 2 enveloppes seront fermées,</P><P>— l'enveloppe intérieure portant, en sus de l'indication du service destinataire, la référence «avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles», «fiche de prospection de (nom du propriétaire ou son représentant)», «à ne pas ouvrir par le service du couurier»,</P><P>— les enveloppes autocollantes seront fermées à l'aide de bandes collantes au travers desquelles sera apposée la signature de l'expéditeur,</P><P>— si le propriétaire ou son représentant souhaite obtenir des renseignements complémentaires avant la date de remise des propositions, il adressera sa demande uniquement par e-mail à l’adresse mail indiquée plus haut au point 1. Les proposants sont par ailleurs invités à consulter régulièrement le site web indique au point 1 qui publiera régulièrement les questions posées et les réponses de la Commission,</P><P>— la date limite pour envoyer les questions est le (10 jours ouvrables avant la date de clôture) 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Βρυξέλλες: Ενημερωτική κοινοποίηση υπόψη της αγοράς ακινήτων — Προβλέψεις πολυετών αναγκών στον τομέα των ακινήτων για τα έτη 2020 έως 2024 για την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή στις Βρυξέλλες και διερεύνηση της τοπικής αγοράς</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αρμόδιο τμήμα της Ευρωπαϊκής Επιτροπής</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Βέλγιο, Ηλεκτρονικό ταχυδρομείο: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Ιστότοπος: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Γενικές πληροφορίες:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Σύμφωνα με την ανακοίνωση της Επιτροπής της 5.9.2007 [COM(2007)501], στόχος της παρούσας κοινοποίησης είναι η ενημέρωση των φορέων της αγοράς ακινήτων, καθώς και οποιουδήποτε ενδιαφερομένου σχετικά με την πρόβλεψη των αναγκών στον τομέα των ακινήτων της Ευρωπαϊκής Επιτροπής στις Βρυξέλλες και η συλλογή πληροφοριών σχετικά με τα σχέδια και τα αγαθά αναφορικά με τα ακίνητα σε μια καθορισμένη ζώνη.</P><P>Ζητούμενα κτίρια</P><P>Προκειμένου να ανταποκριθεί στις ανάγκες για χώρους γραφείων για τα έτη 2020 έως 2024, η Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή αναζητά χώρους γραφείων στις Βρυξέλλες, τα οποία θα βρίσκονται,</P><P>— σε μέγιστη απόσταση 700 μέτρων από τον άξονα του τμήματος μεταξύ του σταθμού μετρό Mérode και του σταθμού μετρό Arts-Loi και μεταξύ του σταθμού μετρό Arts-Loi και του σταθμού μετρό De Brouckère,</P><P>— ή σε μέγιστη απόσταση 700 μέτρων από τον άξονα της γραμμής του μετρό μεταξύ του σταθμού μετρό Arts-Loi και του σταθμού Rogier,</P><P>— ή σε μέγιστη απόσταση 700 μέτρων από τον άξονα της γραμμής του μετρό μεταξύ του σταθμού μετρό Delta και του σταθμού Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Η συνολική ζητούμενη υπέργεια επιφάνεια, προκειμένου να αντικαταστήσει τα κτίρια στο τέλος του κύκλου ζωής τους ή για τα οποία η υφιστάμενη συμφωνία μίσθωσης πρόκειται να λήξει, κυμαίνεται μεταξύ 80.000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> και 150.000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> κατά την περίοδο 2020-2024. Οι συγκεκριμένες ανάγκες θα εξαρτηθούν ιδίως από το αποτέλεσμα των διαπραγματεύσεων που βρίσκονται σε εξέλιξη ή θα ολοκληρωθούν για την ανανέωση των συμβάσεων που πρόκειται να λήξουν τα προσεχή έτη για έναν ορισμένο αριθμό κτιρίων που καταλαμβάνουν οι υπηρεσίες της Επιτροπής.</P><P>Τα ζητούμενα κτίρια για την ικανοποίηση των εν λόγω αναγκών θα πρέπει να έχουν το καθένα μικτή υπέργεια επιφάνεια τουλάχιστον 10.000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Κατά προτίμηση, θα προορίζονται να φιλοξενήσουν εξ ολοκλήρου και αποκλειστικά τις υπηρεσίες της Επιτροπής και/ή τις υπηρεσίες άλλων</P><P>ευρωπαϊκών θεσμικών οργάνων ή κοινοτικών οργανισμών. Οι προτεινόμενες συμβάσεις θα αποτελέσουν συμβάσεις επικαρπίας και/ή προθεσμιακής αγοράς</P><P>Κατά προτίμηση, η κατασκευή των εν λόγω κτιρίων θα πρέπει να έχει ολοκληρωθεί ή να πλησιάζει να ολοκληρωθεί. Ωστόσο, μπορούν να υποβληθούν προτάσεις για σχέδια ώστε να χρησιμοποιηθούν, κατά περίπτωση, στο πλαίσιο μελλοντικών προοπτικών.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Σκοπός της έρευνας</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Σκοπός της έρευνας είναι η συγκέντρωση προτάσεων για κτίρια γραφείων τα οποία θα ανταποκρίνονται στις ανάγκες της Επιτροπής, εντός των ζωνών που αναφέρονται στο σημείο 2 ανωτέρω.</P><P>Προς τον σκοπό αυτό, οι ιδιοκτήτες ή οι εκπρόσωποί τους καλούνται να συμπληρώσουν το δελτίο διερεύνησης που διατίθεται στο τμήμα «Δημόσιες και λοιπές συμβάσεις - Προκήρυξη κτηματομεσιτικής έρευνας» στον ιστότοπο που αναφέρεται στο σημείο 1.</P><P>Η εμπιστευτικότητα των πληροφοριών που λαμβάνονται είναι εγγυημένη. Στη συνέχεια, τα δελτία διερεύνησης θα αρχειοθετηθούν σε μια ασφαλή βάση δεδομένων, η οποία θα είναι προσβάσιμη μόνο σε νόμιμα εξουσιοδοτημένους υπαλλήλους της Ευρωπαϊκής Επιτροπής.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Χρήση των συλλεγόμενων πληροφοριών</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Οι πληροφορίες που συλλέγονται και αρχειοθετούνται στη βάση δεδομένων θα αξιοποιηθούν από την Επιτροπή για τον εντοπισμό κτιρίων που μπορούν να καλύψουν τις ανάγκες των χώρων των γραφείων.</P><P>Για τα καθορισμένα κτίρια, το Γραφείο Υποδομής και Διοικητικής Υποστήριξης (OIB) θα προσεγγίσει τους ιδιοκτήτες προκειμένου να ζητήσει λεπτομερείς πληροφορίες σχετικά με την κατάσταση και τις δυνατότητες του εν λόγω κτιρίου καθώς και με τους προβλεπόμενους οικονομικούς όρους.</P><P>Εάν με βάση τις συγκεκριμένες λεπτομερείς πληροφορίες η Επιτροπή κρίνει ότι τα εν λόγω κτίρια μπορούν να καλύψουν αποτελεσματικά τις ανάγκες της, θα διεξαχθεί διαδικασία με διαπραγμάτευση με τον ιδιοκτήτη ή τους ιδιοκτήτες των εν λόγω κτιρίων, σύμφωνα με τις διατάξεις του άρθρου 134 του κανονισμού (ΕΕ, Ευρατόμ) αριθ. 1268/2012 σχετικά με τους κανόνες εφαρμογής του κανονισμού (ΕΕ, Ευρατόμ) αριθ. 966/2012.</P><P>Η παρούσα δημοσίευση δεν αποτελεί ωστόσο σε καμία περίπτωση δέσμευση για την Επιτροπή στο πλαίσιο των διαδικασιών σύναψης συμβάσεων.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Υποβολή δελτίων διερεύνησης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Τα υπογεγραμμένα και χρονολογημένα δελτία διερεύνησης θα πρέπει να υποβληθούν από τους ιδιοκτήτες ή τους δεόντως εξουσιοδοτημένους εκπροσώπους τους, πριν από τις (30 εργάσιμες ημέρες μετά την ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης) στις 16:30.</P><P>Οι πληροφορίες μπορούν να διαβιβαστούν σύμφωνα με τους ακόλουθους τρόπους, κατ' επιλογή:</P><P>— είτε ταχυδρομικώς με συστημένη επιστολή, με αποδεικτικό τη σφραγίδα του ταχυδρομείου, στην ακόλουθη διεύθυνση: Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Βέλγιο,</P><P>— είτε με ιδιόχειρη κατάθεση (απευθείας ή μέσω αντιπροσώπου του υποψήφιου ή υπηρεσιών ιδιωτικού ταχυδρομείου) στην ακόλουθη διεύθυνση: Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Βέλγιο. Οι ώρες λειτουργίας της υπηρεσίας είναι από τις 8:00 έως τις 16:30 από Δευτέρα έως Πέμπτη και από τις 8:00 έως τις 16:00 την Παρασκευή, εκτός αργιών της Επιτροπής.</P><P>Στην περίπτωση κατάθεσης μέσω υπηρεσιών ιδιωτικού ταχυδρομείου, αποδεικτικό κατάθεσης αποτελεί η ημερομηνία αποστολής του δελτίου του ιδιωτικού ταχυδρομείου. Στην περίπτωση ιδιόχειρης κατάθεσης ή κατάθεσης μέσω αντιπροσώπου, η υποβολή της ανταπόκρισης πραγματοποιείται έναντι απόδειξης παραλαβής φέρουσας ημερομηνία και υπογραφή του παραλαβόντος τα έγγραφα υπαλλήλου της επίσημης υπηρεσίας αλληλογραφίας της Επιτροπής.</P><P>Σε κάθε περίπτωση, ο ιδιοκτήτης ή ο εκπρόσωπός του θα πρέπει επίσης να τηρεί τους ακόλουθους όρους:</P><P>— το δελτίο διερεύνησης θα πρέπει να κατατεθεί σε διπλό φάκελο,</P><P>— οι 2 φάκελοι θα είναι κλειστοί,</P><P>— ο εσωτερικός φάκελος φέρει, εκτός από την ένδειξη της παραλήπτριας υπηρεσίας, την ένδειξη «Avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles» (Προκήρυξη κτηματομεσιτικής έρευνας για την κάλυψη των αναγκών της Ευρωπαϊκής Επιτροπής σε χώρους γραφείων στις Βρυξέλλες), «fiche de prospection de (όνομα του ιδιοκτήτη ή του εκπροσώπου του)» (δελτίο διερεύνησης του), «à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courier» (να μην ανοιχθεί από την υπηρεσία αλληλογραφίας),</P><P>— οι αυτοκόλλητοι φάκελοι θα πρέπει να σφραγισθούν με κολλητική ταινία, η οποία θα φέρει την υπογραφή του αποστολέα,</P><P>— εάν ο ιδιοκτήτης ή ο εκπρόσωπός του επιθυμεί να λάβει συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες πριν από την ημερομηνία υποβολής των προτάσεων, θα πρέπει να αποστείλει το αίτημά του αποκλειστικά μέσω ηλεκτρονικού ταχυδρομείου στη διεύθυνση ηλεκτρονικού ταχυδρομείου που αναφέρεται στο σημείο 1 ανωτέρω. Επίσης, οι υποβάλλοντες πρόταση καλούνται να συμβουλεύονται τακτικά τον δικτυακό τόπο που αναφέρεται στο σημείο 1, όπου θα δημοσιεύονται τακτικά οι ερωτήσεις που θα τίθενται, καθώς και οι απαντήσεις της Επιτροπής,</P><P>— η προθεσμία για την αποστολή ερωτήσεων είναι στις (10 εργάσιμες ημέρες πριν από την καταληκτική ημερομηνία) στις 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Avviso di informazione rivolto al mercato immobiliare — previsioni delle esigenze immobiliari pluriennali della Commissione europea a Bruxelles per gli anni dal 2020 al 2024 e indagine sul mercato locale</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Servizio responsabile della Commissione europea</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Commissione europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgio, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Sito web: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informazioni generali:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Conformemente alla comunicazione della Commissione del 5.9.2007 \[COM(2007)501], il presente avviso ha lo scopo di informare gli esponenti del mercato immobiliare e qualsiasi altro soggetto interessato in merito alle previsioni delle esigenze immobiliari della Commissione europea a Bruxelles e di raccogliere le informazioni sui progetti e i beni immobiliari in un perimetro definito.</P><P>Edifici ricercati</P><P>Al fine di soddisfare i fabbisogni di spazio per uffici per il periodo 2020-2024, la Commissione europea è alla ricerca di superfici per uffici a Bruxelles, situati sia</P><P>— a un massimo di 700 metri dall'asse dei segmenti tra la stazione della metropolitana Mérode e la stazione Arts-Loi e tra la stazione della metropolitana Arts-Loi e la stazione De Brouckère,</P><P>— o a un massimo di 700 metri dell’asse della linea metropolitana tra la stazione Arts-Loi e la stazione Rogier,</P><P>— o a un massimo di 700 metri dell’asse della linea metropolitana tra la stazione Delta e la stazione Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>La superficie totale fuori dal suolo ricercata allo scopo di sostituire gli edifici alla fine del proprio ciclo di vita o per i quali il contratto scade è compresa tra 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> e 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> durante il periodo 2020-2024. I fabbisogni effettivi dipenderanno, in particolare, dall'esito dei negoziati in corso o da stipulare per il rinnovo degli accordi che scadranno nei prossimi anni per un certo numero di edifici occupati dai servizi della Commissione.</P><P>Ciascuno degli edifici ricercati per il soddisfacimento di tali fabbisogni dovranno avere una superfice lorda di almeno 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> fuori dal suolo. Saranno preferibilmente adibiti ad essere interamente ed esclusivamente occupati dai servizi della Commissione e/o dai servizi di altre</P><P>istituzioni europee o di organismi comunitari. I contratti proposti saranno contratti di usufrutto e/o di acquisto a termine</P><P>Gli edifici in questione dovranno essere preferibilmente completati o in via di completamento. Tuttavia, si potranno proporre anche progetti aventi lo scopo di servire, se del caso, al contesto di una prospettiva futura.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finalità dell’indagine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lo scopo dell’indagine consiste nella raccolta di proposte di edifici ad uso uffici che possano soddisfare le esigenze della Commissione, all'interno dei perimetri indicati al punto 2 di cui sopra.</P><P>A tal fine, i proprietari o i loro rappresentanti sono invitati a compilare la scheda dell’indagine disponibile nella sezione "Contratti e appalti pubblici — Avviso di indagine immobiliare" del sito indicato al punto 1.</P><P>Sarà garantita la riservatezza delle informazioni ricevute. Le schede dell’indagine saranno quindi archiviate in una banca dati sicura che sarà accessibile solo agli agenti statutari della Commissione europea debitamente abilitati.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Utilizzo delle informazioni raccolte</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le informazioni raccolte e archiviate nella banca dati saranno utilizzate dalla Commissione per identificare gli edifici che potranno soddisfare le esigenze di spazi per uffici.</P><P>Per gli edifici identificati, OIB si rivolgerà ai proprietari per ottenere informazioni dettagliate sullo stato e sulle capacità dell'edificio interessato, nonché sulle condizioni finanziarie previste.</P><P>Se, in base a tali informazioni dettagliate la Commissione riterrà che gli edifici in questione possano effettivamente soddisfare le proprie esigenze, potrà essere avviata una procedura negoziata con il proprietario o i proprietari degli edifici interessati, conformemente alle disposizioni dell'articolo 134 del regolamento (UE, Euratom) n. 1268/2012 relativo alle norme di attuazione del regolamento (UE, Euratom) n. 966/2012.</P><P>Tuttavia la presente pubblicazione non costituirà alcun impegno per la Commissione nel quadro delle proprie procedure di aggiudicazione di appalti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Consegna delle schede dell’indagine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le schede inerenti l’indagine, firmate e datate, dovranno essere trasmesse dai proprietari o dai loro rappresentanti debitamente autorizzati, entro il (30 giorni lavorativi dopo la data di pubblicazione) alle ore 16:30.</P><P>Le informazioni dovranno essere trasmesse secondo le modalità seguenti, a scelta:</P><P>— tramite posta, a mezzo raccomandata, nel qual caso farà fede il timbro postale, al seguente indirizzo: Commissione europea, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgio,</P><P>— oppure tramite consegna (direttamente o tramite un mandatario del candidato, compresi i servizi di messaggeria), al seguente indirizzo: Commissione europea, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgio. Il servizio è aperto dalle ore 8:00 alle 16:30, dal lunedì al giovedì, e dalle ore 8:00 alle 16:00 il venerdì, salvo i giorni festivi della Commissione.</P><P>Nel caso di consegna tramite messaggeria, farà fede la data apposta sulla lettera di vettura emessa dalla messaggeria. In caso di consegna eseguita direttamente o tramite mandatario, la consegna della risposta sarà certificata dal rilascio di una ricevuta datata e firmata dal funzionario del servizio postale centrale della Commissione che avrà preso in consegna i documenti.</P><P>In tutti i casi, il proprietario o il suo rappresentante dovrà inoltre rispettare le seguenti condizioni:</P><P>— la scheda dell’indagine deve essere presentata in doppia busta,</P><P>— le 2 buste dovranno essere chiuse,</P><P>— la busta interna dovrà recare, oltre all'indicazione del servizio destinatario, le diciture «avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles» (avviso d’indagine immobiliare per soddisfare le esigenze della Commissione europea di spazi per uffici a Bruxelles), «fiche de prospection de (nom du propriétaire ou son représentant)» [scheda d’indagine di (nome del proprietario o del suo rappresentante)], «à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courrier» (non deve essere aperto dal servizio postale),</P><P>— le buste autoadesive dovranno essere chiuse con nastro adesivo recante di traverso la firma del mittente,</P><P>— se il proprietario o il suo rappresentante desidera ottenere ulteriori informazioni prima della data di consegna delle proposte, dovrà trasmettere la propria domanda unicamente per e-mail all’indirizzo email sopra indicato al punto 1. I proponenti sono inoltre invitati a consultare regolarmente il sito web indicato al punto 1, sul quale verranno pubblicate regolarmente le domande e le risposte della Commissione,</P><P>— la scadenza per l’invio delle domande è il (10 giorni lavorativi prima della scadenza del termine) alle ore 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussel: Kennisgeving van informatie voor de vastgoedmarkt — Raming van de meerjarige vastgoedbehoeften voor de jaren 2020-2024 voor de Europese Commissie in Brussel en prospectie van de lokale markt</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verantwoordelijke dienst van de Europese Commissie:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europese Commissie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, België, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Website: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Algemene inlichtingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>In overeenstemming met Mededeling COM(2007) 501 van de Commissie van 5.9.2007, is het de bedoeling van onderhavige kennisgeving om de actoren van de vastgoedmarkt, alsook elke andere geïnteresseerde partij, te informeren over de ramingen van de vastgoedbehoeften van de Europese Commissie in Brussel en om informatie te verzamelen over de projecten en gebouwen in een vastgesteld gebied.</P><P>Gezochte gebouwen:</P><P>Om te beantwoorden aan haar behoefte aan kantoorruimten tegen 2020-2024, is de Europese Commissie op zoek naar kantooroppervlakten in Brussel dat is gelegen:</P><P>— op maximaal 700 meter van de as van de segmenten tussen het metrostation Merode en het metrostation Kunst-Wet, en tussen het metrostation Kunst-Wet en het metrostation De Brouckère;</P><P>— of op maximaal 700 meter van de as van de metrolijn tussen het metrostation Kunst-Wet en het Rogierstation;</P><P>— of op maximaal 700 meter van de as van de metrolijn tussen het metrostation Delta en het station Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Om gebouwen te vervangen die aan het einde van hun levenscyclus zijn of waarvan de huurovereenkomst ten einde loopt, wordt gezocht naar een totale bovengrondse oppervlakte tussen 80 000 m² en 150 000 m² tijdens de periode 2020-2024. De werkelijke behoeften zijn met name afhankelijk van het resultaat van de lopende of nog te voeren onderhandelingen voor de vernieuwing van de overeenkomsten die ten einde lopen, in de komende jaren, voor een bepaald aantal gebouwen die worden gebruikt door de diensten van de Commissie.</P><P>De gebouwen die worden gezocht om aan deze behoefte te voldoen moeten elk een bovengrondse bruto-oppervlakte hebben van minstens 10 000 m². Zij worden bij voorkeur volledig en exclusief gebruikt door de diensten van de Commissie en/of door de diensten van andere</P><P>Europese instellingen of gemeenschapsentiteiten. De voorgestelde overeenkomsten zullen overeenkomsten voor vruchtgebruik en/of termijnkoopovereenkomsten zijn.</P><P>De desbetreffende gebouwen moeten bij voorkeur afgewerkt zijn of worden momenteel afgewerkt. Projecten kunnen echter worden voorgesteld om, in voorkomend geval, te dienen voor een toekomstige prognose.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Doelstellingen van de prospectie:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De prospectie beoogt voorstellen te verzamelen voor kantoorgebouwen die aan de behoefte van de Commissie kunnen beantwoorden, binnen het gebied vermeld in punt 2 hierboven.</P><P>Daarom worden de eigenaars of hun gemachtigde vertegenwoordigers uitgenodigd om de prospectiefiche die beschikbaar is onder de afdeling „contrats et marchés publics — Avis de prospection immobilière” (opdrachten en aanbestedingen — Prospectienota over de vastgoedmarkt) van de in punt 1 vermelde website.</P><P>De vertrouwelijkheid van de ontvangen informatie wordt gewaarborgd. De prospectiefiches worden daarna opgeslagen in een beveiligde databank die enkel toegankelijk is voor naar behoren gemachtigde statutaire ambtenaren van de Europese Commissie.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Gebruik van de verzamelde informatie:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De verzamelde en in de databank opgeslagen informatie wordt door de Commissie gebruikt om gebouwen te identificeren die kunnen tegemoet komen aan haar behoefte op vlak van kantooroppervlakte.</P><P>Voor de geïdentificeerde gebouwen zal het OIB de eigenaars benaderen om gedetailleerde informatie te verwerven over de staat en de capaciteiten van het desbetreffende gebouw evenals over de beoogde financiële voorwaarden.</P><P>Als de Commissie op basis van deze gedetailleerde informatie van mening is dat de desbetreffende gebouwen daadwerkelijk tegemoet kunnen komen aan haar behoefte, kan een onderhandelingsprocedure worden opgestart met de eigenaar(s) van de desbetreffende gebouwen, conform de bepalingen van artikel 134 van Gedelegeerde Verordening (EU, Euratom) nr. 1268/2012 houdende uitvoeringsvoorschriften voor Verordening (EU, Euratom) nr. 966/2012.</P><P>Onderhavige bekendmaking houdt voor de Commissie geen enkele verplichting in wat gunningsprocedures voor opdrachten betreft.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indiening van de prospectiefiches:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De ondertekende en gedateerde propctiefiches moeten door de eigenaars of hun naar behoren gemachtigde vertegenwoordigers worden ingediend, vóór (30 werkdagen na de datum van de bekendmaking), om 16:30.</P><P>De informatie moet naar keuze op een van de volgende manieren worden ingediend:</P><P>— ofwel per aangetekend schrijven (de poststempel geldt als bewijs) naar volgend adres: Europese Commissie, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, België,</P><P>— ofwel via afgifte (rechtstreeks of door een vertegenwoordiger van de gegadigde, of per koeriersdienst), op volgend adres: Europese Commissie, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, België. Deze dienst is van maandag tot en met donderdag open van 8:00 tot 16:30 en op vrijdag van 8:00 tot 16:00, behalve op de feestdagen van de Commissie.</P><P>In het geval van een afgifte per koeriersdienst geldt de verzendingsdatum op het borderel van de koeriersdienst als bewijs. In het geval van een persoonlijke afgifte of een afgifte door een gevolmachtigde wordt de afgifte van het antwoord vastgesteld aan de hand van een gedateerd ontvangstbewijs dat ondertekend wordt door de ambtenaar van de centrale postkamer van de Commissie aan wie de documenten zijn afgegeven.</P><P>In elk geval moet de eigenaar of zijn vertegenwoordiger ook de volgende voorwaarden eerbiedigen:</P><P>— de deelnemingsaanvraag moet in een dubbele enveloppe worden ingediend;</P><P>— de 2 enveloppen moeten gesloten zijn;</P><P>— op de binnenste enveloppe moet voornoemde begunstigde dienst vermeld staan, alsook de referentie «avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles», «fiche de prospection de (naam van de eigenaar of zijn vertegenwoordiger)», «à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courier»;</P><P>— indien zelfklevende enveloppen worden gebruikt, moeten zij worden dichtgekleefd met plakband en moet de afzender zijn handtekening over dit plakband heen zetten;</P><P>— indien de eigenaar of zijn vertegenwoordiger aanvullende inlichtingen wil vóór de datum voor indiening van de antwoorden, moet hij zijn vraag per e-mail sturen naar het hiervoor in punt 1 vermelde adres. De aanbieders worden trouwens uitgenodigd om de in punt 1 van deze aankondiging vermelde website regelmatig te raadplegen aangezien de door de aanbieders gestelde vragen en de antwoorden van de Commissie er op gezette tijden worden gepubliceerd;</P><P>— de uiterste datum voor het versturen van vragen is (10 werkdagen na de uiterste datum voor indiening) om 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelas: Anúncio de informação à atenção do mercado imobiliário — Previsões das necessidades imobiliárias plurianuais para o período de 2020-2024 para a Comissão Europeia em Bruxelas e prospeção do mercado local</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Departamento responsável da Comissão Europeia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Comissão Europeia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica, Endereço eletrónico: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Sítio Web: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informação geral:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Em conformidade com a comunicação da Comissão de 5.9.2007 [COM(2007)501], o presente anúncio destina-se a informar os agentes do mercado imobiliário, bem como qualquer outra parte interessada, sobre a previsão das necessidades imobiliárias da Comissão Europeia em Bruxelas e recolher informações sobre projetos e bens imobiliários dentro de uma área definida.</P><P>Edifícios visados</P><P>Para cumprir as necessidades de espaço de escritórios em 2020-2024, a Comissão Europeia está à procura de escritórios em Bruxelas, localizados,</P><P>— a uma distância máxima de 700 metros do eixo dos segmentos entre a estação de metro Mérode e a estação de metro Arts-Loi e entre a estação de metro Arts-Loi e a estação de metro De Brouckère,</P><P>— ou a uma distância máxima de 700 metros do eixo da linha do metro entre a estação de metro Arts-Loi e a estação Rogier,</P><P>— ou a uma distância máxima de 700 metros do eixo da linha do metro entre a estação de metro Delta e a estação Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>A área total acima do nível do solo procurada, para substituir os edifícios no fim do respetivo ciclo de vida ou para os quais o contrato de arrendamento atinge o seu termo é de 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> e 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> durante o período 2020-2024. As necessidades reais dependerão, em particular, do resultado das negociações em curso ou a realizar para a renovação de acordos que expiram nos próximos anos para um certo número de edifícios ocupados pelos serviços da Comissão.</P><P>Os edifícios procurados para atender a essas necessidades devem ter uma área bruta de, pelo menos, 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> acima do solo. De preferência, serão preferencialmente ocupados de forma completa e exclusiva pelos serviços da Comissão e/ou pelos serviços de outros</P><P>Instituições europeias ou organizações comunitárias. Os contratos propostos serão contratos de usufruto e/ou de compra a termo</P><P>Os edifícios em questão devem, de preferência, estar concluídos ou quase concluídos. Contudo, podem ser propostos projetos para servir, conforme o caso, no contexto de uma prospectiva futura.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finalidades da prospeção</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O objetivo da prospeção é recolher propostas para edifícios de escritórios que possam atender às necessidades da Comissão, dentro dos perímetros indicados no ponto 2 supra.</P><P>Para o efeito, os proprietários ou os seus representantes são convidados a preencher a folha de prospeção disponível na seção «Contratos e concursos públicos - Aviso de prospeção imobiliária» do sítio Internet indicado no ponto 1.</P><P>É garantida a confidencialidade das informações recebidas. As fichas de prospeção serão então arquivadas numa base de dados segura, que só será acessível para funcionários da Comissão Europeia legalmente autorizados.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atualização das informações recolhidas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>As informações recolhidas e arquivadas na base de dados serão utilizadas pela Comissão para identificar edifícios que possam atender às necessidades do seu espaço de escritórios.</P><P>Para os edifícios identificados, o OIB abordará os proprietários para obter informações detalhadas sobre a condição e as capacidades do edifício em questão, bem como sobre as condições financeiras previstas.</P><P>Se, com base nas informações detalhadas, a Comissão considerar que os edifícios em questão podem satisfazer eficazmente as suas necessidades, pode ser iniciado um processo por negociação com o(s) proprietário(s) dos edifícios em causa, em conformidade com o disposto no artigo 134.º do regulamento (UE, Euratom) n.º 1268/2012 relativo às normas de execução do Regulamento (UE, Euratom) n.º966/2012.</P><P>A presente publicação não constitui, de forma alguma, um compromisso para a Comissão no quadro dos procedimentos de adjudicação de contratos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Apresentação das fichas de prospeção</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Os registos de prospeção assinados e datados devem ser apresentados pelos proprietários ou os seus representantes devidamente autorizados até (30 dias úteis após a data de publicação) às 16:30.</P><P>As informações devem ser apresentadas segundo as modalidades seguintes, à escolha:</P><P>— quer por correio registado, fazendo fé a data do carimbo dos correios, no endereço seguinte: Comissão Europeia, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Bélgica,</P><P>— quer por entrega (diretamente, ou por qualquer mandatário do candidato, inclusive por um serviço de correio por mensageiro), no endereço seguinte: Comissão Europeia, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Bélgica. Este serviço está aberto das 8:00 às 16:30, de segunda a quinta-feira, e das 8:00 às 16:00 à sexta-feira, exceto nos dias feriados da Comissão.</P><P>No caso de entrega através de um mensageiro, faz fé a data de envio. No caso de entrega direta ou por qualquer mandatário, a entrega da resposta deverá ser comprovada através de um recibo datado e assinado pelo funcionário do serviço central de receção do correio da Comissão a quem os documentos foram entregues.</P><P>Em todos os casos, o proprietário ou o seu representante deve respeitar igualmente as seguintes condições:</P><P>— a proposta deve ser apresentada em 2 sobrescritos,</P><P>— os 2 sobrescritos devem ser fechados,</P><P>— o envelope interior deve conter, além da indicação do serviço do destinatário, a referência «Anúncio de prospeção de imóveis para atender às necessidades da Comissão Europeia em instalações de escritórios em Bruxelas», «Ficha de prospeção de (nome do proprietário ou seu representante)», «Não abrir pelos serviços do correio»,</P><P>— os sobrescritos autocolantes devem ser fechados com fita adesiva sobre a qual será aposta a assinatura do remetente,</P><P>— se o proprietário ou o seu representante desejar obter informações adicionais antes da data de apresentação das propostas, deve enviar o seu pedido apenas por correio eletrónico para o endereço eletrónico indicado no ponto 1 supra. Além disso, os proponentes são convidados a consultar regularmente o sítio Internet indicado no ponto 1 do presente anúncio, que publicará regularmente as questões colocadas pelos proponentes e as respostas da Comissão,</P><P>— a data-limite para o envio de questões é (10 dias úteis antes da data de encerramento) às 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: Meddelande med information till fastighetsmarknaden – prognos för Europeiska kommissionens fleråriga fastighetsbehov i Bryssel och undersökning av den lokala marknaden (2020–2024)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ansvarig avdelning vid Europeiska kommissionen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska kommissionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien, E-postadress: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> – Webbplats: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Allmän information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>I överensstämmelse med kommissionens meddelande KOM(2007)501 av den 5.9.2007 är avsikten med detta meddelande att informera aktörerna på fastighetsmarknaden och övriga intresserade parter avseende prognosen om Europeiska kommissionens fastighetsbehov i Bryssel och att samla in information gällande projekt och fastigheter inom ett definierat område.</P><P>De lokaler som eftersöks</P><P>För att uppfylla sina behov avseende kontorsyta under 2020–2024 eftersöker Europeiska kommissionen kontorsutrymmen i Bryssel som ligger:</P><P>– inom 700 meter från sträckan mellan tunnelbanestationen Mérode och Arts-Loi samt mellan tunnelbanestationen Arts-Loi och De Brouckère,</P><P>– eller inom 700 meter från tunnelbanesträckan mellan tunnelbanestationen Arts-Loi och stationen Rogier,</P><P>– eller inom 700 meter från tunnelbanesträckan mellan tunnelbanestationen Delta och stationen Hermann-Debroux,</P><P>Ytan där byggnader eftersöks, där man ska byta ut antingen de byggnader som är i slutet av sin livscykel eller de vars hyresavtal löper ut, består av mellan 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> et 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> under perioden 2020–2024. De faktiska behoven kommer särskilt att bero på resultatet av pågående förhandlingar eller att genomföras för att förnya avtal som kommer att löpa ut de kommande åren för ett visst antal byggnader som nyttjas av kommissionen.</P><P>De byggnader som eftersöks för att uppfylla dessa behov måste alla ha en bruttoyta på minst 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> över mark. De kommer företrädesvis att helt och uteslutande nyttjas av kommissionen och/eller andra europeiska institutioner eller gemenskapsorgan.</P><P> De föreslagna kontrakten kommer att vara kontrakt för nyttjanderätt och/eller framtida köp</P><P>Byggnaderna i fråga ska vara färdigställda eller ska färdigställas i framtiden. Projekt kan dock föreslås för användning, i förekommande fall, inom ramen för en framtida prospekt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Syften med prospektering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Syftet med prospekteringen är att samla in förslag på kontorsbyggnader som kan fylla kommissionens behov, inom området som anges under punkt 2 ovan.</P><P>För detta ändamål uppmanas ägarna eller deras representanter att slutföra prospekteringsdokumentet som finns tillgängligt i avsnittet "Kontrakt och offentlig upphandling – Meddelande om fastighetsprospektion" på den webbplats som anges i punkt 1.</P><P>Den mottagna informationens konfidentialitet garanteras. Prospekteringsdokumenten sparas i en säker databas till vilken endast Europeiska kommissionens bemyndigade offentliganställda har tillgång.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Användning av insamlad information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Den insamlade informationen som lagrats i databasen används av kommissionen för att identifiera byggnader som kan tillgodose dess krav på kontorsyta.</P><P>För de identifierade byggnaderna ska Infrastruktur- och logistikbyrån vända sig till ägarna för att få detaljerad information om byggnadens skick, kapacitet samt de planerade ekonomiska förutsättningarna.</P><P>Om kommissionen, baserat på den detaljerade informationen, anser att byggnaderna i fråga kan uppfylla dess behov kan ett förhandlat förfarande inledas med ägarna av byggnaderna i fråga, i enlighet med artikel 134 i förordning (EU, Euratom) nr 1268/2012 om tillämpningsföreskrifterna för förordning (EU, Euratom) nr 966/2012.</P><P>Detta meddelande innebär dock inte på något sätt ett åtagande från kommissionens sida med avseende på dess förfaranden för tilldelning av kontrakt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Leverans av prospekteringsdokument</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De signerade och daterade prospekteringsdokumenten måste lämnas av ägaren eller dess behöriga representanter senast kl. 16:30, 30 vardagar efter publiceringsdatumet.</P><P>Informationen måste lämnas på ett av följande sätt:</P><P>–antingen via rekommenderad post, varvid poststämpeln gäller som bevis, till följande adress: Europeiska kommissionen, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgien,</P><P>– Eller genom direktinlämning (personligen, genom ombud för den sökande eller genom budfirma), till följande adress: Europeiska kommissionen, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgien. Denna avdelning är öppen 8:00–16:30 måndag till torsdag och 8:00–16:00 på fredagar, med undantag för kommissionens helgdagar.</P><P>Vid inlämning via bud gäller det datum som står på budets leveranssedel som datum för avsändande. Personlig inlämning eller inlämning via ombud ska i förekommande fall bekräftas genom ett mottagningsbevis som daterats och undertecknats av den tjänsteman vid kommissionens centrala postavdelning som mottar handlingarna.</P><P>I vilket fall ska ägaren eller dess representant respektera följande villkor:</P><P>– Prospekteringsdokumentet ska insändas i dubbla kuvert.</P><P>– Båda kuverten ska förslutas.</P><P>– På det inre kuvertet ska, förutom indikation om mottagare, referensen “avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles” [prospektionsmeddelande av byggnader för att uppfylla Europeiska kommissionens behov gällande kontorsytor i Bryssel], “fiche de prospection de (namn på ägaren eller dess representant)” [prospekteringsdokument för], “à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courrier” [öppnas ej av posttjänsten] stå skriven,</P><P>– Självhäftande kuvert ska förslutas med tejp, över vilken avsändaren ska skriva sin namnteckning.</P><P>– Om ägaren eller dess representant vill få kompletterande upplysningar innan inlämningsdatumet för förslag, skickar hen sin förfrågan till e-postadressen som anges i punkt 1 ovan. Sökande ombes också att regelbundet kontrollera den webbplats som anges i punkt 1 eftersom frågor och kommissionens svar på dessa regelbundet kommer att publiceras där.</P><P>– Frågor ska skickas senast kl 16:00, 10 vardagar innan tidsfristen löper ut.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: Oznámení určené trhu s nemovitostmi – Předběžné oznámení o víceleté potřebě služeb v oblasti nemovitostí v letech 2020 až 2024, které budou poskytovány Evropské komisi v Bruselu, včetně průzkumu místního trhu</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Odpovědné oddělení Evropské komise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská komise</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>Úřad pro infrastrukturu a logistiku v Bruselu – département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgie, email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> - Internetová stránka: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Obecné informace:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>V souladu se sdělením Komise KOM (2007)501 ze dne 5.9.2007 je cílem tohoto oznámení informovat subjekty zapojené do trhu s nemovitostmi a ostatní zainteresované strany o předběžných informacích týkajících se oblasti nemovitostí v rámci Evropské komise v Bruselu a sbírat informace o nemovitých projektech a nemovitostech v definovaném okruhu.</P><P>Hledané nemovitosti</P><P>Vzhledem k potřebě kancelářských prostor, které bude Evropská komise v horizontu 2020-2024 potřebovat, hledá komise kancelářské prostory v Bruselu, které se nacházejí:</P><P>- v maximální vzdálenosti do 700 m na ose mezi zastávkami metra Mérode a Arts-Loi a zastávkami metra Arts-Loi a De Brouckère,</P><P>- nebo v maximální vzdálenosti do 700 m na ose linky metra mezi zastávkami Arts-Loi a Rogier,</P><P>- nebo v maximální vzdálenosti do 700 m na ose linky metra mezi zastávkami Delta a Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Celková nezastavěná plocha hledaných prostor, které by měly v období 2020-2024 nahradit budovy, které jsou na konci své životnosti nebo u nichž dochází k vypršení nájemní smlouvy, se pohybuje mezi 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> a 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Skutečné potřeby se odvinou od výsledku probíhajících nebo budoucích jednání o obnovení nájemních smluv týkajících se určitého počtu budov využívaných útvary Komise, jejichž platnost vyprší v následujících letech.</P><P>Hrubá podlažní plocha hledaných budov pro tyto potřeby musí být nejméně 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Tyto budovy budou zcela a výhradně používány útvary Komise a/nebo útvary</P><P>jiných evropských institucí nebo orgánů společenství. Navržené smlouvy budou buď smlouvy na užívací právo a/nebo termínový nákup</P><P>Dotčené budovy musí být již hotové nebo dokončeny v blízké budoucnosti. Projekty, mohou být v případě potřeby nabídnuty k budoucímu využití.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Účel průzkumu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cílem průzkumu je sběr nabídek kancelářských prostor, které odpovídají požadavkům Komise, a to v okruhu uvedeném v bodě č. 2.</P><P>Majitelé nemovitostí nebo zmocnění jednatelé jsou vyzváni k vyplnění formuláře průzkumu, který je k dispozici v rubrice „smlouvy a veřejné zakázky - výzva k průzkumu trhu s nemovitostmi“ na webové stránce uvedené v bodě č. 1.</P><P>Sebrané informace zůstanou důvěrné. Formuláře průzkumu budou následně archivovány v zabezpečené databázi, ke které budou mít přístup pouze zmocnění pracovníci ve služebním poměru k Evropské komisi.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Použití sebraných informací:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sebrané a archivované informace budou použity Evropskou komisí za účelem nalezení budov odpovídajících potřebám Komise v otázce kancelářských prostor o požadované rozloze.</P><P>OIB kontaktuje majitele vybraných nemovitostí za účelem získání podrobných informací o stavu a způsobilosti budov a předpokládaných finančních podmínkách.</P><P>Pokud Komise na základě podrobných informací vyhodnotí, že dané budovy odpovídají potřebám Komise, bude s majitelem/i dané nemovitosti zahájeno jednací řízení, a to v souladu s ustanovením článku 134 nařízení č. 1268/2012 (EU, Euratom) o prováděcích pravidlech k nařízení (EU, Euratom) č. 966/2012.</P><P>Toto oznámení Komisi nijak nezavazuje, pokud jde o řízení pro zadání zakázek.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Předložení formulářů průzkumu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Podepsané a datované formuláře průzkumu musí být majiteli nemovitostí nebo jejich pověřenými zástupci zaslány do (30 pracovních dní od zveřejnění) 16:30.</P><P>Přihlášky musí být podány 1 z následujících způsobů:</P><P>— doporučenou zásilkou, o čemž svědčí poštovní razítko, na následující adresu: Evropská komise, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 - Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgie,</P><P>— doručením (osobně nebo prostřednictvím jakékoliv strany, která uchazeče zastupuje, nebo kurýra) na následující adresu: Evropská komise, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 - Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgie. Toto oddělení je otevřeno od 8:00 do 16:30, pondělí až čtvrtek, od 8:00 do 16:00 v pátky s výjimkou státních svátků Komise.</P><P>Pro doručení kurýrem bude platným datem odeslání datum na dodacím listu kurýra. V případě osobního doručení nebo doručení prostřednictvím jakéhokoliv zástupce bude přijetí odezvy potvrzeno datovaný potvrzením podepsaným úředníkem ústředního podatelny Komise, jenž zásilku dokumentů převezme.</P><P>V každém případě musí majitel nemovitosti nebo jeho zástupce respektovat následující podmínky:</P><P>- formuláře průzkumu musí být zaslány ve dvojité obálce,</P><P>- obě obálky musí být zalepené,</P><P>- na vnitřní obálce musí být uvedeno jméno oddělení, označení „průzkum trhu nemovitostí v oblasti kancelářských prostor pro potřeby Evropské komise“, „formulář průzkumu (jméno majitele nemovitosti nebo jeho zástupce)“, „neotvírat v podatelně“,</P><P>- samolepící obálky musí být přelepeny lepící páskou, s podpisem odesilatele přes pásku,</P><P>- pokud si majitel nemovitosti nebo jeho zástupce přeje obdržet doplňující informace před termínem pro podávání přihlášek, zašle svůj dotaz pouze prostřednictvím emailové zprávy na adresu uvedenou v bodě č.1. Navrhovatelé se také vyzývají k pravidelným návštěvám internetové stránky uvedené v bodě 1, protože zde budou pravidelně zveřejňovány dotazy navrhovatelů a odpovědi Komise,</P><P>- lhůta pro zasílání dotazů je (10 pracovních dní před datem uzávěrky) do 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: Kinnisvaraturule suunatud teade – mitmeaastased prognoosid Euroopa Komisjoni kinnisvaranõudluse kohta Brüsselis (2020–2024) ja kohaliku turu uurimine</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Euroopa Komisjoni vastutav osakond</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Komisjon</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia, e-post: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Veebisait: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Üldteave:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Käesoleva teate eesmärk on kooskõlas komisjoni 5.9.2007 teatisega [COM(2007)501] teavitada kinnisvaraturul osalejaid ning kõiki muid huvitatud pooli prognoosidest Euroopa Komisjoni kinnisvaranõudluse kohta Brüsselis ja koguda teavet ehitusprojektide ja kinnisvara kohta määratud piirkonnas.</P><P>Uuritud hooned</P><P>Omale perioodil 2020–2024 vajalike bürooruumide hankimiseks korraldab Euroopa Komisjon uuringu Brüsselis asuvate büroopindade kohta, mis asuvad</P><P>— maksimaalselt 700 meetrit Mérode‘i metroojaama ja Arts-Loi metroojaama vahele ning Arts-Loi metroojaama ja De Brouckère‘i metroojaama vahele jäävade osade teljest;</P><P>— või maksimaalselt 700 meetrit Arts-Loi metroojaama ja Rogieri jaama vahele jääva metrooliini teljest;</P><P>— või maksimaalselt 700 meetrit Delta metroojaama ja Hermann-Debroux‘ jaama vahele jääva metrooliini teljest.</P><P>Otsitav maapealne kogupind, et asendada hooneid, mille olelusring hakkab ajavahemikul 2020–2024 lõpule jõudma või mille rendileping hakkab lõppema, on vahemikus 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> kuni 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Konkreetne vajadus tuleneb eelkõige toimuvatest või tulevastest läbirääkimistest lähiaastatel saabuvate lõpptähtaegadega rendilepingute pikendamiseks teatud hulga komisjoni teenistuste kasutuses oleva kinnisvara kasutamiseks.</P><P>Nende vajaduste rahuldamiseks otsitavate hoonte maapealne üldpindala peab olema vähemalt 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Eelistatult on need täielikult ja üksnes komisjoni teenistuste ja/või muude</P><P>Euroopa institutsioonide või ühenduse asutuste teenistuste kasutuses. Pakutavad lepingud on omandiosalusega ja/või lihtforvardi põhised ostulepingud.</P><P>Eelistatult on kõnealused hooned valmis või valmivad tulevikus. Vajaduse korral võib neid projekte siiski välja pakkuda ka tulevikuperspektiivi raamistikus kasutamiseks.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uuringu eesmärgid</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uuringu eesmärk on koguda eespool punktis 2 nimetatud piirkondades asuvate büroohoonete pakkumisi, mis võivad vastata komisjoni vajadustele.</P><P>Selleks on omanikud või nende volitatud esindajad kutsutud täitma uuringulehte, mis on kättesaadav punktis 1 nimetatud veebisaidi osas „lepingud ja riigihanked — Kinnisvara uuringu teade“.</P><P>Saadud teabe konfidentsiaalsus on tagatud. Uuringulehti säilitatakse turvalises andmebaasis, millele on juurdepääs ainult Euroopa Komisjoni korrakohaselt volitatud avalikel teenistujatel.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kogutud teabe kasutamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kogutud ja andmebaasis arhiveeritud teavet kasutab komisjon selleks, et valida välja hooned, mis võivad vastata selle vajadustele büroopinna osas.</P><P>Välja valitud hoonete omanikega võtab infrastruktuuri- ja logistikaamet ühendust, et saada üksikasjalikku teavet vastava hoone seisukorra ja omaduste ning ka plaanitavate rahaliste tingimuste kohta.</P><P>Kui selle üksikasjaliku teabe põhjal arvab komisjon, et asjaomased hooned võivad tõepoolest vastata selle vajadustele, võidakse asjaomaste hoonete omanikuga/omanikega alustada läbirääkimistega menetluse vastavalt määruse (EL, Euratom) nr 1268/2012, mis käsitleb määruse (EL, EURATOM) nr 966/2012 kohaldamise eeskirju, artiklile 134.</P><P>Siiski ei kohusta käesolev teade Euroopa Komisjoni mitte mingil viisil lepingut sõlmima.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uuringulehtede edastamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Omanikud või nende nõuetekohaselt volitatud esindajad peavad saatma allkirjastatud ja kuupäevastatud uuringulehed (hiljemalt 30 tööpäeva pärast avaldamise kuupäeva) enne kella 16:30.</P><P>Teave tuleb saata ühel alljärgneval viisil:</P><P>— tähitud postiga, mida tõendab postitempel, aadressil: Euroopa Komisjon, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgia;</P><P>— käsipostiga (isiklikult või kandidaadi volitatud esindaja kaudu või kulleriteenust kasutades) aadressil: Euroopa Komisjon, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgia. Nimetatud osakond on avatud esmaspäevast neljapäevani 8:00–16:30 ning reedeti 8:00–16:00, välja arvatud komisjoni puhkepäevadel.</P><P>Kulleriteenuse puhul arvestatakse väljasaatmise kuupäeva kulleri saatelehel. Juhul kui dokumendid toimetatakse kohale isiklikult või esindaja kaudu, kinnitab üleandmist kuupäevastatud kviitung, millele kirjutab alla komisjoni keskpostitalituse ametnik, kes dokumendid vastu võtab.</P><P>Igal juhul peab omanik või tema esindaja järgima järgmisi reegleid:</P><P>— uuringuleht tuleb saata kahekordses ümbrikus;</P><P>— need 2 ümbrikut peavad olema suletud;</P><P>— sisemisel ümbrikul peab olema lisaks vastuvõtva teenistuse aadressile viide „avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles“, „fiche de prospection de (nom du propriétaire ou son représentant)“, „à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courrier“;</P><P>— iseliimuvad ümbrikud tuleb sulgeda kleeplindiga, üle mille kirjutab saatja oma allkirja;</P><P>— kui omanik või tema esindaja soovib saada enne pakkumiste esitamise tähtpäeva lisateavet, peab ta saatma taotluse vaid e-postiga eespool punktis 1 nimetatud aadressile. Pakkujatel palutakse samuti regulaarselt külastada teate punktis 1 nimetatud veebisaiti, kus avaldatakse regulaarselt komisjoni antud vastused esitatud küsimustele;</P><P>— küsimuste saatmise tähtaeg on (10 tööpäeva enne lõppkuupäeva) kell 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüsszel: Tájékoztató felhívás az ingatlanpiac számára – többéves előrejelzések az Európai Bizottság brüsszeli ingatlanok iránti igényei kapcsán (2020–2024), valamint a helyi piac felmérése</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az Európai Bizottság illetékes szervezeti egysége</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európai Bizottság</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium, e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Weboldal: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Általános információ:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>E hirdetmény célja – az 5.9.2007 keltezésű COM(2007)501 bizottsági közleménnyel összhangban – az ingatlanpiac résztvevői és más érdekelt felek tájékoztatása az Európai Bizottság brüsszeli ingatlanok iránti várható igényeiről, valamint a megadott területen található ingatlanprojektekről és ingatlanokról történő információgyűjtés.</P><P>Keresett ingatlanok</P><P>A 2020-tól 2024-ig terjedő időtartamra vonatkozó irodaterület-igényeinek kielégítése érdekében az Európai Bizottság az alábbiaknak megfelelő irodaterületeket keres:</P><P>— a Mérode és az Arts-Loi metróállomás közötti, valamint az Arts-Loi és a De Brouckère metróállomás közötti szegmensek legfeljebb 700 méteres körzetében lévő irodaterületek,</P><P>— vagy az Arts-Loi metróállomás és a Rogier állomás közötti metróvonal tengelyétől számított legfeljebb 700 méteres körzetben,</P><P>— vagy a Delta metróállomás és a Hermann-Debroux állomás közötti metróvonal tengelyétől számított legfeljebb 700 méteres körzetben.</P><P>A keresett felszín feletti terület nagysága 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> és 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> közötti a 2020-tól 2024-ig terjedő időszakra vonatkozóan, az életciklusuk végén járó épületek cseréje céljából, vagy azon épületek vonatkozásában, melyek esetében a területbérlési megállapodás lejár. Az aktuális igények nevezetesen az elkövetkezendő években folyamatban lévő vagy a lejártukhoz közeledő megállapodások megújítása vonatkozásában folytatandó tárgyalások eredményeinek függvénye, bizonyos számú, a Bizottság szervezeti egységei által elfoglalt épületekre irányulóan.</P><P>Az igények kielégítése céljából keresett valamennyi épület bruttó felszíni területének legalább 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>-nek kell lennie. Ezen épületeknek lehetőség szerint alkalmasnak kell lenniük arra, hogy teljességgel és kizárólagosan a Bizottság szervezeti egységei és/vagy egyéb európai intézmények vagy közösségi szervek szervezeti egységei foglalják el őket.</P><P> Az ajánlott szerződések haszonélvezeti és/vagy határidős vételi szerződések lesznek</P><P>A szóban forgó épületeknek befejezettnek kell lenniük vagy befejezés előtt kell állniuk. Ennek ellenére az ajánlatok tervekre is vonatkozhatnak, amelyeket adott esetben egy jövőbeli lehetőség keretében figyelembe vehetnek.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A felmérés céljai</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A felmérés célja olyan irodaépületekre irányuló javaslatok gyűjtése, melyek megfelelnek a Bizottság igényeinek, és a fenti 2. pontban megadott területen belül helyezkednek el.</P><P>E célból a tulajdonosokat vagy képviselőiket felkérik az 1. pontban feltüntetett címen elérhető weboldal „contrats et marchés publics — Avis de prospection immobilière” részében elérhető felmérési adatlap kitöltésére.</P><P>A megadott információkat bizalmasan kezelik. A felmérési adatlapok ezt követően egy biztonságos adatbázisban kerülnek archiválásra, amelyhez kizárólag az Európai Bizottság megfelelően felhatalmazott közszolgálati alkalmazottai férhetnek hozzá.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A gyűjtött információk felhasználása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A gyűjtött és az adatbázisban archivált információkat a Bizottság az irodaterület-igényeinek megfelelő épületek azonosítására használja fel.</P><P>Az OIB felveszi a kapcsolatot azonosított épületek tulajdonosaival az érintett épületek állapotáról és kapacitásairól történő részletes információszerzés, valamint a tervezett pénzügyi feltételek megállapítása céljából.</P><P>E részletes információk alapján a Bizottság megállapítja, hogy a szóban forgó épületek ténylegesen megfelelnek-e az igényeinek, és amennyiben igen, tárgyalásos eljárást indíthat az érintett épületek tulajdonosaival a 966/2012/EU, Euratom rendelet alkalmazási szabályairól szóló 1268/2012/EU, Euratom rendelet 134. cikkében szereplő rendelkezéseknek megfelelően.</P><P>A jelen hirdetmény azonban nem kötelezi a Bizottságot szerződés odaítélésére a közbeszerzési eljárásai keretében.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A felmérési adatlapok benyújtása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Az aláírt és dátummal ellátott felmérési adatlapokat a tulajdonosoknak vagy a megfelelően meghatározott képviselőknek a következő határidőig kell benyújtaniuk: (a közzététel dátumát követő 30 munkanap), 16:30.</P><P>Az információkat a következő módok egyikén benyújtani:</P><P>– a következő címre küldött ajánlott küldeményben (a feladást a postabélyegzőn szereplő dátum igazolja): Európai Bizottság, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgium,</P><P>– kézbesítés útján (személyesen vagy a jelölt képviselője által, beleértve a futárszolgálatot is) a következő címre: Európai Bizottság, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgium. A hivatal hétfőtől csütörtökig 8:00–16:30 között, pénteken 8:00–16:00 között áll rendelkezésre, a Bizottság munkaszüneti napjainak kivételével.</P><P>A futár általi kézbesítés esetén annak érvényes időpontja a futár kézbesítési szelvényén található dátum. Ha a jelentkezést személyesen vagy képviselő útján nyújtják be, akkor a kézbesítést a Bizottság Központi Postaszolgálata részéről a dokumentumokat átvevő tisztviselő dátummal és aláírással ellátott átvételi elismervénye igazolja.</P><P>A tulajdonosnak vagy képviselőjének minden esetben be kell tartania az alábbi szabályokat is:</P><P>— a felmérési adatlapot dupla borítékban kell elküldeni,</P><P>— mindkét borítékot le kell zárni,</P><P>— a belső borítékon a címzett részleg neve mellett az alábbiakat is fel kell tüntetni: „avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles”, „fiche de prospection de (a tulajdonos vagy képviselője neve)”, „à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courrier”,</P><P>— az öntapadó borítékokat ragasztószalaggal kell lezárni, és a szalagot a feladónak átlósan alá kell írnia,</P><P>— amennyiben a tulajdonosnak vagy képviselőjének további információra lenne szüksége az ajánlatok benyújtási határideje előtt, akkor kérdését a fenti 1. pontban megadott címre küldheti, kizárólag e-mailben. Az ajánlattevőknek rendszeresen fel kell keresniük az 1. pontban szereplő weboldalt is, ahol rendszeresen közzéteszik a feltett kérdéseket és a Bizottság válaszait,</P><P>— a kérdések beküldésének határideje: (a lezárási határidő előtt 10 munkanappal), 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Briuselis: Informacinis pranešimas dėl nekilnojamojo turto rinkos – Europos Komisijos Briuselyje daugiametės nekilnojamojo turto poreikių prognozės nuo 2020 iki 2024 m. ir vietos rinkos žvalgymas</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsakingas Europos Komisijos departamentas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos Komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija, el. paštas: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> – interneto svetainė: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bendra informacija:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Vadovaujantis 5.9.2007 Komisijos komunikatu [COM(2007)501] šiuo skelbimu siekiama informuoti nekilnojamojo turto rinkos dalyvius ir kitas suinteresuotas šalis apie Briuselyje įsikūrusios Europos Komisijos nekilnojamojo turto poreikius ir surinkti informaciją apie nekilnojamojo turto projektus ir esančius objektus apibrėžtoje teritorijoje.</P><P>Ieškoma objektų</P><P>Siekdama patenkinti savo biuro patalpų poreikius periodui 2020–2024 m., Europos Komisija ieško biuro patalpų Briuselyje, esančių</P><P>— ne daugiau kaip 700 metrų atstumu nuo rajono ašies tarp metro stoties „Mérode“ ir „Arts-Loi“ metro stoties, tarp „Arts-Loi“ metro stoties ir metro stoties „De Brouckère“,</P><P>— arba ne daugiau kaip 700 metrų nuo metro linijos ašies tarp metro stoties „Arts-Loi“ ir stoties „Rogier“,</P><P>— arba ne daugiau kaip 700 metrų nuo metro linijos ašies tarp metro stoties „Delta“ ir stoties „Hermann-Debroux“.</P><P>Bendras plotas be žemės, kurio ieškoma, siekiant pakeisti pastatus esančius naudojimo ciklo pabaigoje arba kurių nuomos sutarties laikotarpis baigiasi, yra nuo 80 000 kv. m iki 150 000 kv. m, laikotarpiui nuo 2020 iki 2024 m. Faktiniai poreikiai pirmiausia priklausys nuo vykstančių arba būsimų derybų dėl besibaigiančių sutarčių atnaujinimo, kurios baigs galioti artimiausiais metais, ir yra susijusios su keletu pastatų, kuriuose įsikūrusios Komisijos tarnybos.</P><P>Ieškomų pastatų bendras plotas, kad užtikrintų šiuos poreikius, kiekvieno turi būti ne mažesnis nei 10 000 kv. m be žemės. Pageidautina, kad juos visiškai ir pilnai užimtų Komisijos tarnybos ir (arba) kitų Europos institucijų tarnybos</P><P>arba Bendrijos įstaigos. Siūlomos sutartys bus uzufrukto ir (arba) išankstinio pirkimo sutartys.</P><P>Pageidautina, kad aptariami pastatai būtų užbaigti arba artimiausiu metu planuojami užbaigti. Tačiau projektai, vis dėlto irgi gali būti siūlomi, atsižvelgiant į konkretų atvejį dėl ateityje ieškomų objektų.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Žvalgymo tikslai</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Žvalgymo tikslas – surinkti biurų pastatų pasiūlymus, kurie galėtų patenkinti Komisijos poreikius, pagal anksčiau 2 punkte, nurodytas zonas.</P><P>Šiuo tikslu savininkai arba jų atstovai kviečiami užpildyti žvalgymo anketą, esančią interneto svetainės 1 skyriuje „Sutartys ir viešieji pirkimai“ – pranešimas apie nekilnojamojo turto žvalgymą“.</P><P>Informacijos konfidencialumas garantuojamas. Tada žvalgybos anketos bus patalpinamos į archyvą ir saugomos saugioje duomenų bazėje, prie kurios prieigą turės tik statutiniai Europos Komisijos tinkamai įgalioti darbuotojai.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Surinktos informacijos naudojimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Surinkta ir archyvo duomenų bazėje saugoma informacija naudosis Komisija atrenkant pastatus, kurie tenkintų jos biurų poreikius.</P><P>Su atrinktų pastatų savininkais susisieks OIB ir prašys išsamios informacijos apie atitinkamo pastato būklę ir pajėgumus, o taip pat apie numatomas finansines sąlygas.</P><P>Jei remdamasi šia išsamia informacija Komisija mano, kad aptariami pastatai iš tikrųjų gali patenkinti jos poreikius, gali būti pradėta derybų procedūra su atitinkamų pastatų savininku (-ais) pagal Reglamento 134 straipsnio nuostatas (ES, Euratomas) Nr. 1268/2012 dėl Reglamento (ES, Euratomas) Nr. 966/2012 įgyvendinimo taisyklių.</P><P>Šis skelbimas jokiu būdu neįpareigoja Komisijos sutarties skyrimo procedūrų požiūriu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Žvalgymo anketų teikimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Žvalgymo anketas su parašu ir data turi pateikti savininkai arba jų tinkamai įgalioti atstovai iki (30 darbo dienų nuo paskelbimo datos) 16:30.</P><P>Informacija turi būti pateikta šiais būdais, pasirinktinai:</P><P>— paštu, registruotu laišku, su patvirtinančiu pašto antspaudu, šiuo adresu: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgija,</P><P>— pristatant (tiesiogiai arba per kandidatą atstovaujantį asmenį arba per kurjerį), šiuo adresu: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgija. Ši tarnyba dirba pirmadieniais–ketvirtadieniais nuo 8:00 iki 16:30, o penktadienį nuo 8:00 iki 16:00, išskyrus Komisijos šventines dienas.</P><P>Jeigu pristato kurjeris, ant pristatymo kvito bus nurodyta išsiuntimo data. Pristatant asmeniškai arba per atstovą, pristatymas bus patvirtintas dokumentus priimančio Komisijos centrinio pašto skyriaus pareigūno pasirašytu kvitu su data, kuriam dokumentai buvo įteikti.</P><P>Visais atvejais savininkas arba jo atstovas privalo laikytis šių sąlygų:</P><P>— žvalgymo anketa turi būti siunčiama dvigubame voke,</P><P>— abu vokai turi būti užklijuoti,</P><P>— vidinis vokas nurodant gavėjo tarnybą su nuoroda „skelbimas apie pastatų žvalgymą dėl Europos Komisijos biurų patalpų poreikių tenkinimo Briuselyje“, „žvalgymo anketa (savininko vardas arba jo atstovas)“, „negali būti atplėšiamas pašto tarnybos“,</P><P>— užklijuojami vokai dar turi būti užklijuoti lipnia juostele, per kurią turi būti matomas siuntėjo parašas,</P><P>— jei savininkas arba jo atstovas nori gauti papildomos informacijos iki pasiūlymų pateikimo dienos, jis turi pateikti savo prašymą tik aukščiau 1 punkte nurodytu elektroniniu paštu. Pasiūlymų teikėjai taip pat yra kviečiami reguliariai apsilankyti 1 punkte nurodytoje tinklavietėje, kuri nuolat skelbs pateiktus klausimus ir Komisijos atsakymus,</P><P>— klausimų pateikimo terminas yra (10 darbo dienų iki galutinės datos) 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brisele: Informatīvs paziņojums nekustamā īpašuma tirgum – daudzgadu prognozes (2020.–2024. gadam) par Eiropas Komisijas ar nekustamo īpašumu saistītajām vajadzībām Briselē un vietējā tirgus izpēte</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Eiropas Komisijas atbildīgais departaments</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Beļģija, e-pasts: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> , tīmekļa vietne: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vispārīga informācija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Saskaņā ar Komisijas 5.9.2007 Paziņojumu COM(2007) 501 šā paziņojuma mērķis ir informēt nekustamā īpašuma tirgū iesaistītās, kā arī jebkuras citas ieinteresētās personas par prognozi attiecībā uz Eiropas Komisijas ar nekustamo īpašumu saistītajām vajadzībām Briselē un apkopot informāciju par projektiem un nekustamo īpašumu noteiktajās teritorijas robežās.</P><P>Meklētās ēkas</P><P>Lai izpildītu nepieciešamās ar biroju telpām saistītās vajadzības 2020.–2024. gadam, Eiropas Komisija meklē biroju telpas Briselē, kas atrodas:</P><P>— ne vairāk kā 700 metrus no līnijas, kas savieno metro stacijas Mérode un Arts-Loi un metro stacijas Arts-Loi un De Brouckère,</P><P>— vai ne vairāk kā 700 metrus no līnijas, kas savieno metro stacijas Arts-Loi un Rogier,</P><P>— vai ne vairāk kā 700 metrus no līnijas, kas savieno metro stacijas Delta un Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Meklēto telpu kopējā virszemes platība pēc iepriekšējo telpu dzīves cikla beigām vai, ja tām beidzas īres līgums, ir 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>–150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> 2020.–2024. gadam. Faktiskās vajadzības būs jo īpaši atkarīgas no notiekošo vai turpmāko sarunu rezultāta par līgumu, kuru darbības laiks beidzas nākamo gadu laikā, atjaunošanu saistībā ar noteiktu skaitu ēku, kurās atrodas Komisijas dienesti.</P><P>Lai izpildītu šīs vajadzības, meklēto ēku katrai virszemes platībai jābūt vismaz 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Vēlams, lai telpās pilnībā atrastos tikai Komisijas dienesti un/vai citu</P><P>Eiropas iestāžu dienesti vai Eiropas Savienības struktūrvienības. Piedāvātie līgumi būs lietošanas tiesību un/vai nākotnes pirkšanas līgumi.</P><P>Vēlams, lai attiecīgās ēkas jau būtu vai drīzumā tiktu pabeigtas. Tomēr vajadzības gadījumā projektus var piedāvāt arī turpmākai atsaucei.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Izpētes mērķi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Izpētes mērķis ir apkopot piedāvājumus par biroju ēkām, lai izpildītu Komisijas vajadzības attiecībā uz iepriekš 2. punktā norādītajām platību robežām.</P><P>Šim nolūkam īpašnieki vai viņu pārstāvji ir aicināti aizpildīt izpētes veidlapu, kas pieejama 1. punktā norādītajā tīmekļa vietnē sadaļā “contrats et marchés publics — Avis de prospection immobilière” (“Līgumi un publiskie iepirkumi – paziņojums par nekustamā īpašuma izpēti”).</P><P>Saņemtās informācijas konfidencialitāte ir garantēta. Pēc tam izpētes veidlapas tiks arhivētas drošā datubāzē, kurai piekļuve dota tikai pienācīgi pilnvarotiem Eiropas Komisijas oficiālajiem darbiniekiem.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Apkopotās informācijas izmantošana</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Apkopoto un datubāzē arhivēto informāciju Komisija izmantos, lai atrastu savām vajadzībām nepieciešamās biroju telpas.</P><P>Tādā gadījumā OIB vērsīsies pie šo ēku īpašniekiem, lai iegūtu sīkāku informāciju par ēkas stāvokli un ietilpību, kā arī plānotajiem finanšu nosacījumiem.</P><P>Ņemot vērā šo informāciju, ja Komisija uzskata, ka attiecīgās ēkas atbilst tās vajadzībām, var tikt izsludināta sarunu procedūra ar šo ēku īpašnieku(-iem) saskaņā ar Komisijas Deleģētās regulas (ES) Nr. 1268/2012 (2012. gada 29. oktobris) par Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regulas (ES, Euratom) Nr. 966/2012 par finanšu noteikumiem, ko piemēro Savienības vispārējam budžetam, piemērošanas noteikumu 134. pantu.</P><P>Šis paziņojums nekādā veidā nav saistošs Komisijai attiecībā uz līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas procedūrām.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Izpētes veidlapu iesniegšana</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Īpašniekiem vai viņu pienācīgi pilnvarotajiem pārstāvjiem parakstītas un datētas izpētes veidlapas jāiesniedz 30 darbdienu laikā no paziņojuma publicēšanas brīža (līdz plkst. 16:30).</P><P>Informācija ir jānosūta 1 no tālāk norādītajiem veidiem.</P><P>— Nosūtot ierakstītu vēstuli, ko apliecina pasta zīmogs, uz šādu adresi: Eiropas Komisija, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique – Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 – Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Beļģija,</P><P>— Piegādājot (personīgi vai ar kandidāta pārstāvi, vai ar kurjeru) uz šādu adresi: Eiropas Komisija, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique – Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 – Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Beļģija. no pirmdienas līdz ceturtdienai plkst. 8:00–16:30 un piektdienās plkst. 8:00–16:00, izņemot Komisijas brīvdienas.</P><P>Ja veidlapas tiks piegādātas ar kurjeru, par nosūtīšanas datumu tiks uzskatīts kurjera pavadzīmē norādītais datums. Ja veidlapas tiks nodotas personīgi vai ar pārstāvja starpniecību, šādā gadījumā piegādi apliecinās kvīts, ko datējusi un parakstījusi par dokumentu saņemšanu atbildīgā Komisijas Centrālās pasta nodaļas amatpersona.</P><P>Visos gadījumos īpašniekam vai viņa pārstāvim jāievēro arī šādi nosacījumi:</P><P>— izpētes veidlapa ir jānosūta dubultā aploksnē,</P><P>— abām aploksnēm jābūt aizlīmētām,</P><P>— uz iekšējās aploksnes jābūt norādei, kuram dienestam tā ir adresēta, kā arī norādei “avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles” (paziņojums par nekustamā īpašuma izpēti Eiropas Komisijas vajadzību izpildei saistībā ar biroja telpām Briselē), “fiche de prospection de (īpašnieka vai pārstāvja vārds)” (izpētes veidlapa – (īpašnieka vai pārstāvja vārds)) un “à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courrier” (pasta dienestam neatvērt),</P><P>— pašlīmējošās aploksnes jāaizlīmē ar līmlenti, kurai pāri sūtītājs parakstās,</P><P>— ja īpašniekam vai viņa pārstāvim ir nepieciešama papildu informācija pirms piedāvājumu iesniegšanas datuma, viņam jānosūta pieprasījums uz iepriekš 1. punktā norādīto e-pasta adresi. Piedāvājumu iesniedzēji arī tiek aicināti regulāri apmeklēt 1. punktā norādīto tīmekļa vietni, jo tajā regulāri tiks publicēti uzdotie jautājumi un Komisijas atbildes,</P><P>— jautājumu nosūtīšanas termiņš ir 10 darbdienas pirms piedāvājumu iesniegšanas termiņa (līdz plkst. 16:00).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussell: Avviż ta' tagħrif għall-attenzjoni tas-suq tal-proprjetà — tbassir multiannwali għal ħtiġijiet tal-proprjetà tal-Kummissjoni Ewropea fi Brussell (mill-2020 sal-2024) u l-istħarriġ tas-suq lokali</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-dipartiment tal-Kummissjoni Ewropea responsabbli</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Il-Kummissjoni Ewropea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Belġju, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Sit tal-Internet: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif ġenerali:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bi qbil mal-Komunikazzjoni tal-Kummissjoni COM(2007)501 tal-5 ta' Settembru 2007, l-għan ta' dan l-avviż huwa li jgħarraf lil dawk involuti fis-suq tal-proprjetà, u kull parti oħra interessata, bit-tbassir għall-ħtiġijiet tal-proprjetà tal-Kummissjoni Ewropea fi Brussell, u biex jiġbor informazzjoni dwar il-proġetti u l-proprjetà immobbli f'żona definita.</P><P>Proprjetà rriċerkata</P><P>Sabiex tindirizza l-ħtiġijiet tagħha ta' spazju għal uffiċċji mill-2020 sal-2024, il-Kummissjoni Ewropea qed tfittex spazji għal uffiċċji fi Brussell, li jinsabu jew,</P><P>— f'massimu ta' 700 metru fil-medda bejn l-istazzjon tal-metro Mérode u l-istazzjon tal-metro ta' Arts-Loi u bejn l-istazzjon tal-metro ta' Arts-Loi u l-istazzjon tal-metro De Brouckère,</P><P>— jew f'massimu ta' 700 metru fil-medda fuq il-linja tal-metro bejn l-istazzjon tal-metro ta' Arts-Loi u l-istazzjon Rogier,</P><P>— jew f'massimu ta' 700 metru fil-medda fuq il-linja tal-metro bejn l-istazzjon tal-metro Delta u l-istazzjon Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Is-superfiċje fuq l-art totali rriċerkata, sabiex jiġu ssostitwiti proprjetajiet fl-aħħar taċ-ċiklu tal-ħajja jew li l-kuntratt tal-kiri tagħhom wasal biex jiskadi, hija bejn 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> u 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> għall-perijodu 2020-2024. Il-ħtiġijiet effettivi se jirriżultaw partikolarment min-negozjati li jkunu għaddejjin jew li se jitwettqu għat-tiġdid tal-ftehim li wasal biex jiskadi, fis-snin li ġejjin, għal ċertu numru ta' proprjetajiet okkupati mis-servizzi tal-Kummissjoni.</P><P>Kull waħda mill-binjiet irriċerkati biex jissodisfaw dawn il-ħtiġijiet għandu jkollhom superfiċje grossa ta' mill-inqas 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> fuq l-art. Preferibbilment, dawn ikunu okkupati kompletament u esklussivament mis-servizzi tal-Kummissjoni u/jew is-servizzi ta'</P><P>Istituzzjonijiet Ewropej oħra jew korpi komunitarji. Il-kuntratti proposti se jkunu kuntratti ta' użufrutt u/jew ta' xiri għal terminu ta' żmien</P><P>Preferibbilment il-binjiet inkwistjoni jkunu kompluti b'kollox jew ikunu se jitlestew fil-futur. Madankollu, jistgħu jkunu proposti proġetti sabiex, jekk ikun meħtieġ, iservu fil-qafas ta' strateġija futura.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Għanijiet tal-istħarriġ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-isħarriġ għandu l-għan li jiġbor il-proposti ta' proprjetajiet ta' uffiċċji li jistgħu jissodisfaw il-ħtiġijiet tal-Kummissjoni, fil-perimetri indikati fil-punt 2 hawn fuq.</P><P>Għaldaqstant, il-proprjetarji jew ir-rappreżentanti tagħhom huma mistiedna li jimlew il-formola ta' stħarriġ disponibbli fit-taqsima "kuntratti u sejħiet għal offerti pubbliċi — Avviż ta' stħarriġ tas-suq tal-proprjetà" fis-sit tal-Internet indikat fil-punt 1.</P><P>Il-kunfidenzjalità tal-informazzjoni riċevuta hija garantita. Il-formoli ta' stħarriġ wara se jkunu arkivjati f'bażi tad-dejta sikura li għaliha għandhom aċċess biss l-aġenti statutorji tal-Kummissjoni Ewropea awtorizzati li jagħmlu dan.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-użu tal-informazzjoni miġbura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-informazzjoni miġbura u arkivjata fil-bażi tad-dejta se tintuża mill-Kummissjoni biex tidentifika l-binjiet li jistgħu jissodisfaw il-ħtiġijiet tas-superfiċje tal-uffiċċji.</P><P>Għall-binjiet identifikati, l-OIB se jikkuntattja lill-proprjetarji sabiex jikseb informazzjoni dettaljata dwar l-istat u l-kapaċitajiet tal-bini kkonċernat kif ukoll il-kundizzjonijiet finanzjarji maħsuba.</P><P>Jekk fuq il-bażi ta' din l-informazzjoni dettaljata, il-Kummissjoni tqis li l-proprjetajiet inkwistjoni jistgħu fil-fatt jissodisfaw il-ħtiġijiet tagħha, tista' tinbeda proċedura nnegozjata mal-proprjetarju/i tal-binjiet ikkonċernati, skont id-dispożizzjonijiet tal-Artikolu 134 tar-Regolament (UE, Euratom) Nru 1268/2012 dwar ir-regoli tal-applikazzjoni tar-Regolament (UE, Euratom) Nru 966/2012.</P><P>Dan l-avviż madankollu bl-ebda mod ma jorbot lill-Kummissjoni f'dak li għandu x'jaqsam mal-proċeduri tagħha tal-għoti tal-kuntratt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-preżentazzjoni tal-formoli ta' stħarriġ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-formoli ta' stħarriġ iffirmati u ddatati għandhom jintbagħtu mill-propjetarji jew mir-rappreżentanti tagħhom awtorizzati li jagħmlu dan, qabel l-16:30 (fi żmien 30 jum ta' xogħol mid-data tal-pubblikazzjoni).</P><P>It-tagħrif irid jintbagħat b'wieħed mill-metodi li ġejjin:</P><P>— permezz ta' posta rreġistrata, kif juri t-timbru tal-posta, fl-indirizz li ġej: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, il-Belġju,</P><P>— billi jitwasslu (personalment jew minn xi rappreżentant tal-kandidat, jew permezz ta' kurrier) fl-indirizz li ġej: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, il-Belġju. Dan id-dipartiment ikun miftuħ mit-8:00 sal-16:30, mit-Tnejn sal-Ħamis, u mit-8:00 sal-16:00 nhar ta' Ġimgħa, ħlief fil-btajjel tal-Kummissjoni.</P><P>Għall-kunsinni bil-kurrier, id-data valida tad-dispaċċ se tkun id-data fuq in-nota tal-kunsinna tal-kurrier. Għall-kunsinni li jsiru b'mod personali jew minn xi rappreżentant, f'dan il-każ il-konferma li tkun waslet it-tweġiba se tingħata permezz ta' rċevuta bid-data u ffirmata minn uffiċjal tad-Dipartiment Ċentrali tal-Posta tal-Kummissjoni li jirċievi d-dokumenti.</P><P>Fi kwalunkwe każ, il-proprjetarju jew ir-rappreżentant tiegħu għandu jirrispetta wkoll it-termini li ġejjin:</P><P>— il-formola ta' stħarriġ għandha tintbagħat f'envelopp doppju,</P><P>— iż-żewġ envelopps se jkunu ssiġillati,</P><P>— l-envelopp ta' ġewwa ikollu fuqu, fuq l-indikazzjoni tas-servizz destinatarju, ir-referenza "avviż ta' stħarriġ tas-suq tal-proprjetà għall-ħtiġijiet tal-Kummissjoni Ewropea bħala spazji għal uffiċċji fi Brussell", "formola ta' stħarriġ ta' (isem il-proprjetarju jew tar-rappreżentant tiegħu)", "ma għandux jinfetaħ mis-servizz tal-kurrier",</P><P>— l-envelopps li jeħlu waħedhom iridu jingħalqu bit-tejp, bil-firma ta' min jibgħathom tul it-tejp,</P><P>— jekk il-proprjetarju jew ir-rappreżentant tiegħu jkun jixtieq jikseb informazzjoni supplimentari qabel id-data tal-preżentazzjoni tal-proposti, dan għandu jindirizza t-talba biss permezz ta' email fl-indirizz li hemm referenza għalih aktar 'il fuq f'punt 1. Il-proponenti huma mistiedna wkoll biex jikkonsultaw fuq bażi regolari s-sit tal-Internet li hemm referenza għaliha fil-punt 1, għaliex dan huwa fejn il-mistoqsijiet u t-tweġibiet tal-Kummissjoni se jkunu ppubblikati regolarment,</P><P>— id-data tal-iskadenza biex jintbagħtu l-mistoqsijiet hija fl-16:00 (10 ijiem ta' xogħol qabel id-data tal-għeluq).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruksela: Ogłoszenie informacyjne skierowane do sektora nieruchomości — szacunki dotyczące wieloletnich potrzeb lokalowych Komisji Europejskiej w Brukseli w latach 2020–2024 oraz rozpoznanie rynku lokalnego</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dział Komisji Europejskiej odpowiedzialny za procedurę:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komisja Europejska</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 — 09/P001, cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia, adres e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — witryna internetowa </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacje ogólne:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Zgodnie z komunikatem Komisji z dnia 5.9.2007 \[COM(2007)501] niniejsze ogłoszenie jest skierowane do podmiotów z sektora nieruchomości oraz do wszystkich stron zainteresowanych szacunkami dotyczącymi potrzeb lokalowych Komisji Europejskiej w Brukseli, ma na celu również zebranie informacji na temat projektów i nieruchomości na określonym obszarze.</P><P>Poszukiwane budynki</P><P>Aby zaspokoić zapotrzebowanie na przestrzenie biurowe w perspektywie lat 2020-2024, Komisja Europejska poszukuje powierzchni biurowych w Brukseli, znajdujących się albo</P><P>— w promieniu maksymalnie 700 m od odcinków znajdujących się pomiędzy stacją metra Mérode i stacją metra Arts-Loi oraz między stacją metra Arts-Loi i stacją metra De Brouckère,</P><P>— albo w promieniu maksymalnie 700 metrów od linii metra pomiędzy stacją metra Arts-Loi i stacją Rogier,</P><P>— lub w promieniu maksymalnie 700 m od linii metra pomiędzy stacją metra Delta i stacją Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>W okresie 2020-2024 całkowita poszukiwana powierzchnia (liczona powyżej wysokości gruntu) budynków, których cykl życia się kończy lub dla których niebawem wygasa umowa dzierżawy, wynosi między 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> a 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Rzeczywiste potrzeby będą zależały między innymi od wyników trwających lub podjętych później negocjacji na odnowienie porozumień dotyczących niektórych budynków zajmowanych przez służby Komisji, które mają wygasnąć w ciągu najbliższych lat.</P><P>Każdy z poszukiwanych budynków powinien mieć przynajmniej 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> powierzchni całkowitej powyżej wysokości gruntu. Budynki te będą przeznaczone albo do całościowego wykorzystania wyłącznie przez służby Komisji albo także przez służby innych</P><P>instytucji europejskich i organów Wspólnoty. Zaproponowane zostaną umowy użytkowania albo zakupu terminowego</P><P>Przedmiotowe budynki muszą być już ukończone lub zostać ukończone w najbliższej przyszłości. Jeśli zajdzie taka potrzeba, będzie można jednak zaproponować projekty, które zostaną wzięte pod uwagę w kolejnym rozpoznaniu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cele rozpoznania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozpoznanie ma na celu zebranie propozycji budynków biurowych, które mogą zaspokoić potrzeby Komisji, usytuowanych w obszarach określonych w punkcie 2 powyżej.</P><P>W tym celu zaprasza się właścicieli i ich pełnomocników do wypełnienia karty rozpoznania dostępnej w sekcji „umowy i zamówienia publiczne — ogłoszenie o rozpoznaniu rynku nieruchomości” („contrats et marchés publics — Avis de prospection immobilière”) ze strony internetowej podanej w punkcie 1.</P><P>Gwarantuje się poufność otrzymanych informacji. Karty rozpoznania zostaną zarchiwizowane w zabezpieczonej bazie danych, do której będą mieli dostęp wyłącznie urzędnicy Komisji Europejskiej posiadający odpowiednie uprawnienia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sposób wykorzystywania zebranych informacji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Zebrane i zarchiwizowane w bazie danych informacje będą wykorzystywane przez Komisję w celu wyznaczenia budynków, które mogą zaspokoić jej zapotrzebowanie w zakresie powierzchni biurowych.</P><P>Departament OIB zwróci się do właścicieli wyznaczonych budynków w celu otrzymania szczegółowych informacji na temat stanu i możliwości tych budynków, jak również przedstawianych warunków finansowych.</P><P>Jeśli na podstawie tych informacji Komisja uzna, że dane budynki mogą zaspokoić jej potrzeby, będzie można wszcząć procedurę negocjacyjną z właścicielami odnośnych budynków, zgodnie z przepisami artykułu 134 rozporządzenia (EU, Euratom) nr 1268/2012 w sprawie zasad stosowania rozporządzenia (EU, Euratom) nr 966/2012.</P><P>Niniejsza publikacja nie zobowiązuje Komisji do udzielenia zamówienia w ramach procedur udzielania zamówienia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Składanie kart rozpoznania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Podpisane karty rozpoznania opatrzone datą powinny zostać złożone przez właścicieli i ich uprawnionych przedstawicieli (pełnomocników) do (30 dni roboczych od daty publikacji), do godz. 16.30.</P><P>Informacje należy dostarczyć w jeden z następujących sposobów:</P><P>— wysłać pocztą, przesyłką poleconą, decyduje data stempla pocztowego, na następujący adres: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgia,</P><P>— albo doręczając (osobiście lub przez pełnomocnika kandydata, w tym przez kuriera), na adres: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgia. Dział pracuje od poniedziałku do czwartku w godzinach 8:00–16:30 i w piątek w godzinach 8:00–16:00, z wyjątkiem dni wolnych Komisji.</P><P>W przypadku doręczenia przesyłką kurierską decyduje data potwierdzenia nadania. W przypadku dostarczenia osobistego lub przez pełnomocnika kandydata o otrzymaniu informacji będzie świadczyć potwierdzenie odbioru, podpisane przez urzędnika działu korespondencji Komisji Europejskiej, który zajmuje się odbiorem dokumentów.</P><P>We wszystkich przypadkach właściciel lub jego przedstawiciel będą musieli przestrzegać także następujących warunków:</P><P>— wnioski należy wysyłać w podwójnej kopercie,</P><P>— obydwie koperty muszą być zaklejone,</P><P>— oprócz wskazania instytucji, do której jest adresowana, koperta wewnętrzna musi zawierać dopisek «avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles» („ogłoszenie o rozpoznaniu rynku nieruchomości w celu zaspokojenia zapotrzebowania Komisji Europejskiej na przestrzenie biurowe”), «fiche de prospection de (nom du propriétaire ou son représentant)» („karta rozpoznania (nazwisko właściciela lub jego przedstawiciela)), «à ne pas ouvrir par le service du couurier» („nie należy otwierać przy rozdzielaniu poczty”),</P><P>— koperty z taśmą klejącą muszą być zaklejone za pomocą taśm klejących w poprzek których postawiony będzie podpis nadawcy,</P><P>— w celu otrzymania dodatkowych informacji przed datą składania ofert, właściciel lub jego przedstawiciel powinni wysłać wniosek o takie informacje za pośrednictwem adresu e-mail wskazanego w punkcie 1 powyżej. Oferenci są ponadto proszeni o regularne odwiedzanie witryny internetowej podanej w pkt 1, w której są systematycznie publikowane zadane przez oferentów pytania i odpowiedzi Komisji.</P><P>— pytania można przesyłać do (10 dni roboczych przed terminem składania ofert), do godz. 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: Informačné oznámenie do pozornosti trhu s nehnuteľnosťami – Prognózy viacročných potrieb Európskej komisie týkajúcich sa nehnuteľností v Bruseli na obdobie rokov 2020 – 2024 a prieskum miestneho trhu</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zodpovedné oddelenie Európskej komisie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európska komisia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique, Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgicko, e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> , webová stránka: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Všeobecné informácie:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>V súlade s oznámením Komisie KOM(2007)501 z 5.9.2007 je cieľom tohto oznámenia informovať strany prítomné na trhu s nehnuteľnosťami a všetky ostatné zainteresované strany o prognóze potrieb Európskej komisie týkajúcich sa nehnuteľností v Bruseli a získať informácie o projektoch a nehnuteľnostiach vo vymedzenej oblasti.</P><P>Vyhľadávané budovy</P><P>Európska komisia hľadá, s cieľom naplniť svoje potreby kancelárskych priestorov v časovom horizonte 2020 – 2024, kancelárske priestory v Bruseli, ktoré sa nachádzajú buď:</P><P>— v okruhu do 700 metrov od trasy medzi stanicou metra Mérode a stanicou metra Arts-Loi a medzi stanicou metra Arts-Loi a stanicou metra De Brouckère,</P><P>— alebo v okruhu do 700 metrov od trasy metra medzi stanicou Arts-Loi a stanicou Rogier,</P><P>— alebo v okruhu do 700 metrov od trasy metra medzi stanicou Delta a stanicou Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Európska komisia hľadá celkovú podlahovú plochu medzi 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> a 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> na obdobie rokov 2020 – 2024, s cieľom nahradiť budovy na konci životného cyklu alebo budovy, ktorým končí platnosť nájomnej zmluvy. Skutočné potreby budú závisieť najmä od výsledku prebiehajúcich alebo budúcich rokovaní o obnovení dohôd, ktorých platnosť zanikne v nadchádzajúcich rokoch, pre určitý počet budov využívaných útvarmi Komisie.</P><P>Vyhľadávané budovy vyhovujúce týmto potrebám musia mať hrubú podlahovú plochu aspoň 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Budú úplne a výlučne využívané útvarmi Komisie a/alebo útvarmi iných európskych inštitúcií, prípadne subjektmi Spoločenstva.</P><P> Navrhnuté zmluvy budú zmluvy o využívaní a/alebo termínované kúpne zmluvy.</P><P>Tieto budovy musia byť už dostavané alebo by sa mali čoskoro dostavať. Ponúknuté však môžu byť aj projekty, ktoré by v prípade potreby predstavovali ďalšiu možnosť do budúcnosti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Účel vyhľadávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Účelom vyhľadávania je zhromaždiť ponuky kancelárskych budov, ktoré by vyhovovali potrebám Komisie, v okruhoch uvedených v bode 2 vyššie.</P><P>Na tento účel vyzývame vlastníkov alebo ich zástupcov, aby vyplnili formulár na oslovenie potenciálneho zákazníka („fiche de prospection“), ktorý je dostupný v časti „contrats et marchés publics — Avis de prospection immobilière“ („zmluvy a verejné obstarávania – Oznámenie o hľadaní nehnuteľností“) webovej stránky uvedenej v bode 1.</P><P>Zaručuje sa dôvernosť získaných informácií. Formuláre na oslovenie potenciálneho zákazníka budú následne archivované v zabezpečenej databáze, do ktorej budú mať prístup len oprávnení štatutárni zamestnanci Európskej komisie.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Použitie zhromaždených informácií</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Komisia použije zhromaždené a archivované informácie v databáze na určenie budov, ktoré by vyhovovali jej potrebám, pokiaľ ide o kancelárske priestory.</P><P>V prípade týchto budov nadviaže úrad OIB kontakt s jednotlivými vlastníkmi, aby získal podrobné informácie o stave a kapacitách príslušnej budovy, ako aj o plánovaných finančných podmienkach.</P><P>Ak na základe týchto podrobných informácií Komisia usúdi, že by dané budovy účinne vyhovovali jej potrebám, môže sa začať rokovacie konanie s vlastníkom (vlastníkmi) týchto budov v súlade s ustanoveniami článku 134 nariadenia (EÚ, Euratom) č. 1268/2012 o pravidlách uplatňovania nariadenia (EÚ, Euratom) č. 966/2012.</P><P>Toto oznámenie však nie je pre Komisiu záväzné, pokiaľ ide o jej postupy pridelenia obstarávania.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Odovzdanie formulárov na oslovenie potenciálneho zákazníka</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Vlastníci alebo ich náležite poverení zástupcovia musia poslať podpísané a datované formuláre na oslovenie potenciálneho zákazníka do (30 pracovných dní od dátumu zverejnenia), 16:30.</P><P>Informácie musia byť odoslané použitím 1 z týchto metód:</P><P>— buď doporučenou zásielkou (oficiálnou poštovou službou) na adresu: Európska komisia, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgicko,</P><P>— alebo doručením (osobne alebo ktoroukoľvek stranou zastupujúcou uchádzača, prípadne kuriérskou službou) na adresu: Európska komisia, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgicko. Toto oddelenie je otvorené v pondelok až štvrtok od 8:00 do 16:30 a v piatok od 8:00 do 16:00 okrem voľných dní Komisie.</P><P>Pre doručenia kuriérskou službou bude platným dátumom doručenia dátum na potvrdenke kuriéra o doručení. V prípade osobných doručení alebo doručení zástupcom uchádzača bude doručenie ponúk potvrdené datovanou potvrdenkou o prijatí podpísanou úradníkom centrálneho poštového oddelenia Komisie, ktorý prevezme dokumenty.</P><P>Vlastník alebo jeho zástupca musí v každom prípade dodržiavať aj tieto postupy:</P><P>— formulár na oslovenie potenciálneho zákazníka musí byť zaslaný v dvojitej obálke,</P><P>— obidve obálky musia byť zapečatené,</P><P>— na vnútornej obálke musí byť uvedený, okrem názvu útvaru, ktorému je adresovaná, odkaz: «avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles», «fiche de prospection de (meno vlastníka alebo jeho zástupcu)», «à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courrier»,</P><P>— samolepiace obálky musia byť prelepené lepiacou páskou, cez ktorú sa odosielateľ musí podpísať,</P><P>— ak vlastník alebo jeho zástupca potrebuje dodatočné informácie pred dátumom predloženia návrhov, zašle svoju žiadosť výlučne e-mailom na adresu uvedenú v bode 1 vyššie. Predkladateľom návrhov takisto odporúčame, aby pravidelne navštevovali webovú stránku uvedenú v bode 1, kde sa budú pravidelne zverejňovať otázky, na ktoré bude odpovedať Komisia.</P><P>— konečný termín na posielanie otázok je (10 pracovných dní pred termínom uzávierky), 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselj: Informativno obvestilo v vednost trgu nepremičnin – Večletne napovedi potreb Evropske komisije po nepremičninah v Bruslju za leta 2020–2024 in povpraševanje za lokalni nepremičninski trg</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Odgovorni oddelek Evropske komisije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija; e‑naslov: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — spletno mesto: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Splošne informacije:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>V skladu s Sporočilom Komisije z dne 5.9.2007 [COM(2007) 501] je namen tega obvestila obvestiti akterje na trgu nepremičnin in vse druge zainteresirane strani o napovedi potreb Evropske komisije po nepremičninah v Bruslju ter pridobiti informacije o nepremičninskih projektih in nepremičninah na določenem območju.</P><P>Iskane nepremičnine</P><P>Da bi zadovoljila svoje potrebe po poslovnih površinah v obdobju 2020–2024, Evropska komisija išče poslovne površine v Bruslju, ki se nahajajo:</P><P>— največ 700 metrov od osi odsekov med postajama podzemne železnice Mérode in Arts-Loi ter med postajama podzemne železnice Arts-Loi in De Brouckère,</P><P>— ali največ 700 metrov od osi linije podzemne železnice med postajama Arts-Loi in Rogier,</P><P>— ali največ 700 metrov od osi linije podzemne železnice med postajama Delta in Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Da bi nadomestili stavbe, ki se jim bliža konec življenjske dobe ali iztek najemne pogodbe, se iščejo prostori s skupno nadzemno površino med 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> in 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> za obdobje 2020–2024. Dejanske potrebe bodo odvisne predvsem od izidov pogajanj, ki že potekajo ali pa še bodo, za podaljšanje pogodb, ki se v prihodnjih letih iztečejo za določeno število stavb, ki jih zasedajo službe Komisije.</P><P>Za zadovoljitev teh potreb morajo iskane stavbe imeti vsaka po najmanj 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> bruto nadzemne površine. Zaželeno je, da bi stavbe lahko v celoti in izključno zasedale službe Komisije in/ali službe drugih</P><P>institucij Evropske unije ali organov Skupnosti. Predlagane pogodbe bodo pogodbe o osebni služnosti in/ali o postopnem odkupu.</P><P>Zaželeno je, da so zadevne stavbe že dokončane ali pa bodo dokončane v bližnji prihodnosti. Predlagajo pa se lahko tudi drugi projekti, ki bodo morda lahko zadostili prihodnjim povpraševanjem.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cilj povpraševanja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cilj povpraševanja je zbrati ponudbe za poslovne stavbe, ki bi lahko zadovoljile potrebe Komisije, znotraj območja, opredeljenega v točki 2 zgoraj.</P><P>V ta namen so lastniki ali njihovi zastopniki vabljeni, da izpolnijo obrazec za povpraševanje, ki je na voljo v razdelku „Contrats et marchés publics – Avis de prospection immobilière“ [Pogodbe in javna naročila – Obvestilo o nepremičninskem povpraševanju] spletnega mesta iz točke 1.</P><P>Zaupnost prejetih podatkov je zagotovljena. Obrazci za povpraševanje bodo potem shranjeni v zavarovano podatkovno zbirko, ki bo dostopna le ustrezno pooblaščenim uradnim uslužbencem Evropske komisije.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uporaba zbranih podatkov</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Zbrane in v podatkovno zbirko shranjene podatke bo Komisija uporabila za določitev primernih stavb, ki bi lahko zadovoljile njene potrebe po poslovnih površinah.</P><P>OIB bo potem lastnike teh primernih stavb prosil za podrobnejše podatke o stanju in zmogljivostih zadevne stavbe ter o predvidenih finančnih pogojih.</P><P>Če bo na podlagi teh podrobnih podatkov Komisija mnenja, da lahko zadevne stavbe dejansko zadovoljijo njene potrebe, lahko z lastniki zadevnih stavb sproži postopek s pogajanji, v skladu z določbami člena 134 Delegirane uredbe Komisije (EU) št. 1268/2012 z dne 29.10.2012 o pravilih uporabe Uredbe (EU, Euratom) št. 966/2012 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta o finančnih pravilih, ki se uporabljajo za splošni proračun Unije.</P><P>Vendar pa to obvestilo Komisije na noben način ne zavezuje v zvezi z njenimi postopki javnih naročil.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oddaja obrazcev za povpraševanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lastniki ali njihovi ustrezno pooblaščeni zastopniki morajo podpisane in datirane obrazce za povpraševanje predložiti v roku 30 delovnih dni po datumu objave tega obvestila (16:30).</P><P>Informacije je treba predložiti na enega od naslednjih načinov:</P><P>— po pošti s priporočeno pošiljko, katere pravočasnost bo razvidna iz poštnega žiga, na naslednji naslov: Evropska komisija, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1, avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgija,</P><P>— ali z dostavo (osebno ali prek kandidatovega zastopnika ali s kurirsko službo) na naslednji naslov: Evropska komisija, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1, avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgija. Ta oddelek je odprt od ponedeljka do četrtka 8:00–16:30 in ob petkih 8:00–16:00, razen ob praznikih Komisije.</P><P>V primeru dostave s kurirsko službo bo pravočasnost razvidna iz datuma odpošiljanja na dostavnici kurirske službe. V primeru osebne dostave ali dostave prek zastopnika bo prevzem odgovora potrjen v obliki datiranega in podpisanega potrdila o prejemu, ki ga izda uradnik centralne poštne službe Komisije, ki je dokumente prevzel.</P><P>V vsakem primeru pa mora lastnik ali njegov zastopnik pri predložitvi upoštevati tudi naslednje zahteve:</P><P>— obrazce za povpraševanje je treba predložiti v dvojni ovojnici,</P><P>— obe ovojnici morata biti zapečateni,</P><P>— na notranji ovojnici mora biti poleg navedbe točnega naslovnika tudi sklic „Avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles“ [Obvestilo o nepremičninskem povpraševanju za zadovoljitev potreb Evropske komisije po poslovnih prostorih v Bruslju] ter pripisa „fiche de prospection de (ime lastnika ali njegovega zastopnika)“ [obrazec za povpraševanje] in „à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courier“ [naj ne odpira poštna služba],</P><P>— samolepilne ovojnice je treba zapečatiti z lepilnim trakom, preko katerega se mora pošiljatelj podpisati,</P><P>— če želi lastnik ali njegov zastopnik pred datumom oddaje ponudb pridobiti dodatne informacije, mora svoj zahtevek poslati izključno po elektronski pošti na e‑naslov, naveden v točki 1 zgoraj. Ponudniki so prav tako vabljeni, da redno spremljajo spletno mesto, navedeno v točki 1, kjer se bodo redno objavljala zastavljena vprašanja ponudnikov in odgovori Komisije,</P><P>— rok za pošiljanje vprašanj je 10 delovnih dni pred rokom za oddajo ponudb (16:00).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-An Bhruiséil: Fógra faisnéise don mhargadh maoine - Réamhaisnéisí de riachtanais mhaoine ilbhliantúla do na blianta 2020 chuig 2024 don Choimisiún Eorpach sa Bhruiséil agus cuardach sa mhargadh áitiúil</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Roinn an Choimisiúin Eorpaigh atá freagrach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An Coimisiún Eorpach</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Bheilg, Ríomhphost: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Láithreán gréasáin: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis ghinearálta:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>I gcomhréir le Cumarsáid ón gCoimisiún an 5.9.2007 [COM(2007)501], tá an fógra seo ceaptha chun rannpháirtithe sa mhargadh maoine agus aon pháirtithe leasmhara eile a chur ar an eolas faoi réamhaisnéis an Choimisiúin Eorpaigh faoi éilimh mhaoine sa Bhruiséil, agus chun faisnéis a bhailiú faoi thionscadail agus maoine laistigh de pharaiméadar sainithe.</P><P>Maoine ag teastáil</P><P>Is chun a chuid éileamh chun spás oifige a shásamh idir na blianta 2020-2024 atá an Coimisiún Eorpach ag lorg spáis oifige sa Bhruiséil, agus é suite,</P><P>— 700 méadar ar a uasmhéid ó ais na ndeighleog idir stáisiún meitreo Mérode agus stáisiún meitreo Arts-Loi, agus idir stáisiún meitreo Arts-Loi agus stáisiún meitreo De Brouckère,</P><P>— nó 700 méadar ar a uasmhéid ó ais na líne meitreo idir stáisiún meitreo Arts-Loi agus stáisiún Rogier,</P><P>— nó 700 méadar ar a uasmhéid ó ais na líne meitreo idir stáisiún meitreo Delta agus stáisiún Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Is idir 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> agus 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> i rith na tréimhse 2020-2024 é an t-achar iomlán os cionn na talún a theastaíonn chun maoine ag deireadh a saolré a athsholáthar, nó ar éag a léasanna. Braithfidh na riachtanais iarbhír go sonrach ar thoradh na n-idirbheartaíochtaí faoi lánseoil nó le stiúradh d’athnuachan na gcomhaontuithe a rachaidh in éag sna blianta beaga amach romhainn i leith roinnt maoin faoi áitíocht ranna an Choimisiúin.</P><P>Caitheann ollachar talún 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> ar a laghad bheith ag na foirgnimh a theastaíonn chun na héilimh sin a shásamh. B’fhearr go mbeidís go hiomlán agus go heisiach faoi áitíocht an Choimisiúin féin agus/nó na ranna le</P><P>hinstitiúidí Eorpacha nó le comhlachtaí Comhphobail eile. Is conarthaí cirt úsáide agus/nó réamhcheannaigh a bheidh sna conarthaí molta</P><P>B’fhearr go mbeadh na foirgnimh i gceist críochnaithe nó gar dá gcríochnú amach anseo. D’fhéadfaí tionscadail a mholadh ámh chun fónamh mar chuid de staidéar ionchasach leantach, dá mba ghá.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cuspóirí an chuardaigh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Is é cuspóir an chuardaigh chun tograí a bhailiú do mhaoine oifige ar féidir leo éilimh an Choimisiúin a shásamh sna réimsí a thásctar i bpointe 2 thuas.</P><P>Is chun na críche sin a thugtar cuireadh d’úinéirí agus dá n-ionadaithe chun an fhoirm chuardaigh a chomhlánú ar féidir í a fháil san rannóg “Conarthaí agus an soláthar poiblí - Fógra cuardaigh mhaoine” ar an láithreán gréasáin a thugtar i bpointe 1.</P><P>Ráthaítear rúndachta na faisnéise a fhaightear. Is amhlaidh a chartlannófar na comhaid chuardaigh ansin i mbunachar sonraí slán nach mbeidh rochtain ach ag oifigigh an Choimisiúin Eorpaigh arna n-údarás go cuí.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Úsáid na faisnéise bailithe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bainfidh an Coimisiún leas as an bhfaisnéis a bhailítear agus a stóráiltear sa bhunachar sonraí chun foirgnimh a aithint ar féidir leo a n-éilimh do spás oifige a shásamh.</P><P>Maidir leis na maoine a aithníodh, rachaidh an OIB faoi dhéin na n-úinéirí chun faisnéis mhionsonraithe a fháil faoi riocht agus cumas an fhoirgnimh i gceist, chomh maith le coinníollacha airgeadais a cheaptar.</P><P>Má bhreithníonn an Coimisiún, ar bhunús na faisnéise mionsonraithe sin, gur féidir leis na maoine i gceist a chuid éileamh a shásamh go héifeachtach, b’amhlaidh a sheolfaí nós imeachta idirbheartaithe leis an úinéir/na húinéirí de na maoine i gceist, i gcomhréir le forálacha d’Airteagal 134 de Rialachán (AE, Euratom) Uimh. 1268/2012 maidir le rialacha cur chun feidhme i leith Rialachán (AE, Euratom) Uimh. 966/2012.</P><P>Ní hionann an foilseachán sin agus tiomantas ar son an Choimisiúin ina chuid nósanna imeachta soláthair.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Taisceadh na bhfoirmeacha cuardaigh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Caithfidh na húinéirí nó a n-ionadaithe le húdarú cuí na foirmeacha cuardaigh sínithe agus dátaithe a sheoladh, roimh 16:30 an (30 lá oibre tar éis an dáta foilsithe).</P><P>Ní mór faisnéis a sheoladh ach leas a bhaint as ceann amháin de na modhanna seo a leanas:</P><P>— post cláraithe, i bhfianaise an phostmhairc, chuig an seoladh seo a leanas: An Coimisiún Eorpach, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, an Bheilg,</P><P>— seachadadh (go pearsanta nó le haon pháirtí ag feidhmiú thar ceann iarrthóra, nó trí chúiréir) chuig an seoladh seo a leanas: An Coimisiún Eorpach, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, an Bheilg. Bíonn an rannóg sin ar oscailt idir 8:30 agus 16:00, ó Luan go Déardaoin agus idir 8:00 agus 16:00 ar an Aoine, ach amháin ar laethanta saoire an Choimisiúin.</P><P>Is é an dáta ar nóta seachadta an chúiréara an dáta bailí seolta do sheachadtaí trí chúiréir. Maidir leis na seachadtaí a dhéantar go pearsanta nó a dhéanann aon ionadaí, deimhneofar seachadadh na freagartha sa chás sin, le hadmháil dhátaithe agus shínithe ag an oifigeach ó Lár-Roinn Poist an Choimisiúin a ghlacann seachadadh ar na doiciméid.</P><P>I ngach aon chás, ní mór don úinéir nó dá ionadaí glacadh freisin leis na coinníollacha seo a leanas:</P><P>— caithfear an fhoirm chuardaigh a thíolacadh i gclúdach dúbailte,</P><P>— caithfidh an dá chlúdach bheith séalaithe,</P><P>— caithfear an tagairt “avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles”, “fiche de prospection de (ainm an úinéara nó a ionadaí)”, “à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courier” bheith ar an gclúdach laistigh, i dteannta le hainm na rannóige dá seoltar é,</P><P>— ní mór clúdaigh fhéinghreamaitheacha a shéalú le téip ghreamaitheach, agus síniú an tseoltóra scríofa trasna na téipe,</P><P>— más mian leis an úinéir nó lena ionadaí faisnéis bhreise a fháil roimh dháta do chur isteach na dtograí, caithfidh siad a n-iarratas a sheoladh, trí ríomhphost amháin, chuig an seoladh ríomhphoist a thásctar thuas i bpointe 1. Tugtar cuireadh do mholtóirí freisin chun an láithreán gréasáin a thásctar i bpointe 1 a cheadú ar bhonn rialta, mar a bhfoilseofar na ceisteanna a chuirtear ar an gCoimisiún agus na freagraí,</P><P>— is ionann an spriocdháta do chur ceisteanna agus 16:00 an (10 lá oibre roimh an dáta deiridh).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Брюксел: Информационно обявление на вниманието на пазара за недвижима собственост – многогодишна прогноза за изискванията за собственост на Европейската комисия в Брюксел (2020–2024) и проучване на местния пазар</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Отговорен отдел на Европейската комисия</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейска комисия</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Белгия, електронна поща: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Интернет страница: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Обща информация:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Съгласно Съобщение COM(2007)501 на Комисията от 5.9.2007 г. целта на това обявление е да информира участниците в пазара на недвижима собственост и всички други заинтересовани страни относно прогнозата за изисквания за собственост на Европейската комисия в Брюксел и да събере информация за проекти и имоти в определен периметър.</P><P>Търсени сгради</P><P>За да отговори на своите изисквания за офис пространство до 2020-2024 г., Европейската комисия търси площи в Брюксел, намиращи се:</P><P>— в рамките на 700 метра от станцията на метрото Mérode до станцията на метрото Arts-Loi и станцията на метрото De Brouckère,</P><P>— или в рамките на 700 метра от метро линията на станция Arts-Loi до станция Rogier.,</P><P>— или в рамките на 700 метра от метро линията на станция Delta и станция Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Общата търсена надземна площ, с цел да се заменят сгради достигнали края на жизнения цикъл или чийто договор за наем е изтекъл, е 80 000 m{^&gt;2&lt;^} и 150 000 m{^&gt;2&lt;^} за периода 2020-2024 г. Действителните нужди ще зависят по-специално от резултата от преговорите, които са в ход или ще бъдат осъществени за подновяване на споразумения, които ще изтекат през следващите години за определен брой сгради, заети от службите на Комисията.</P><P>За да удовлетворят тези нужди, всяка от търсените сгради трябва да бъде с най-малко 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> брутна надземна площ. За предпочитане е те да бъдат изцяло и изключително заети от службите на Комисията и / или службите на други</P><P>Европейски институции или организации на Oбщността. Предложените договори ще бъдат или договори за ползване и и/или за форуърд-покупка</P><P>За предпочитане е въпросните сгради да бъдат завършени или пред бъдещо завършване. Проектите обаче могат да бъдат предложени за използване, ако е целесъобразно, в бъдеща перспектива.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Цели на проучването</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Целта на проучването е да събере предложения за офис сгради, които могат да отговорят на нуждите на Комисията в рамките на посочените по-горе в точка 2 периметри.</P><P>За тази цел собствениците или техни представители са поканени да попълнят формулярът за проучването, предоставен в раздел „Договори и обществени поръчки — Обявление за проучване на недвижими имоти“ на уебсайта, посочен в точка 1.</P><P>Поверителността на получената информация е гарантирана. След това формулярите за проучването ще бъдат архивирани в сигурна база данни, която ще бъде достъпна само за длъжностните лица на Европейската комисия.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Използване на събраната информация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Събраната и архивирана в базата данни информация ще бъде използвана от Комисията за идентифициране на сгради, които могат да посрещнат нейните нужди от офис пространство.</P><P>За идентифицираните сгради, OIB ще се обърне към собствениците, за да получи подробна информация за състоянието и капацитета на съответната сграда и за предвидените финансови условия.</P><P>Ако въз основа на тази подробна информация Комисията счете, че въпросните сгради могат ефективно да посрещнат нуждите ѝ, може да се започне процедура на договаряне със собственика/собствениците на съответните сгради в съответствие с разпоредбите на член 134 от Делегиран регламент (EС) № 1268/2012 относно правилата за прилагане на Регламент (ЕС, Евратом) № 966/2012.</P><P>Настоящото обявление по никакъв начин не обвързва Комисията по отношение на процедурите по възлагане на поръчки.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Подаване на формулярите за проучване</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Подписаните и датирани формуляри за проучване трябва да бъдат подадени от собствениците или техните надлежно упълномощени представители до (30 работни дни след датата на публикуване) 16:30 часа.</P><P>Информацията трябва да бъде изпратена по 1 от следните начини:</P><P>— препоръчана поща, удостоверена с пощенската марка, на следния адрес: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Белгия,</P><P>— доставка (лично или от лице, представляващо кандидата, или по куриер) на следния адрес: Commission européenne, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, Unité OIB.RE.1 — avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Белгия. Този отдел работи от 8:00–16:30 ч. от понеделник до четвъртък и от 8:00–16:00 ч. в петък, с изключение на официалните празници на Комисията.</P><P>За доставки по куриер, като валидна дата на изпращане ще се приема датата на изпращане от куриерската товарителница. В случай на доставки, извършени лично или от представител, доставянето на отговора ще бъде потвърдено чрез разписка, с подпис и дата от длъжностното лице в Централна пощенска служба на Комисията, която приема доставките на документите.</P><P>Във всички случаи собственикът или неговият представител също трябва да спазват следните условия:</P><P>— формулярът за проучването трябва да бъде изпратен в двоен плик,</P><P>— 2-та плика трябва да бъдат запечатани,</P><P>— на вътрешния плик трябва да бъде отбелязано, освен наименованието на отдела, до който е адресиран, следното «avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles»(„Обявление за проучване за недвижими имоти за да отговори на нуждите на Европейската комисия от офис пространство в Брюксел“), «fiche de prospection de (nom du propriétaire ou son représentant)»( „формуляр за проучване на ( име на собственика или неговият представител)“), «à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courier („да не се отваря от пощенската служба“),</P><P>— самозалепващите се пликове трябва да бъдат залепени със самозалепваща лента, с подписа на изпращача върху лентата,</P><P>— ако собственикът или неговият представител желае да получи допълнителна информация преди датата на подаване на офертите, той трябва да изпрати искането си само по електронна поща на посочения по-горе в т.1 електронен адрес. Оферентите са поканени и редовно да правят справка с интернет страницата, посочена в точка 1 на това обявление, тъй като там регулярно ще се публикуват поставените въпроси и отговорите на Комисията,</P><P>— крайният срок за изпращане на въпроси е (10 работни дни преди крайната дата) 16:00 часа.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Anunț de informare în atenția pieței imobiliare – Previziuni multianuale privind necesitățile imobiliare ale Comisiei Europene în Bruxelles pentru perioada 2020 - 2024 și prospectarea pieței locale</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Departamentul responsabil al Comisiei Europene</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Comisia Europeană</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Site-ul: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informații generale:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>În conformitate cu Comunicarea COM(2007)501 a Comisiei din 5.9.2007, scopul acestui anunț este de a-i informa pe actorii din cadrul pieței imobiliare și pe orice altă parte interesată cu privire la previziunea privind necesitățile imobiliare ale Comisiei Europene în Bruxelles și de a colecta informații despre proiectele imobiliare și proprietățile dintr-un perimetru definit.</P><P>Imobile căutate</P><P>Pentru a-și satisface nevoile de spații de birouri pentru perioada 2020-2024, Comisia Europeană caută spații de birouri la Bruxelles, situate fie,</P><P>— la o distanță maximă de 700 de metri de axa segmentelor dintre stația de metrou Mérode și stația de metrou Arts-Loi și între stația de metrou Arts-Loi și stația de metrou De Brouckère,</P><P>— fie la o distanță maximă de 700 de metri de axa liniei de metrou între stația de metrou Arts-Loi și stația Rogier,</P><P>— fie la o distanță maximă de 700 de metri de linia de metrou dintre stația de metrou Delta și stația Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Suprafața totală deasupra solului căutată, pentru a înlocui clădirile care se află la sfârșitul ciclului de viață sau pentru care expiră contractul de închiriere, variază de la 80.000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> la 150.000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> în perioada 2020-2024. Nevoile reale vor depinde, în special, de rezultatul negocierilor în curs sau care vor fi efectuate pentru reînnoirea acordurilor care vor expira în următorii ani pentru un anumit număr de clădiri ocupate de serviciile Comisiei.</P><P>Clădirile căutate pentru a satisface aceste nevoi trebuie să aibă fiecare o suprafață brută de cel puțin 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>, deasupra nivelului solului. Acestea, de preferință, vor fi ocupate integral și exclusiv de serviciile Comisiei și / sau de serviciile altor</P><P>Instituții europene sau organizații comunitare. Contractele propuse vor fi contracte de uzufruct și / sau cumpărare în avans</P><P>Clădirile în cauză ar trebui, de preferință, să fie finalizate sau aproape de finalizare. Cu toate acestea, pot fi propuse proiecte pentru utilizare, după caz, în contextul unei perspective viitoare.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Scopurile prospectării</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prospectarea are scopul colectării propunerilor de clădiri de birouri care ar putea satisface nevoile Comisiei, în perimetrele menționate la punctul 2 de mai sus.</P><P>În acest scop, proprietarii sau mandatarii acestora sunt invitați să completeze fișa de prospectare disponibilă în secțiunea „Contracte și contracte de achiziții publice - Anunț de prospectare imobiliară“ de pe site-ul menționat la punctul 1.</P><P>Confidențialitatea informațiilor primite este garantată. Fișele de prospectare vor fi apoi arhivate într-o bază de date securizată, care va fi accesibilă numai personalului statutar al Comisiei Europene autorizat legal.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Utilizarea informațiilor colectate</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Informațiile colectate și arhivate în baza de date vor fi utilizate de către Comisie pentru a identifica clădirile care pot satisface nevoile sale de spațiu de birouri.</P><P>Pentru clădirile identificate, OIB se va adresa proprietarilor pentru a obține informații detaliate privind starea și capacitățile clădirii în cauză, precum și condițiile financiare preconizate.</P><P>În cazul în care, pe baza acestor informații detaliate, Comisia consideră că imobilele în cauză pot răspunde efectiv nevoilor sale, ar putea fi inițiată o procedură de negociere cu proprietarul (proprietarii) imobilelor în cauză, în conformitate cu dispozițiile articolului 134 din regulament (UE, Euratom) nr. 1268/2012 privind normele de aplicare a Regulamentului (UE, Euratom) nr. 966/2012.</P><P>Prezentul anunț nu obligă totuși în niciun fel Comisia cu privire la procedurile sale de atribuire a contractului.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Depunerea fișelor de prospectare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fișele de prospectare semnate și datate trebuie prezentate de către proprietari sau reprezentanții lor autorizați în termen de (30 zile lucrătoare de la data publicării) 16:30.</P><P>Informațiile trebuie trimise utilizând una dintre următoarele metode:</P><P>— fie prin scrisoare recomandată, cu dovada ștampilei poștale, la următoarea adresă: Comisia Europeană, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgia,</P><P>— fie prin livrare (personal sau prin orice reprezentant al candidatului sau prin serviciul de curierat) la următoarea adresă: Comisia Europeană, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1 — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgia. Acest departament este deschis de luni până joi între orele 8:00 și 16:30, iar vineri între orele 8:00 și 16:00, cu excepția zilelor de sărbătoare ale Comisiei.</P><P>Pentru expedierea prin curier, data valabilă a expedierii va fi data menționată pe recipisa serviciului de curierat. Pentru expedierile făcute personal sau de către orice reprezentant, expedierea răspunsului, în acest caz, va fi certificată printr-o chitanță datată și semnată de către un funcționar din cadrul departamentului serviciului poștal central al Comisiei care primește livrările de documente.</P><P>În toate cazurile, proprietarul sau reprezentantul acestuia trebuie să respecte și următoarele condiții:</P><P>— fișa de prospectare trebuie prezentată într-un plic dublu,</P><P>— cele 2 plicuri trebuie sigilate,</P><P>—plicul interior care poartă, pe lângă indicarea serviciului destinatar, referința „anunț de prospectare imobiliară pentru a răspunde nevoilor Comisiei Europene în materie de spații de birouri la Bruxelles“, „fișă de prospectare (numele proprietarului sau reprezentantul acestuia)“, „a nu se deschide de serviciul de curierat“,</P><P>— plicurile autoadezive trebuie sigilate cu bandă adezivă, purtând semnătura expeditorului de-a lungul acesteia,</P><P>— dacă proprietarul sau reprezentantul său dorește să obțină informații suplimentare înainte de data depunerii propunerilor, acesta va trimite cererea numai prin e-mail la adresa indicată la punctul 1 de mai sus. De asemenea, ofertanții sunt invitați să consulte cu regularitate site-ul indicat la punctul 1, unde se vor publica periodic întrebările adresate și răspunsurile Comisiei,</P><P>— termenul pentru trimiterea întrebărilor este cu 10 zile lucrătoare înainte de data limită, la ora 16:00.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Informacijska obavijest na pažnju tržištu nekretnina — višegodišnje prognoze potreba za nekretninama u razdoblju od 2020. do 2024. za Europsku komisiju u Bruxellesu te predviđanja lokalnog tržišta</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nadležni odjel Europske komisije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, département OIB.RE. Gestion des biens immobiliers, bureau: CSM1 09/P001, Cours Saint-Michel 23, 1049 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija, e-pošta: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>oib-mail-rel@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — mrežna stranica: </BLK_BTX><URL>http://ec.europa.eu/oib/</URL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opće informacije:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>U skladu s Komunikacijom Komisije [COM(2007)501] od 5.9.2007., cilj je ove obavijesti informiranje sudionika na tržištu nekretnina i drugih zainteresiranih strana o prognozi potreba Europske komisije u Bruxellesu za nekretninama i prikupljanje informacija o projektima i nekretninama unutar definiranog područja.</P><P>Nekretnine koje se traže</P><P>U svrhu zadovoljavanja prostornih potrebna za urede koji se planiraju u razdoblju od 2020.-2024. Europska komisija traži prostore za urede u Bruxellesu, koji se nalaze:</P><P>— najviše 700 metara udaljeni od osi dionica između stanica podzemne željeznice Mérode i Arts-Loi te između stanica podzemne željeznice Arts-Loi i De Brouckère; ili</P><P>— najviše 700 metara od osi linije podzemne željeznice, između stanica Arts-Loi i Rogier; ili</P><P>— najviše 700 metara od osi linije podzemne željeznice, između stanica Delta i Hermann-Debroux.</P><P>Ukupna tražena nadzemna površina kojom bi se zamijenile nekretnine koje su dosegle kraj svog životnog vijeka ili čiji je ugovor o najmu istekao iznosi 80 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT> i 150 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>, tijekom razdoblja od 2020.-2024. Stvarne potrebe utvrdit će se prije svega ovisno o rezultatima tekućih pregovora ili onih koji će se voditi vezano na obnovu sporazuma koji su pred istekom u idućih nekoliko godina, za određeni broj nekretnina kojima se koriste službe Komisije.</P><P>Tražene zgrade koje bi mogle zadovoljiti navedene potrebe moraju biti bruto nadzemne površine od najmanje 10 000 m<FT TYPE="SUP">2</FT>. Poželjno je da te prostorije u cijelosti i isključivo koriste službe Komisije i/ili službe drugih</P><P>europskih institucija ili tijela zajednice. Predloženi ugovori predstavljaju ugovore o korištenju i/ili terminske ugovore o kupoprodaji</P><P>Poželjno je da predmetne zgrade budu dovršene ili da je njihov dovršetak planiran u budućnosti. Međutim projekti se mogu predlagati i, ovisno o pojedinom slučaju, u okviru naknadnog planiranja.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Svrha planiranja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Planiranje u svrhu prikupljanja prijedloga za nekretnine namijenjene uredima, koje mogu zadovoljiti potrebe Zajednice, u području ranije navedenom u točki 2.</P><P>U tu svrhu vlasnici ili njihovi zastupnici pozivaju se da popune obrazac o nekretnini dostupan u dijelu „Ugovori i javne nabave - obavijest o traženju nekretnina” na mrežnoj stranici navedenoj u točki 1.</P><P>Tajnost dobivenih informacija je zajamčena. Kartice s rezultatima traženja zatim se pohranjuju u zaštićenoj bazi podataka kojoj imaju pristup samo ovlašteni predstavnici Europske komisije koji su za to pravilno osposobljeni.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Korištenje prikupljenih informacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prikupljene informacije pohranjene u bazi podataka Komisija će koristiti za identifikaciju zgrada čije površine mogu zadovoljiti potrebe uredskih prostorija.</P><P>Za te zgrade OIB će kontaktirati vlasnike, kako bi se prikupile detaljne informacije o stanju i kapacitetima tih zgrada te o predviđenim financijskim uvjetima.</P><P>Ako na temelju tih detaljnih informacija Komisija zaključi da predmetna nekretnina može uspješno zadovoljiti njene potrebe, može započeti postupak pregovaranja s jednim ili više vlasnika nekretnine, u skladu s odredbama članka 134. uredbe (EU, Euratom) br. 1268/2012 o pravilima primjene uredbe (EU, Euratom) br. 966/2012.</P><P>Ova obavijest, međutim, ni na koji način ne obvezuje Komisiju u smislu postupaka sklapanja ugovora.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predaja kartica s rezultatima traženja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Potpisane i datirane obrasce o nekretnini vlasnici ili njihovi ovlašteni zastupnici moraju dostaviti (30 radnih dana nakon datuma objavljivanja) do 16:30.</P><P>Informacije se moraju dostaviti na jedan od sljedećih načina:</P><P>— preporučenom poštom, što se potvrđuje poštanskim žigom, na sljedeću adresu: Europska komisija, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1, — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgium,</P><P>— dostavom (osobno ili putem bilo koje strane koja predstavlja natjecatelja ili kurirskom službom) na sljedeću adresu: Europska komisija, Office pour les infrastructures et la logistique — Bruxelles, unité OIB.RE.1, — Avenue du Bourget 1, 1140 Bruxelles, Belgium. Odjel je otvoren 8:00 – 16:30, od ponedjeljka do četvrtka i 8:00 – 16:00 petkom , osim na praznike Komisije.</P><P>Za isporuke putem dostavljača, valjani datum slanja bit će datum na potvrdi dostavljača o dostavi. Za isporuke koje su osobno dostavljene ili koje je dostavio predstavnik, isporuka odgovora će se u tom slučaju potvrditi računom koji je datirao i potpisao Komisijin središnji odjel za poštu koji preuzima dostavu dokumenata.</P><P>U svakom slučaju, vlasnik ili njegov zastupnik moraju se također pridržavati sljedećih načina:</P><P>— obrazac o nekretnini mora se slati u dvostrukoj omotnici;</P><P>— obje omotnice moraju biti zapečaćene;</P><P>— na unutarnjoj omotnici, ispod naziva službe primatelja, potrebno je navesti referencu „avis de prospection d'immeubles pour satisfaire les besoins de la Commission européenne en espaces de bureaux à Bruxelles” („obrazac o nekretnini koja zadovoljava potrebe Europske komisije vezane na uredske prostorije u Bruxellesu”), „fiche de prospection de („obrazac o nekretnini” (ime i prezime vlasnika ili njegovog zastupnika), „à ne pas ouvrir par le service du courier” („ne otvarati”);</P><P>— samoljepljive omotnice moraju se zatvoriti ljepljivom trakom, s potpisom pošiljatelja ispisanim preko trake;</P><P>— ako vlasnik ili njegov zastupnik prije datuma za podnošenje obrasca o nekretnini želi dobiti dodatne podatke, svoj zahtjev treba uputiti isključivo putem e-pošte na adresu ranije navedenu u točki 1. Ponuditelji se također pozivaju da redovito provjeravaju mrežnu stranicu iz točke 1., budući da će se na njoj redovito objavljivati pitanja i odgovori Komisije;</P><P>— krajnji datum za slanje pitanja je (10 radnih dana prije datuma isteka roka za podnošenje) u 16:00 sati.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>