<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="129472-2018" EDITION="2018059"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-128982-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180407</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>59</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180324</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 059-129472</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:129472-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN DE FR</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="66100000">Banking and investment services</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="66140000">Portfolio management services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180320</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180406 14:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>OB302</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Tyskland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Begrænset udbud 2738 med forudgående prækvalifikationsprocedure</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Deutschland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bekanntmachung beschränkte ausschreibung NR. 2738 mit vorausgehender Präqualifikation</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Germany</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Restricted invitation to tender 2738 with preceding pre-qualification procedure</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Alemania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Múnich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Invitación a licitar restringida 2738 con procedimiento de preselección previo</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Saksa</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Rajoitettu tarjouspyyntö 2738 (jota edeltää esikarsintamenettely)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Allemagne</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Appel à la concurrence restreint 2738 précédé d’une procédure de présélection</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Γερμανία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Μόναχο</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Πρόσκληση υποβολής προσφορών κλειστής διαδικασίας αριθ. 2738 με προηγηθείσα διαδικασία προεπιλογής</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Germania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Monaco di Baviera</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Gara d'appalto ristretta 2738 preceduta da una procedura di pre-qualifica.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Duitsland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Niet-openbare uitnodiging tot inschrijving nr. 2738 met voorafgaande prekwalificatieprocedure</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Alemanha</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munique</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anúncio publicado de convite limitado a concurso 2738 com procedimento de pré-qualificação prévio</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Tyskland</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Selektiv anbudsinfordran nr 2738 med föregående förhandsförfarande</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Německo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Mnichov</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Výzva k účasti v užším nabídkovém řízení č. 2738 s předcházejícím řízením předběžné kvalifikace</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Saksamaa</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Piiratud hankemenetlus 2738, eelneva eelkvalifitseerimismenetlusega</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Németország</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>2738. számú meghívásos pályázati eljárás megelőző előminősítési eljárással</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Vokietija, VFR</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Miunchenas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ribotas kvietimas pateikti pasiūlymus 2738 su išankstine atrankos procedūra</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Vācija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Minhene</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Uzaicinājums uz slēgtu konkursu 2738 ar iepriekšēju priekšatlases procedūru</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Ġermanja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Munich</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Stedina ristretta għall-offerti 2738 bi proċedura ta' prekwalifikazzjoni li tippreċedi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Niemcy</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Monachium</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Zaproszenie do składania ofert przy przetargu ograniczonym nr 2738 z uprzednią kwalifikacją wstępną</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Nemecko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Mníchov</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Užšia výzva na prekladanie ponúk č. 2738 s predchádzajúcim konaním predbežného výberu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Nemčija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Omejen javni razpis 2738 s predhodnim predkvalifikacijskim postopkom</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Ghearmáin, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Cuireadh srianta chun tairisceana 2738 le nós imeachta réamhcháilithe roimhe sin</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Гepмaния</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Мюнхен</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ограничена покана за участие в търг 2738 с предходна процедура преди класирането</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Germania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Invitare la licitație restrânsă 2738 anterioară procedurii de pre-calificare</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Njemačka</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>München</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ograničenipoziv za dostavu ponuda 2738 s prethodnim postupkom predkvalifikacije</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Patentorganisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Organisation européenne des brevets (OEB)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Begrænset udbud 2738 med forudgående prækvalifikationsprocedure</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Bekanntmachung beschränkte ausschreibung NR. 2738 mit vorausgehender Präqualifikation</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Auftraggeber:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Patentorganisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, handelnd durch das Europäische Patentamt mit Hauptsitz in D-80469 München, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, Postanschrift: EPA, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>München</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, DEUTSCHLAND</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Die Europäische Patentorganisation ist eine zwischenstaatliche Organisation, die durch das 1977 in Kraft getretene Europäische Patentübereinkommen gegründet wurde. Ihr gehören derzeit 38 Mitgliedstaaten an (Albanien, Belgien, Bulgarien, Dänemark, Deutschland, ehemalige jugoslawische Republik Mazedonien, Estland, Finnland, Frankreich, Griechenland, Irland, Island, Italien, Kroatien, Lettland, Liechtenstein, Litauen, Luxemburg, Malta, Monaco, Niederlande, Norwegen, Österreich, Polen, Portugal, Rumänien, San Marino, Schweden, Schweiz, Serbien, Slowakei, Slowenien, Spanien, Tschechische Republik, Türkei, Ungarn, Vereinigtes Königreich und Zypern). Ausführendes Organ der EPO ist das Europäische Patentamt, das die Recherche und Prüfung europäischer Patentanmeldungen und die Erteilung europäischer Patente zur Aufgabe hat. Es beschäftigt rund 6 700 Bedienstete am Hauptsitz des EPA in München, in einer Zweigstelle in Den Haag/Rijswijk (NL) und in zwei Dienststellen in Berlin und Wien. (Die Zahl der Mitgliedstaaten und der Bediensteten kann sich ändern.)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vergabeverfahren:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Beschränkte Ausschreibung im Leistungswettbewerb</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Gegenstand des Auftrags:</P><P>Erbringung von Dienstleistungen im Bereich Gewerbe- und Büroimmobilien zur Unterstützung bei der Vermietung von Büroräumen in München, Deutschland.</P><P>b) Teilung in Lose:</P><P>Nicht zutreffend.</P><P>c) Erforderliche Sicherheiten und Bürgschaften:</P><P>Wird in den Ausschreibungsunterlagen festgelegt.</P><P>d) Wichtigste Zahlungsbedingungen:</P><P>Innerhalb von 30 Tagen nach Abschluss und Abnahme der Arbeiten.</P><P>e) Rechtlich vorgeschriebene Qualifikationen:</P><P>Wie für professionelle Gewerbeimmobiliendienstleistungen gefordert (s. auch Vorauswahlfragen unter Nr. 11.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Erfüllungsort und Leistungsfrist:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Erfüllungsort:</P><P>In den Räumlichkeiten des Auftragnehmers; gelegentlich in einem der EPA Dienstgebäude.</P><P>b) Vertragslaufzeit oder Ausführungsfrist:</P><P>Ab Vertragsunterzeichnung bis zur erfolgreichen Anmietung.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Änderungsvorschläge:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Änderungsvorschläge, die sich in einer erheblichen Einschränkung der Rechte und Sicherheiten der EPO niederschlagen würden, sind nicht zulässig.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsform einer Bietergemeinschaft:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Reichen mehrere Bieter ein gemeinsames Angebot ein, so haften sie gesamtschuldnerisch für die Erfüllung der vertraglichen Verpflichtungen. Zusammen mit dem Angebot ist eine entsprechende von allen Mitgliedern der Bietergemeinschaft unterzeichnete Erklärung einzureichen, in der ein Vertreter bestimmt ist, der bevollmächtigt ist, für alle Mitglieder zu handeln.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kriterien für die Beurteilung der zur Auftragsausführung erforderlichen Fachkunde, Leistungsfähigkeit und Zuverlässigkeit des Bieters:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Angebote von Bietern, die nicht die unter Nr. 11 genannten Auswahlkriterien erfüllen und/oder deren finanzielle und professionelle Zuverlässigkeit aufgrund ihrer Verhältnisse ernstlich infrage steht (s. Artikel 2 der Allgemeinen Ausschreibungsbedingungen, abrufbar unter www.epo.org), sind von der Auftragsvergabe ausgeschlossen.</P><P>Die zur Auftragsausführung erforderliche Fachkunde, Leistungsfähigkeit und Zuverlässigkeit des Bieters wird auf der Grundlage der Angaben und Nachweise beurteilt, die in Beantwortung des Fragebogens in Anhang 1 der Allgemeinen Ausschreibungsbedingungen und zusätzlicher Fragebögen zu den Verdingungsunterlagen erbracht werden.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bindefrist:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sechs Monate ab dem Annahmeschluss für Angebote, der mit dem Versand der Verdingungsunterlagen mitgeteilt wird.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kriterien für die Zuschlagserteilung:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Der Zuschlag wird dem Bieter erteilt, der am besten in der Lage ist, die Anforderungen</P><P>Der EPO zu erfüllen. Ausschlaggebend sind dabei:</P><P>Finanzielle Aspekte: 40 %,</P><P>Technische Aspekte: 60 %.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sonstige Angaben:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bieter, die sich für die Teilnahme an dieser Ausschreibung interessieren, übermitteln ihre Antworten auf die Fragen des unter Nr. 6 angegebenen Fragebogens einschließlich der erforderlichen Nachweise bis zu dem unter Nr. 6 a) genannten Datum an die unter Nr. 6 e) angegebene E-Mail-Adresse.</P><P>Die Vorauswahlfragen betreffen unter anderem:</P><P>Wirtschaftliche und finanzielle Kapazität des Bieters</P><P>1. Bestätigen Sie unter Vorlage entsprechender Nachweise, dass Sie über mindestens fünf Jahre Erfahrung mit Gewerbeimmobilienstrategien und insbesondere mit dem deutschen Büroimmobilienmarkt verfügen;</P><P>2. Der Bieter erklärt, dass sein Unternehmen nicht insolvent ist oder abgewickelt wird, die gewerbliche Tätigkeit nicht eingestellt oder ausgesetzt hat, nicht einer gerichtlichen Verwaltung unterstellt ist, keine Vereinbarungen mit Gläubigern getroffen hat bzw. sich nicht in einer ähnlichen Lage befindet;</P><P>3. Der Bieter erklärt sich damit einverstanden, dass die EPO über eine externe Quelle eine Bonitätsprüfung seines Unternehmens durchführen darf;</P><P>4. Nennen Sie die Namen und Kontaktdaten der Mitarbeiter, die im Namen Ihres Unternehmens unterschriftsberechtigt sind, und fügen Sie einen aktuellen Auszug aus dem Handelsregister oder einem ähnlichen Verzeichnis für Ihr Unternehmen bei (ggf. ergänzt durch weitere Informationen). Falls das Register keine entsprechenden konkreten Angaben enthält, ist für eine Bevollmächtigung zu sorgen;</P><P>Wirtschaftliche und professionelle Kapazität des Bieters</P><P>5. Bestätigen Sie unter Vorlage entsprechender Nachweise, dass Sie die EPO auf dem Münchner Mietmarkt für Gewerbe- und Büroimmobilien durch Kontakte im nationalen und internationalen Umfeld aktiv unterstützen können;</P><P>6. Beschreiben Sie die Hauptfelder Ihrer Immobilientätigkeit;</P><P>7. Bestätigen Sie unter Vorlage entsprechender Nachweise, dass Sie Zugang zum Münchner Mietmarkt für Gewerbe- und Büroimmobilien haben;</P><P>8. Reichen Sie mindestens drei Referenzen/schriftliche Kundenberichte von früheren/aktuellen Kunden ein, für die Sie in Europa ähnliche Dienstleistungen erbracht haben. Dabei sollte die folgende Struktur verwendet werden:</P><P>— Allgemeine Angaben:</P><P>Name des Kunden/Länder, Standorte/Wirtschaftszweig.</P><P>— Einzelheiten:</P><P>Beschreibung der Leistungen und wichtigste technische Einzelheiten der erbrachten Dienstleistungen/Zeitraum der Leistung/Mietvolumen</P><P>Beachten Sie Nr. 6 b) und c) dieser Bekanntmachung bezüglich der auf die Vorauswahlphase folgenden Schritte.</P><P>Derzeit wird davon ausgegangen, dass der Zuschlag im Juni 2018 erteilt wird.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munich: Restricted invitation to tender 2738 with preceding pre-qualification procedure</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Múnich: Invitación a licitar restringida 2738 con procedimiento de preselección previo</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Rajoitettu tarjouspyyntö 2738 (jota edeltää esikarsintamenettely)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munich: Appel à la concurrence restreint 2738 précédé d’une procédure de présélection</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVIS PUBLIÉ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autorité responsable du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>L'</BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>Organisation européenne des brevets (OEB)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, agissant par l'intermédiaire de l'Office européen des brevets; siège: Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich; adresse postale: OEB, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ALLEMAGNE.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>L'Organisation européenne des brevets est une organisation intergouvernementale instituée par la Convention sur le brevet européen, entrée en vigueur en 1977. Elle compte actuellement 38 États membres (l'Albanie, l’Allemagne, l’Autriche, la Belgique, la Bulgarie, Chypre, la Croatie, le Danemark, l’Espagne, l'Estonie, l'ex-République yougoslave de Macédoine, la Finlande, la France, la Grèce, la Hongrie, l’Irlande, l’Islande, l’Italie, la Lettonie, le Liechtenstein, la Lituanie, le Luxembourg, Malte, Monaco, la Norvège, les Pays-Bas, la Pologne, le Portugal, la Roumanie, le Royaume-Uni, Saint-Marin, la Serbie, la Slovaquie, la Slovénie, la Suède, la Suisse, la République tchèque et la Turquie). L'organe exécutif de l'OEB est l'Office européen des brevets, qui est chargé de la recherche et de l'examen des demandes de brevet européen et de la délivrance de brevets européens. Il emploie environ 6 700 agents en poste à son siège à Munich, dans son département à La Haye/Rijswijk (NL) et dans ses agences à Berlin et à Vienne (le nombre d'États membres et d'agents indiqués peut changer).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Mode de passation du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Appel à la concurrence restreint avec attribution discrétionnaire.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Objet du marché:</P><P>Fourniture de services dans le secteur immobilier commercial, en soutien à la location d'espaces de bureaux à Munich, Allemagne.</P><P>(b) Partage en lots:</P><P>Sans objet.</P><P>(c) Dépôts et garanties exigés:</P><P>«seront définis dans le cahier des charges»</P><P>(d) Principales conditions relatives au paiement:</P><P>Dans un délai de 30 jours à compter de l'exécution et de l'acceptation.</P><P>(e) Qualifications exigées par la loi:</P><P>Telles qu'applicables pour la fourniture de services professionnels dans le secteur immobilier commercial (voir aussi critères de présélection au point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lieu et période d'exécution:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Lieu où les services doivent être fournis:</P><P>Fourniture des services dans vos locaux, avec des rencontres ponctuelles sur l'un des sites de l'OEB.</P><P>(b) Durée du contrat ou délai de livraison ou d'exécution des prestations:</P><P>Le contrat sera établi pour la durée nécessaire jusqu'à l'achèvement des services, à compter de la date de signature du contrat.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variantes:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les propositions de variantes susceptibles de réduire de façon significative les droits et garanties de l'OEB ne sont pas autorisées.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure de présélection et d'appel à la concurrence:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Date finale de réponse aux questions de présélection (voir point 11 de cet Avis publié):</P><P>Le 6.4.2018 (14:00) (HEC)</P><P>Les parties intéressées peuvent faire part de leur intérêt à participer à la procédure d'appel à la concurrence en répondant par courrier électronique aux questions de présélection telles que décrites au point 11 (Autres informations), à l'aide du questionnaire fourni via le lien suivant et envoyé à l'adresse électronique indiquée au point 6(e) du présent avis.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Veuillez suivre attentivement les instructions figurant sur le questionnaire, compléter et signer le document établi et l'envoyer à l'OEB:</P><P>Scannez le questionnaire complété et signé, ainsi que toutes les informations pertinentes. Envoyez les documents à l'adresse postale et la version scannée à l'adresse électronique indiquée au point 6(e) du présent avis publié, avant la date indiquée précédemment.</P><P>Dans l'éventualité où des précisions seraient nécessaires en ce qui concerne les réponses aux questions de présélection, l'OEB saurait gré aux parties intéressées de soumettre leurs questions au sujet des questions de présélection avant le 29.3.2018 (12:00) (HEC) au plus tard, afin de pouvoir respecter les délais ultérieurs.</P><P>(b) Envoi du cahier des charges:</P><P>Le cahier des charges ne sera transmis qu'à 6 candidats potentiels au maximum. Les candidats éligibles seront sélectionnés sur la base d'une évaluation initiale des réponses fournies dans les questionnaires. Cette présélection sera effectuée après évaluation des critères suivants:</P><P>Respect des critères de sélection définis au point 11 et qualité des réponses fournies dans les autres informations (questions de présélection), telles que détaillées dans le questionnaire.</P><P>La diffusion du cahier des charges aux candidats retenus est provisoirement prévue pour le 11.4.2018.</P><P>(c) Date limite de réception par l’OEB des demandes de précisions pour le cahier des charges:</P><P>— provisoirement prévue pour le 18.4.2018. La date exacte sera communiquée aux candidats éligibles lors de l'envoi du cahier des charges,</P><P>— les questions doivent parvenir par lettre ou par courrier électronique.</P><P>(d) Date limite de dépôt des offres / Nombre d'exemplaires à envoyer à l'Office:</P><P>— provisoirement prévue pour le 2.5.2018. La date exacte sera communiquée aux candidats éligibles lors de l'envoi du cahier des charges,</P><P>— les offres doivent être soumises en une version originale avec des informations sur les prix (formulaire d'offre et documents d'appui éventuels) et une copie enregistrée sur un support de données, sans informations sur les prix, sous forme de PDF avec possibilité de recherche.</P><P>(e) Adresse à laquelle doivent être envoyées les demandes de précisions, les réponses aux questions de présélection et les offres:</P><P>Office européen des brevets</P><P>(2738 Sélection)</P><P>Service central des achats</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Les offres doivent être soumises uniquement par courrier postal, et non par télécopie ou par courrier électronique. Les offres soumises par télécopie ou par courrier électronique ne peuvent être prises en considération.</P><P>(f) Langue ou langues dans lesquelles les demandes de précisions, les réponses aux questions de présélection et les offres doivent être rédigées:</P><P>Anglais</P><P>Le questionnaire et le cahier des charges ne seront disponibles qu’en anglais.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Forme légale du groupement, en cas d'offre soumise en commun:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Si plusieurs candidats soumettent une offre en commun, ils doivent être conjointement et solidairement responsables de l’exécution de leurs obligations au titre du contrat. Une déclaration à cet effet, dûment signée par tous les membres du groupement et désignant un représentant autorisé à agir pour le compte de tous les membres, doit accompagner l’offre.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critères visant à évaluer les compétences, les capacités et la fiabilité des candidats pour pouvoir exécuter le marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Seront éliminées les offres émanant de candidats qui ne satisfont pas aux critères de sélection énoncés au point 11 de cet avis publié et/ou dont la situation suscite des doutes sérieux quant à leur fiabilité du point de vue financier et professionnel (cf. article 2 des conditions générales relatives aux appels à la concurrence, qui figurent à l'adresse www.epo.org).</P><P>Les compétences, les capacités et la fiabilité des candidats pour pouvoir exécuter le marché seront évaluées sur la base des informations et pièces justificatives soumises en réponse au questionnaire de l'annexe 1 aux conditions générales relatives aux appels à la concurrence, et en réponse à tout questionnaire supplémentaire inclus dans le cahier des charges.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Durée obligatoire de validité des offres:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 mois à compter de la date limite de dépôt des offres, qui sera indiquée lors de l'envoi du cahier des charges.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critères d'attribution du marché:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le marché sera attribué (critères d’attribution) au candidat dont l’offre a été retenue sur la base de sa capacité à satisfaire aux besoins et aux exigences de l’OEB, mesurée ainsi:</P><P>— aspects financiers: 40 %,</P><P>— aspects techniques: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autres informations:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Si les parties sont intéressées pour participer à cet appel à la concurrence, elles doivent envoyer leurs réponses aux questions figurant dans le point 6 du questionnaire, accompagnées des justificatifs demandés, à l'adresse électronique mentionnée au point 6(e) du présent Avis publié dans période d'avis mentionné au point 6(a):</P><P>Les questions de présélection comprennent notamment les suivantes:</P><P>Capacité financière et économique du candidat:</P><P>1. veuillez confirmer et fournir des justificatifs attestant que vous appliquez des stratégies dans le secteur immobilier commercial, notamment en ce qui concerne les espaces de bureaux sur le marché allemand, depuis au moins 5 ans;</P><P>2. le candidat déclare que sa société n'est pas en état de faillite, de liquidation, de cessation ou de suspension d'activités, n'est pas sous concordat judiciaire, n'a pas conclu d'accords avec des créanciers et ne se trouve dans aucune situation analogue;</P><P>3. le candidat accepte-t-il que l'OEB effectue un contrôle de solvabilité dans son entreprise par l'intermédiaire d'une source externe?</P><P>4. veuillez fournir les coordonnées et les noms du ou des représentant(s) autorisé(s) à apposer sa/leur signature au nom de votre entreprise, ainsi qu'un extrait récent de votre entreprise au registre du commerce ou auprès d'un registre similaire (si besoin est accompagné d'informations supplémentaires). Si ces informations ne sont pas concrètement précisées dans le registre, veuillez prendre vos dispositions pour une procuration.</P><P>Aptitude professionnelle et technique du candidat:</P><P>5. veuillez confirmer et fournir des justificatifs attestant que vous êtes en mesure de soutenir activement l'OEB sur le marché de la location de biens immobiliers commerciaux à Munich, avec des contacts sur le plan national et international;</P><P>6. veuillez décrire les principaux axes de votre activité immobilière;</P><P>7. veuillez confirmer et fournir des justificatifs attestant que vous pouvez gagner en visibilité commerciale à Munich pour la location de biens immobiliers commerciaux;</P><P>8. veuillez fournir au moins 3 références/témoignages écrits de clients anciens/actuels auxquels le candidat a fourni des services similaires en Europe. Il convient d'utiliser la structure suivante:</P><P>— informations générales:</P><P>Nom de l'organisation/sites dans le pays/secteur commercial,</P><P>— détails:</P><P>Descriptions des services et principaux détails techniques du service fourni/période de service/superficie de la location.</P><P>Veuillez tenir compte des points 6(b) et 6(c) du présent avis publié pour le suivi de ce qui précède.</P><P>Selon les prévisions actuelles, le marché devrait être attribué en juin 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Μόναχο: Πρόσκληση υποβολής προσφορών κλειστής διαδικασίας αριθ. 2738 με προηγηθείσα διαδικασία προεπιλογής</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Monaco di Baviera: Gara d'appalto ristretta 2738 preceduta da una procedura di pre-qualifica.</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Niet-openbare uitnodiging tot inschrijving nr. 2738 met voorafgaande prekwalificatieprocedure</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munique: Anúncio publicado de convite limitado a concurso 2738 com procedimento de pré-qualificação prévio</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Selektiv anbudsinfordran nr 2738 med föregående förhandsförfarande</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Mnichov: Výzva k účasti v užším nabídkovém řízení č. 2738 s předcházejícím řízením předběžné kvalifikace</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Piiratud hankemenetlus 2738, eelneva eelkvalifitseerimismenetlusega</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: 2738. számú meghívásos pályázati eljárás megelőző előminősítési eljárással</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Miunchenas: Ribotas kvietimas pateikti pasiūlymus 2738 su išankstine atrankos procedūra</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Minhene: Uzaicinājums uz slēgtu konkursu 2738 ar iepriekšēju priekšatlases procedūru</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Munich: Stedina ristretta għall-offerti 2738 bi proċedura ta' prekwalifikazzjoni li tippreċedi</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Monachium: Zaproszenie do składania ofert przy przetargu ograniczonym nr 2738 z uprzednią kwalifikacją wstępną</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Mníchov: Užšia výzva na prekladanie ponúk č. 2738 s predchádzajúcim konaním predbežného výberu</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Omejen javni razpis 2738 s predhodnim predkvalifikacijskim postopkom</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Cuireadh srianta chun tairisceana 2738 le nós imeachta réamhcháilithe roimhe sin</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-Мюнхен: Ограничена покана за участие в търг 2738 с предходна процедура преди класирането</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Invitare la licitație restrânsă 2738 anterioară procedurii de pre-calificare</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>DE-München: Ograničenipoziv za dostavu ponuda 2738 s prethodnim postupkom predkvalifikacije</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Published notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding Authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>The European Patent Organisation (EPO)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX> acting through the European Patent Office: Headquarters, Bob-van-Benthem-Platz 1, D-80469 Munich, Postal address: EPO, D-80298 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Munich</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, GERMANY.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The European Patent Organisation is an intergovernmental organisation set up pursuant to the European Patent Convention which entered into force in 1977. At present it has 38 Member States (Albania, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Croatia, Cyprus, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Romania, San Marino, Serbia, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey and United Kingdom). The executive body of the EPO is the European Patent Office which is charged with the searching and examination of European patent applications and the granting of European patents. It employs approximately 6700 staff at EPO headquarters in Munich, a branch at The Hague/Rijswijk (NL) and sub-offices in Berlin and Vienna (the number of Member states and staff members indicated may change).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Award procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted invitation to tender with discretionary award of contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description of the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Purpose of the contract:</P><P>Provision of Commercial Office Real Estate Services for support in rental of office space in Munich, Germany.</P><P>(b) Division into lots:</P><P>Not applicable.</P><P>(c) Any deposits and guarantees required:</P><P>“will be defined in tender documents”</P><P>(d) Main terms concerning payment:</P><P>Within 30 days of completion and acceptance.</P><P>(e) Qualifications required by law:</P><P>As applicable for provision of professional commercial real estate services (see also pre-selection criteria under point 11).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place and period of performance:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>(a) Place at which the contract is to be performed:</P><P>Delivery at your premises, with occasional meetings at one of the EPO sites.</P><P>(b) Duration of contract or time limit for delivery or completion of services/work:</P><P>The contract shall be for the duration until success, from contract signature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Variants:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proposals for variants, the effect of which would be to reduce significantly the rights and safeguards of the EPO, are not allowed.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pre-selection and Tender Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>a) Final date for reply to Pre-Selection Questions (see point 11 of this Published Notice):</P><P>6.4.2018, 14:00 hrs (CET)</P><P>Interested parties may show their interest in participating in this tender procedure by replying to the Pre-selection Questions as described under point 11 (Other information), using the questionnaire provided under the following link and sent to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice.</P><P>http://webserv.epo.org/download.nsf/0/C81EA7575DDFFF18C1258255005788DC?OpenDocument</P><P>Please follow the instructions on the questionnaire carefully, complete and sign the resulting document and send it to the EPO:</P><P>Scan the completed and signed questionnaire, together with all relevant information. Send the documents to the postal address AND the scan to the e-mail address listed under point 6e of this Published Notice, both by the date stated above</P><P>As clarification of answers to the Pre-selection Questions might be required, the EPO would appreciate it, if interested parties submit their questions to the Pre-selection Questions by latest 29.03.2018; 12:00 (CET) in order to maintain subsequent timelines.</P><P>b) Dispatch of procurement documents:</P><P>The procurement documents will only be made available to up to 6 potential bidders. The eligible participants will be selected based on an initial evaluation of the responses to the questionnaires. This pre-selection will be evaluated based on:</P><P>The fulfilment of the selection criteria under point 11 and the quality of responses to other information (pre-selection questions) detailed in the questionnaire.</P><P>The distribution of the procurement documents to the selected participants is provisionally scheduled for 11.4.2018.</P><P>c) Final date for receipt by the EPO of requests for clarification to the procurement documents:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 18.4.18. The exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Questions must be submitted by letter or E-Mail.</P><P>d) Final date for receipt of bids / number of copies to be sent:</P><P>— Provisionally scheduled for 2.5.18. Exact date will be communicated to the eligible participants with the dispatch of the procurement documents,</P><P>— Bids shall be submitted in one original with price information (offer form and any supporting documents) and one copy, to be filed on data carrier, without price information as searchable PDF.</P><P>e) Address to which the requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be sent:</P><P>European patent office</P><P>(2738 Selection)</P><P>Central Procurement</P><P>Bob-van-Benthum-Platz 1</P><P>80469 München</P><P>E-mail: mntenderclarifications@epo.org</P><P>Please submit bids by post only and not by fax or e-mail. Bids submitted by fax or e-mail will be excluded.</P><P>f) Language or languages in which requests for clarification, pre-selection answers and bids must be drawn up:</P><P>English;</P><P>The questionnaire and procurement documents will be available in English only.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal form of the grouping in the event of a joint bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If several bidders submit a joint bid, they must be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the obligations under the contract. A declaration to this effect, duly signed by all members of the grouping and appointing a representative that is authorised to act on behalf of all members, must be submitted with the bid.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for assessing bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bids from bidders who do not fulfil the selection criteria stated in Point 11 of this Published notice and/or whose circumstances are such as seriously to call into question their financial and professional reliability (see Article 2 of the General Conditions of Tender, available under www.epo.org) will not be considered for contract award.</P><P>Bidders' know-how, capacity and reliability to fulfil the contract will be assessed on basis of the information and evidence submitted in reply to the questionnaire in Annex 1 to the General conditions of tender and any additional questionnaire(s) included in the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Period during which the bidder is bound by his bid:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>6 months following the final date for receipt of bids which will be indicated with the dispatch of the Procurement documents.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteria for the award of contract:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The contract shall be awarded (award criteria) to the bidder whose bid is to be preferred having regard to the bidder's ability to meet the requirements of the EPO to be measured by:</P><P>Financial aspects: 40 %</P><P>Technical aspects: 60 %</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>If interested in participating in this tender, parties shall send their reply to the questions provided in the questionnaire under point 6, including requested evidence to the e-mail address mentioned under point 6e of this Published Notice within the notice period mentioned under point 6a:</P><P>Pre-selection Questions include:</P><P>Economic and Financial Capacity of the bidder</P><P>1. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have at least a track record of 5 years in Commercial Real Estate strategies, especially office space in the German market.</P><P>2. The applicant declares that his company is not bankrupt or being wound up, have ceased or suspended business activities, is being administered by courts or have entered into arrangements with creditors or analogous situations?</P><P>3. The applicant agrees that the EPO runs a solvency check on your company via an external source?</P><P>4. Please supply details and the name(s) of the representative(s) authorised to sign on behalf of your company, together with a recent excerpt from the commercial or similar register for your company (where so needed supplemented by additional information). In case the register does not specify this concretely, please arrange for a power of attorney.</P><P>Technical and professional capacity of the bidder:</P><P>5. Please confirm, and provide evidence, that you have the ability to actively support the EPO in Commercial office real estate rental market in Munich with contacts in the national and international environment.</P><P>6. Please describe your main lines of real estate activity.</P><P>7. Please confirm, and provide evidence that you can gain market exposure in Munich for commercial office real estate rental.</P><P>8. Please provide a minimum of three references/ written customer testimonials from previous / current customers to whom the bidder has provided similar services within Europe. The following structure should be used:</P><P>— General info:</P><P>Organisation name/ Country locations/ Business sector;</P><P>— Details:</P><P>Service descriptions and main technical details of the service provided / Service period / Size of rental</P><P>Please observe Points 6(b) and 6(c) of this Published Notice for the follow up to the above.</P><P>Contract award is expected to take place in June 2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>