<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="130482-2018"
            EDITION="2018059">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-134482-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180424</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>59</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180324</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 059-130482</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:130482-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.nhsscotlandprocurement.scot.nhs.uk/</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/Default.aspx</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="72000000">IT services: consulting, software development, Internet and support</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="48000000">Software package and information systems</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKM">SCOTLAND</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKM">SCOTLAND</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">1750000</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180323</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180424 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="6">Body governed by public law</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="H">Health</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Единбург</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>ИТ услуги: консултации, разработване на софтуер, Интернет и поддръжка</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Informační technologie: poradenství, vývoj programového vybavení, internet a podpora</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>It-tjenester: rådgivning, programmeludvikling, internet og support</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-Dienste: Beratung, Software-Entwicklung, Internet und Hilfestellung</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Εδιμβούργο</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες τεχνολογίας των πληροφοριών: παροχή συμβουλών, ανάπτυξη λογισμικού, Διαδίκτυο και υποστήριξη</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT services: consulting, software development, Internet and support</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edimburgo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios TI: consultoría, desarrollo de software, Internet y apoyo</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-teenused: nõuande-, tarkvaraarendus-, Interneti- ja tugiteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tietotekniset palvelut: neuvonta, ohjelmistojen kehittäminen, Internet ja tuki</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Édimbourg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de technologies de l'information, conseil, développement de logiciels, internet et appui</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Dún Éideann</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT services: consulting, software development, Internet and support</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge informacijske tehnologije: savjetovanje, razvoj programske podrške, internet i podrška</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-szolgáltatások: tanácsadás, szoftverfejlesztés, internet és támogatás</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edimburgo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi informatici: consulenza, sviluppo di software, Internet e supporto</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT paslaugos: konsultavimas, programinės įrangos kūrimas, internetas ir aptarnavimo paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburga</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT pakalpojumi konsultēšana, programmatūras izstrāde, internets un atbalsts</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinbugh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' IT: konsulenza, żvilupp ta' softwer, Internet u appoġġ</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-diensten: adviezen, softwareontwikkeling, internet en ondersteuning</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edynburg</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi informatyczne: konsultacyjne, opracowywania oprogramowania, internetowe i wsparcia</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edimburgo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de TI: consultoria, desenvolvimento de software, Internet e apoio</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii IT: consultanţă, dezvoltare de software, internet şi asistenţă</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Služby informačných technológií: konzultácie, vývoj softvéru, internet a podpora</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve informacijske tehnologije: svetovanje, razvoj programske opreme, internet in podpora</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Edinburgh</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-tjänster: konsultverksamhet, programvaruutveckling, Internet och stöd</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">The Common Services Agency (more commonly known as NHS National Services Scotland) (“NSS")</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>48e9badd-4650-45c1-8f76-297bc043a064</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>The Common Services Agency (more commonly known as NHS National Services Scotland) (“NSS")</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Gyle Square (NSS Head Office), 1 South Gyle Crescent</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Edinburgh</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>EH12 9EB</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <E_MAIL>jim.binnie@nhs.net</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.nhsscotlandprocurement.scot.nhs.uk/</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/search/Search_AuthProfile.aspx?ID=AA11883</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CENTRAL_PURCHASING/>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/Default.aspx</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/Default.aspx</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="BODY_PUBLIC"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="HEALTH"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>National Catering Information System</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="72000000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>NHS National Services Scotland (formerly the Common Services Agency), on behalf of NHS Scotland, wish to contract a service provider to provide a bespoke Catering Information System to replace the current methods used in all NHS Health Boards across Scotland.</P>
               <P>The contract will be let as a single-supplier framework by NHS National Services Scotland and will be available for use by all Health Boards, including Special Health Boards and any associated organisations engaged with Health Boards in the provision of Healthcare in Scotland. The successful supplier will be expected to, migrate data from legacy systems, implement new system, train users and support the system throughout Scotland. A National Licence for the software may be purchased. The system must be supported for a minimum of seven years from the project completion date.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">1750000</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="48000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKM"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Scotland.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The need for a National Catering Information System (NCIS) was first identified whilst catering reviews of NHS Boards were being undertaken in 2013 as part of the National Strategic Review of Soft Facilities. During the catering review process, catering managers identified the need for a catering IT system that could provide them with timely data across a number of service areas, to enabling informed decision-making for the service, without the need to wait for official finance statements.</P>
                  <P>The proposed NCIS will include the following modules:</P>
                  <P>— Stock planning, management and control,</P>
                  <P>— Production planning, purchasing and waste management,</P>
                  <P>— Recipe costing,</P>
                  <P>— Financial, management, benchmarking reports,</P>
                  <P>— Non-patient catering sales reporting and analysis,</P>
                  <P>— Bedside electronic patient meal ordering and delivery.</P>
                  <P>Scope.</P>
                  <P>The overall project objective is to implement an integrated IT solution to support the management of food production and catering services.</P>
                  <P>NHS Boards require a system that will support the tracking and analysis of all aspects of catering production and service for both patient and non-patient catering services.</P>
                  <P>The catering service also requires a system that will allow NHS Boards to develop their own bespoke reports, for example financial management reports, trend analysis, and benchmarking.</P>
                  <P>The system must have the ability to manage individual patient menu choices, the collation of orders into a consolidated list for the production of the food, and split the resulting food order into individual wards for the delivery of the food, then return to individual choices for the serving of the food.</P>
                  <P>To ensure that the NCIS covers all aspects of catering, the system must have the ability to manage and maintain non-patient catering services and sales.</P>
                  <P>The system must either have the ability to provide Nutritional Analysis functionality or integrate with current Nutritional systems.</P>
                  <P>To achieve all of the above the system must be web enabled and have the ability to be used on multiple platforms such as PC and handheld devices, and must work both on and offline.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">1750000</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">48</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>5</NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>Call off contracts from the framework will be for 7 years with the option of annual renewal thereafter.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>ESPD Q.4B.1.1 Bidders will be required to have a minimum “general” yearly turnover of 100 000 GBP for the last 2 years: Please provide annual accounts for the relevant 2 years.</P>
               <P>ESPD Q.4B.5.1 Please provide evidence of insurance levels listed below.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>ESPD Q.4B.1.1 Suppliers must demonstrate the following financial capacity over the last 2 years: Turnover of 100 000 GBP per annum over last 2 financial years.</P>
               <P>Q.4B.5.1. It is a requirement of this contract that bidders hold, or can commit to obtain prior to the commence of any subsequently awarded contract, the types and levels of insurance indicated below:</P>
               <P>Employers Liability Insurance: 5 000 000 GBP,</P>
               <P>Public Liability Insurance: 1 000 000 GBP,</P>
               <P>Professional Indemnity Insurance: 1 000 000 GBP,</P>
               <P>Product Liability Insurance: 1 000 000 GBP.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>4C.1.2 Please provide details of three relevant examples of services carried out during the last three years as specified in the Contract Notice. Weighing 60 % as per scoring model below.</P>
               <P>4.C.2 Bidders will be required to confirm details of the technicians or technical bodies such as ISO or equivalent who they can call upon, especially those responsible for quality control. Weighting 10 % as per scoring model below.</P>
               <P>4.C.6 Professional qualifications held by The service provider or the contractor itself such as the following: ISO27001 or equivalent ITIL qualifications [Helpdesk, etc] or equivalent.</P>
               <P>Other professional qualifications relevant to the services outlined in the Contract.</P>
               <P>Notice. Weighing 20 % as per scoring model below.</P>
               <P>ESPD scoring provided as additional document to this notice.</P>
               <P>4C.8.1 Bidders will be required to confirm their average annual manpower for the last 3 years. Weighing 10 % as per scoring model below.</P>
               <P>Score Meaning.</P>
               <P>0 Unacceptable as determined by: no response or no information provided in response to the question where there is a requirement to provide a response or information and/or a response which demonstrates a significant misunderstanding of the question and/or</P>
               <P>A response which demonstrates no relevant experience in terms of scale, complexity, scope and match to proposed service characteristics and/or</P>
               <P>A response which does not demonstrate capacity and capability (in terms of resources and appropriately qualified and experienced personnel).</P>
               <P>1 Weak as determined by: a response which provides minimum information in response to the question and/or</P>
               <P>A response which demonstrates minimum relevant experience in terms of scale, complexity, scope and match to proposed service characteristics and/or</P>
               <P>A response which fails to satisfactorily answer the question and/or</P>
               <P>A response which demonstrates limited capacity and capability (in terms of resources and appropriately qualified and experienced personnel) to deliver requirement.</P>
               <P>3 Fair as determined by: a response which provides the majority but not all of the information requested; and/or reasonable evidence of relevant experience in terms of scale, complexity, scope and match to proposed service characteristics indicated in the response and/or</P>
               <P>A response which demonstrates reasonable capacity and capability (in terms of resources and appropriately qualified and experience personnel).</P>
               <P>5 Good as determined by: a response which meets all aspects of the question and provides all information requested and/or</P>
               <P>A response which is comprehensive, unambiguous and demonstrates adequate and complete evidence of experience in terms of scale, complexity, scope and match to proposed service characteristics and adequate capacity and capability.</P>
               <P>Scoring Table.</P>
               <P>Criteria Weighting % Score Total Score available.</P>
               <P>4.B Financial Standing (0, 1, 3, 5) Yes/No.</P>
               <P>4C.1.2 References 60 300.</P>
               <P>4.C.2 Quality Control / ISO 10 50.</P>
               <P>4.C.6 Qualifications 20 100.</P>
               <P>4.C.8.1 Staff numbers 10 50.</P>
               <P>4.C.10 Sub-contract Not scored.</P>
               <P>ESPD Scoring table has been added to this notice.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_RESTRICTED/>
            <FRAMEWORK>
               <SINGLE_OPERATOR/>
            </FRAMEWORK>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-04-24</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>2018-05-01</DATE_DISPATCH_INVITATIONS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>ESPD scoring document added as additional document to this notice.</P>
               <P>Note: To register your interest in this notice and obtain any additional information please visit the Public Contracts Scotland Web Site at http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/Search/Search_Switch.aspx?ID=536469</P>
               <P>The buyer has indicated that it will accept electronic responses to this notice via the Postbox facility. A user guide is available at http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/sitehelp/help_guides.aspx</P>
               <P>Suppliers are advised to allow adequate time for uploading documents and to dispatch the electronic response well in advance of the closing time to avoid any last minute problems.</P>
               <P>(SC Ref:536469).</P>
               <P>Download the ESPD document here: http://www.publiccontractsscotland.gov.uk/ESPD/ESPD_Download.aspx?id=536469</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>The Common Services Agency (more commonly known as NHS National Services Scotland) ("NSS")</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Gyle Square (NSS Head Office), 1 South Gyle Crescent</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Edinburgh</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>EH12 9EB</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <URL>http://www.nhsscotlandprocurement.scot.nhs.uk/</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-23</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
