<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="006238-2018" EDITION="2018005"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>17-731181-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180331</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>5</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180109</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 005-006238</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006238-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79400000">Business and management consultancy and related services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20171220</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180331</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="Z">Not specified</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>EC302</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser i forbindelse med opstilling af liste over eksterne eksperter til vurdering af programmer til udryddelse, kontrol og overvågning af dyresygdomme og zoonoser.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Aufruf zur Interessenbekundung für die Erstellung einer Liste externer Experten zur Bewertung von Programmen zur Tilgung, Bekämpfung und Überwachung von Tierseuchen und Zoonosen.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussels</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Call for expression of interest for the setting up of a list of external experts for the assessment of programmes for the eradication, control and surveillance of animal diseases and zoonoses.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés para la elaboración de una lista de expertos externos para la evaluación de programas para la erradicación, el control y el seguimiento de las enfermedades animales y zoonosis.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntö ulkoisten asiantuntijoiden luettelon laatimiseksi eläintautien ja zoonoosien hävittämis-, torjunta- ja seurantaohjelmien arviointia varten</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Belgique</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Appel de manifestation d'intérêt en vue de l'établissement d'une liste d'experts externes pour l'évaluation de programmes d'éradication, de contrôle et de surveillance des maladies animales et des zoonoses.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Βέλγιο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος για την κατάρτιση καταλόγου εξωτερικών εμπειρογνωμόνων για την αξιολόγηση προγραμμάτων καταπολέμησης, ελέγχου και επιτήρησης των ασθενειών των ζώων και των ζωονόσων.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Belgio</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Invito a manifestare interesse per la creazione di un elenco di esperti esterni per la valutazione dei programmi di eradicazione, di lotta e di sorveglianza riguardanti le malattie animali e le zoonosi.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>België</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling voor het opstellen van een lijst van externe deskundigen voor de beoordeling van programma's voor uitroeiing, bestrijding en surveillance van dierenziekten en zoönosen.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Convite à manifestação de interesse para a elaboração de uma lista de peritos externos para a avaliação de programas de vigilância, controlo e erradicação de doenças animais e de zoonoses.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Uppmaning till intresseanmälan för upprättandet av en förteckning över externa experter för bedömning av program för utrotning, bekämpning och övervakning av djursjukdomar och zoonoser.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Belgie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Výzva k vyjádření zájmu ve vztahu k sestavování seznamu externích odborníků pro posouzení programů vymýcení, kontroly a sledování nemocí zvířat a zoonóz.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Huvi väljendamise kutse loomahaiguste ja zoonooside likvideerimise, tõrje ja seire programmide hindamise asutuseväliste ekspertide nimekirja koostamiseks</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüsszel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Szándéknyilatkozati felhívás külső szakértők listájának összeállítására az állatbetegségek és zoonózisok megszüntetésére, megfékezésére és felügyeletére irányuló programok értékelésére vonatkozóan.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Briuselis</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Kvietimas pareikšti susidomėjimą dėl gyvūnų ligų ir zoonozių likvidavimo, kontrolės ir stebėjimo programoms vertinti skirtų išorės ekspertų sąrašo sudarymo.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Beļģija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brisele</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Uzaicinājums paust ieinteresētību par tādu ārējo ekspertu saraksta izveidi, kas veic dzīvnieku slimību un zoonožu izskaušanas, kontroles un uzraudzības programmu novērtēšanu.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Belġju</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussell</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess għat-twaqqif ta' lista ta' esperti esterni għall-valutazzjoni ta' programmi għall-qerda, il-kontroll u s-sorveljanza tal-mard tal-annimali u ż-żoonosi.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruksela</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Zaproszenie do wyrażenia zainteresowania w celu utworzenia listy ekspertów zewnętrznych na potrzeby oceny programów zwalczania i eliminowania chorób zwierząt i chorób odzwierzęcych oraz nadzoru nad tymi chorobami.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Belgicko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Výzva na vyjadrenie záujmu o zostavenie zoznamu externých odborníkov na hodnotenie programov pre vyhubenie, kontrolu a sledovanie zvieracích chorôb a zoonóz.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselj</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Poziv k prijavi interesa za vzpostavitev seznama zunanjih strokovnjakov za vrednotenje programov za izkoreninjenje, nadzor in spremljanje živalskih bolezni in zoonoz.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Bheilg, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Glao ar léiriú spéise chun liosta saineolaithe seachtracha a bhunú le haghaidh cláir a mheasúnú do dhíothú, rialú agus faireachas na ngalar ainmhithe agus zónóisí.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бeлгия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Брюксел</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Покана за изразяване на интерес за създаване на списък с външни експерти за оценяване на програмите за премахване, контрол и наблюдение на болести по животните и зоонози.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Cerere de scrisori de interes în vederea întocmirii unei liste de experți externi pentru evaluarea de programe de eradicare, control și supraveghere a bolilor animalelor și a zoonozelor.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Poziv na iskazivanje interesa za sastavljanje popisa vanjskih stručnjaka za ocjenjivanje programa iskorjenjivanja, kontrole i nadzora bolesti životinja i zoonoza.</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Europa-Kommissionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Kommission</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Commission</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">Comisión Europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan komissio</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Commission européenne</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Commissione europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europese Commissie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">Comissão Europeia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska kommissionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská komise</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Komisjon</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Európai Bizottság</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos Komisija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Komisija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">Il-Kummissjoni Ewropea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Komisja Europejska</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európska komisia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska komisija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An Coimisiún Eorpach</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейска комисия</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Comisia Europeană</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska komisija</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser i forbindelse med opstilling af liste over eksterne eksperter til vurdering af programmer til udryddelse, kontrol og overvågning af dyresygdomme og zoonoser.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europa-Kommissionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food Safety Programme, Emergency Funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Denne bekendtgørelse er en indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fysiske personer, der ønsker at ansøge, bedes gøre dette i henhold til bestemmelserne i denne indkaldelse.</P><P>Denne indkaldelse skal gøre det muligt for Kommissionens tjenestegrene, efter gennemgang af de indsendte ansøgninger, at opstille en liste over eksperter, der kan tildeles en kontrakt på de områder, der er beskrevet i punkt C.</P><P>Hver gang en vurderingsaktivitet med relation til en af de nedenfor anførte sygdomme skal udføres, vil den ordregivende myndighed udvælge enten alle ansøgere på listen eller nogle af dem på grundlag af objektive og ikke-diskriminatoriske udvælgelseskriterier for den konkrete vurdering.</P><P>Optagelse på listen forpligter ikke på nogen måde Europa-Kommissionen retligt til at tildele en kontrakt.</P><P>For hver af de nævnte sygdomme vil en liste over eksperter blive opstillet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udtømmende beskrivelse af områder omfattet af denne indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Artikel 9 i Europa-Parlamentet og Rådets (1) forordning (EU) nr. 652/2014 fastlægger unionens finansielle bidrag til gennemførelsen af nationale programmer til udryddelse, kontrol og overvågning af visse dyresygdomme og zoonoser.</P><P>Kommissionen vil vurdere disse programmer, indgivet af medlemsstaterne hvert år, ud fra veterinære og finansielle hensyn.</P><P>Med henblik på at stille et yderligere værktøj til rådighed til vurdering af programmerne søger Kommissionen ekstern, teknisk bistand til at udføre en forhåndsvurdering af programmerne indgivet af medlemsstaterne for 2019.</P><P>Der efterspørges ekstern bistand til evalueringen af programmer med relation til følgende sygdomme:</P><P>Afrikansk svinepest</P><P>Fugleinfluenza</P><P>Bluetongue</P><P>Kvægbrucellose</P><P>Kvægtuberkulose</P><P>Klassisk svinepest</P><P>Lumpy skin disease</P><P>Fåre- og gedebrucellose</P><P>Rabies</P><P>Salmonellose (zoonotisk salmonella)</P><P>Fåre- og gedepest</P><P>Fåre- og gedekopper</P><P>Overførbare spongiforme encephalopatier</P><P>Ansøgere skal tydeligt angive den sygdom, de specialiserer sig i. Jf. punkt F i udvælgelseskriterierne.</P><P>Kontrakter underskrevet i forbindelse med denne indkaldelse af ansøgninger vil være standardkontrakter og vil blive indgået til en dagssats på 450 EUR (fire hundrede og halvtreds euro). Rejseudgifter, opholdsudgifter og andre omkostninger vil blive refunderet i henhold til Kommissionens standardregler (2). Som hovedregel vil kontrakterne ikke overstige 30 dage/år i alt.</P><P>Dagsatsen på 450 EUR kan blive genstand for årlige eller halvårlige gennemgange.</P><P>(1) Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 652/2014 af 15.5.2014 om bestemmelser vedrørende forvaltning af udgifter i tilknytning til fødevarekæden, dyresundhed og dyrevelfærd samt til plantesundhed og planteformeringsmateriale, om ændring af Rådets direktiv 98/56/EF, 2000/29/EF og 2008/90/EF, Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EF) nr. 178/2002, (EF) nr. 882/2004 og (EF) nr. 396/2005, direktiv 2009/128/EF og Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EF) nr. 1107/2009 og om ophævelse af Rådets afgørelse 66/399/EØF, 76/894/EØF og 2009/470/EF. EUT L 189, 27.6.2014, s. 11.</P><P>(2) Kommissionens afgørelse af 5.12.2007 (DOC C(2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udførelsessted</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Udførelsesstedet vil være en ekstern lokalitet (f.eks. ekspertens faste eller officielle adresse) og Europa-Kommissionens kontorer.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udelukkelseskriterium</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>For at blive optaget på listen skal ansøgere udfylde de i formularen indeholdte erklæringer til indsendelse af ansøgninger.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udvælgelseskriterier</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>For at blive optaget på listen skal ansøgere have:</P><P>— en grad i veterinærmedicin</P><P>— meget godt kendskab til mundtligt og skriftligt engelsk</P><P>— grundlæggende it-viden</P><P>— mindst 5 års erfaring i</P><P>—— enten faglige færdigheder og erfaring inden for forvaltning og gennemførelse af udryddelses-, kontrol- og overvågningsprogrammer for mindst en af ovennævnte sygdomme, eller</P><P>—— faglig erfaring inden for epidemiologi i forbindelse med mindst 1 af dyresygdommene angivet ovenfor.</P><P>Videnskabelige publikationer vedrørende de ovennævnte sygdomme og gode sprogkundskaber ud over engelsk vil blive betragtet som en fordel.</P><P>Før underskrivelsen af kontrakten vil de udvalgte ansøgere blive bedt om at undertegne en erklæring om, at de ikke befinder sig i nogen interessekonflikt i forbindelse med den pågældende evaluering, og at de uden forsinkelse vil underrette Kommissionen, hvis der opstår en sådan interessekonflikt i løbet af evalueringsperioden. Der opstår en interessekonflikt, i tilfælde hvor den upartiske og objektive udførelse af en evaluators funktioner bringes i fare af grunde, der involverer familie, følelsesliv, politisk eller nationalt tilhørsforhold, økonomiske interesser eller enhver anden interesse, vedkommende måtte have i henseende til de pågældende programmer. I løbet af evalueringsprocessen skal evaluatorerne udvise en passende pligtopfyldenhed samt respektere fortroligheden af de oplysninger og dokumenter, de får kendskab til i løbet af processen.</P><P>Ansøgere kan blive anmodet om at fremlægge understøttende dokumenter (dvs. kopi af bevis for universitetsgrad og attester på arbejdserfaring). Manglende indgivelse heraf vil medføre, at ansøgningen bliver afvist.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oplysninger om ansøgningsskemaet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Skemaet, der skal udfyldes, findes på følgende internetadresse:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Denne formular bør gemmes på harddisken, udfyldes og indsendes, ved at man trykker på den pågældende knap.</P><P>Ved problemer med downloadning af skemaet (manglende softwarekompatibilitet mv.) bedes De sende en e-mail til sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Systemet vil ikke tillade indsendelse af en ufuldstændig indgivelse.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Andre oplysninger</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Listen over valgte eksperter vil være gyldig i 1 år at regne fra datoen for offentliggørelse af indkaldelsen af interessetilkendegivelser i EU-Tidende.</P><P>Enhver interesseret person kan indgive en ansøgning på ethvert tidspunkt i løbet af listens gyldighedsperiode, undtagen de sidste 3 måneder af denne periode.</P><P>Ansøgere kan trække deres ansøgning tilbage på ethvert tidspunkt i løbet af listens gyldighedsperiode ved skriftlig meddelelse herom til den ordregivende myndighed.</P><P>Alle ansøgere vil få oplyst, hvorvidt de er optaget på listen.</P><P>I forbindelse med evaluering af programmer for et givet år N skal de påtænkte opgaver udføres fra den anden halvdel af juni til den første halvdel af juli i år N-1. Eksperterne skal være disponible i mindst 2 uger i løbet af denne periode til at udføre evalueringen, og de skal kunne deltage i et møde hos Generaldirektoratet for Sundhed og Fødevaresikkerhed i Bruxelles (eksperter, der er involveret i flere sygdomme, skal påregne mere end 1 dag i Bruxelles).</P><P>I forbindelse med evalueringen af programmer for 2019 vil kun ansøgninger indgivet pr. 31.3.2018 blive taget i betragtning.</P><P>Allerede valgte ansøgere må ikke genindgive en ansøgning.</P><P>Europa-Kommissionen vil sikre, at evalueringspanelerne, som oprettes på grundlag af listen over eksperter fra denne indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser, bliver sammensat på en balanceret måde, og at der er behørig ekspertrotation. Ansøgeres geografiske oprindelse og faglige baggrund vil blive taget i betragtning. Europa-Kommissionen lægger også vægt på en ligelig fordeling af mænd og kvinder.</P><P>Opfølgningen på svaret på indkaldelsen af interessetilkendegivelser vil kræve registrering og behandling af personlige data (såsom navne- og adresseoplysninger og cv). Sådanne data vil blive behandlet i overensstemmelse med kravene i forordning (EF) 45/2001 om beskyttelse af fysiske personer i forbindelse med behandling af personoplysninger i fællesskabsinstitutionerne og -organerne og om fri udveksling af sådanne oplysninger. Hvis ikke andet er angivet, er svar på spørgsmål og de anmodede personlige data nødvendige for vurderingen af ansøgningen og vil kun blive behandlet af Generaldirektoratet for Sundhed og Fødevaresikkerhed, afdeling D4. De kan, efter anmodning, få oplyst videregivelsen af Deres personoplysninger og korrigere unøjagtige eller ufuldstændige personoplysninger deri. Har De spørgsmål vedrørende behandlingen af Deres personoplysninger, bedes De henvende dem til Generaldirektoratet for Sundhed og Fødevaresikkerhed, afdeling D4, på følgende adresse: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu I forbindelse med behandlingen af Deres personoplysninger har De på et hvilket som helst tidspunkt ret til at henvende Dem til Den Europæiske Tilsynsførende for Databeskyttelse på følgende e-mailadresse: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Den ordregivende myndighed vil på sit websted periodisk offentliggøre listen over eksperter, der har indgået kontrakt med Europa-Kommissionen.</P><P>Alle anmodninger om yderligere oplysninger bedes sendt til: sante-ami-prog-d4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dato for afsendelse af bekendtgørelsen fra Generaldirektoratet for Sundhed og Fødevaresikkerhed:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dato for modtagelse af bekendtgørelsen i Publikationskontoret:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: Aufruf zur Interessenbekundung für die Erstellung einer Liste externer Experten zur Bewertung von Programmen zur Tilgung, Bekämpfung und Überwachung von Tierseuchen und Zoonosen.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Auftraggeber:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Kommission</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, E-Mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Diese Bekanntmachung ist ein Aufruf zur Abgabe von Interessenbekundungen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Natürliche Personen, die sich bewerben möchten, werden aufgefordert, dies in Übereinstimmung mit den Bestimmungen der vorliegenden Bekanntmachung zu tun.</P><P>Dieser Aufruf soll es den Dienststellen der Kommission nach Prüfung der eingereichten Bewerbungen ermöglichen, eine Liste von Experten zu erstellen, die für die Vergabe eines Auftrags in den unter Buchstabe C beschriebenen Bereichen infrage kommen könnten.</P><P>Jedes Mal, wenn eine Bewertungstätigkeit im Zusammenhang mit einer der unten angegebenen Krankheiten ausgeführt werden muss, wird der öffentliche Auftraggeber entweder alle Bewerber auf der Liste oder nur einige von ihnen gemäß objektiven und nicht diskriminierenden Auswahlkriterien, die für die betreffende Bewertung spezifisch sind, einladen.</P><P>Eine Aufnahme in diese Liste stellt keine rechtliche Verpflichtung seitens der Europäischen Kommission dar, einen Auftrag zu vergeben.</P><P>Für jede der aufgeführten Krankheiten wird eine Liste von Experten erstellt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Detaillierte Beschreibung der von dem Aufruf zur Interessenbekundung abgedeckten Bereiche</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Der Artikel 9 der Verordnung (EU) Nr. 652/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates (1) enthält Bestimmungen für den finanziellen Beitrag der Union zur Umsetzung von nationalen Programmen zur Tilgung, Bekämpfung und Überwachung von Tierseuchen und Zoonosen.</P><P>Die Kommission bewertet die von den Mitgliedstaaten jährlich vorgelegten Programme unter veterinärrechtlichen und finanziellen Gesichtspunkten.</P><P>Um ein zusätzliches Instrument für die Bewertung der Programme bereitzustellen, sucht die Kommission nach externer technischer Hilfe zur Durchführung einer Vorbewertung der von den Mitgliedstaaten eingereichten Programme für 2019.</P><P>Es wird externe Unterstützung bei der Bewertung der Programme im Zusammenhang mit folgenden Krankheiten benötigt:</P><P>Afrikanische Schweinepest,</P><P>Aviäre Influenza (Vogelgrippe),</P><P>Blauzungenerkrankung,</P><P>Rinderbrucellose,</P><P>Rindertuberkulose,</P><P>Klassische Schweinepest,</P><P>Hautknotenkrankheit,</P><P>Schaf- und Ziegenbrucellose,</P><P>Tollwut,</P><P>Salmonellose (zoonotische Salmonellenerkrankungen),</P><P>Pest der kleinen Wiederkäuer,</P><P>Schaf- und Ziegenpocken,</P><P>Transmissible Spongiforme Enzephalopathien (TSE),</P><P>Die Bewerber müssen die Krankheit, auf die sie spezialisiert sind, eindeutig angeben. Die Auswahlkriterien sind Abschnitt F zu entnehmen.</P><P>Bei den im Rahmen dieses Aufrufs zur Abgabe von Bewerbungen unterzeichneten Verträgen wird es sich um Standardaufgabenverträge zu einem Tagessatz von 450 EUR (vierhundertfünfzig Euro) handeln. Reise-, Aufenthalts- und andere Kosten werden gemäß der standardmäßigen Regelung der Kommission erstattet (2). Die Verträge werden üblicherweise insgesamt 30 Tage/Jahr nicht übersteigen.</P><P>Der Tagessatz von 450 EUR kann jährlich oder alle 2 Jahre überprüft werden.</P><P>(1) Verordnung (EU) Nr. 652/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 15.5.2014 (Verordnung (EU) mit Bestimmungen für die Verwaltung der Ausgaben in den Bereichen Lebensmittelkette, Tiergesundheit und Tierschutz sowie Pflanzengesundheit und Pflanzenvermehrungsmaterial, zur Änderung der Richtlinien des Rates 98/56/EG, 2000/29/EG und 2008/90/EG, der Verordnungen (EG) Nr. 178/2002, (EG) Nr. 882/2004 und (EG) Nr. 396/2005 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates, der Richtlinie 2009/128/EG des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates sowie der Verordnung (EG) Nr. 1107/2009 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates und zur Aufhebung der Entscheidungen des Rates 66/399/EWG, 76/894/EWG und 2009/470/EG. ABl. L 189 vom 27.6.2014, S. 11.</P><P>(2) Beschluss der Kommission vom 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Erfüllungsort</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Die Arbeiten sind in den Räumlichkeiten der Europäischen Kommission und auswärts (z. B. am festen oder offiziellen Sitz des Experten) auszuführen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ausschlusskriterium</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Um in die Liste aufgenommen zu werden, müssen die Bewerber die für die Angebotsabgabe erforderlichen Erklärungen machen, die Bestandteil des Formulars sind.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Auswahlkriterien</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Um in die Liste aufgenommen zu werden, müssen die Bewerber Folgendes vorweisen können:</P><P>— einen Abschluss in Veterinärmedizin,</P><P>— sehr gute Englischkenntnisse in Wort und Schrift,</P><P>— EDV-Grundkenntnisse,</P><P>— mindestens 5 Jahre an</P><P>—— entweder Berufserfahrung und berufliche Befähigung in der Verwaltung und Umsetzung von Programmen zur Tilgung, Bekämpfung und Überwachung mindestens einer der oben aufgelisteten Krankheiten oder</P><P>—— Berufserfahrung im Bereich Epidemiologie in Verbindung mit mindestens einer der oben aufgeführten Tierseuchen.</P><P>Wissenschaftliche Veröffentlichungen in Verbindung mit den oben genannten Krankheiten und gute Kenntnisse in anderen Sprachen als Englisch würde einen Vorteil darstellen.</P><P>Vor der Unterzeichnung des Vertrags müssen die ausgewählten Bewerber eine Erklärung unterzeichnen, in der sie bestätigen, dass sie sich im Hinblick auf die betreffende Bewertung in keinem Interessenkonflikt befinden und dass sie die Kommission umgehend darüber benachrichtigen, wenn ein solcher Konflikt im Laufe der Bewertung entstehen sollte. Ein Interessenkonflikt besteht dann, wenn die unparteiische und objektive Ausübung der Funktionen des Bewerters aus Gründen, die seine Familie, sein Gefühlsleben, seine politische oder nationale Affinität oder wirtschaftliche Interessen bzw. gemeinsames Interesse mit den vorgelegten Programmen betreffen, beeinträchtigt ist. Während des gesamten Bewertungsverfahrens müssen die Bewerter ein angemessenes Pflichtbewusstsein an den Tag legen und die Geheimhaltung hinsichtlich der Informationen und Unterlagen wahren, die ihnen im Laufe des Bewertungsverfahrens vorgelegt werden bzw. in die sie Einsicht erhalten.</P><P>Die Bewerber können aufgefordert werden, Nachweise vorzulegen (d. h. Kopie des Hochschulabschlusses und Bescheinigungen über die Berufserfahrung). Werden Nachweise nicht vorgelegt, führt dies zur Ablehnung der Bewerbung.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informationen bezüglich des Bewerbungsformulars</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Das auszufüllende Formular ist auf der folgenden Website erhältlich:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Dieses Formular wird auf der Festplatte gespeichert, ausgefüllt und anschließend über einen Mausklick auf die entsprechende Taste gesendet.</P><P>Falls Probleme beim Herunterladen des Formulars (aufgrund der Inkompatibilität der Software usw.) auftreten, ist eine E-Mail an sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu zu senden.</P><P>Dieses System ermöglicht nur den Versand komplett ausgefüllter Formulare.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sonstige Informationen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Die Liste der ausgewählten Experten hat eine Gültigkeitsdauer von 1 Jahr ab dem Tag der Veröffentlichung des Aufrufs zur Interessenbekundung im Amtsblatt.</P><P>Interessierte Parteien können zu jedem Zeitpunkt der Gültigkeit dieser Liste eine Bewerbung einreichen, mit Ausnahme der letzten drei Monate des Gültigkeitszeitraums.</P><P>Die Bewerber können ihre Bewerbung während des Gültigkeitszeitraums der Liste jederzeit durch schriftliche Mitteilung an den öffentlichen Auftraggeber widerrufen.</P><P>Alle Bewerber werden darüber informiert, ob sie in die Liste aufgenommen wurden oder nicht.</P><P>Für die Bewertung der Programme für ein bestimmtes Jahr N müssen die geplanten Arbeiten im Zeitraum zwischen der zweiten Junihälfte und Ende Juli des Jahres N-1 ausgeführt werden. Die Experten müssen während dieses Zeitraums mindestens zwei Wochen lang verfügbar sein, um die Bewertung auszuführen. Sie müssen für die Teilnahme an einer Besprechung mit der GD GESUNDHEIT in Brüssel zur Verfügung stehen (Experten, die in Bezug auf mehrere Krankheiten tätig sind, müssen mehr als einen Tag in Brüssel einplanen).</P><P>Für die Bewertung von Programmen für 2019 werden nur Bewerbungen berücksichtigt, die bis zum 31.3.2018 eingereicht werden.</P><P>Ausgewählte Bewerber dürfen eine Bewerbung nicht erneut einreichen.</P><P>Die Europäische Kommission wird sicherstellen, dass es bei den Bewertungsgremien, die auf der Grundlage der aus dem vorliegenden Aufruf zur Abgabe von Interessenbekundungen resultierenden Liste von Experten gebildet werden, zu einer ausgewogenen Zusammensetzung sowie zu einer angemessenen Rotation der Experten kommt. Es werden Herkunft und Werdegang der Bewerber berücksichtigt. Die Europäische Kommission ist auch an einer ausgewogenen Teilnahme von Frauen und Männern interessiert.</P><P>Die Bearbeitung der Interessenbekundungen im Zusammenhang mit dem Aufruf zur Interessenbekundung erfordert die Erfassung und weitere Verarbeitung persönlicher Daten (z. B. Name, Adresse und Lebenslauf). Diese Daten werden gemäß den Vorgaben der Verordnung (EG) Nr. 45/2001 zum Schutz natürlicher Personen bei der Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten durch die Organe und Einrichtungen der Gemeinschaft und zum freien Datenverkehr verarbeitet. Soweit nicht anders angegeben, werden die Antworten auf Fragen und die abgefragten persönlichen Daten für die Bewertung der Bewerbung benötigt. Sie werden ausschließlich vom Referat GESUNDHEIT/D4 verwaltet. Auf Anforderung werden den betreffenden Personen ihre persönlichen Daten übermittelt und sie werden, falls diese ungenau oder unvollständig sein sollten, berichtigt. Fragen zur Verarbeitung persönlicher Daten sind an das Referat GESUNDHEIT/D4 unter folgender Adresse zu richten: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu. Was die Verarbeitung der persönlichen Daten anbelangt, sind die betreffenden Personen jederzeit berechtigt, sich an den Europäischen Datenschutzbeauftragten unter der folgenden Adresse zu wenden: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Der öffentliche Auftraggeber wird auf seiner Website regelmäßig die Liste der Experten veröffentlichen, die mit der Europäischen Kommission einen Vertrag unterzeichnet haben.</P><P>Sämtliche Anfragen betreffend weiterführende Informationen sind an folgende Adresse zu richten: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tag der Absendung der Bekanntmachung durch GD GESUNDHEIT:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum des Eingangs der Bekanntmachung bei OPOCE:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussels: Call for expression of interest for the setting up of a list of external experts for the assessment of programmes for the eradication, control and surveillance of animal diseases and zoonoses.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Awarding authority:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Commission</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussels</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium Fax: </BLK_BTX><FAX>+32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>This notice is a call for expression of interest</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Natural persons who wish to apply are invited to do so in compliance with the provisions of this notice.</P><P>This call should allow the services of the commission, after examination of the applications submitted, to set up a list of experts who could be awarded a contract in the fields described in point C.</P><P>Each time that an assessment activity relating to one of the diseases mentioned below has to be carried out, the awarding authority will invite either all candidates entered on the list, or only some of them, on the basis of objective and non discriminatory selection criteria specific to the concrete assessment.</P><P>Inclusion on the list does not constitute any legal commitment on the part of the European Commission to award a contract.</P><P>For each of the mentioned diseases, a list of experts will be set up.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Exhaustive description of the matters covered by the call for expression of interest</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Article 9 of Regulation (EU) Nº 652/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council (1) provides for Union financial contribution for the implementation of national programmes for the eradication, control and surveillance of certain animal diseases and zoonoses.</P><P>The Commission shall assess those programmes, submitted by the member states each year, from the veterinary and the financial angles.</P><P>In order to provide an additional tool for the assessment of the programmes, the Commission is looking for external, technical assistance to carry out a pre-assessment of the programmes submitted by member states for 2019.</P><P>We are looking for external assistance for the evaluation of the programmes related to the following diseases:</P><P>African swine fever,</P><P>Avian influenza,</P><P>Bluetongue,</P><P>Bovine brucellosis,</P><P>Bovine tuberculosis,</P><P>Classical swine fever,</P><P>Lumpy skin disease,</P><P>Ovine and caprine brucellosis,</P><P>Rabies,</P><P>Salmonellosis (zoonotic salmonella),</P><P>Sheep and goat plague,</P><P>Sheep and goat pox,</P><P>Transmissible spongiform encephalopathies (TSE),</P><P>Applicants should indicate clearly the disease in which they specialise. See point F for the selection criteria.</P><P>Contracts signed under this call for applications will be standard task contracts concluded with a daily rate of 450 EUR (four hundred and fifty Euro). Travel, subsistence and other costs will be reimbursed according to standard Commission rules (2). Contracts will, as a general rule, not cumulatively exceed 30 days per year.</P><P>The daily rate of 450 EUR may be subject to annual or biannual revision.</P><P>(1) Regulation (EU) Nº 652/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 15.5.2014 laying down provisions for the management of expenditure relating to the food chain, animal health and animal welfare, and relating to plant health and plant reproductive material, amending Council Directives 98/56/EC, 2000/29/EC and 2008/90/EC, Regulations (EC) Nº 178/2002, (EC) Nº 882/2004 and (EC) Nº 396/2005 of the European Parliament and of the Council, Directive 2009/128/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council and Regulation (EC) Nº 1107/2009 of the European Parliament and of the Council and repealing Council Decisions 66/399/EEC, 76/894/EEC and 2009/470/EC. OJ L 189, 27.6.2014, p. 11.</P><P>(2) Commission Decision of 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Place of work</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The place of work will be a remote place (e.g. the expert's permanent or official address), and the offices of the European Commission.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Exclusion criterion</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>In order to be included in the list, applicants must fill in the application submission statements that they will find in the form.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Selection criteria</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>In order to be included in the list, applicants will have:</P><P>— a degree in veterinary medicine,</P><P>— very good spoken and written English,</P><P>— basic informatics knowledge,</P><P>— a minimum of five years of,</P><P>—— either professional skills and experience in the management and implementation of programmes for the eradication, control and surveillance for at least one of the diseases listed above; or,</P><P>—— professional experience in epidemiology related to at least one of the animal diseases listed above.</P><P>Scientific publications related to the above-mentioned diseases and good language skills other than in English would constitute an advantage.</P><P>Before signing the contract, the selected candidates will have to sign a declaration certifying that they have no conflict of interest for the evaluation concerned and that they will without delay inform the Commission if such conflict of interest should emerge during the course of the evaluation. There is a conflict of interest where the impartial and objective exercise of the functions of an evaluator is compromised for reasons involving family, emotional life, political or national affinity, economic interest or any other shared interest with the submitted programmes. Throughout the evaluation process, the evaluators must demonstrate appropriate devotion to duty and observe the confidentiality of the information and documents brought to their attention during the process.</P><P>The candidates may be requested to present supporting documents (i.e. copy of university degree and certificates of working experience). The unavailability of those will result in the rejection of the application.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Information concerning the application form</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The form to be completed can be found at the following web address:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>This form should be saved to the hard drive, completed and sent by clicking on the corresponding button.</P><P>In case of problems with downloading the form (because of software incompatibility etc.), please send an e-mail to sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>The system will not allow to send a submission that is incomplete.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Other information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The list of the selected experts will be valid for 1 year from the date of publication of the call for expression of interest in the Official Journal.</P><P>Any interested person may submit an application at any time during the period of validity of the list with the exception of the last three months of that period.</P><P>Candidates may withdraw their application at any moment during the period of validity of the list by written notice to the awarding authority.</P><P>All applicants will be informed whether or not they are included in the list.</P><P>For the evaluation of the programmes of a given year N, the work envisaged is to be done between the second half of June and the end of July of year N-1. The experts should be available for a minimum of at least two weeks during this period to carry out the evaluation and should be available to attend a meeting in DG SANTE in Brussels (experts involved in several diseases must calculate more than one day in Brussels).</P><P>For the evaluation of 2019 programmes, only applications submitted by 31.3.2018 will be considered.</P><P>Once selected, the candidates must not resubmit an application.</P><P>The European Commission will ensure that the evaluation panels set up on the basis of the list of experts from this call for expression of interest are established in a balanced way and there is appropriate rotation of experts. Applicants' geographical origin as well as professional background will be taken into account. The European Commission also seeks the balanced participation of men and women.</P><P>The follow-up of your response to the call for expression of interest will require the recording and further processing of personal data (such as your name, address and CV). This data will be processed in accordance with the requirements of Regulation (EC) 45/2001 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data by the Community institutions and bodies and on the free movement of such data. Except if mentioned otherwise, replies to questions and personal data requested are necessary for the purpose of assessing your application and will only be managed by Unit SANTE/D4. You may, upon request, obtain the communication of your personal data and rectify any inaccurate or incomplete personal data. Should you have any queries concerning the processing of your personal data, please address them to Unit SANTE/D4 at the following address: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu As regards the processing of your personal data, you have a right to recourse at any time to the European data protection Supervisor at following email address: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>The awarding authority will publish periodically in its web site the list of experts who have signed a contract with the European Commission.</P><P>All requests for additional information may be sent to: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date of dispatch of the notice by DG SANTE:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date of receipt of the notice by the OPOCE:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselas: Convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés para la elaboración de una lista de expertos externos para la evaluación de programas para la erradicación, el control y el seguimiento de las enfermedades animales y zoonosis.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de contratación:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Comisión Europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Correo electrónico: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>El presente anuncio es una convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Las personas físicas que deseen participar en la licitación están invitadas a hacerlo en conformidad con las disposiciones del presente anuncio.</P><P>La presente convocatoria permitirá a los servicios de la Comisión, tras el examen de las candidaturas presentadas, establecer una lista de expertos que pueden ser adjudicatarios de un contrato en los ámbitos descritos en la letra C.</P><P>Cada vez que se necesite realizar una actividad de evaluación relacionada con alguna de las enfermedades mencionadas a continuación, el poder adjudicador invitará a todos los candidatos incluidos en la lista o solo a algunos de ellos, basándose en los criterios de selección objetivos y no discriminatorios específicos de la evaluación en cuestión.</P><P>La inclusión en la lista no constituye ningún compromiso jurídico por parte de la Comisión Europea de adjudicar un contrato.</P><P>Se establecerá una lista de expertos por cada una de las susodichas enfermedades.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción detallada de los ámbitos que comprende la convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El artículo 9 del Reglamento (UE) n.º 652/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo (1) prevé una contribución financiera de la Unión Europea para la ejecución de programas nacionales para la erradicación, el control y el seguimiento de determinadas enfermedades animales y zoonosis.</P><P>La Comisión evaluará estos programas, presentados cada año por los Estados miembros, desde el punto de vista veterinario y financiero.</P><P>Con el fin de proporcionar una herramienta complementaria para la evaluación de los programas, la Comisión está buscando asistencia técnica externa para la realización de una evaluación previa de los programas presentados por los Estados miembros para 2019.</P><P>Estamos buscando asistencia externa para la evaluación de los programas relacionados con las siguientes enfermedades:</P><P>peste porcina africana,</P><P>gripe aviar,</P><P>lengua azul,</P><P>brucelosis bovina,</P><P>tuberculosis bovina,</P><P>peste porcina clásica,</P><P>dermatosis nodular contagiosa,</P><P>brucelosis ovina y caprina,</P><P>rabia,</P><P>salmonelosis (salmonela zoonótica),</P><P>peste de los pequeños rumiantes,</P><P>viruela ovina y caprina,</P><P>encefalopatías espongiformes transmisibles (EET).</P><P>Los candidatos deberán indicar claramente la enfermedad en la que están especializados. Véase la letra F para los criterios de selección.</P><P>Los contratos firmados en el marco de la presente convocatoria de presentación de solicitudes serán contratos de tareas estándar con una tasa diaria de 450 EUR (cuatrocientos cincuenta euros). Los viajes, dietas y otros gastos se reembolsarán en conformidad con las normas estándar de la Comisión (2). Como regla general, los contratos no superarán, acumulativamente, los 30 días al año.</P><P>La tasa diaria de 450 EUR puede estar sujeta a revisión anual o bianual.</P><P>(1) El Reglamento (UE) n.º 652/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 15.5.2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, por el que se establecen disposiciones para la gestión de los gastos relativos a la cadena alimentaria, la salud animal y el bienestar de los animales, y relativos a la fitosanidad y a los materiales de reproducción vegetal, y por el que se modifican las Directivas 98/56/CE, 2000/29/CE y 2008/90/CE del Consejo; los Reglamentos (CE) n.º 178/2002, (CE) n.º 882/2004 y (CE) n.º 396/2005 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo; la Directiva 2009/128/CE del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, y el Reglamento (CE) n.º 1107/2009 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, y por el que se derogan las Decisiones 66/399/CEE, 76/894/CEE y 2009/470/CE del Consejo. DO L 189 de 27.6.2014, p. 11.</P><P>(2) Decisión de la Comisión de 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lugar de trabajo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El lugar de trabajo podrá ser tanto un lugar a distancia (por ejemplo, la dirección permanente u oficial del experto), como las oficinas de la Comisión Europea.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criterio de exclusión</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Con el fin de ser incluidos en la lista, los solicitantes deberán completar las declaraciones de envío de solicitudes incluidas en el formulario.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criterios de selección</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Con el fin de ser incluidos en la lista, los solicitantes poseerán:</P><P>— un título universitario en medicina veterinaria,</P><P>— excelente dominio oral y escrito del inglés,</P><P>— conocimientos informáticos básicos,</P><P>— un mínimo de cinco años de:</P><P>—— experiencia y competencias profesionales en la gestión e implementación de programas de erradicación, control y seguimiento de, al menos, una de las enfermedades indicadas anteriormente, o</P><P>—— experiencia profesional en epidemiología, relacionada con al menos una de las enfermedades animales enumeradas anteriormente.</P><P>Se valorarán positivamente las publicaciones científicas relacionadas con las enfermedades mencionadas y las buenas competencias lingüísticas en otro idioma distinto al inglés.</P><P>Antes de la firma del contrato, los candidatos seleccionados deberán firmar una declaración que certifique que no se encuentran en ningún conflicto de intereses para la evaluación en cuestión y que informarán a la Comisión, sin demora, en caso de que se produjera tal conflicto de intereses durante el curso de la evaluación. Existirá un conflicto de intereses si el ejercicio imparcial y objetivo de las funciones de un evaluador se ve comprometido por razones familiares, sentimentales, de afinidad política o nacional, por intereses económicos o por cualquier otro interés compartido con los programas presentados. Durante el proceso de evaluación, los evaluadores deberán demostrar un adecuado rigor deontológico adecuado y respetar la confidencialidad de la información y de la documentación que hayan recibido durante el proceso.</P><P>Podrá solicitarse a los candidatos que presenten documentos justificativos (es decir, copia del título universitario y certificados de la experiencia laboral). La no presentación de los mismos dará lugar al rechazo de la solicitud.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información relativa al formulario de candidatura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El formulario que se deberá cumplimentar se encuentra en la siguiente dirección de Internet:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Deberán guardar el formulario en el disco duro, rellenarlo y enviarlo haciendo clic en el botón correspondiente.</P><P>En caso de problemas al descargar el formulario (por incompatibilidad del «software», etc.), se ruega a los candidatos que envíen un correo electrónico a sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>El sistema no permite enviar una presentación incompleta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información complementaria</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>La lista de expertos seleccionados será válida durante 1 año desde la fecha de publicación de la convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés en el Diario Oficial.</P><P>Todas las personas interesadas podrán presentar una candidatura en cualquier momento durante el período de validez de la lista, a excepción de los tres últimos meses de dicho período.</P><P>Los candidatos pueden retirar su candidatura en cualquier momento durante el período de validez de la lista, mediante un anuncio por escrito al poder adjudicador.</P><P>Se informará a todos los candidatos de su inclusión o no en la lista.</P><P>Para la evaluación de los programas de un determinado año N, el trabajo previsto se realizará entre la segunda mitad de junio y finales de julio del año N-1. Los expertos deberán estar disponibles durante un mínimo de dos semanas durante dicho período para llevar a cabo la evaluación, y deberán estar disponibles para asistir a una reunión en la DG SANTE en Bruselas (los expertos que participan en varias enfermedades deben calcular más de un día en Bruselas).</P><P>Para la evaluación de los programas de 2019 solo se tendrán en cuenta las solicitudes presentadas hasta el 31.3.2018.</P><P>Una vez hayan sido seleccionados, los candidatos no deberán volver a presentar una candidatura.</P><P>La Comisión Europea se asegurará de que los comités de evaluación, establecidos basándose en la lista de expertos que resulte de la presente convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés, se hayan creado de manera equitativa y de que exista una apropiada rotación de expertos. Se tendrá en cuenta el origen geográfico de los solicitantes, así como la experiencia profesional. La Comisión Europea también busca la participación equitativa de hombres y mujeres.</P><P>El tratamiento de su respuesta a la convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés requerirá el registro y posterior procesamiento de datos personales (tales como su nombre, dirección y curriculum vitae). Estos datos serán procesados de acuerdo con los requisitos del Reglamento (CE) n.º 45/2001 relativo a la protección de las personas físicas en lo que respecta al tratamiento de datos personales por las instituciones y los organismos comunitarios y a la libre circulación de estos datos. A no ser que se especifique lo contrario, es necesario que responda a las preguntas y facilite los datos personales solicitados a efectos de evaluar su candidatura, que serán gestionados únicamente por la Unidad SANTE/D4. El candidato podrá recibir información sobre sus datos personales, si así lo solicita, y podrá rectificarlos en caso de que sean inexactos o se encuentren incompletos. En caso de que tenga alguna pregunta relacionada con el procesamiento de sus datos personales, preséntelas a la Unidad SANTE/D4, en la siguiente dirección: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu. En lo que respecta al procesamiento de sus datos personales, tiene derecho a presentar un recurso, en cualquier momento, ante el Supervisor Europeo de Protección de Datos, escribiendo a la siguiente dirección: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>El poder adjudicador publicará de manera periódica en su sitio web la lista de expertos que hayan firmado un contrato con la Comisión Europea.</P><P>Todas las solicitudes de información adicional se podrán enviar a: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha de envío del anuncio por la DG SANTE:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha de recepción por la Oficina de Publicaciones:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: Kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntö ulkoisten asiantuntijoiden luettelon laatimiseksi eläintautien ja zoonoosien hävittämis-, torjunta- ja seurantaohjelmien arviointia varten</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan komissio</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, sähköpostiosoite: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tämä ilmoitus on kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntö</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Luonnollisia henkilöitä, jotka haluavat osallistua, pyydetään tekemään se tämän ilmoituksen määräysten mukaisesti.</P><P>Tämän pyynnön tarkoituksena on tarjota Euroopan komission yksiköille mahdollisuus laatia toimitettujen hakemusten tarkastelun jälkeen luettelo asiantuntijoista, joiden kanssa voitaisiin tehdä kohdassa C kuvattuihin aloihin liittyviä sopimuksia.</P><P>Aina, kun on suoritettava johonkin jäljempänä mainittuun tautiin liittyvä arviointitoimi, hankintaviranomainen pyytää joko kaikkia luettelossa olevia hakijoita tai ainoastaan joitakin heistä suorittamaan toimen kutakin arviointia varten erikseen määritettyjen puolueettomien ja syrjimättömien valintaperusteiden perusteella.</P><P>Luetteloon valinta ei millään tavoin oikeudellisesti velvoita Euroopan komissiota tekemään sopimusta.</P><P>Kunkin mainitun taudin osalta laaditaan asiantuntijaluettelo.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kattava kuvaus kiinnostuksenilmaisupyynnön kohteena olevista aiheista:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetuksen (EU) n:o 652/2014 artiklassa 9 säädetään unionin rahoituksellisesta tuesta tiettyjen eläintautien ja zoonoosien kansallisten hävittämis-, torjunta- ja seurantaohjelmien toteuttamista varten (1).</P><P>Komissio arvioi jäsenvaltioiden vuosittain esittämät ohjelmat sekä eläinlääkintää että rahoitusta koskevasta näkökulmasta.</P><P>Jotta voidaan tarjota lisätyökalu ohjelmien arviointia varten, komissio etsii ulkoista teknistä tukea jäsenvaltioiden vuonna 2019 ja sen jälkeen esittämien ohjelmien esiarvioinnin suorittamista varten.</P><P>Ulkoista tukea etsitään seuraavia tauteja koskevien ohjelmien arviointia varten:</P><P>afrikkalainen sikarutto,</P><P>lintuinfluenssa,</P><P>sinikielitauti,</P><P>naudan bruselloosi,</P><P>nautatuberkuloosi,</P><P>klassinen sikarutto,</P><P>karjan kyhmynahkatauti (lumpy skin -tauti),</P><P>lampaan ja vuohen bruselloosi,</P><P>raivotauti,</P><P>salmonelloosi (zoonoottinen salmonella),</P><P>lammas- ja vuohirutto,</P><P>lammas- ja vuohirokko,</P><P>tarttuvat spongiformiset enkefalopatiat (TSE).</P><P>Hakijoiden on ilmoitettava selvästi tauti, johon he ovat erikoistuneet. Katso valintaperusteet kohdasta F.</P><P>Tämän hakemuspyynnön perusteella tehtävät sopimukset ovat vakiomuotoisia tehtäväkohtaisia sopimuksia, joiden päiväpalkkio on 450 (neljäsataaviisikymmentä) euroa. Matka- ja oleskelukustannukset sekä muut kustannukset korvataan komission yleisohjeiden (2) mukaisesti. Yhteenlaskettu sopimusten pituus ei pääsääntöisesti ylitä 30 päivää vuodessa.</P><P>450 euron päiväpalkkio voidaan tarkistaa kerran tai kahdesti vuodessa.</P><P>(1) Elintarvikeketjuun, eläinten terveyteen ja eläinten hyvinvointiin, kasvien terveyteen ja kasvien lisäysaineistoon liittyvien menojen hallinnointia koskevista säännöksistä, neuvoston direktiivien 98/56/EY, 2000/29/EY ja 2008/90/EY, Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetusten (EY) n:o 178/2002, (EY) n:o 882/2004, (EY) n:o 396/2005, Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston direktiivin 2009/128/EY ja Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetuksen (EY) n:o 1107/2009 muuttamisesta sekä neuvoston päätösten 66/399/ETY, 76/894/ETY ja 2009/470/EY kumoamisesta 15.5.2014 annetun (EUVL L 189, 27.6.2014, s. 11) Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetuksessa (EU) n:o 652/2014 säädetään unionin rahoituksellisesta tuesta tiettyjen eläintautien ja zoonoosien kansallisten hävittämis-, torjunta- ja seurantaohjelmien toteuttamista varten. </P><P>(2) komission päätös, annettu 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Suorituspaikka:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Työt suoritetaan etätöinä (esimerkiksi asiantuntijan vakituisessa tai virallisessa osoitteessa) ja Euroopan komission toimistoissa.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Poissulkemisperuste:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Voidakseen tulla sisällytetyksi luetteloon hakijoiden on allekirjoitettava lomakkeessa oleva kunnian ja omantunnon kautta annettava vakuutus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Valintaperusteet:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Voidakseen tulla sisällytetyksi luetteloon hakijoilla on oltava</P><P>— tutkinto eläinlääketieteen alalta,</P><P>— erittäin hyvä suullinen ja kirjallinen englannin kielen taito,</P><P>— perustason tietotekninen tietämys,</P><P>— vähintään viiden vuoden ajalta</P><P>—— ammatilliset taidot ja kokemus hävittämis-, torjunta- ja seurantaohjelmien johtamisesta ja toteuttamisesta vähintään yhden edellä mainitun taudin osalta tai</P><P>—— ammatillinen kokemus vähintään yhteen edellä mainituista eläintaudeista liittyvästä epidemiologiasta.</P><P>Edellä mainittuihin tauteihin liittyvät tieteelliset julkaisut ja muun kielen kuin englannin hyvä kielitaito katsotaan eduksi.</P><P>Ennen sopimuksen allekirjoittamista valittujen hakijoiden on allekirjoitettava vakuutus siitä, ettei kyseinen arviointi aiheuta heille eturistiriitaa ja että he ilmoittavat välittömästi Euroopan komissiolle, mikäli tällainen eturistiriita tulee esiin arvioinnin aikana. Eturistiriita vallitsee silloin, jos arvioijan toimien tasapuolinen ja puolueeton suorittaminen vaarantuu syistä, jotka liittyvät perheeseen, tunne-elämään, poliittiseen tai kansalliseen yhteenkuuluvuuteen, taloudelliseen etuun tai mihin tahansa muuhun yhteiseen etuun kyseessä olevien ohjelmien suhteen. Arviointiprosessin aikana arvioijien on osoitettava asiaankuuluvaa tehtävään omistautumista ja otettava huomioon prosessin aikana heille toimitettavien tietojen ja asiakirjojen luottamuksellisuus.</P><P>Hakijoita voidaan pyytää esittämään todistusasiakirjat (eli jäljennös yliopistotutkinnosta ja todistukset työkokemuksesta). Jollei kyseisiä asiakirjoja ole saatavilla, hakemus hylätään.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hakemuslomaketta koskevat tiedot:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Täytettävä lomake on saatavilla seuraavasta internetosoitteesta:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Tämä lomake tulisi tallettaa kovalevylle, täyttää ja lähettää napsauttamalla ao. nappia.</P><P>Jos hakijalla on vaikeuksia ladata lomake (esimerkiksi ohjelmistojen yhteensopimattomuuden vuoksi), asiasta on ilmoitettava sähköpostitse osoitteeseen sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Järjestelmä ei hyväksy puutteellisien hakemusten lähettämistä.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Muut tiedot:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Luettelo valituista asiantuntijoista on voimassa yhden (1) vuoden alkaen päivästä, jona kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntö julkaistaan Euroopan unionin virallisessa lehdessä.</P><P>Kiinnostuneet henkilöt voivat jättää hakemuksensa milloin tahansa tämän luettelon voimassaoloaikana kolmea viimeistä kuukautta lukuun ottamatta.</P><P>Hakijat voivat vetää hakemuksensa pois milloin tahansa luettelon voimassaoloaikana toimittamalla kirjallisen ilmoituksen hankintaviranomaiselle.</P><P>Kaikille hakijoille ilmoitetaan, hyväksytäänkö heidät luetteloon.</P><P>Tietyn vuoden N ohjelmien arviointia varten suunniteltu työ on suoritettava vuoden N-1 kesäkuun jälkipuoliskon ja heinäkuun lopun välisenä aikana. Asiantuntijoiden on oltava käytettävissä vähintään kahden viikon ajan kyseisen ajanjakson aikana arvioinnin suorittamista varten, ja heidän on pystyttävä osallistumaan kokoukseen terveyden ja elintarviketurvallisuuden pääosaston toimitiloissa Brysselissä (asiantuntijoiden, jotka ovat mukana useampaa tautia koskevassa työssä, on varattava yli yksi päivä Brysselissä).</P><P>Ainoastaan 31.3.2018 mennessä jätetyt hakemukset otetaan huomioon vuoden 2019 ohjelmien arviointia varten.</P><P>Tultuaan valituiksi hakijat eivät saa toimittaa uutta hakemusta.</P><P>Euroopan komissio huolehtii siitä, että arvioijaryhmät, jotka on perustettu tämän kiinnostuksenilmaisupyynnön perusteella laaditun asiantuntijoiden luettelon pohjalta, ovat koostumukseltaan tasapainoisia ja että niissä noudatetaan asiaankuuluvaa vuorottelua. Hakijoiden maantieteellinen alkuperä sekä ammatillinen tausta otetaan huomioon. Euroopan komissio aikoo valita tasapuolisesti naisia ja miehiä.</P><P>Kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntöön toimitetun vastauksen käsittely edellyttää hakijan henkilötietojen (esimerkiksi nimi, osoite ja ansioluettelo) kirjaamista ja lisäkäsittelyä. Kyseisiä tietoja käsitellään yksilöiden suojelusta yhteisöjen toimielinten ja elinten suorittamassa henkilötietojen käsittelyssä ja näiden tietojen vapaasta liikkuvuudesta annetun asetuksen (EY) N:o 45/2001 mukaisesti. Ellei toisin ilmoiteta, kysymyksiin annettuja vastauksia sekä pyydettyjä henkilötietoja tarvitaan hakemusten arvioimiseksi. Kyseisiä tietoja hallinnoi ainoastaan terveyden ja elintarviketurvallisuuden PO:n yksikkö D4. Hakija voi pyynnöstä saada ilmoituksen käsiteltävistä henkilötiedoistaan ja oikaista mahdolliset epätarkat tai vaillinaiset henkilötiedot. Mikäli henkilötietojen käsittelyn osalta on kysymyksiä, kysymykset on lähetettävä terveyden ja elintarviketurvallisuuden pääosaston yksikölle D4 seuraavaan sähköpostiosoitteeseen: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu Henkilötietojen käsittelyyn liittyvissä asioissa voidaan milloin tahansa kääntyä Euroopan tietosuojavaltuutetun puoleen lähettämällä postia seuraavaan osoitteeseen: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Hankintaviranomainen julkaisee verkkosivustollaan määräajoin luettelon asiantuntijoista, jotka ovat allekirjoittaneet sopimuksen Euroopan komission kanssa.</P><P>Kaikki lisätietopyynnöt voidaan lähettää seuraavaan sähköpostiosoitteeseen: sante-ami-prog-d4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tämän elintarviketurvallisuuden pääosaston ilmoituksen lähetyspäivä:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen vastaanottopäivä julkaisutoimistossa:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Appel de manifestation d'intérêt en vue de l'établissement d'une liste d'experts externes pour l'évaluation de programmes d'éradication, de contrôle et de surveillance des maladies animales et des zoonoses.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pouvoirs adjudicateur :</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Commission européenne</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food Safety Programme, Emergency Funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgique.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Courriel : </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Le présent avis constitue un appel de manifestation d'intérêt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les personnes physiques qui souhaitent présenter leur candidature sont invitées à le faire en se conformant aux dispositions du présent avis.</P><P>Le présent appel devra permettre aux services de la Commission, après examen des candidatures reçues, d'établir une liste d'experts susceptibles de se voir attribuer un marché dans les domaines décrits au point C.</P><P>Chaque fois qu'une activité d'évaluation en rapport avec l'une des maladies mentionnées ci-après s'avérera nécessaire, le pouvoir adjudicateur invitera tous les candidats inscrits sur la liste, ou certains d'entre eux seulement, sur la base de critères de sélection objectifs et non discriminatoires spécifiques à l'évaluation concernée.</P><P>L'inscription sur la liste n'implique aucun engagement juridique de la part de la Commission européenne quant à l'attribution du marché.</P><P>Une liste d'experts sera établie pour chacune des maladies indiquées.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description exhaustive des domaines couverts par l'appel de manifestation d'intérêt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L'article 9 du règlement (UE) no 652/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil (1) prévoit une contribution financière de l’Union pour la mise en œuvre de programmes nationaux pour l’éradication, le contrôle et la surveillance de certaines maladies animales et de zoonoses.</P><P>La Commission évalue les programmes soumis par les États membres chaque année, tant du point de vue vétérinaire que du point de vue financier.</P><P>Afin de disposer d'un outil supplémentaire pour l'évaluation des programmes, la Commission souhaite faire appel à des services d'assistance technique externe en vue de la réalisation d'une évaluation préalable des programmes soumis par les États membres pour 2019.</P><P>La Commission recherche des services d'assistance externe pour l'évaluation des programmes relatifs aux maladies suivantes :</P><P>Peste porcine africaine,</P><P>Grippe aviaire,</P><P>Fièvre catarrhale,</P><P>Brucellose bovine,</P><P>Tuberculose bovine,</P><P>Peste porcine classique,</P><P>Dermatose nodulaire contagieuse,</P><P>Brucellose ovine et caprine,</P><P>Rage,</P><P>Salmonellose (salmonelles zoonotiques),</P><P>Peste des petits ruminants,</P><P>Varicelle des petits ruminants,</P><P>Encéphalopathies spongiformes transmissibles (EST).</P><P>Les candidats doivent indiquer clairement la maladie dans laquelle ils sont spécialisés. Voir point F pour les critères de sélection.</P><P>Les contrats signés dans le cadre du présent appel de candidatures seront des contrats de mission types au tarif journalier de 450 EUR (quatre cent cinquante euros). Les frais de déplacement et de séjour ainsi que les autres frais seront remboursés conformément aux règles normales de la Commission (2). De manière générale, la durée cumulative des contrats ne pourra dépasser 30 jours/an.</P><P>Le tarif journalier de 450 EUR pourra faire l'objet d'une révision annuelle ou semestrielle.</P><P>(1) Règlement (UE) no 652/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 15.5.2014 fixant des dispositions pour la gestion des dépenses relatives, d'une part, à la chaîne de production des denrées alimentaires, à la santé et au bien-être des animaux et, d'autre part, à la santé et au matériel de reproduction des végétaux, modifiant les directives du Conseil 98/56/CE, 2000/29/CE et 2008/90/CE, les règlements du Parlement européen et du Conseil (CE) no 178/2002, (CE) no 882/2004 et (CE) no 396/2005 ainsi que la directive 2009/128/CE no 1107/2009 du Parlement européen et du Conseil et abrogeant les décisions du Conseil no 66/399/CEE, 76/894/CEE et 2009/470/CE. JO L 189 du 27.6.2014, p. 11.</P><P>(2) Décision de la Commission du 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lieu de prestation</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Les services seront fournis sur un site externe (par exemple à l'adresse permanente ou officielle de l'expert) et dans les bureaux de la Commission européenne.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critères d'exclusion</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pour figurer sur la liste, les candidats devront remplir les déclarations de soumission de candidature incluses dans le formulaire.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critères de sélection</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pour figurer sur la liste, les candidats devront :</P><P>- Être titulaires d'un diplôme en médecine vétérinaire,</P><P>- Avoir une très bonne connaissance écrite et orale de l'anglais,</P><P>- Avoir des connaissances informatiques de base,</P><P>- Un minimum de cinq ans,</P><P>— D'expérience et de compétences professionnelles dans la gestion et la mise en œuvre de programmes pour l'éradication, le contrôle et la surveillance d'au moins une des maladies énumérées ci-dessus ; ou,</P><P>— D'expérience professionnelle en épidémiologie pour au moins une des maladies animales énumérées ci-dessus.</P><P>Des publications scientifiques en rapport avec les maladies susmentionnées et de bonnes aptitudes linguistiques dans une autre langue que l'anglais constitueront un avantage.</P><P>Avant de signer le contrat, les candidats sélectionnés devront signer une déclaration certifiant l'absence de tout conflit d'intérêts dans le cadre de l'évaluation concernée, et attestant qu'ils s'engagent à informer sans délai la Commission si un tel conflit d'intérêts se présentait au cours de l'évaluation. Un évaluateur se trouve en situation de conflit d'intérêts lorsque l'exercice impartial et objectif de ses fonctions est compromis pour des raisons faisant intervenir un des éléments suivants : famille, vie affective, affinités politiques ou nationales, intérêts économiques ou tout autre intérêt partagé avec les programmes proposés. Au cours du processus d'évaluation, les évaluateurs devront démontrer une assiduité à la tâche et observer le principe de confidentialité des informations et des documents portés à leur attention au cours du processus.</P><P>Les candidats pourront être invités à présenter des pièces justificatives (par exemple, une copie du diplôme universitaire et des certificats d'expérience professionnelle). La non-présentation de ces documents entraînera le rejet de la candidature.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informations relatives au formulaire de candidature</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le formulaire à compléter est disponible à l'adresse Internet suivante :</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Ce formulaire doit être enregistré sur disque dur, renseigné et envoyé en cliquant sur le bouton correspondant.</P><P>En cas de problème de téléchargement du formulaire (en raison d'une incompatibilité de logiciel, etc.), veuillez envoyer un courrier électronique à l'adresse : sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Le système ne permettra pas d’envoyer une candidature incomplète.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Renseignements complémentaires</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>La liste des experts sélectionnés aura une validité de 1 an à compter de la date de publication de l'appel de manifestation d'intérêt au Journal officiel.</P><P>Toute personne intéressée pourra présenter sa candidature à tout moment durant le délai de validité de la liste, à l'exception des 3 derniers mois dudit délai.</P><P>Les candidats peuvent retirer leur candidature à tout moment au cours de la période de validité de la liste par notification écrite au pouvoir adjudicateur.</P><P>Tous les candidats seront informés de la suite réservée à leur candidature.</P><P>Pour l'évaluation des programmes d'une année N, le travail envisagé doit être réalisé entre la seconde quinzaine de juin et la fin du mois de juillet de l'année N-1. Les experts devront être disponibles pendant au moins 2 semaines au cours de cette période afin de réaliser l'évaluation, ainsi que pour assister à une réunion dans les locaux de la DG SANTE à Bruxelles (les experts participant à l'appel pour plusieurs maladies doivent prévoir plus d'un jour à Bruxelles).</P><P>Pour l'évaluation des programmes de 2019, seules les candidatures présentées avant le 31.3.2018 seront prises en compte.</P><P>Une fois sélectionnés, les candidats ne doivent pas soumettre une nouvelle candidature.</P><P>La Commission européenne veillera à ce que les panels d'évaluation, constitués à partir de la liste d'experts établie à la suite du présent appel de manifestation d'intérêt, soient équilibrés, et à ce qu'une rotation appropriée des experts soit mise en place. L'origine géographique des candidats ainsi que leur expérience professionnelle seront prises en compte. La Commission européenne souhaite également une participation équilibrée des hommes et des femmes.</P><P>Le suivi des candidatures au présent appel de manifestation d'intérêt requiert l'enregistrement et le traitement ultérieur de données à caractère personnel (par exemple les noms, les adresses ou les CV des personnes physiques). Ces données seront traitées conformément aux exigences du règlement (CE) no 45/2001 relatif à la protection des personnes physiques à l'égard du traitement des données à caractère personnel par les institutions et les organes communautaires et à la libre circulation de ces données. Sauf mention contraire, les réponses aux questions et les données à caractère personnel requises sont nécessaires à l'évaluation des candidatures ; elles seront gérées uniquement par l'unité SANTE/D4. Sur demande, il est possible d'obtenir la communication des données à caractère personnel et de rectifier les données inexactes ou incomplètes. Pour toute question concernant le traitement de ces données, il y aura lieu de prendre contact avec l'unité SANTE/D4 à l'adresse suivante : sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu À tout moment, le contrôleur européen de la protection des données pourra être saisi au sujet du traitement des données à caractère personnel à l’adresse suivante : DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Le pouvoir adjudicateur publiera régulièrement sur son site Internet la liste des experts qui ont signé un contrat avec la Commission européenne.</P><P>Toute demande de renseignements complémentaires peut être adressée à : sante-ami-prog-d4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date d'envoi de l'avis par DG SANTE :</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date de réception de l'avis par l'OP (l'Office des publications) :</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Βρυξέλλες: Πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος για την κατάρτιση καταλόγου εξωτερικών εμπειρογνωμόνων για την αξιολόγηση προγραμμάτων καταπολέμησης, ελέγχου και επιτήρησης των ασθενειών των ζώων και των ζωονόσων.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>Α.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα αρχή:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Βέλγιο.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Ηλεκτρονικό Ταχυδρομείο: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>Β.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Η παρούσα συνιστά πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος.</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Τα φυσικά πρόσωπα που επιθυμούν να υποβάλουν αίτηση καλούνται να τηρήσουν τους όρους της παρούσας προκήρυξης.</P><P>Η παρούσα πρόσκληση θα επιτρέψει στις υπηρεσίες της Επιτροπής, αφού εξετάσουν τις υποψηφιότητες που θα υποβληθούν, να καταρτίσουν κατάλογο εμπειρογνωμόνων στους οποίους θα μπορούσαν να ανατεθούν συμβάσεις στους τομείς που περιγράφονται στο σημείο Γ.</P><P>Κάθε φορά που θα απαιτείται η εκτέλεση μιας δραστηριότητας αξιολόγησης σχετικά με κάποια από τις ασθένειες που αναφέρονται παρακάτω, η αναθέτουσα αρχή θα καλεί είτε όλους τους υποψηφίους του καταλόγου είτε μόνο ορισμένους από αυτούς, βάσει αντικειμενικών και αμερόληπτων κριτηρίων επιλογής που θα έχουν καθοριστεί ειδικά για τη συγκεκριμένη αξιολόγηση.</P><P>Η συμπερίληψη στον κατάλογο δεν συνιστά νομική δέσμευση εκ μέρους της Ευρωπαϊκής Επιτροπής για την ανάθεση σύμβασης.</P><P>Για κάθε αναφερόμενη ασθένεια θα καταρτιστεί ένας κατάλογος εμπειρογνωμόνων.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>Γ.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Εξαντλητική περιγραφή των θεμάτων που καλύπτονται από την παρούσα πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Το άρθρο 9 του κανονισμού (ΕΕ) αριθ. 652/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου (1) προβλέπει χρηματοδοτική συνεισφορά της Ένωσης για την εφαρμογή εθνικών προγραμμάτων καταπολέμησης, ελέγχου και επιτήρησης των ασθενειών των ζώων και των ζωονόσων.</P><P>Η Επιτροπή θα αξιολογεί τα προγράμματα που υποβάλλονται από τα κράτη μέλη κάθε χρόνο, από κτηνιατρική και οικονομική άποψη.</P><P>Προκειμένου να παράσχει ένα πρόσθετο εργαλείο για την αξιολόγηση των προγραμμάτων, η Επιτροπή αναζητά εξωτερική τεχνική βοήθεια για την εκ των προτέρων αξιολόγηση των προγραμμάτων που υποβάλλουν τα κράτη μέλη για το 2019.</P><P>Αναζητούμε εξωτερική βοήθεια για την αξιολόγηση των προγραμμάτων που σχετίζονται με τις ακόλουθες ασθένειες:</P><P>αφρικανική πανώλη των χοίρων,</P><P>γρίπη των πτηνών,</P><P>καταρροϊκό πυρετό,</P><P>βρουκέλλωση των βοοειδών,</P><P>φυματίωση των βοοειδών,</P><P>κλασική πανώλη των χοίρων,</P><P>οζώδη δερματίτιδα,</P><P>βρουκέλλωση των αιγοπροβάτων,</P><P>λύσσα,</P><P>σαλμονέλλωση (ζωονοσογόνος σαλμονέλα),</P><P>πανώλη των μικρών μηρυκαστικών,</P><P>ευλογιά των αιγοπροβάτων,</P><P>μεταδοτικές σπογγώδεις εγκεφαλοπάθειες (ΜΣΕ),</P><P>Οι υποψήφιοι πρέπει να αναφέρουν σαφώς την ασθένεια στην οποία εξειδικεύονται. Βλέπε σημείο ΣΤ για τα κριτήρια επιλογής.</P><P>Οι συμβάσεις που θα υπογραφούν στο πλαίσιο της παρούσας πρόσκλησης υποβολής υποψηφιοτήτων θα είναι τυπικές συμβάσεις εργασιών έναντι ημερήσιας αμοιβής 450 EUR (τετρακοσίων πενήντα ευρώ). Τα έξοδα μετακίνησης, διαμονής και τα λοιπά έξοδα θα επιστρέφονται σύμφωνα με τους βασικούς κανόνες της Επιτροπής (2). Οι συμβάσεις, κατά γενικό κανόνα, αθροιστικά δεν θα υπερβαίνουν τις 30 ημέρες ανά έτος.</P><P>Η ημερήσια αμοιβή των 450 EUR ενδέχεται να αναθεωρείται μία ή δύο φορές ετησίως.</P><P>(1) Ο κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 652/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 15.5.2014 για τη θέσπιση διατάξεων σχετικά με τη διαχείριση των δαπανών που αφορούν τη διατροφική αλυσίδα, την υγεία των ζώων και την καλή μεταχείριση των ζώων καθώς και την υγεία των φυτών και το φυτικό αναπαραγωγικό υλικό, για την τροποποίηση των οδηγιών του Συμβουλίου 98/56/ΕΚ, 2000/29/ΕΚ, 2008/90/ΕΚ των κανονισμών του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου (ΕΚ) αριθ. 178/2002, (ΕΚ) αριθ.882/2004 και (ΕΚ) αριθ.396/2005 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της οδηγίας 2009/128/ΕΚ του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου και του κανονισμού (ΕΚ) αριθ. 1107/2009 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου και την κατάργηση των αποφάσεων 66/399/ΕΟΚ, 76/894/ΕΟΚ και 2009/470/ΕΚ. ΕΕ L 189 της 27.6.2014, σ. 11.</P><P>(2) Απόφαση της Επιτροπής της 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>Δ.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τόπος εργασίας</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ο τόπος εργασίας θα είναι κάποια απομακρυσμένη τοποθεσία (π.χ. η μόνιμη ή επίσημη διεύθυνση του εμπειρογνώμονα) και τα γραφεία της Ευρωπαϊκής Επιτροπής.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>Ε.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Κριτήριο αποκλεισμού</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Προκειμένου να συμπεριληφθούν στον κατάλογο, οι υποψήφιοι πρέπει να συμπληρώσουν την υποβολή αίτησης που περιλαμβάνεται στο έντυπο.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>ΣΤ.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Κριτήρια επιλογής</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Προκειμένου να συμπεριληφθούν στον κατάλογο, οι υποψήφιοι θα πρέπει να διαθέτουν:</P><P>— πτυχίο κτηνιατρικής,</P><P>— πολύ καλή γνώση (γραπτή και προφορική) της αγγλικής γλώσσας,</P><P>— βασικές γνώσεις πληροφορικής,</P><P>— τουλάχιστον πέντε έτη,</P><P>—— είτε επαγγελματικών προσόντων και εμπειρίας στη διαχείριση και υλοποίηση προγραμμάτων καταπολέμησης, ελέγχου και επιτήρησης για τουλάχιστον μία από τις προαναφερθείσες νόσους, είτε,</P><P>—— επαγγελματικής εμπειρίας στην επιδημιολογία σχετικά με τουλάχιστον μία από τις προαναφερθείσες νόσους.</P><P>Οι επιστημονικές δημοσιεύσεις σχετικά με τις ανωτέρω ασθένειες και η καλή γνώση μιας δεύτερης ξένης γλώσσας εκτός των αγγλικών αποτελούν πλεονέκτημα.</P><P>Πριν από την υπογραφή της σύμβασης, οι επιλεγμένοι υποψήφιοι θα πρέπει να υπογράψουν δήλωση που να βεβαιώνει ότι δεν βρίσκονται σε κατάσταση σύγκρουσης συμφερόντων σχετικά με τη συγκεκριμένη αξιολόγηση και ότι θα ενημερώσουν άμεσα την Επιτροπή εφόσον προκύψει τέτοια σύγκρουση συμφερόντων κατά τη διάρκεια της αξιολόγησης. Σύγκρουση συμφερόντων υφίσταται όταν τίθεται υπό αμφισβήτηση η αμερόληπτη και αντικειμενική άσκηση των καθηκόντων ενός αξιολογητή για λόγους που αφορούν την οικογενειακή ή συναισθηματική ζωή του, τις πολιτικές ή εθνικές πεποιθήσεις του, τα οικονομικά συμφέροντα του ή οποιαδήποτε άλλα συμφέροντά του που θα συνδέονται με τα υποβαλλόμενα προγράμματα. Καθ΄όλη τη διάρκεια της διαδικασίας αξιολόγησης, οι αξιολογητές πρέπει να επιδεικνύουν τη δέουσα αφοσίωση στα καθήκοντά τους και να διαφυλάσσουν την εμπιστευτικότητα των πληροφοριών και των εγγράφων που θα έχουν περιέλθει σε γνώση τους κατά τη διαδικασία.</P><P>Οι υποψήφιοι ενδέχεται να κληθούν να προσκομίσουν αποδεικτικά έγγραφα (ήτοι αντίγραφο του πανεπιστημιακού πτυχίου και πιστοποιητικά της εργασιακής εμπειρίας τους). Η μη υποβολή των εν λόγω εγγράφων θα έχει ως αποτέλεσμα την απόρριψη της υποψηφιότητας.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>Ζ.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Πληροφορίες σχετικά με το έντυπο υποβολής υποψηφιότητας</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Το έντυπο προς συμπλήρωση διατίθεται στην ακόλουθη διεύθυνση στο διαδίκτυο:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Αυτό το έντυπο θα πρέπει να αποθηκεύεται στο σκληρό δίσκο, να συμπληρώνεται και να αποστέλλεται κάνοντας κλικ στο αντίστοιχο κουμπί.</P><P>Σε περίπτωση προβλημάτων κατά την καταφόρτωση του εντύπου (λόγω ασυμβατότητας λογισμικού κ.λπ.), οι υποψήφιοι παρακαλούνται να αποστείλουν μήνυμα ηλεκτρονικού ταχυδρομείου στην διεύθυνση sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Το σύστημα δεν θα επιτρέψει την αποστολή υποβολής υποψηφιότητας που είναι ελλιπής.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>Η.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Λοιπές πληροφορίες</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ο κατάλογος των επιλεγμένων εμπειρογνωμόνων θα ισχύει για 1 έτος από την ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης της πρόσκλησης εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος στην Επίσημη Εφημερίδα.</P><P>Κάθε ενδιαφερόμενος μπορεί να καταθέσει υποψηφιότητα οποιαδήποτε χρονική στιγμή κατά τη διάρκεια της περιόδου ισχύος του καταλόγου, με εξαίρεση τους τελευταίους τρεις μήνες της εν λόγω περιόδου.</P><P>Οι υποψήφιοι μπορούν να αποσύρουν την υποψηφιότητά τους οποιαδήποτε χρονική στιγμή κατά τη διάρκεια της περιόδου ισχύος του καταλόγου με γραπτή ειδοποίηση προς την αναθέτουσα αρχή.</P><P>Όλοι οι υποψήφιοι θα ενημερωθούν εάν έχουν συμπεριληφθεί ή όχι στον κατάλογο.</P><P>Για την αξιολόγηση των προγραμμάτων ενός δεδομένου έτους N, οι προβλεπόμενες εργασίες αναμένεται να εκτελεστούν εντός διαστήματος που διαρκεί από το δεύτερο δεκαπενθήμερο του Ιουνίου έως το τέλος του Ιουλίου του έτους N-1. Οι εμπειρογνώμονες θα πρέπει να είναι διαθέσιμοι για τουλάχιστον δύο εβδομάδες κατά τη διάρκεια αυτής της περιόδου για την εκπόνηση της αξιολόγησης και θα πρέπει να δύνανται να παραστούν στη συνεδρίαση με τη ΓΔ Υγείας και Ασφάλειας των Τροφίμων στις Βρυξέλλες (οι εμπειρογνώμονες που ασχολούνται με περισσότερες από μία ασθένειες πρέπει να υπολογίσουν παραπάνω από μία ημέρες στις Βρυξέλλες).</P><P>Για την αξιολόγηση των προγραμμάτων του 2019, θα ληφθούν υπόψη μόνο υποψηφιότητες που θα υποβληθούν έως τις 31.3.2018.</P><P>Μετά την επιλογή τους, οι υποψήφιοι δεν πρέπει να υποβάλουν εκ νέου υποψηφιότητα.</P><P>Η Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή θα διασφαλίσει τη σύσταση ισορροπημένων επιτροπών αξιολόγησης, βάσει του καταλόγου εμπειρογνωμόνων που θα προκύψει από την παρούσα πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος, με απασχόληση των εμπειρογνωμόνων εκ περιτροπής. Θα ληφθεί υπόψη η γεωγραφική προέλευση καθώς και το επαγγελματικό υπόβαθρο των υποψηφίων. Η Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή επιθυμεί επίσης την ισορροπημένη συμμετοχή ανδρών και γυναικών.</P><P>Η παρακολούθηση της ανταπόκρισής σας στην παρούσα πρόσκληση εκδήλωσης ενδιαφέροντος θα απαιτεί την καταγραφή και περαιτέρω επεξεργασία προσωπικών δεδομένων (για παράδειγμα όνομα, διεύθυνση και βιογραφικό σημείωμα). Η επεξεργασία αυτών των δεδομένων θα γίνει σύμφωνα με τις απαιτήσεις του κανονισμού (ΕΚ) αριθ. 45/2001 σχετικά με την προστασία των φυσικών προσώπων έναντι της επεξεργασίας δεδομένων προσωπικού χαρακτήρα από τα όργανα και τους οργανισμούς της Κοινότητας και σχετικά με την ελεύθερη κυκλοφορία των δεδομένων αυτών. Εκτός εάν αναφέρεται διαφορετικά, η παροχή απαντήσεων στις τιθέμενες ερωτήσεις και η υποβολή των ζητούμενων προσωπικών δεδομένων είναι απαραίτητες για τον σκοπό της αξιολόγησης της υποψηφιότητάς σας, και θα τύχουν επεξεργασίας αποκλειστικά από τη ΓΔ Υγείας και Ασφάλειας των Τροφίμων, Μονάδα D4. Οι ενδιαφερόμενοι μπορούν, κατόπιν αιτήματος, να λάβουν τη δήλωση των προσωπικών τους δεδομένων και να διορθώσουν τυχόν ανακριβή ή ελλιπή προσωπικά δεδομένα. Εάν οι ενδιαφερόμενοι έχουν απορίες σχετικά με την επεξεργασία των προσωπικών τους δεδομένων, παρακαλούνται να τις υποβάλουν στη ΓΔ Υγείας και Ασφάλειας των Τροφίμων, Μονάδα D4 στην ακόλουθη διεύθυνση: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu. Όσον αφορά στην επεξεργασία των προσωπικών δεδομένων, οι ενδιαφερόμενοι έχουν δικαίωμα να προσφύγουν ανά πάσα στιγμή στον Ευρωπαίο Επόπτη Προστασίας Δεδομένων στην ακόλουθη διεύθυνση ηλεκτρονικού ταχυδρομείου: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Η αναθέτουσα αρχή θα δημοσιεύει περιοδικά στον δικτυακό τόπο της τον κατάλογο των εμπειρογνωμόνων που θα έχουν υπογράψει σύμβαση με την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή.</P><P>Κάθε αίτηση για περαιτέρω πληροφορίες μπορεί να αποσταλεί στη διεύθυνση: sante-ami-prog-d4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>Θ.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ημερομηνία αποστολής της προκήρυξης προς δημοσίευση από την ΓΔ Υγείας και Ασφάλειας των Τροφίμων:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>Ι.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ημερομηνία παραλαβής της παρούσας από την Υπηρεσία Εκδόσεων:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Invito a manifestare interesse per la creazione di un elenco di esperti esterni per la valutazione dei programmi di eradicazione, di lotta e di sorveglianza riguardanti le malattie animali e le zoonosi.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Amministrazione aggiudicatrice:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Commissione europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgio.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il presente avviso è un invito a manifestare interesse</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le persone fisiche che intendono presentare la propria candidatura sono pregate di farlo secondo le disposizioni del presente avviso.</P><P>Il presente avviso dovrà permettere ai servizi della Commissione, dopo l'esame delle candidature pervenute, di stilare un elenco di esperti cui potrà essere aggiudicato un appalto nei settori descritti al punto C.</P><P>Ogni volta che dovrà essere svolta un'attività di valutazione relativa a una delle malattie menzionate di seguito, l'amministrazione aggiudicatrice inviterà tutti i candidati presenti nell'elenco, o solo alcuni di essi, operando una selezione in base a criteri obiettivi e non discriminatori specifici alla valutazione concreta.</P><P>L'iscrizione nell'elenco non comporta alcun obbligo giuridico a carico della Commissione europea in merito all'aggiudicazione di un appalto.</P><P>Per ciascuna delle malattie menzionate verrà stilato un elenco di esperti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dettagliata dei settori oggetto del presente invito a manifestare interesse</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L'articolo 9 del regolamento (UE) n. 652/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio (1) prevede il contributo finanziario dell'Unione per l'attuazione di programmi nazionali di eradicazione, di lotta e di sorveglianza riguardanti certe malattie animali e zoonosi.</P><P>La Commissione dovrà valutare tali programmi, presentati dagli Stati membri ogni anno, dal punto di vista veterinario e finanziario.</P><P>Al fine di fornire uno strumento aggiuntivo per la valutazione dei programmi, la Commissione ricerca assistenza tecnica esterna per eseguire una valutazione preliminare dei programmi presentati dagli Stati membri per il 2019.</P><P>Si cerca un'assistenza esterna per la valutazione dei programmi in relazione alle seguenti malattie:</P><P>peste suina africana,</P><P>influenza aviaria,</P><P>bluetongue,</P><P>brucellosi bovina,</P><P>tubercolosi bovina,</P><P>peste suina classica,</P><P>dermatite nodulare contagiosa,</P><P>brucellosi ovina e caprina,</P><P>rabbia,</P><P>salmonellosi (salmonella zoonotica),</P><P>peste ovina e caprina,</P><P>vaiolo caprino e ovino,</P><P>encefalopatia spongiforme trasmissibile (TSE).</P><P>I candidati dovranno indicare chiaramente la malattia nella quale sono specializzati. Cfr. punto F per i criteri di selezione.</P><P>I contratti firmati nell'ambito di questo invito a presentare candidature saranno dei contratti standard per incarichi conclusi con una tariffa giornaliera di 450 EUR (quattrocentocinquanta euro). Le spese di viaggio, di sussistenza e di altra natura verranno rimborsate in conformità delle norme standard della Commissione (2). Di norma i contratti non supereranno nell'insieme i 30 giorni all'anno.</P><P>La tariffa giornaliera di 450 EUR potrà essere oggetto di revisioni annuali o biennali.</P><P>(1) Regolamento (UE) n. 652/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, del 15.5.2014, che fissa le disposizioni per la gestione delle spese relative alla filiera alimentare, alla salute e al benessere degli animali, alla sanità delle piante e al materiale riproduttivo vegetale, che modifica le direttive 98/56/CE, 2000/29/CE e 2008/90/CE del Consiglio, i regolamenti (CE) n. 178/2002, (CE) n. 882/2004 e (CE) n. 396/2005 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, la direttiva 2009/128/CE del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, nonché il regolamento (CE) n. 1107/2009 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, e che abroga le decisioni 66/399/CEE, 76/894/CEE e 2009/470/CE del Consiglio. GU L 189 del 27.6.2014, pag. 11.</P><P>(2) Decisione della Commissione del 5.12.2007, DOC C (2007) 5858.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Luogo di esecuzione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il luogo di lavoro potrà essere un luogo distante (per es. l'indirizzo ufficiale o permanente dell'esperto), e gli uffici della Commissione europea.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteri di esclusione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Per essere inclusi nell'elenco, i candidati dovranno firmare la dichiarazione sull'onore inclusa nel modulo.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteri di selezione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Per essere inclusi nell'elenco, i candidati dovranno essere in possesso di:</P><P>— una laurea in medicina veterinaria,</P><P>— ottima padronanza orale e scritta dell'inglese,</P><P>— conoscenze informatiche di base,</P><P>— un minimo di 5 anni di</P><P>—— competenze ed esperienze professionali nella gestione e realizzazione di programmi di lotta, di sorveglianza e di eradicazione per almeno una delle malattie elencate in precedenza, oppure</P><P>—— esperienza professionale nel campo dell'epidemiologia inerente ad almeno 1 delle malattie animali elencate in precedenza.</P><P>La pubblicazione di testi scientifici inerenti alle malattie summenzionate e delle buone competenze linguistiche diverse dall'inglese costituiranno un vantaggio.</P><P>Prima di firmare il contratto, i candidati selezionati dovranno sottoscrivere una dichiarazione nella quale confermano l'assenza di conflitti d'interesse nell'ambito della valutazione da svolgere e si impegnano a segnalare immediatamente alla Commissione l'eventuale insorgere di un conflitto nel corso della valutazione. Esiste un conflitto di interessi laddove l'esercizio imparziale e obiettivo delle funzioni di un valutatore sia compromesso per ragioni dettate da un'affinità di tipo familiare, emotivo, politico o nazionale, da un interesse economico o da qualsiasi altro interesse condiviso con i programmi presentati. Nell'intero processo di valutazione i valutatori dovranno dimostrare un'adeguata dedizione al dovere e osservare la riservatezza delle informazioni e dei documenti a essi sottoposti nel corso del processo.</P><P>Ai candidati potrà essere richiesto di presentare dei documenti di supporto (ovvero copia del titolo universitario e certificati relativi all'esperienza lavorativa). La mancata disponibilità di tali documenti comporterà il rifiuto della candidatura.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informazioni relative all'atto di candidatura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il modulo da compilare è disponibile al seguente indirizzo Internet:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Questo modulo dovrà essere salvato sul disco fisso, compilato e inviato facendo clic sul pulsante corrispondente.</P><P>Nel caso in cui non si riuscisse a scaricare il modulo (a causa di incompatibilità del software, ecc.), si prega di inviare un'e-mail all'indirizzo sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Il sistema non consentirà l’invio di moduli incompleti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Altre informazioni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L'elenco degli esperti selezionati sarà valido per un periodo di 1 anno dalla data di pubblicazione dell'invito a manifestare interesse nella Gazzetta ufficiale.</P><P>Le persone interessate possono presentare candidatura in qualsiasi momento durante il periodo di validità dell'elenco, a eccezione degli ultimi 3 mesi.</P><P>I candidati potranno ritirare le proprie candidature in qualsiasi momento durante il periodo di validità dell'elenco mediante comunicazione scritta all'ente appaltante.</P><P>Tutti i candidati saranno informati in merito alla loro iscrizione o mancata iscrizione nell'elenco.</P><P>Per la valutazione dei programmi di un dato anno N, il lavoro previsto deve essere svolto tra la seconda metà di giugno e la fine di luglio dell'anno "N-1". Gli esperti dovranno essere disponibili per un periodo minimo di almeno 2 settimane durante tale periodo per eseguire la valutazione e dovranno essere disponibili a partecipare a una riunione della DG Salute e sicurezza alimentare a Bruxelles (gli esperti coinvolti in diverse malattie devono calcolare più di 1 giorno a Bruxelles).</P><P>Per la valutazione dei programmi del 2019, saranno prese in considerazione soltanto le candidature presentate entro il 31.3.2018.</P><P>Una volta selezionati, i candidati non dovranno ripresentare una candidatura.</P><P>La Commissione europea garantirà che i gruppi di valutazione, istituiti in base all'elenco di esperti derivante dal presente invito a manifestare interesse, siano formati in modo equilibrato e che ci sia un'opportuna rotazione di esperti. Saranno prese in considerazione anche l'origine geografica e l'esperienza professionale dei candidati. La Commissione europea cerca inoltre di garantire un'equilibrata partecipazione di donne e uomini.</P><P>Dare seguito alle risposte all'invito a manifestare interesse richiederà la registrazione e l'ulteriore trattamento dei dati personali (quali il nome, indirizzo e CV). Queste informazioni verranno trattate conformemente al disposto del regolamento (CE) n. 45/2001 concernente la tutela delle persone fisiche in relazione al trattamento dei dati personali da parte delle istituzioni e degli organismi comunitari, nonché la libera circolazione di tali dati. Fatta eccezione se menzionato diversamente, le risposte alle domande e i dati personali richiesti sono necessari per valutare la candidatura e saranno utilizzati soltanto dalla DG Salute e sicurezza alimentare, unità D4. I candidati possono, su richiesta, farsi trasmettere i propri dati personali e rettificare eventuali inesattezze o aggiornare i dati personali incompleti. Eventuali domande riguardanti il trattamento dei dati personali dovranno essere trasmesse alla DG Salute e sicurezza alimentare, unità D4 al seguente indirizzo: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu. Per quanto concerne il trattamento dei vostri dati personali, avete il diritto di far ricorso in qualsiasi momento al supervisore europeo alla protezione dei dati al seguente indirizzo: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>L'ente appaltante pubblicherà periodicamente sul proprio sito web l'elenco degli esperti che hanno firmato un contratto con la Commissione europea.</P><P>Tutte le richieste di ulteriori informazioni potranno essere inviate al seguente indirizzo: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data di spedizione dell'avviso da parte della DG Salute e sicurezza alimentare:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data di ricezione dell'avviso da parte dell'Ufficio delle pubblicazioni ufficiali:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussel: Oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling voor het opstellen van een lijst van externe deskundigen voor de beoordeling van programma's voor uitroeiing, bestrijding en surveillance van dierenziekten en zoönosen.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europese Commissie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, België.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, e-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Deze aankondiging is een oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Natuurlijke personen die een aanvraag wensen in te dienen, worden verzocht dit te doen overeenkomstig de bepalingen van deze aankondiging.</P><P>Deze oproep moet de diensten van de Commissie, na onderzoek van de ingediende aanvragen, in staat stellen een lijst van deskundigen op te stellen aan wie een opdracht op de gebieden beschreven in punt C kan worden gegund.</P><P>Telkens als een beoordelingsactiviteit in verband met een van de onderstaande ziekten moet worden uitgevoerd, zal de aanbestedende dienst ofwel alle gegadigden op de lijst ofwel slechts enkelen onder hen uitnodigen, op basis van objectieve en niet-discriminatoire selectiecriteria die specifiek zijn voor de betreffende beoordeling.</P><P>Opname op de lijst vormt geen juridisch engagement vanwege de Europese Commissie om een opdracht te gunnen.</P><P>Voor elk van de vermelde ziekten zal een lijst van deskundigen worden opgesteld.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Volledige beschrijving van de onderwerpen die door de oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling worden bestreken:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Artikel 9 van Verordening (EU) nr. 652/2014 van het EP en de Raad (1) voorziet een financiële bijdrage van de Unie voor de tenuitvoerlegging van nationale programma‘s voor de uitroeiing, bestrijding en surveillance van bepaalde dierenziekten en zoönosen.</P><P>De Commissie beoordeelt die door de lidstaten jaarlijks ingediende programma’s uit zowel veterinair als financieel oogpunt.</P><P>Om een bijkomend instrument te verstrekken, zoekt de Commissie externe technische bijstand om een voorlopige beoordeling van de programma's ingediend door de lidstaten voor 2019 en de volgende jaren uit te voeren.</P><P>We zijn op zoek naar externe bijstand voor de evaluatie van de programma's in verband met de volgende ziekten:</P><P>Afrikaanse varkenspest,</P><P>vogelgriep,</P><P>blauwtong,</P><P>runderbrucellose,</P><P>rundertuberculose,</P><P>klassieke varkenspest,</P><P>nodulaire dermatose;</P><P>schapen- en geitenbrucellose,</P><P>hondsdolheid,</P><P>salmonellose (zoönotische salmonella),</P><P>pest bij kleine herkauwers,</P><P>schapen- en geitenpokken,</P><P>overdraagbare spongiforme encefalopathieën (TSE),</P><P>Aanvragers moeten duidelijk vermelden in welke ziekte zij gespecialiseerd zijn. Zie F voor de selectiecriteria.</P><P>Contracten ondertekend in het kader van deze oproep tot aanvragen zullen standaardcontracten zijn met een dagtarief van 450 EUR. Reis-, verblijfs- en andere kosten worden vergoed volgens de standaardregels van de Commissie (2). In de regel zal het totaal van de opdrachten de 30 dagen per jaar niet overschrijden.</P><P>Het dagtarief van 450 EUR kan jaarlijks of tweejaarlijks worden herzien.</P><P>(1) Verordening (EU) nr. 652/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 15.5.2014 tot vaststelling van bepalingen betreffende het beheer van de uitgaven in verband met de voedselketen, diergezondheid en dierenwelzijn, alsmede in verband met plantgezondheid en teeltmateriaal, tot wijziging van de Richtlijnen van de Raad van 98/56/EG, 2000/29/EG en 2008/90/EG, Verordeningen (EG) nr. 178/2002, (EG) nr. 882/2004 en (EG) nr. 396/2005 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad, Richtlijn 2009/128/EG van het Europees Parlement en de Raad en Verordening (EG) nr. 1107/2009 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad en tot intrekking van de Besluiten 66/399/EG, 76/894/EEG en 2009/470/EG van de Raad. PB L 189, 27.6.2014, blz. 11.</P><P>(2) Besluit van de Commissie van 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plaats van uitvoering:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Het werk zal extern (bijv. op het vaste of officiële adres van de deskundige) en in de kantoren van de Europese Commissie worden uitgevoerd.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uitsluitingscriteria:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Om in de lijst te worden opgenomen, moeten aanvragers de verklaring op erewoord ondertekenen die ze kunnen vinden in het formulier.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Selectiecriteria:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Om in de lijst te worden opgenomen, moeten de aanvragers:</P><P>— een diploma diergeneeskunde hebben,</P><P>— zeer goed Engels kunnen spreken en schrijven,</P><P>— basiskennis IT hebben,</P><P>— minstens 5 jaar,</P><P>—— ofwel professionele vaardigheden en ervaring inzake het beheer en de tenuitvoerlegging van programma's voor bestrijding, monitoring en uitroeiing van minstens een van de hierboven genoemde ziekten, ofwel</P><P>—— beroepservaring in epidemiologie met betrekking tot minstens een van de bovenstaande dierenziekten.</P><P>Wetenschappelijke publicaties over de bovenstaande ziekten en goede taalvaardigheid in andere talen naast het Engels vormen een pluspunt.</P><P>Vóór de ondertekening van het contract moeten de geselecteerde gegadigden een verklaring ondertekenen waarin zij bevestigen dat zij geen belangenconflict hebben voor de betrokken evaluatie en dat zij de Commissie onverwijld zullen inlichten als een dergelijk belangenconflict zich in de loop van de evaluatie zou voordoen. Er is een belangenconflict wanneer de onpartijdige en objectieve uitoefening van de functies van een evaluator in gevaar wordt gebracht om redenen in verband met familie, emotioneel leven, politieke of nationale affiniteit, economisch belang of elk ander gemeenschappelijk belang met de ingediende programma's. Tijdens het evaluatieproces moeten de evaluators blijk geven van voldoende toewijding aan hun taak en moeten ze de informatie en documenten waarvan ze tijdens het proces kennis krijgen vertrouwelijk behandelen.</P><P>De gegadigden kunnen worden gevraagd ondersteunende documenten voor te leggen (i.e. kopie van een universitair diploma en certificaten van de werkervaring). Indien deze niet beschikbaar zijn, leidt dit tot de verwerping van de aanvraag.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informatie betreffende het aanvraagformulier:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Het in te vullen formulier is te vinden op de volgende website:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Het formulier moet worden opgeslagen naar de harde schijf, ingevuld en verzonden door te klikken op de desbetreffende knop.</P><P>In geval van problemen met het downloaden van het formulier (vanwege incompatibiliteit van de software, enz.), mail dan naar sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Het systeem staat niet toe dat een indiening wordt verzonden die onvolledig is.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Overige inlichtingen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De lijst van de geselecteerde deskundigen zal 1 jaar geldig blijven vanaf de datum van bekendmaking van de oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling in het Publicatieblad.</P><P>Geïnteresseerde personen mogen tijdens de hele geldigheidstermijn van de lijst een aanvraag indienen, met uitzondering van de laatste 3 maanden van die termijn.</P><P>Gegadigden mogen hun aanvraag op elk moment tijdens de geldigheidstermijn intrekken door dit schriftelijk aan de aanbestedende dienst te melden.</P><P>Alle aanvragers zullen ervan op de hoogte worden gebracht of ze al dan niet op de lijst zijn opgenomen.</P><P>Voor de evaluatie van de programma's van een bepaald jaar N moet het beoogde werk worden uitgevoerd tussen de tweede helft van juni en het einde van juli van jaar N-1. De deskundigen moeten gedurende deze periode minstens 2 weken beschikbaar zijn voor het uitvoeren van de evaluatie en voor het deelnemen aan een vergadering in DG Gezondheid en Voedselveiligheid te Brussel (deskundigen die bij meerdere ziekten betrokken zijn, moeten meer dan 1 dag in Brussel incalculeren).</P><P>Voor de evaluatie van programma's voor 2019 worden enkel de aanvragen ingediend vóór 31.3.2018 in overweging genomen.</P><P>Zodra de gegadigden zijn geselecteerd, mogen ze niet opnieuw een aanvraag indienen.</P><P>De Europese Commissie zal erop toezien dat de evaluatiepanels die worden gevormd op basis van de lijst van deskundigen van deze oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling evenwichtig worden samengesteld en dat er voldoende rotatie van deskundigen is. Zowel de geografische oorsprong als de professionele achtergrond van de aanvragers zal in acht worden genomen. De Europese Commissie streeft ook naar een evenwichtige deelname van mannen en vrouwen.</P><P>De follow-up van uw reactie op deze oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling vereist het registreren en verder verwerken van persoonlijke gegevens (zoals uw naam, adres en cv). Deze gegevens zullen worden verwerkt overeenkomstig Verordening (EG) nr. 45/2001 betreffende de bescherming van natuurlijke personen in verband met de verwerking van persoonsgegevens door de communautaire instellingen en organen en betreffende het vrije verkeer van die gegevens. Tenzij anders vermeld, zijn antwoorden op vragen en de vereiste persoonsgegevens noodzakelijk voor de beoordeling van uw aanvraag en zullen deze alleen worden beheerd door DG Gezondheid en Voedselveiligheid, eenheid D4. U kunt inzage vragen in uw persoonsgegevens om foute of onvolledige gegevens te verbeteren. Mocht u vragen hebben met betrekking tot de verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens, dan kunt u zich wenden tot DG Gezondheid en Voedselveiligheid, eenheid D4, op het volgende adres: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu Met betrekking tot de verwerking van uw persoonsgegevens heeft u te allen tijde het recht een beroep te doen op de Europese toezichthouder op gegevensbescherming op het volgende adres: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>De aanbestedende dienst zal regelmatig de lijst van deskundigen die een contract hebben ondertekend met de Europese Commissie op haar website bekendmaken.</P><P>Alle aanvragen voor bijkomende informatie kunnen worden gestuurd naar: sante-ami-prog-d4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum van verzending van de aankondiging door DG Gezondheid en Voedselveiligheid:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum van ontvangst door het Bureau voor officiële publicaties:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelas: Convite à manifestação de interesse para a elaboração de uma lista de peritos externos para a avaliação de programas de vigilância, controlo e erradicação de doenças animais e de zoonoses.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Comissão Europeia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Endereço eletrónico: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>O presente anúncio consiste num convite à manifestação de interesse</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>As pessoas singulares que desejam candidatar-se são convidadas a fazê-lo em conformidade com as disposições do presente anúncio.</P><P>O presente concurso deverá permitir aos serviços da Comissão, após análise das candidaturas apresentadas, elaborar uma lista de peritos aos quais possa ser adjudicado um contrato nos domínios descritos no ponto C.</P><P>Sempre que tenha de ser realizada uma atividade de avaliação relacionada com uma das doenças mencionadas a seguir, a entidade adjudicante convidará todos os candidatos inscritos na lista ou apenas alguns deles com base em critérios de seleção objetivos e não discriminatórios específicos à avaliação concreta.</P><P>A inclusão na lista não vincula juridicamente a Comissão Europeia a adjudicar um contrato.</P><P>Será elaborada uma lista de peritos para cada uma das doenças mencionadas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição exaustiva dos domínios abrangidos pelo convite à manifestação de interesse</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O artigo 9.º do Regulamento (UE) n.º 652/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho (1) prevê a contribuição financeira da União para a execução de programas nacionais de vigilância, controlo e erradicação de certas doenças animais e zoonoses.</P><P>A Comissão deverá avaliar estes programas, apresentados pelos Estados-Membros todos os anos, a partir dos pontos de vista veterinário e financeiro.</P><P>A fim de fornecer uma ferramenta adicional para a avaliação dos programas, a Comissão pretende contratar assistência técnica externa para realizar uma pré-avaliação dos programas apresentados pelos Estados-Membros para 2019.</P><P>Procuramos assistência externa para a avaliação dos programas relacionados com as seguintes doenças:</P><P>Peste suína africana,</P><P>Gripe aviária,</P><P>Febre catarral ovina (língua azul),</P><P>Brucelose bovina,</P><P>Tuberculose bovina,</P><P>Peste suína clássica,</P><P>Dermatite nodular contagiosa,</P><P>Brucelose ovina e caprina,</P><P>Raiva,</P><P>Salmonelose (salmonela zoonótica),</P><P>Peste dos pequenos ruminantes,</P><P>Varíola ovina e caprina,</P><P>Encefalopatia espongiforme transmissível (EET),</P><P>Os candidatos devem indicar claramente em que doença são especializados. Consultar o ponto F para os critérios de seleção.</P><P>Os contratos assinados no âmbito do presente convite à apresentação de propostas serão contratos-tipo de tarefas celebrados com uma taxa diária de 450 EUR (quatrocentos e cinquenta euros). As despesas de viagem, subsistência e outras despesas serão reembolsadas de acordo com as regras normalizadas da Comissão (2). De modo geral, os contratos não devem exceder cumulativamente 30 dias por ano.</P><P>A taxa diária de 450 EUR poderá estar sujeita a revisão anual ou bianual.</P><P>(1) Regulamento (UE) n.º 652/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 15.5.2014, que estabelece disposições para a gestão das despesas relacionadas com a cadeia alimentar, a saúde e o bem-estar animal, a fitossanidade e o material de reprodução vegetal, que altera as Diretivas do Conselho 98/56/CE, 2000/29/CE e 2008/90/CE, Regulamentos (CE) n.º 178/2002, (CE) n.º 882/2004 e (CE) n.º 396/2005 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, a Diretiva 2009/128/CE do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho e o Regulamento (CE) n.º 1107/2009 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho e que revoga as Decisões do Conselho 66/399/CEE, 76/894/CEE e 2009/470/CE. OJ L 189, 27.6.2014, p. 11.</P><P>(2) Decisão da Comissão de 5.12.2007 [DOC C (2007) 5858].</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Local de trabalho</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O local de trabalho será um local remoto (por exemplo, o endereço oficial ou permanente do perito) e os gabinetes da Comissão Europeia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critérios de exclusão</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De modo a serem incluídos na lista, os candidatos devem preencher a apresentação de candidatura, que se encontra no formulário.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critérios de seleção</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De modo a serem incluídos na lista, os candidatos deverão possuir:</P><P>— um diploma em Medicina Veterinária,</P><P>— excelente domínio de inglês, a nível oral e escrito,</P><P>— conhecimentos informáticos básicos,</P><P>— um mínimo de cinco anos de,</P><P>—— experiência e competências profissionais na gestão e implementação de programas de erradicação, controlo e vigilância para, pelo menos, uma das doenças acima referidas; ou,</P><P>—— experiência profissional em epidemiologia relacionada com, pelo menos, uma das doenças animais enumeradas acima.</P><P>A publicação de documentos científicos relacionados com as doenças supramencionadas e boas competências linguísticas noutra língua, para além do inglês, serão consideradas uma vantagem.</P><P>Antes de assinarem o contrato, os candidatos selecionados terão de assinar uma declaração que comprove a ausência de conflito de interesses para a avaliação visada e que informarão, de imediato, a Comissão caso surja algum conflito de interesses durante o decorrer da avaliação. Verifica-se uma situação de conflito de interesses quando o exercício imparcial e objetivo das funções de um avaliador é comprometido devido a motivos familiares, vida emocional, afinidade política ou nacional, interesse económico ou qualquer outro interesse partilhado com os programas apresentados. Ao longo do processo de avaliação, os avaliadores devem demonstrar uma dedicação apropriada à tarefa e observar a confidencialidade da informação e dos documentos aos quais tiverem acesso durante o processo.</P><P>Os candidatos poderão ter de apresentar documentos comprovativos (ou seja, cópia do diploma universitário e certificados de experiência profissional). A indisponibilidade dos mesmos resultará na rejeição da candidatura.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informações relativas ao formulário de candidatura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O formulário a preencher poderá ser obtido no seguinte endereço Web:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Este formulário deve ser guardado no disco rígido, preenchido e enviado clicando no botão correspondente.</P><P>Em caso de dificuldades de descarregamento do formulário (devido a incompatibilidade de software, etc.), deverá enviar uma mensagem eletrónica para o endereço: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>O sistema não permitirá enviar uma candidatura incompleta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Outras informações</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A lista dos peritos selecionados será válida durante 1 ano a contar da data de publicação do convite à manifestação de interesse no Jornal Oficial.</P><P>Os interessados podem apresentar a sua candidatura em qualquer momento durante o período de validade da lista, exceto nos três últimos meses desse período.</P><P>Os candidatos podem retirar a sua candidatura a qualquer momento durante o período de validade da lista mediante notificação por escrito à entidade adjudicante.</P><P>Todos os candidatos serão informados sobre a sua inclusão ou não na lista.</P><P>Para a avaliação dos programas de um determinado ano N, o trabalho previsto deve ser feito entre a segunda metade de junho e finais de julho do ano N-1. Os peritos devem estar disponíveis por um período mínimo de duas semanas durante este período para efetuar a avaliação e devem estar disponíveis para participar numa reunião na DG SANTE em Bruxelas (os peritos envolvidos em várias doenças devem permanecer mais de um dia em Bruxelas).</P><P>Para a avaliação de programas de 2019, serão consideradas apenas as candidaturas apresentadas até 31.3.2018.</P><P>Após serem selecionados, os candidatos não podem apresentar novamente uma candidatura.</P><P>A Comissão Europeia deverá garantir que os painéis de avaliação, estabelecidos com base na lista de peritos elaborada na sequência deste convite à manifestação de interesse, são constituídos de modo equilibrado e garantir uma rotação apropriada dos peritos. A origem geográfica dos candidatos, bem como o histórico profissional serão tomados em consideração. A Comissão Europeia pretende ainda a participação equilibrada de homens e mulheres.</P><P>O acompanhamento da sua resposta ao convite à manifestação de interesse irá requerer o registo e o processamento posterior de dados pessoais (tais como o nome, endereço, currículo). Estes dados serão tratados em conformidade com o Regulamento (CE) n.º 45/2001 relativo à proteção das pessoas singulares no que diz respeito ao tratamento de dados pessoais pelas instituições e pelos órgãos comunitários e à livre circulação desses dados. Exceto indicação em contrário, as respostas às questões e os dados pessoais exigidos são necessários para fins de avaliação da sua candidatura e serão geridos apenas pela DG SANTE, Unidade D4. Poderá, a pedido, obter uma descrição dos seus dados pessoais e retificar qualquer informação pessoal imprecisa ou incompleta. Se tiver qualquer questão sobre o processamento dos seus dados pessoais, recorra à DG SANTE, Unidade D4 pelo seguinte endereço: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu No que diz respeito ao processamento dos seus dados pessoais, poderá recorrer em qualquer momento à Autoridade Europeia para a Proteção de Dados pelo seguinte endereço: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>A entidade adjudicante publicará periodicamente no seu sítio Web a lista de peritos que assinaram um contrato com a Comissão Europeia.</P><P>Todos os pedidos de informação suplementar deverão ser enviados para: sante-ami-prog-d4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data de envio do anúncio pela DG SANTE:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data de receção do anúncio pelo SPOCE:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: Uppmaning till intresseanmälan för upprättandet av en förteckning över externa experter för bedömning av program för utrotning, bekämpning och övervakning av djursjukdomar och zoonoser.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska kommissionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, E-post: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Detta meddelande är en uppmaning till intresseanmälan</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fysiska personer som önskar ansöka uppmanas att göra detta i enlighet med bestämmelserna i detta meddelande.</P><P>Efter granskning av de inlämnade ansökningarna ska kommissionens avdelningar med hjälp av detta meddelande kunna upprätta en förteckning över experter som kan komma att tilldelas ett kontrakt inom de områden som anges i punkt C.</P><P>Varje gång en bedömningsverksamhet med anknytning till en av de sjukdomar som anges nedan ska utföras kommer den upphandlande myndigheten att bjuda in antingen alla sökande i förteckningen eller endast vissa av dem på grundval av objektiva och icke-diskriminerande uttagningskriterier som är specifika för den konkreta bedömningen.</P><P>Att en sökande tas med i förteckningen innebär inte att Europeiska kommissionen har någon juridisk skyldighet att tilldela ett kontrakt.</P><P>En förteckning över experter kommer att upprättas för varje angiven sjukdom.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uttömmande beskrivning av föremålen för denna uppmaning till intresseanmälan</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Artikel 9 i Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 652/2014 (1) föreskriver finansiella bidrag från unionen till genomförandet av nationella program för utrotning, bekämpning och övervakning av vissa djursjukdomar och zoonoser.</P><P>Kommissionen ska bedöma dessa program, som lämnas av medlemsstaterna varje år, utifrån veterinär och finansiell synvinkel.</P><P>I syfte att tillhandahålla ytterligare ett verktyg för bedömning av programmen söker kommissionen externt tekniskt stöd för att genomföra en förhandsbedömning av de program som lämnas av medlemsstaterna för 2019.</P><P>Externt stöd efterfrågas för utvärdering av de program som har anknytning till följande sjukdomar:</P><P>Afrikansk svinpest,</P><P>Aviär influensa,</P><P>Blåtunga,</P><P>Bovin brucellos,</P><P>Bovin tuberkulos,</P><P>Klassisk svinpest,</P><P>Lumpy skin disease,</P><P>Ovin och kaprin brucellos,</P><P>Rabies,</P><P>Salmonellos (zoonotisk salmonella),</P><P>Peste des petits ruminants (PPR),</P><P>Får- och getkoppor,</P><P>Transmissibel spongiform encefalopati (TSE),</P><P>Sökande ska tydligt ange de sjukdomar som de är specialiserade på. Se punkt F för uttagningskriterierna.</P><P>Kontrakt som tecknas inom ramen för denna ansökningsinfordran kommer att vara standardkontrakt för uppdrag och slutas med en dagersättning på 450 EUR (fyrahundra och femtio euro). Resor, uppehälle och andra kostnader kommer att ersättas enligt kommissionens standardregler (2). Kontrakten kommer som regel inte att vara längre än sammanlagt 30 dagar per år.</P><P>Dagersättningen på 450 EUR kan komma att ändras, årsvis eller halvårsvis.</P><P>(1) Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 652/2014 av den 15 maj 2014 om fastställande av bestämmelser för förvaltningen av utgifter för livsmedelskedjan, djurhälsa, djurskydd, växtskydd och växtförökningsmaterial, och om ändring av rådets direktiv 98/56/EG, 2000/29/EG och 2008/90/EG, Europaparlamentets och rådets förordningar (EG) nr 178/2002, (EG) nr 882/2004 och (EG) nr 396/2005, Europaparlamentets och rådets direktiv 2009/128/EG samt Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EG) nr 1107/2009, och om upphävande av rådets beslut 66/399/EEG, 76/894/EEG och 2009/470/EG. EUT L 189, 27.6.2014, s. 11.</P><P>(2) Kommissionens beslut av den 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plats för arbetet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Arbetet kommer att utföras på distans (t.ex. på expertens fasta eller officiella adress) och i Europeiska kommissionens kontor.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uteslutningskriterium</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>För att inkluderas i förteckningen ska sökande fylla i de uttalanden avseende inlämning av ansökning som återfinns i formuläret.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uttagningskriterier</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>För att inkluderas i förteckningen ska sökande ha följande:</P><P>— en examen i veterinärmedicin,</P><P>— mycket goda muntliga och skriftliga kunskaper i engelska,</P><P>— grundläggande IT-kunskap,</P><P>— minst 5 år av,</P><P>—— antingen yrkeskompetens och yrkeserfarenhet inom ledning och genomförande av program för bekämpning, övervakning och utrotning för minst en av de sjukdomar som anges ovan, eller,</P><P>—— yrkeserfarenhet i epidemiologi med anknytning till minst 1 av de djursjukdomar som anges ovan.</P><P>Vetenskapliga publikationer med anknytning till ovannämnda sjukdomar och goda språkkunskaper i andra språk än engelska utgör en fördel.</P><P>Före undertecknandet av kontraktet ska den utvalda sökande underteckna en försäkran som styrker att ingen intressekonflikt föreligger för utvärderingen i fråga och att denne utan dröjsmål kommer att informera kommissionen om en intressekonflikt skulle uppstå under utvärderingens gång. En intressekonflikt föreligger om det opartiska och objektiva genomförandet av utvärderarens arbetsuppgifter äventyras av skäl som inbegriper familjeband, känsloliv, politisk eller nationell samhörighet, ekonomiska intressen eller något annat gemensamt intresse med de inlämnade programmen. Utvärderarna ska under hela utvärderingsförfarandet kunna uppvisa lämplig yrkesetik och att visa att de respekterar sekretessen vad gäller information och handlingar som de tar del av under förfarandet.</P><P>Den sökande kan komma att uppmanas att lämna styrkande handlingar (dvs. kopia på universitetsexamen och intyg på arbetslivserfarenhet). Om dessa inte görs tillgängliga kommer detta att leda till att ansökan avslås.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Information om ansökningsformuläret</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Formuläret som ska fyllas i kan hämtas från följande webbadress:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Formuläret ska sparas på hårddisken, fyllas i och sändas genom att klicka på motsvarande knapp.</P><P>Om problem uppstår vid nedladdningen av formuläret (p.g.a. programinkompatibilitet etc.) uppmanas sökande att skicka ett e-postmeddelande till sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Systemet kommer inte tillåta att ett ofullständigt ifyllt formulär skickas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kompletterande upplysningar</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Förteckningen över utvalda experter kommer att vara giltig i 1 år från datumet för publicering av uppmaningen till intresseanmälan i Europeiska unionens officiella tidning.</P><P>Intresserade personer kan lämna en ansökan när som helst under förteckningens giltighetstid med undantag för de sista 3 månaderna av denna period.</P><P>Sökande kan återkalla sin ansökan vid vilken tidpunkt som helst under förteckningens giltighetstid genom skriftligt meddelande till den upphandlande myndigheten.</P><P>Alla sökande kommer att informeras om de har tagits med i förteckningen eller inte.</P><P>För utvärdering av programmen för ett visst år N ska det arbete som planeras utföras mellan andra hälften av juni och slutet av juli år N-1. Experterna ska vara tillgängliga för minst 2 veckor under denna period för att utföra utvärderingen och ska kunna närvara vid ett möte vid GD Hälsa och livsmedelssäkerhet i Bryssel (experter som arbetar med flera sjukdomar ska räkna med mer än 1 dag i Bryssel).</P><P>För utvärderingen av 2019 års program kommer endast ansökningar som lämnas senast den 31.3.2018 att beaktas.</P><P>Utvalda sökande ska inte lämna in en ny ansökan.</P><P>Europeiska kommissionen kommer att se till att utvärderingspanelerna som upprättas utifrån förteckningen över experter från denna uppmaning till intresseanmälan får en balanserad sammansättning och att rotationen av dessa experter sker på ett lämpligt sätt. Sökandes geografiska ursprung samt yrkesbakgrund kommer att beaktas. Europeiska kommissionen söker även ett balanserat deltagande av män och kvinnor.</P><P>Uppföljning av de sökandes svar på uppmaningen till intresseanmälan kräver att personuppgifter (såsom namn, adress och meritförteckning) registreras och behandlas vidare. Dessa uppgifter kommer att behandlas i enlighet med reglerna i Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EG) nr 45/2001 av den 18 december 2000 om skydd för enskilda då gemenskapsinstitutionerna och gemenskapsorganen behandlar personuppgifter och om den fria rörligheten för sådana uppgifter. Om inte annat nämns krävs svar på frågor samt de erfordrade personuppgifterna för att ansökan ska kunna utvärderas. Denna information kommer endast att handhas av GD Hälsa och livsmedelssäkerhet, enhet SANTE/D4. Den sökande kan på begäran erhålla ett utdrag ur sina personuppgifter och rätta felaktiga eller ofullständiga personuppgifter i detta. Eventuella frågor om behandling av personuppgifter ska skickas till GD Hälsa och livsmedelssäkerhet, enhet D4 på följande adress: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu Vad gäller behandling av personuppgifter har den sökande rätt att när som helst vända sig till Europeiska datatillsynsmannen på följande e-postadress: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Den upphandlande myndigheten kommer på sin webbplats periodvis att publicera förteckningen över experter som har tecknat ett kontrakt med Europeiska kommissionen.</P><P>Alla begäranden om ytterligare information kan sändas till: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum för avsändande av meddelandet av GD Hälsa och livsmedelssäkerhet:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum för mottagande av meddelandet av Publikationsbyrån:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: Výzva k vyjádření zájmu ve vztahu k sestavování seznamu externích odborníků pro posouzení programů vymýcení, kontroly a sledování nemocí zvířat a zoonóz.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zadavatel:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská komise</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgie.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Toto oznámení je výzvou k vyjádření zájmu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fyzické osoby, které mají v úmyslu podat přihlášku, se tímto vyzývají, aby tak učinily v souladu s ustanoveními tohoto oznámení.</P><P>Tato výzva by měla službám Komise umožnit, aby po prozkoumání podaných přihlášek sestavily seznam odborníků, kterým by mohly být zadávány zakázky v oblastech popsaných v bodě C.</P><P>Pokaždé, když nastane nutnost provedení hodnotící činnosti ve vztahu k 1 z nemocí uvedených níže, vyzve veřejný zadavatel všechny uchazeče zařazené na seznam nebo jen některé z nich vybrané na základě objektivních a nediskriminačních kritérií pro výběr týkajících se tohoto konkrétního hodnocení.</P><P>Ze samotného zařazení na seznam nevyplývá Evropské komisi žádný závazek zadat zakázku.</P><P>V případě každé ze zmiňovaných nemocí bude sestaven seznam odborníků.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vyčerpávající popis problematik řešených touto výzvou k vyjádření zájmu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Článek 9 nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 652/2014 (1) stanovuje finanční příspěvek Unie na provádění národních programů pro vymýcení, kontrolu a sledování určitých chorob zvířat a zoonóz.</P><P>Komise posoudí tyto programy předkládané každoročně ze strany členských států, a to z veterinárního a finančního hlediska.</P><P>S cílem poskytnout další nástroj na hodnocení programů Komise hledá externí technickou pomoc na provedení předběžného posouzení programů předkládaných členskými státy pro rok 2019.</P><P>Poptáváme externí pomoc pro vyhodnocení programů týkajících se těchto chorob:</P><P>africký prasečí mor,</P><P>ptačí chřipka,</P><P>katarální horečka ovcí,</P><P>brucelóza skotu,</P><P>tuberkulóza skotu,</P><P>klasický prasečí mor,</P><P>nodulární dermatitida skotu,</P><P>brucelóza ovcí a koz,</P><P>vzteklina,</P><P>salmonelóza (zoonotická salmonela),</P><P>mor ovcí a koz,</P><P>neštovice ovcí a koz,</P><P>přenosné spongiformní encefalopatie (TSE).</P><P>Uchazeči by měli jasně uvést chorobu, na kterou se specializují. Výběrová kritéria viz bod F.</P><P>Smlouvy podepsané v rámci této výzvy k podání přihlášek budou standardními smlouvami na provedení úkolu uzavřenými s denní sazbou 450 EUR (čtyři sta padesát euro). Cestovné, diety a další náklady budou propláceny dle standardních pravidel Komise (2). Smlouvy zpravidla kumulativně nepřesáhnou rozsah 30 dní ročně.</P><P>Denní sazba 450 EUR může být předmětem roční nebo pololetní úpravy.</P><P>(1) Nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 652/2014 ze dne 15.5.2014, kterým se stanoví pravidla pro řízení výdajů v oblasti potravinového řetězce, zdraví a dobrých životních podmínek zvířat a zdraví rostlin a rozmnožovacího materiálu rostlin, kterým se mění směrnice Rady 98/56/ES, 2000/29/ES a 2008/90/ES, nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (ES) č. 178/2002, (ES) č. 882/2004 a (ES) č. 396/2005, směrnice Evropského parlamentu a Rady 2009/128/ES a nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (ES) č. 1107/2009 a kterým se zrušují rozhodnutí Rady 66/399/EHS, 76/894/EHS a 2009/470/ES. Úř. věst. L 189, 27.6.2014, s. 11.</P><P>(2) Rozhodnutí Komise ze dne 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Místo práce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Místem práce bude vzdálené místo (např. trvalé nebo úřední sídlo daného odborníka), a kanceláře Evropské komise.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kritérium pro vyloučení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aby mohli být uchazeči zařazeni na seznam, musí vyplnit prohlášení o podání přihlášek, které naleznou ve formuláři.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kritéria pro výběr uchazečů</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aby mohli být uchazeči zahrnuti do seznamu, budou disponovat:</P><P>— vysokoškolským vzděláním v oboru veterinárního lékařství,</P><P>— velmi dobrou znalostí mluvené a psané angličtiny,</P><P>— základními znalostmi v oblasti informatiky,</P><P>— alespoň pěti lety:</P><P>—— buďto odbornými dovednostmi a praxí v oblasti řízení a provádění programů pro vymycování, kontrolu a sledování v případě alespoň 1 z výše uvedených chorob nebo</P><P>—— odbornou praxí v oboru epidemiologie ve vztahu k alespoň 1 z chorob zvířat uvedených výše.</P><P>Na vědecké publikace týkající se výše uvedených chorob a dobré znalosti jiných jazyků než angličtina bude pohlíženo jako na výhodu.</P><P>Před podpisem smlouvy budou muset vybraní uchazeči podepsat prohlášení potvrzující, že se nenacházejí v situaci střetu zájmů v případě daného hodnocení a že budou bez prodlení informovat Komisi v případě, že takový střet zájmů vznikne v průběhu hodnocení. Střet zájmů vzniká v okamžiku, kdy dojde k ohrožení nestranného a objektivního výkonu funkcí hodnotitele z důvodů souvisejících s rodinným, citovým životem, politickou nebo národní spřízněností, ekonomickými zájmy nebo jinými sdílenými zájmy s předkládanými programy. Po celou dobu hodnotícího procesu musí být hodnotitelé prokázat, že se náležitě věnují svým pracovním povinnostem, a dodržovat důvěrnost informací a dokumentů, které se dostanou do jejich povědomí během procesu.</P><P>Uchazeči mohou být vyzváni k předložení dokladů (tj. kopií vysokoškolských diplomů a osvědčení o pracovní praxi). Pokud tyto nepředloží, bude daná přihláška zamítnuta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informace o formuláři přihlášky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Formulář, který se má vyplnit, je k dispozici na této internetové adrese:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Tento formulář by měl být uložen na pevný disk, vyplněn a odeslán kliknutím na odpovídající tlačítko.</P><P>V případě problémů se stahováním formuláře (kvůli neslučitelnosti softwaru atd.) zašlete prosím e-mail na adresu sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Systém neumožní odeslání přihlášky, která je neúplná.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Další informace</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tento seznam vybraných odborníků bude platit po dobu 1 roku od data zveřejnění výzvy k vyjádření zájmu v Úředním věstníku.</P><P>Přihlášku může podat jakákoli osoba mající zájem, a to kdykoli během doby platnosti tohoto seznamu s výjimkou posledních 3 měsíců tohoto období.</P><P>Uchazeči mohou svou přihlášku odvolat kdykoliv během doby platnosti seznamu podáním písemného oznámení veřejnému zadavateli.</P><P>Všichni uchazeči budou informováni, zda byli na seznam zařazeni, či nikoli.</P><P>V případě hodnocení programů na daný rok N musí být plánovaná práce hotová mezi druhou polovinou června a koncem července roku N-1. Odborníci musí být k dispozici minimálně alespoň 2 týdny během tohoto období, aby provedli vyhodnocení, a musí být k dispozici, aby se zúčastnili jednání na Generálním ředitelství pro zdraví a bezpečnosti potravin v Bruselu (odborníci zapojení do práce týkající se několika chorob musí počítat s více než 1 dnem v Bruselu).</P><P>V případě hodnocení programů na rok 2019 budou brány do úvahy pouze přihlášky podané do 31.3.2018.</P><P>Jakmile budou uchazeči vybráni, nesmí již přihlášku podat znovu.</P><P>Komise zajistí, aby hodnotící poroty sestavené na základě seznamu odborníků pocházející z této výzvy k vyjádření zájmu byly sestaveny vyváženým způsobem a bylo zajištěno patřičné střídání odborníků. Bude zohledněn zeměpisný původ a odborné zázemí uchazečů. Evropská komise bude rovněž usilovat o vyvážené zastoupení mužů a žen.</P><P>Vyhodnocení vaší odpovědi na tuto výzvu k vyjádření zájmu si vyžádá záznam a další zpracování osobních údajů (jako například vašeho jména, adresy a životopisu). Tyto údaje budou zpracovávány v souladu s nařízením (ES) č. 45/2001 o ochraně fyzických osob v souvislosti se zpracováním osobních údajů orgány a institucemi Společenství a o volném pohybu těchto údajů. Není-li stanoveno jinak, jsou odpovědi na otázky a požadované osobní údaje nezbytně nutné pro účely vyhodnocení vaší přihlášky a budou spravovány pouze oddělením SANTE/D4. Na požádání můžete obdržet informace o svých osobních údajích a opravit případné nepřesnosti nebo neúplné osobní údaje. Pokud budete mít jakékoliv otázky týkající se zpracování vašich osobních údajů, zašlete je prosím oddělení SANTE/D4 na následující adresu: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu. V souvislosti se zpracováním vašich osobních údajů máte právo se kdykoliv obrátit na evropského inspektora ochrany údajů na následující adrese: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Veřejný zadavatel bude pravidelně zveřejňovat na své internetové stránce seznam odborníků, kteří podepsali smlouvu s Evropskou komisí.</P><P>Veškeré žádosti o další informace lze zasílat na adresu: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum odeslání oznámení Generálním ředitelstvím pro zdraví a bezpečnost potravin:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum přijetí oznámení Úřadem pro publikace Evropské unie:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: Huvi väljendamise kutse loomahaiguste ja zoonooside likvideerimise, tõrje ja seire programmide hindamise asutuseväliste ekspertide nimekirja koostamiseks</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaliku sektori hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Komisjon</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Käesolev teade on huvi väljendamise kutse</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Taotleda soovivatel füüsilistel isikutel palutakse seda teha käesoleva teate sätete kohaselt.</P><P>Käesolev kutse peab võimaldama komisjoni talitustel pärast esitatud taotluste läbivaatamist koostada nimekiri kandidaatidest, kellega oleks võimalik punktis C kirjeldatud valdkondades leping sõlmida.</P><P>Iga kord, kui tuleb ellu viia 1 allpool nimetatud haigusega seotud hindamise tegevus, saadab hankija kutse kas kõikidele nimekirja kantud kandidaatidele või ainult mõnele neist, tuginedes konkreetse hindamise erieesmärgile ja vastavatele objektiivsetele ja mittediskrimineerivatele valikukriteeriumidele.</P><P>Nimekirja kandmisega ei võta Euroopa Komisjon mingit juriidilist kohustust lepingut sõlmida.</P><P>Ekspertide nimekiri koostatakse iga nimetatud haiguse kohta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Huvi väljendamise kutsega hõlmatud valdkondade ammendav kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu määruse (EÜ) nr{b&gt; &lt;b}652/2014 artikkel 9 (1) näeb ette liidu rahalise toetuse liikmesriikide programmide elluviimiseks, mille eesmärk on teatud loomataudide ja zoonooside likvideerimine, tõrje ja seire.</P><P>Komisjon hindab liikmesriikide igal aastal esitatavaid programme nii veterinaarsest kui ka rahalisest küljest.</P><P>Komisjon soovib programmide hindamise lisatööriistana saada asutusevälist tehnilist abi liikmesriikide esitatavate 2019. aasta programmide eelhindamiseks.</P><P>Hankija soovib saada järgmiste haigustega seotud programmide hindamiseks asutusevälist abi:</P><P>sigade aafrika katk;</P><P>linnugripp;</P><P>lammaste katarraalne palavik;</P><P>veiste brutselloos;</P><P>veiste tuberkuloos;</P><P>sigade klassikaline katk;</P><P>nodulaarne dermatiit,</P><P>lammaste ja kitsede brutselloos;</P><P>marutaud;</P><P>salmonelloos (zoonootiline salmonelloos);</P><P>lammaste ja kitsede katk;</P><P>lammaste ja kitsede rõuged;</P><P>transmissiivsed spongioossed entsefalopaatiad (TSE).</P><P>Taotlejad peavad selgelt märkima, millisele haigusele nad spetsialiseeruvad. Vt valikukriteeriumide punkti F.</P><P>Käesoleva taotluste kutse alusel allkirjastatud lepingud on ülesannete tüüplepingud, mis sõlmitakse päevatasuga 450 EUR (nelisada viiskümmend eurot). Reisi-, elamis- ja muud kulud hüvitatakse komisjoni tüüpeeskirjade kohaselt (2).Lepingute kogukestus ei ole üldreeglina üle 30 päeva aastas. </P><P>Päevatasu 450 EUR võidakse muuta 1 või 2 korda aastas.</P><P>(1) Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 15.5.2014 määrus (EL) nr 652/2014, millega nähakse ette sätted toiduahela, loomade tervise ja heaolu ning taimetervise ja taimse paljundusmaterjaliga seotud kulude haldamise kohta ning muudetakse nõukogu direktiive 98/56/EÜ, 2000/29/EÜ ja 2008/90/EÜ, Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu määruseid (EÜ) nr 178/2002, (EÜ) nr 882/2004 ja (EÜ) nr 396/2005, Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu direktiivi 2009/128/EÜ ja Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu määrust (EÜ) nr 1107/2009 ning tunnistatakse kehtetuks nõukogu otsused 66/399/EMÜ, 76/894/EMÜ ja 2009/470/EÜ.ELT L 189, 27.6.2014, lk 11. </P><P>(2) Komisjoni 5.12.2007 otsus (dokument K(2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Töö tegemise koht</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tööde tegemise koht on eemalasuv koht (nt eksperdi elu- või töökoha aadress) ja Euroopa Komisjoni büroo.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kõrvalejätmiskriteerium</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Et taotlejad kantaks nimekirja, peavad nad täitma vormile lisatud taotluse esitamise avaldused.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Valikukriteeriumid</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Taotlejate nimekirja kandmiseks peab (peavad) neil olema</P><P>– diplom loomaarstiteaduses;</P><P>– väga hea kirjaliku ja suulise inglise keele oskus;</P><P>– algteadmised informaatikast;</P><P>– vähemalt viie aasta jooksul omandatud</P><P>—— kas kutseoskused ja -kogemused vähemalt 1 eespool nimetatud haiguse likvideerimise, tõrje ja seire programmi juhtimise ja rakendamise valdkonnas või</P><P>—— kutsekogemused vähemalt 1 eespool nimetatud loomahaiguse epidemioloogia valdkonnas.</P><P>Eeliseks peetakse eespool nimetatud haigusi käsitlevaid avaldatud teadustöid ja muu kui inglise keele head oskust.</P><P>Enne lepingu allkirjastamist peavad valitud kandidaadid allkirjastama kinnituse selle kohta, et neil ei ole kõnealuse hindamise puhul huvide konflikti ja et nad teavitavad komisjoni viivitamata, kui selline huvide konflikt peaks hindamise käigus tekkima. Huvide konfliktiga on tegemist siis, kui hindaja töökohustuste erapooletut ja objektiivset täitmist ohustavad perekondlikud, emotsionaalsed, poliitilisel või rahvuslikul määratlusel põhinevad huvid ning majandushuvid või muud esitatud programmidega seotud ühised huvid. Kogu hindamisprotsessi käigus peavad hindajad pühenduma korrakohaselt ülesannete täitmisele ning järgima töö käigus nendeni jõudnud teabe ja neile esitatud dokumentide konfidentsiaalsuse nõuet.</P><P>Kandidaatidelt võidakse nõuda alusdokumentide (s.o ülikoolidiplomi koopia ja töökogemuste tõendite koopiate) esitamist.Nende kättesaadamatuse korral lükatakse taotlus tagasi. </P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Taotlusvormi käsitlev teave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Täidetava vormi leiate veebiaadressil</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>See vorm tuleb salvestada kõvakettale, täita ja saata ära vastavale nupule klõpsamisega.</P><P>Juhul kui vormi allalaadimisel tekivad tõrked (tarkvara ühildumatuse vms tõttu), palume saata kiri e-posti teel aadressil sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Süsteem ei luba esitada pooleliolevat dokumenti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Muu teave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Valitud ekspertide nimekiri kehtib 1 aastat alates huvi väljendamise kutse avaldamisest Euroopa Liidu Teatajas.</P><P>Mis tahes huvitatud isik võib esitada taotluse mis tahes ajal nimekirja kehtivuse jooksul, välja arvatud kehtivusaja viimasel 3 kuul.</P><P>Kandidaadid võivad mis tahes ajal nimekirja kehtivuse jooksul oma taotluse tagasi võtta, saates hankijale kirjaliku teate.</P><P>Kõiki taotlejaid teavitatakse sellest, kas nad on kantud nimekirja või mitte.</P><P>Vaadeldava aasta N programmide hindamiseks ettenähtud töö tuleb ära teha vahemikus aasta N–1 juuni 2. poolest kuni juuli 1. pooleni. Eksperdid peavad olema nimetatud ajavahemiku jooksul vähemalt 2 nädala vältel kättesaadavad, et teha hindamist. Ühtlasi peavad eksperdid olema valmis osalema koosolekutel tervise ja toiduohutuse peadirektoraadis Brüsselis (mitme haigusega seotud eksperdid peavad arvestama rohkem kui 1 Brüsselis veedetava päevaga).</P><P>2019. aasta programmide hindamiseks võetakse arvesse ainult hiljemalt 31.3.2018 esitatud taotlusi.</P><P>Juba valitud kandidaadid ei tohi taotlust uuesti esitada.</P><P>Euroopa Komisjon tagab selle, et hindamiskogud, mis moodustatakse käesoleva huvi väljendamise kutse alusel koostatud ekspertide nimekirjale tuginedes, on moodustatud tasakaalustatult ning et toimib ekspertide korrakohane rotatsioon. Arvesse võetakse nii taotlejate geograafilist päritolu kui ka erialast tausta. Euroopa Komisjon üritab samuti hoida tasakaalu mees- ja naissoost osalejate vahel.</P><P>Huvi väljendamise kutsele saadetud vastuse jätkuvaks käsitlemiseks on vajalik salvestada ja edasi töödelda isikuandmeid (nt taotleja nimi, aadress, elulookirjeldus). Nimetatud andmeid töödeldakse kooskõlas määruse (EÜ) nr 45/2001 üksikisikute kaitse kohta isikuandmete töötlemisel ühenduse institutsioonides ja asutustes ning selliste andmete vaba liikumise kohta nõuetega. Juhul kui ei ole nimetatud teisiti, on nõutud vastused küsimustele ja isikuandmed vajalikud teie taotluse hindamiseks. Nimetatud teavet haldab vaid tervise ja toiduohutuse peadirektoraadi üksus D4. Nõudmisel saate oma isikuandmete kohta teavet ja võite parandada neis esinevaid ebatäpsusi või puudujääke. Kui teil peaks tekkima küsimusi teie isikuandmete töötlemise kohta, palume esitada need tervise ja toiduohutuse peadirektoraadi üksusele D4 (aadressil sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu). Teie isikuandmete töötlemise küsimustes on teil õigus igal ajal pöörduda Euroopa Andmekaitseinspektori poole järgmisel elektronposti aadressil: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Avaliku sektori hankija avaldab oma veebisaidil korrapäraselt Euroopa Komisjoniga lepingu allkirjastanud ekspertide nimekirja.</P><P>Kõik taotlused täiendava teabe saamiseks võib saata aadressil sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tervise ja toiduohutuse peadirektoraadi poolt teate lähetamise kuupäev:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teate Euroopa Liidu Väljaannete Talitusse laekumise kuupäev:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüsszel: Szándéknyilatkozati felhívás külső szakértők listájának összeállítására az állatbetegségek és zoonózisok megszüntetésére, megfékezésére és felügyeletére irányuló programok értékelésére vonatkozóan.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európai Bizottság</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüsszel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ez a hirdetmény egy szándéknyilatkozati felhívás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kérjük azokat a természetes személyeket, akik részt kívánnak venni, hogy az e felhívásban foglalt előírásokkal összhangban jelentkezzenek.</P><P>E felhívásnak lehetővé kell tennie a Bizottság szolgálatai számára azt, hogy a benyújtott jelentkezések vizsgálata után összeállítsa azoknak a szakértőknek a listáját, akik részére a C pontban ismertetett területeken szerződés ítélhető oda.</P><P>Amikor az alább felsorolt betegségek valamelyikével kapcsolatos értékelési tevékenységet kell végezni, az ajánlatkérő a listán szereplő összes jelentkezőt, vagy az adott értékelésre vonatkozó objektív és nem diszkriminatív kiválasztási kritériumok alapján kiválasztott néhány jelentkezőt kér fel pályázatbenyújtásra.</P><P>A listára történő felvétel nem jelenti azt, hogy az Európai Bizottságnak jogi kötelezettsége lenne a szerződés odaítélésére vonatkozóan.</P><P>Minden egyes felsorolt betegségre szakértői listát állítanak össze.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szándéknyilatkozati felhívásban foglalt területek részletes bemutatása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A 652/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet 9. cikke (1) biztosítja a bizonyos állatbetegségek és zoonózisok megszüntetésére, megfékezésére és felügyeletére irányuló nemzeti programok megvalósításához szükséges pénzügyi hozzájárulást.</P><P>A Bizottság a tagállamok által évente benyújtott programokat állat-egészségügyi és pénzügyi szempontból is megvizsgálja.</P><P>Annak érdekében, hogy a program értékeléséhez egy további eszközt biztosítson, a Bizottság külső, szakmai segítségnyújtást keres a tagállamok által 2019-re benyújtott programok előzetes értékelésének elvégzésére.</P><P>Az alábbi betegségekkel kapcsolatos programok értékeléséhez kívánunk igénybe venni külső segítségnyújtást:</P><P>Afrikai sertéspestis,</P><P>Madárinfluenza,</P><P>Kéknyelv-betegség,</P><P>Szarvasmarha-brucellózis,</P><P>Szarvasmarha-tuberkulózis,</P><P>Klasszikus sertéspestis,</P><P>Bőrcsomósodáskór,</P><P>Juh- és kecskebrucellózis,</P><P>Veszettség,</P><P>Szalmonellózis (zoonózist okozó szalmonella),</P><P>Juh- és kecskepestis,</P><P>Juh- és kecskehimlő,</P><P>Fertőző szivacsos agyvelőbántalmak (TSE),</P><P>A jelentkezőknek egyértelműen meg kell adniuk, hogy mely betegség a szakterületük. Lásd a kiválasztási kritériumok F pontját.</P><P>Az e pályázati felhívás keretében aláírt szerződések standard megbízásos szerződések lesznek 450 EUR (négyszázötven euró) napidíjjal. Az utazási, ellátási és egyéb költségeket a szokásos bizottsági szabályok (2) alapján térítik meg. A szerződések volumene összességében általában nem haladja meg a 30 nap/évet.</P><P>Előfordulhat, hogy a 450 EUR összegű napidíjat éves vagy kétéves felülvizsgálatnak vetik alá.</P><P>(1) A 2000/29/EK, 2008/90/EK, a 178/2002/EK és a 882/2004/EK tanácsi irányelv, a 396/2005/EK, a 2009/128/EK és a 1107/2009/EK európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet, a 66/399/EK európai parlamenti és tanácsi irányelv, valamint a 76/894/EGK és a 2009/470/EK tanácsi határozat hatályon kívül helyezéséről szóló 98/56/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet módosításáról szóló, 15.5.2014 keltezésű 652/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet (az élelmiszerlánccal, az állategészségüggyel és állatjóléttel, valamint a növényegészségüggyel és a növényi szaporítóanyagokkal kapcsolatos kiadások kezelésére vonatkozó rendelkezések megállapításáról). HL L 189., 27.6.2014, 11. o.</P><P>(2) 5.12.2007 keltezésű bizottsági határozat (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Munkavégzés helye</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A munkavégzés helye egy külső helyszín (pl. a szakértő állandó vagy hivatalos címe) és az Európai Bizottság irodái.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kizárási kritériumok</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A listára való felvétel érdekében a jelentkezőknek ki kell tölteniük a formanyomtatványhoz csatolt jelentkezésbenyújtási nyilatkozatokat.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kiválasztási kritériumok</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A listára való felkerülés érdekében a jelentkezőknek a következőkkel kell rendelkezniük:</P><P>— állatorvosi diploma,</P><P>— kiváló angol nyelvtudás szóban és írásban,</P><P>— alapvető informatikai ismeretek,</P><P>— legalább öt évnyi:</P><P>—— szakmai jártasság és tapasztalat a fent felsorolt állatbetegségek legalább egyikének megszüntetésére, megfékezésére és felügyeletére irányuló programok irányítása és végrehajtása terén, vagy</P><P>—— szakmai tapasztalat a fent felsorolt állatbetegségek legalább egyikével kapcsolatos járványtan terén.</P><P>A fenti betegségekkel kapcsolatos tudományos publikációk, valamint az angolon kívüli egyéb nyelvek alapos ismerete előnyt jelent.</P><P>A kiválasztott jelentkezőknek a szerződés aláírása előtt alá kell írniuk egy nyilatkozatot, amely tanúsítja, hogy az érintett értékelés tekintetében nincsenek összeférhetetlenségi helyzetben, és haladéktalanul értesítik a Bizottságot, amennyiben az értékelés során összeférhetetlenség merül fel. Összeférhetetlenségi helyzet áll fenn, ha az értékelő feladatainak pártatlan és objektív teljesítését családi, érzelmi, politikai vagy nemzeti azonossággal összefüggő tényezők, gazdasági érdekek vagy a benyújtott programokkal kapcsolatos közös érdekek veszélyeztetik. Az értékelési eljárás során az értékelőknek megfelelő elkötelezettséget kell tanúsítaniuk a feladat iránt, és bizalmasan kell kezelniük az eljárás során megismert információkat és dokumentumokat.</P><P>A jelentkezőket felkérhetik igazoló dokumentumok benyújtására (pl. egyetemi diploma másolata vagy munkatapasztalat igazolása). Ezek hiánya a jelentkezés elutasításához vezet.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A jelentkezési formanyomtatvánnyal kapcsolatos információk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A kitöltendő formanyomtatvány az alábbi weboldalról tölthető le:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Ezt a formanyomtatványt el kell menteni a merevlemezre, majd kitöltés után el kell küldeni a megfelelő gombra kattintva.</P><P>Kérjük a jelentkezőket, hogy a formanyomtatvány letöltésekor tapasztalt (szoftver-inkompatibilitás stb. miatti) problémákat e-mailben jelezzék a sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu címen</P><P>A rendszer hiányos dokumentumok elküldését nem engedélyezi.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Egyéb információk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A kiválasztott szakértők listája a szándéknyilatkozati felhívásnak a Hivatalos Lapban való közzétételétől számított 1 évig lesz érvényes.</P><P>Az érdeklődő felek a lista érvényességi ideje alatt – az utolsó három hónap kivételével – bármikor benyújthatnak jelentkezést.</P><P>A jelentkezők a lista érvényességi ideje alatt bármikor visszavonhatják jelentkezésüket az ajánlatkérő írásos értesítésével.</P><P>Valamennyi jelentkezőt tájékoztatják arról, hogy felkerült-e a listára.</P><P>Adott N. év programjainak értékelése esetében a munkát az N-1. év június második felétől július végéig kell végezni. A szakértőknek ez alatt az időszak alatt minimum két hétig kell rendelkezésre állniuk az értékelés elvégzésére, és elérhetőnek kell lenniük egy, az Egészségügyi és Élelmiszerbiztonsági Főigazgatósággal Brüsszelben tartandó értekezlet idejére (több betegség szakértői több nap brüsszeli tartózkodással számoljanak).</P><P>A 2019. évi programok értékelése esetében kizárólag a 31.3.2018 határidőig benyújtott jelentkezéseket veszik figyelembe.</P><P>Ha a jelentkezőket egyszer már kiválasztották, akkor nem kell új jelentkezést benyújtaniuk.</P><P>Az Európai Bizottság biztosítja, hogy a jelen részvételi szándéknyilatkozati felhívás eredményeképpen összeállított szakértői lista alapján felállított értékelőtestületek kialakítása kiegyensúlyozott módon történik, mely során figyelmet fordítanak a szakértők megfelelő rotációjára. A jelentkezők földrajzi származását és szakmai hátterét figyelembe veszik. Az Európai Bizottság a férfiak és nők kiegyensúlyozott arányú részvételére is figyelmet fordít.</P><P>A szándéknyilatkozati felhívásra adott válaszának nyomon követéséhez személyes adatok (pl. név, cím, önéletrajz) rögzítésére és további feldolgozására lesz szükség. Ezen adatok feldolgozására a személyes adatok közösségi intézmények és szervek által történő feldolgozása tekintetében az egyének védelméről, valamint az ilyen adatok szabad áramlásáról szóló 45/2001/EK rendelet követelményeivel összhangban kerül sor. A kérdésekre adott válaszokra és a kért személyes adatokra – amennyiben másként nincs előírva – kizárólag jelentkezésének értékelése céljából lesz szükség, és azokat kizárólag a Egészségügyi és Élelmiszerbiztonsági Főigazgatóság D4 egysége kezeli. A jelentkező kérheti a rá vonatkozó személyes adatállomány megtekintését, és az abban előforduló pontatlanságokat vagy hiányosságokat kijavíthatja. Amennyiben személyes adatainak feldolgozásával kapcsolatban kérdése merül fel, azt elküldheti az Egészségügyi és Élelmiszerbiztonsági Főigazgatóság D4 egységének címére (sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu)A személyes adatainak feldolgozásával kapcsolatos ügyekben joga van bármikor az európai adatvédelmi biztoshoz folyamodni jogorvoslatért: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Az ajánlatkérő rendszeresen közzéteszi weboldalán azoknak a szakértőknek a listáját, akik az Európai Bizottsággal szerződést írtak alá.</P><P>A további tájékoztatásra vonatkozó kérések az alábbi címre küldhetők: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A felhívás az Egészségügyi és Élelmiszerbiztonsági Főigazgatóság általi feladásának dátuma:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A hirdetménynek a Kiadóhivatalba történő beérkezési dátuma:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Briuselis: Kvietimas pareikšti susidomėjimą dėl gyvūnų ligų ir zoonozių likvidavimo, kontrolės ir stebėjimo programoms vertinti skirtų išorės ekspertų sąrašo sudarymo.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Skiriančioji organizacija:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos Komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Briuselis</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, El. p. </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Šis skelbimas yra kvietimas pareikšti susidomėjimą</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fiziniai asmenys, kurie pageidauja teikti paraiškas, kviečiami tai daryti laikantis šio skelbimo nuostatų.</P><P>Išnagrinėjus pateiktas paraiškas, šis konkursas Komisijos tarnyboms turėtų padėti sudaryti ekspertų, kuriems galėtų būti paskirtos C punkte nurodytų sričių sutartys, sąrašą.</P><P>Kiekvieną kartą, kai turi būti atliekamas veiklos, susijusios su viena iš toliau išvardytų ligų, vertinimas, skiriančioji organizacija pakvies arba visus sąraše esančius kandidatus, arba tik kai kuriuos iš jų, remdamasi objektyviais ir nediskriminuojančiais atrankos kriterijais, naudojamais konkretaus vertinimo metu.</P><P>Įtraukimas į sąrašą teisiškai neįpareigoja Europos Komisijos paskirti sutarties.</P><P>Kiekvienai minėtai ligai bus sudarytas ekspertų sąrašas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Išsamus kvietime pareikšti susidomėjimą nurodytų sričių apibūdinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamento (ES) Nr. 652/2014 9 straipsnyje (1) numatytas Sąjungos finansinis įnašas įgyvendinant nacionalines tam tikrų gyvūnų ligų ir zoonozių likvidavimo, kontrolės ir stebėjimo programas.</P><P>Komisija turi įvertinti tas programas, kurias pateikia valstybės narės kiekvienais metais, veterinariniu ir finansiniu požiūriais.</P><P>Kad galėtų tiekti papildomą priemonę programoms vertinti, Komisija ieško išorės, techninės pagalbos teikėjų, kurie atliktų išankstinį valstybių narių 2019 metais pateiktų programų vertinimą.</P><P>Mums reikalinga išorės pagalba, kad galėtume įvertinti su šiomis ligomis susijusias programas:</P><P>afrikinis kiaulių maras,</P><P>paukščių gripas,</P><P>mėlynojo liežuvio liga,</P><P>galvijų bruceliozė,</P><P>galvijų tuberkuliozė,</P><P>klasikinis kiaulių maras,</P><P>žvynelinė,</P><P>avių ir ožkų bruceliozė,</P><P>pasiutligė,</P><P>salmoneliozė (zoonozinė salmonelė),</P><P>smulkiųjų atrajotojų maras,</P><P>avių ir ožkų raupai,</P><P>užkrečiamosios spongiforminės encefalopatijos (USE).</P><P>Pareiškėjai turėtų aiškiai nurodyti ligą, kurioje jie specializuojasi. Žr. F punkto atrankos kriterijus.</P><P>Šio konkurso metu pasirašytos sutartys bus įprastos darbų sutartys, sudarytos mokant 450 EUR (keturių šimtų ir penkiasdešimt eurų) vertės dienos įkainį. Kelionių, pragyvenimo ir kitos išlaidos bus atlyginamos pagal įprastas Komisijos taisykles (2). Sutartys apskritai neturėtų viršyti bendro 30 dienų skaičiaus per metus.</P><P>450 EUR dienos įkainis gali būti peržiūrėtas kartą ar du kartus per metus.</P><P>(1) 15.5.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos (ES) Nr. 652/2014 (ES), kuriuo nustatomos išlaidų, susijusių su maisto grandine, gyvūnų sveikata ir gerove bei augalų sveikata ir augalų dauginamąja medžiaga, valdymo nuostatos ir iš dalies keičiamos Tarybos direktyvos 98/56/EB, 2000/29/EB, 2008/90/EB, Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentai (EB) Nr. 178/2002, (EB) Nr. 882/2004 ir (EB) Nr. 396/2005, (EB) Nr. 2009/128 ir (EB) Nr. 1107/2009, Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos direktyva 66/399/EB ir Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (EB) Nr. 76/894 ir panaikinami Tarybos sprendimai 2009/470/EEB, 76/894/EEB ir 2009/470/EB. OL L 189, 27.6.2014, p. 11.</P><P>(2) Komisijos sprendimas 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Darbo vieta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Darbo vieta bus nuošali vieta (pvz., eksperto nuolatinė ar oficiali darbo vieta), arba Europos Komisijos biurai.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Šalinimo kriterijai</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Norėdami būti įtraukti į sąrašą, pareiškėjai turi užpildyti formoje pateiktus pareiškimus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atrankos kriterijai</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kad būtų įtraukti į sąrašą, pareiškėjai turi:</P><P>— turėti veterinarijos laipsnį,</P><P>— labai gerai kalbėti ir rašyti anglų kalba,</P><P>— turėti informatikos pagrindus,</P><P>— turėti mažiausiai 5 metų</P><P>—— profesinius įgūdžius ir patirtį bent vienos iš išvardytų ligų likvidavimo, kontrolės ir stebėjimo programų valdymo ir įgyvendinimo srityje arba</P><P>—— profesionalios patirties epidemiologijos srityje, kuri susijusi bent su 1 iš išvardytų gyvūnų ligų.</P><P>Su minėtomis ligomis susijusios mokslinės publikacijos ir geri kitos kalbos, kuri nėra anglų, įgūdžiai bus laikomi pranašumu.</P><P>Prieš pasirašydami sutartį, atrinkti kandidatai turės pasirašyti pareiškimą, kuriame patvirtina, kad vertinimo metu jie nėra susiję su interesų konfliktu ir kad jie nedelsdami praneš Komisijai, jeigu kiltų toks konfliktas vertinimo metu. Toks interesų konfliktas galėtų atsirasti, jei dėl šeimos, emocinio gyvenimo, politinių ar valstybinių ryšių, ekonominių ar kitų bendrų interesų, susijusių su pateiktomis programomis, vertintojas negalėtų nešališkai ir objektyviai vykdyti savo funkcijų. Vertinimo metu vertintojai privalės pademonstruoti tinkamą atsidavimą pareigoms ir išlaikyti informacijos ir dokumentų, gautų vertinimo proceso metu, konfidencialumą.</P><P>Kandidatų gali būti paprašyta pateikti patvirtinamuosius dokumentus (t. y. universitetinio išsilavinimo kopiją ir darbo patirties pažymas). Jų nepateikus paraiškos bus atmestos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacija, susijusi su paraiškos forma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Formą, kurią reikės užpildyti, galite rasti toliau nurodytu interneto adresu</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Šią formą reikia išsaugoti standžiajame diske, užpildyti ir išsiųsti spustelėjus atitinkamą mygtuką.</P><P>Jei nepavyktų atsisiųsti formos (dėl programinės įrangos nesuderinamumo ar pan.), parašykite el. laišką adresu sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Sistema neleis išsiųsti nepilnai užpildytos paraiškos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kita informacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Atrinktų ekspertų sąrašas galios 1 metus nuo dienos, kai Oficialiajame leidinyje bus paskelbtas kvietimas pareikšti susidomėjimą.</P><P>Visi susidomėję asmenys gali teikti paraiškas bet kuriuo sąrašo galiojimo metu, išskyrus paskutiniuosius trečiojo laikotarpio mėnesius.</P><P>Kandidatai gali atsiimti savo paraiškas bet kuriuo sąrašo galiojimo laikotarpio metu skiriančiajai organizacijai įteikę raštišką pranešimą.</P><P>Visi dalyviai bus informuoti, ar jie buvo įtraukti į sąrašą.</P><P>Siekiant įvertinti N metų programas, numatytas darbas turi būti atliktas nuo N-1 metų birželio mėn. antrosios pusės iki liepos mėn. pabaigos. Ekspertai turėtų galėti dirbti bent 2 savaites šiuo laikotarpiu, kad galėtų atlikti vertinimą bei turėtų galėti dalyvauti Sveikatos ir maisto saugos generalinio direktorato posėdyje Briuselyje (su keliomis ligomis dirbantys ekspertai turi numatyti daugiau nei 1 dieną Briuselyje).</P><P>Vertinant 2019 m. programas, bus nagrinėjamos tik iki 31.3.2018 pateiktos paraiškos.</P><P>Atrinkti kandidatai negali paraiškų teikti iš naujo.</P><P>Europos Komisija užtikrins, kad vertinimo komisijos, sudarytos pagal ekspertų sąrašą pakvietus juos pareikšti susidomėjimą, išlaikys pusiausvyrą bei vykdys tinkamą ekspertų rotaciją. Bus atsižvelgiama į pareiškėjų geografinę kilmę bei profesinį išsilavinimą. Europos Komisija tai pat nori, kad proporcingai dalyvautų vyrai ir moterys.</P><P>Po jūsų atsako į kvietimą pareikšti susidomėjimą reiks įrašyti ir toliau apdoroti asmens duomenis (jūsų vardą ir pavardę, adresą bei gyvenimo aprašymą). Šie duomenys bus apdorojami vadovaujantis reikalavimais, numatytais Reglamente (EB) Nr. 45/2001 dėl asmenų apsaugos Bendrijos institucijoms ir įstaigoms tvarkant asmens duomenis ir laisvo tokių duomenų judėjimo. Jeigu nenurodyta kitaip, atsakymai į klausimus ir asmens duomenys, kurių prašoma, yra reikalingi vertinant jūsų paraišką ir juos tvarkys tik Sveikatos ir maisto saugos generalinio direktorato D4 skyrius. Pagal pareikalavimą galima gauti informacijos apie savo asmens duomenis ir juos pataisyti, jei yra netikslūs arba nepakankami. Visus su asmens duomenų apdorojimu susijusius klausimus reikėtų siųsti Sveikatos ir maisto saugos generalinio direktorato D4 skyriui šiuo adresu: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu Savo asmens duomenų atžvilgiu, Jūs turite teisę bet kuriuo metu kreiptis pagalbos į Europos duomenų apsaugos priežiūros pareigūną šiuo el. pašto adresu: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Skiriančioji organizacija periodiškai savo svetainėje skelbs ekspertų, kurie pasirašė sutartį su Europos Komisija, sąrašą.</P><P>Visi papildomos informacijos prašymai gali būti siunčiami: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data, kai skelbimą išsiųs Sveikatos ir maisto saugos generalinis direktoratas:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data, kai skelbimą gaus Oficialiųjų leidinių biuras:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brisele: Uzaicinājums paust ieinteresētību par tādu ārējo ekspertu saraksta izveidi, kas veic dzīvnieku slimību un zoonožu izskaušanas, kontroles un uzraudzības programmu novērtēšanu.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Iestāde, kas piešķir līgumu:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brisele</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Beļģija.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, e-pasts: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Šis ir paziņojums par uzaicinājumu paust ieinteresētību:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fiziskas personas, kas vēlas pieteikties, tiek aicinātas to darīt saskaņā ar šā paziņojuma noteikumiem.</P><P>Ar šo paziņojumu Komisijas dienestiem tiek atļauts pēc iesniegto pieteikumu izvērtēšanas izveidot ekspertu sarakstu, kuriem varētu tikt piešķirts līgums C punktā aprakstītajās jomās.</P><P>Ikreiz, kad būs jāveic novērtējums saistībā ar kādu no turpmāk minētajām slimībām, iestāde, kas piešķir līgumu, uzaicinās visus vai dažus sarakstā iekļautos kandidātus, pamatojoties uz attiecīgajam novērtējumam noteiktiem objektīviem un nediskriminējošiem atlases kritērijiem.</P><P>Iekļaušana sarakstā neuzliek Eiropas Komisijai nekādas juridiskas saistības piešķirt līgumu.</P><P>Katrai minētajai slimībai tiks izveidots ekspertu saraksts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Šajā uzaicinājumā paust ieinteresētību ietverto jomu detalizēts apraksts:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regulas (ES) Nr. 652/2014 9. pants (1) paredz Savienības finansiālo ieguldījumu konkrētu dzīvnieku slimību un zoonožu izskaušanas, kontroles un uzraudzības valstu programmu īstenošanai.</P><P>Komisija novērtēs šīs dalībvalstu ik gadu iesniegtās programmas no veterinārā un finansiālā viedokļa.</P><P>Lai nodrošinātu papildu rīku programmu novērtēšanas vajadzībām, Komisija meklē ārēju tehnisko palīdzību, lai veiktu priekšnovērtējumu programmām, kuras dalībvalstis iesniegušas 2019. gadam.</P><P>Nepieciešama ārējā palīdzība, lai izvērtētu ar šādām slimībām saistītas programmas:</P><P>Āfrikas cūku mēris,</P><P>putnu gripa,</P><P>infekciozais katarālais drudzis,</P><P>liellopu bruceloze,</P><P>liellopu tuberkuloze,</P><P>klasiskais cūku mēris,</P><P>nodulārais dermatīts,</P><P>aitu un kazu bruceloze,</P><P>trakumsērga,</P><P>salmoneloze (zoonotiskā salmonella),</P><P>mazo atgremotāju mēris,</P><P>aitu un kazu bakas,</P><P>transmisīvās sūkļveida encefalopātijas (TSE).</P><P>Pieteikumu iesniedzējiem skaidri jānorāda slimība, kurā tie specializējas. Atlases kritērijus skatīt F punktā.</P><P>Līgumi, kas tiks parakstīti šā uzaicinājuma iesniegt pieteikumus ietvaros, būs standarta uzdevumu līgumi, kuru dienas likme būs 450 EUR (četri simti piecdesmit euro). Ceļa, uzturēšanās un citas izmaksas tiks atmaksātas saskaņā ar standarta Komisijas noteikumiem (2). Līgumi parasti kopumā nepārsniegs 30 dienas gadā.</P><P>Dienas likmi (450 EUR) var pārskatīt 1 vai 2 reizes gadā.</P><P>(1) Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes 15.5.2014 Regula (ES) Nr. 652/2014, ar ko paredz noteikumus tādu izdevumu pārvaldībai, kuri attiecas uz pārtikas apriti, dzīvnieku veselību un dzīvnieku labturību, augu veselību un augu reproduktīvo materiālu, un ar ko groza Padomes Direktīvas 98/56/EK, 2000/29/EK un 2008/90/EK, Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regulas (EK) Nr. 178/2002, (EK) Nr. 882/2004 un (EK) Nr. 396/2005, Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Direktīvu 2009/128/EK un Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regulu (EK) Nr. 1107/2009 un atceļ Padomes Lēmumus 66/399/EEK, 76/894/EEK un 2009/470/EK. OV L 189, 27.6.2014, 11. lpp.</P><P>(2) Komisijas 5.12.2007 Lēmums (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Darba vieta:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Darba vieta būs attālināta (piem., eksperta pastāvīgā vai oficiālā adrese) un Eiropas Komisijas biroji.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Izslēgšanas kritērijs:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lai pieteikumu iesniedzēji tiktu iekļauti sarakstā, tiem jāaizpilda pieteikumu iesniegšanas ziņojumi, kas iekļauti veidlapā.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atlases kritēriji:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lai pieteikumu iesniedzēji tiktu iekļauti sarakstā, tiem jābūt:</P><P>— augstākajai izglītībai veterinārajā medicīnā,</P><P>— ļoti labām mutvārdu un rakstveida zināšanām angļu valodā,</P><P>— pamatzināšanām informātikā,</P><P>— turpmāk minētajai pieredzei vismaz 5 gadu apmērā:</P><P>—— vai nu profesionālas prasmes un pieredze kontroles, uzraudzības un izskaušanas programmu vadībā un īstenošanā saistībā ar vismaz 1 no iepriekš uzskaitītajām slimībām, vai</P><P>—— profesionāla pieredze epidemioloģijā saistībā ar vismaz 1 no iepriekš uzskaitītajām dzīvnieku slimībām.</P><P>Par priekšrocību tiks uzskatītas zinātniskas publikācijas, kas saistītas ar iepriekš minētajām slimībām, un labas citu valodu (kas nav angļu valoda) prasmes.</P><P>Pirms līguma parakstīšanas atlasītajiem kandidātiem būs jāparaksta apliecinājums par to, ka viņi nav iesaistīti interešu konfliktā saistībā ar attiecīgo izvērtējumu un ka viņi nekavējoties informēs Komisiju, ja izvērtēšanas laikā radīsies šāda interešu konflikta situācija. Interešu konflikts rodas tad, ja izvērtētāja neatkarīga un objektīva uzdevumu izpilde tiek kompromitēta tādu iemeslu dēļ, kas saistīti ar ģimeni, emocionālo dzīvi, politisko vai valsts piederību, ekonomiskajām interesēm vai citām ar iesniegtajām programmām kopīgām interesēm. Visa izvērtēšanas procesa laikā izvērtētājiem jābūt atbilstošai pienākuma apziņai un jāievēro procesa laikā apstrādājamās informācijas un dokumentu konfidencialitāte.</P><P>Kandidātiem var lūgt iesniegt apliecinošus dokumentus (t. i., augstākās izglītības diploma kopiju un darba pieredzes sertifikātus). Ja kandidāti nespēj iesniegt šos dokumentus, viņu pieteikums tiks noraidīts.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informācija par pieteikuma veidlapu:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aizpildāmā veidlapa ir atrodama šādā tīmekļa adresē:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Šī veidlapa jāsaglabā uz cietā diska, jāaizpilda un jānosūta, noklikšķinot uz atbilstošās pogas.</P><P>Ja rodas problēmas ar veidlapas lejupielādi (programmatūras nesaderības u. c. iemeslu dēļ), lūdzam nosūtīt e-pastu uz adresi: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Sistēma neļaus iesūtīt nepabeigtu pieteikumu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pārējā informācija:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Atlasīto ekspertu saraksts būs spēkā 1 gadu no dienas, kad uzaicinājums paust ieinteresētību tiks publicēts “Oficiālajā Vēstnesī”.</P><P>Ikviena ieinteresētā persona var iesniegt pieteikumu jebkurā brīdī saraksta spēkā esības laikā, izņemot šā perioda pēdējos 3 mēnešus.</P><P>Kandidāti var atsaukt savu pieteikumu jebkurā brīdī saraksta spēkā esības periodā, nosūtot rakstisku paziņojumu iestādei, kas piešķir līgumu.</P><P>Visi pieteikumu iesniedzēji tiks informēti par to, vai viņi ir iekļauti sarakstā.</P><P>Saistībā ar norādītā N gada programmu izvērtējumu paredzētais darbs jāveic no N-1 gada jūnija otrās puses līdz jūlija beigām. Ekspertiem šā perioda laikā jābūt pieejamiem vismaz 2 nedēļas, lai veiktu izvērtēšanu, kā arī jābūt pieejamiem, lai apmeklētu sanāksmi Veselības un pārtikas nekaitīguma ĢD Briselē (ekspertiem, kuru darbs ir saistīts ar vairākām slimībām, jārēķina, ka Briselē būs jāpavada vairāk nekā 1 diena).</P><P>Saistībā ar 2019. gada programmu izvērtējumu tiks izskatīti tikai tie pieteikumi, kas iesniegti līdz 31.3.2018.</P><P>Kad kandidāti ir atlasīti, tiem nav atkārtoti jāiesniedz pieteikums.</P><P>Eiropas Komisija nodrošinās to, ka izvērtēšanas dalībnieku grupas, kas izveidotas, pamatojoties uz šā uzaicinājuma paust ieinteresētību ekspertu sarakstu, tiek izveidotas saskaņoti un ka notiek pienācīga ekspertu rotācija. Tiks ņemta vērā pieteikumu iesniedzēju izcelsmes ģeogrāfiskā vieta, kā arī profesionālā sagatavotība. Eiropas Komisija arī paredz līdzsvarotu sieviešu un vīriešu dalību.</P><P>Izvērtējot attiecībā uz uzaicinājumu paust ieinteresētību iesniegtās atbildes, būs jāveic personas datu (piem., vārds, adrese un CV) reģistrēšana un turpmāka apstrāde. Šie dati tiks apstrādāti saskaņā ar prasībām, kas norādītas Regulā (EK) Nr. 45/2001 par fizisku personu aizsardzību attiecībā uz personas datu apstrādi Kopienas iestādēs un struktūrās un par šādu datu brīvu apriti. Ja vien nav minēts citādi, atbildes uz jautājumiem un pieprasītie personas dati ir nepieciešami, lai novērtētu pieteikumu; tos apstrādās tikai Veselības un pārtikas nekaitīguma ĢD, D4 daļa. Jūs pēc pieprasījuma varat saņemt informāciju par saviem personas datiem un izlabot personas datu neprecizitātes vai nepilnības. Ja jums ir jautājumi par jūsu personas datu apstrādi, lūdzam tos sūtīt Veselības un pārtikas nekaitīguma ĢD D4 daļai uz šādu adresi: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu Attiecībā uz jūsu personas datu apstrādi jums ir tiesības jebkurā laikā vērsties pēc palīdzības pie Eiropas Datu aizsardzības uzraudzītāja, rakstot uz šādu adresi: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Iestāde, kas piešķir līgumu, savā tīmekļa vietnē periodiski publicēs to ekspertu sarakstu, kas ir parakstījuši līgumu ar Eiropas Komisiju.</P><P>Visi papildu informācijas pieprasījumi jāsūta uz: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veselības un pārtikas nekaitīguma ĢD paziņojuma nosūtīšanas datums:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paziņojuma saņemšanas datums Publikāciju birojā:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussell: Sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess għat-twaqqif ta' lista ta' esperti esterni għall-valutazzjoni ta' programmi għall-qerda, il-kontroll u s-sorveljanza tal-mard tal-annimali u ż-żoonosi.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Il-Kummissjoni Ewropea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussell</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Belġju.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dan l-avviż huwa sejħa għal espressjonijiet ta' interess</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Dawk il-persuni naturali li jixtiequ japplikaw huma mistiedna biex jagħmlu dan skont id-dispożizzjonijiet ta' dan l-avviż.</P><P>Permezz ta' din is-sejħa, is-servizzi tal-Kummissjoni, wara li jeżaminaw l-applikazzjonijiet li jaslu, se jkunu jistgħu jiġbru lista ta' esperti li jistgħu jingħataw kuntratt fl-oqsma mfissra f'punt C.</P><P>Kull darba li attività ta' valutazzjoni li għandha x'taqsam ma' waħda mill-mardiet imsemmija hawn taħt trid titwettaq, l-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt se tistieden jew lill-kandidati kollha mniżżla fuq il-lista, jew lil ftit minnhom biss, fuq il-bażi ta' kriterji tal-għażla oġġettivi u mhux diskriminatorji speċifiċi għall-valutazzjoni konkreta.</P><P>L-inklużjoni fil-lista ma jfissirx li jkun hemm xi impenn legali min-naħa tal-Kummissjoni Ewropea biex tagħti kuntratt.</P><P>Għal kull waħda mill-mardiet imsemmija, se titħejja lista ta' esperti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Deskrizzjoni li tkopri l-aspetti kollha tat-temi li jaqgħu taħt is-sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-Artiklu 9 tar-Regolament (UE) Nru 652/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill (1) jipprovdi għal kontribut finanzjarju mill-Unjoni għall-implimentazzjoni tal-programmi nazzjonali għall-qerda, il-kontroll u s-sorveljanza ta' ċertu mard tal-annimali u ż-żoonosi.</P><P>Il-Kummissjoni se tivvaluta dawk il-programmi, li tressqu mill-Istati Membri kull sena, mill-perspettivi veterinarji u finanzjarji.</P><P>Sabiex tipprovdi għodda addizzjonali għall-valutazzjoni tal-programmi, il-Kummissjoni qiegħda tfittex għajnuna teknika, esterna biex twettaq valutazzjoni minn qabel tal-programmi mitfugħa mill-Istati Membri fl-2019.</P><P>Qegħdin infittxu għajnuna esterna għall-evalwazzjoni tal-programmi marbuta mal-mard li ġej:</P><P>Id-deni Afrikan tal-ħnieżer,</P><P>L-influwenza tal-għasafar,</P><P>Il-marda tal-ilsien blu,</P><P>Il-bruċellosi fil-baqar,</P><P>It-tuberkulosi fil-baqar,</P><P>Id-deni klassiku tal-ħnieżer,</P><P>Il-marda tal-infafet fil-ġilda,</P><P>Il-bruċellosi fin-nagħaġ u fil-mogħoż,</P><P>L-idrofobija,</P><P>Is-salmonellożi (is-salmonella żoonotika),</P><P>Il-pesta fin-nagħaġ u fil-mogħoż,</P><P>Il-ġidri fin-nagħaġ u fil-mogħoż,</P><P>L-enċefalopatiji trażmissibbli f'forma ta' sponża (TSE),</P><P>L-applikanti għandhom iniżżlu b'mod ċar il-marda li huma speċjalizzati fiha. Ara l-punt F għall-kriterji tal-għażla.</P><P>Il-kuntratti li jkunu ffirmati bħala parti minn din is-sejħa għall-applikazzjonijiet se jkunu kuntratti standard tax-xogħlijiet li se jsiru b'rata ta' EUR 450 (erba' mija u ħamsin Ewro) kuljum. L-ispejjeż tal-ivvjaġġar, tal-għajxien u spejjeż oħra se jintraddu lura skont ir-regoli standard tal-Kummissjoni (2). Bħala regola ġenerali, il-kuntratti lkoll flimkien mhux se jaqbżu t-30 jum fis-sena.</P><P>Ir-rata ta' EUR 450 kuljum tista' tkun riveduta kull sena jew darbtejn f'sena.</P><P>(1) Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 652/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsnill tal-15.5.2014 li jistabbilixxi dispożizzjonijiet għall-ġestjoni tan-nefqa marbuta mal-katina alimentari, mas-saħħa tal-annimali u mat-trattament xieraq tal-annimali, u marbuta mas-saħħa tal-pjanti u mal-materjal riproduttiv tal-pjanti, li jemenda d-Direttivi tal-Kunsill 98/56/KE, 2000/29/KE u 2008/90/KE, ir-Regolamenti (KE) Nru 178/2002, (KE) Nru 882/2004 u (KE) Nru 396/2005 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill, id-Direttiva 2009/128/KE tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill u r-Regolament (KE) Nru 1107/2009 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill u li jħassar id-Deċiżjonijiet tal-Kunsill 66/399/KEE, 76/894/KEE u 2009/470/KE. il-ĠU L 189, tas-27.6.2014, p. 11.</P><P>(2) Id-Deċiżjoni tal-Kummissjoni tal-5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-post fejn irid isir ix-xogħol</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-post tax-xogħol se jkun post imwarrab (pe.. l-indirizz permanenti jew uffiċjali tal-espert), u l-uffiċċji tal-Kummissjoni Ewropea.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-kriterju tat-twarrib</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Biex jitniżżlu fil-lista, l-applikanti għandhom jimlew l-istqarrijiet għat-tfigħ tal-applikazzjoni li se jsibu fil-formola.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-kriterji tal-għażla</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sabiex ikunu inklużi fil-lista, l-applikanti se jkollhom:</P><P>— grad universitarju fil-mediċina veterinarja,</P><P>— Ingliż mitkellem u miktub tajjeb ħafna,</P><P>— għarfien bażiku dwar l-informatika,</P><P>— minimu ta' ħames snin ta',</P><P>—— jew ħiliet professjonali u esperjenza fl-immaniġġjar u l-implimentazzjoni ta' programmi ta' qerda, kontroll u monitoraġġ għal mill-inqas waħda mill-mardiet imsemmija hawn fuq; jew,</P><P>—— esperjenza professjonali fl-epidemjoloġija relatata ma' mill-inqas waħda mill-mardiet tal-annimali mniżżlin hawn fuq.</P><P>Il-pubblikazzjonijiet xjentifiċi marbuta mal-mard imsemmi hawn fuq u ħiliet lingwistiċi tajbin f'lingwi oħra minbarra l-Ingliż se jitqiesu ta' vantaġġ.</P><P>Qabel jiffirmaw il-kuntratt, il-kandidati magħżula se jkollhom jiffirmaw stqarrija li tiċċertifika li huma m'għandhom l-ebda kunflitt ta' interess għall-valutazzjoni li għandha x'taqsam u li huma se jgħarrfu, mingħajr dewmien, lill-Kummissjoni jekk jinħoloq kunflitt ta' interess bħal dan waqt l-evalwazzjoni. Ikun hemm kunflitt ta' interess jekk it-twettiq imparzjali u oġġettiv tal-funzjonijiet ta' min jagħmel il-valutazzjoni jkun mhedded minħabba raġunijiet li għandhom x'jaqsmu mal-familja, il-ħajja emozzjonali, ir-rabtiet politiċi jew nazzjonali, interess ekonomiku jew kull interess ieħor li jkun komuni mal-programmi mressqa. Matul il-proċess tal-evalwazzjoni, dawk li jagħmlu l-evalwazzjonijiet iridu juru li jwettqu d-dover tagħhom bil-galbu u jħarsu l-kunfidenzjalità tal-informazzjoni u tad-dokumenti li jiġu f'idejhom matul il-proċess.</P><P>Il-kandidati jistgħu jintalbu biex jippreżentaw dokumenti ta' prova (i.e. kopja ta' lawrja universitarja u ċertifikati tal-esperjenza tax-xogħol). Jekk ma jkunux jistgħu jingħataw, dan se jwassal biex titwarrab l-applikazzjoni.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif li jikkonċerna l-formola tal-applikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-formola li trid timtela tista' tinstab fuq l-Internet fl-indirizz li ġej:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Din il-formola trid tiġi ssevjata fuq il-ħard drive, ikkompletata u mibgħuta billi tingħafas il-buttuna korrispondenti.</P><P>F'każ ta' problemi fit-tniżżil tal-formola (minħabba l-inkompatibilità tas-"software" eċċ.), jekk jogħġbok ibgħat Email fl-indirizz sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Is-sistema mhux se tippermetti li tintbagħat sottomissjoni li mhijiex ikkompletata.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif ieħor</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-lista tal-esperti magħżula se tkun tgħodd għal sena waħda (1) mid-data tal-pubblikazzjoni tas-sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess fil-Ġurnal Uffiċjali.</P><P>Kull persuna interessata tista' titfa' applikazzjoni f'kull ħin matul il-perijodu tal-validità tal-lista, barra fl-aħħar tliet xhur ta' dak il-perijodu.</P><P>Il-kandidati jistgħu jirtiraw l-applikazzjoni tagħhom f'kull waqt matul il-perijodu li fih tkun tgħodd il-lista billi jibagħtu avviż bil-miktub lill-awtorità li se tagħti l-kuntratt.</P><P>L-applikanti kollha se jkunu mgħarrfa dwar jekk tniżżlux fil-lista jew le.</P><P>Għall-evalwazzjoni tal-programmi ta' sena partikolari N, ix-xogħol maħsub għandu jsir bejn it-tieni nofs ta' Ġunju u l-aħħar ta' Lulju tas-sena N-1. L-esperti għandhom ikunu disponibbli għal minimu ta' mill-inqas ġimagħtejn matul dan il-perijodu biex iwettqu l-evalwazzjoni u għandhom ikunu disponibbli biex jattendu għal-laqgħa fid-DĠ tas-Saħħa u s-Sigurtà tal-Ikel (SANTE) fi Brussell (l-esperti involuti f'diversi mardiet għandhom jikkalkulaw iżjed minn jum wieħed fi Brussell).</P><P>Għall-evalwazzjoni tal-programm tal-2019, l-applikazzjonijiet mitfugħa sal-31.3.2018 biss se jkunu kkunsidrati.</P><P>Ladarba jintgħażlu, il-kandidati m'għandhomx jerġgħu jibagħtu applikazzjoni oħra.</P><P>Il-Kummissjoni Ewropea se tiżgura li l-bordijiet tal-evalwazzjoni, li jinħatru skont il-lista ta' esperti li titħejja wara din is-sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess, jitwaqqfu b'mod ibbilanċjat u jkun hemm rotazzjoni xierqa fost l-esperti. Se jitqiesu l-oriġini ġeografika kif ukoll l-isfond professjonali tal-applikanti. Il-Kummissjoni Ewropea qiegħda tfittex ukoll li jkun hemm parteċipazzjoni bbilanċjata bejn l-irġiel u n-nisa.</P><P>Wara li tkun bgħatt it-tweġiba tiegħek għas-sejħa għal espressjoni ta' interess, se jkun meħtieġ li ssir ir-reġistrazzjoni u jkompli jkun ipproċessat it-tagħrif personali (bħall-isem, l-indirizz u l-KK). Din id-dejta se tkun ipproċessata skont ir-Regolament (KE) 45/2001dwar il-protezzjoni ta' individwu fir-rigward tal-ipproċessar ta' data personali mill-istituzzjonijiet u l-korpi tal-Komunità u dwar il-movement liberu ta' dak id-data. Ħlief jekk ikun imsemmi mod ieħor, risposti għal domandi u dejta personali mitluba huma meħtieġa għall-iskop tal-valutazzjoni tal-applikazzjoni tiegħek u se jkunu mmaniġġjati biss mill-Unità SANTE/D4. Inti tista', billi tagħmel talba, titlob il-komunikazzjoni tat-tagħrif personali dwarek u tikkoreġi kull tagħrif personali miġbur fih li ma jkunx korrett jew komplut. F'każ li jkollok xi mistoqsijiet li jikkonċernaw l-ipproċessar tad-dejta personali tiegħek, jekk jogħġbok indirizzahom lill-Unità SANTE/D4 fl-indirizz li ġej: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu F'dak li għandu x'jaqsam mal-iproċessar tad-dejta personali tiegħek, għandek dritt għal rikors fi kwalunkwe ħin lill-Kontrollur Ewropew tal-ħarsien tad-dejta fl-indirizz li ġej: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>L-awtorità li se tagħti l-kuntratt minn żmien għal żmien se tippubblika, fuq is-sit tal-Internet tagħha, il-lista tal-esperti li jkunu ffirmaw kuntratt mal-Kummissjoni Ewropea.</P><P>It-talbiet kollha għal informazzjoni addizzjonali jistgħu jintbagħtu lil: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-data tad-dispaċċ tal-avviż mid-DĠ SANTE:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-data meta l-Uffiċċju tal-Pubblikazzjonijiet (OPOCE) irċieva l-avviż:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruksela: Zaproszenie do wyrażenia zainteresowania w celu utworzenia listy ekspertów zewnętrznych na potrzeby oceny programów zwalczania i eliminowania chorób zwierząt i chorób odzwierzęcych oraz nadzoru nad tymi chorobami.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Instytucja zamawiająca:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Komisja Europejska</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food Safety Programme, Emergency Funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruksela</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Niniejsze ogłoszenie jest zaproszeniem do wyrażenia zainteresowania.</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Zainteresowane osoby fizyczne zaprasza się do złożenia wniosku zgodnie z warunkami niniejszego ogłoszenia.</P><P>Niniejsze ogłoszenie powinno umożliwić służbom Komisji, po dokonaniu oceny złożonych wniosków, sporządzenie listy ekspertów, którym może być udzielone zamówienie w dziedzinach opisanych w pkt C.</P><P>Każdorazowo gdy wymagane są działania w zakresie oceny związane z jedną z chorób wymienionych poniżej, instytucja zamawiająca zaprosi wszystkich lub niektórych z kandydatów umieszczonych na liście na podstawie obiektywnych i niedyskryminacyjnych kryteriów wyboru właściwych dla danej oceny.</P><P>Umieszczenie na liście nie stanowi zobowiązania prawnego dla Komisji Europejskiej do udzielenia zamówienia.</P><P>Dla każdej z wymienionych chorób zostanie utworzona lista ekspertów.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pełny opis dziedzin objętych zaproszeniem do wyrażenia zainteresowania:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Artykuł 9 Rozporządzenia (UE) Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady nr 652/2014 (1) ustanawiający przepisy w zakresie wkładu finansowego Unii w zakresie wdrażania krajowych programów zwalczania i eliminowania chorób zwierząt i chorób odzwierzęcych oraz nadzoru nad tymi chorobami.</P><P>Komisja oceni te programy, składane przez państwa członkowskie co roku, pod kątem weterynaryjnym i finansowym.</P><P>Aby zapewnić dodatkowe narzędzie do oceny programów, Komisja poszukuje zewnętrznej pomocy technicznej w celu przeprowadzenia wstępnej oceny programów przedłożonych przez państwa członkowskie na rok 2019.</P><P>Poszukuje się zewnętrznej pomocy technicznej w ocenie programów dotyczących następujących chorób:</P><P>afrykański pomór świń,</P><P>ptasia grypa,</P><P>choroba niebieskiego języka,</P><P>bruceloza bydła,</P><P>gruźlica bydła,</P><P>klasyczny pomór świń,</P><P>choroba guzowata skóry bydła,</P><P>bruceloza kóz i owiec,</P><P>wścieklizna,</P><P>salmoneloza (salmonella odzwierzęca),</P><P>pomór małych przeżuwaczy,</P><P>ospa owiec i kóz,</P><P>pasażowalne encefalopatie gąbczaste (TSE).</P><P>Wnioskodawcy powinny wyraźnie wskazać chorobę, w której się specjalizują. Zob. kryteria wyboru w pkt F.</P><P>Umowy podpisane w ramach niniejszego zaproszenia do składania wniosków będą standardowymi umowami o dzieło zawartymi z dzienną stawką 450 EUR (czterysta pięćdziesiąt euro). Koszty podróży, utrzymania i inne koszty zostaną zwrócone według standardowych zasad Komisji (2). Czas trwania umowy zasadniczo nie przekroczy łącznie 30 dni rocznie.</P><P>Dzienna stawka 450 EUR może podlegać aktualizacji po okresie rocznym lub 2-letnim.</P><P>(1) Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 652/2014 z dnia 15.5.2014r. ustanawiające przepisy w zakresie zarządzania wydatkami odnoszącymi się do łańcucha żywnościowego, zdrowia zwierząt i dobrostanu zwierząt oraz dotyczącymi zdrowia roślin i materiału przeznaczonego do reprodukcji roślin, zmieniające dyrektywy Rady 98/56/WE, 2000/29/WE i 2008/90/WE, rozporządzenia Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (WE) nr 178/2002, (WE) nr 882/2004 i (WE) nr 396/2005, dyrektywę Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady 2009/128/WE i rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (WE) nr 1107/2009 oraz uchylające decyzje Rady 66/399/EWG, 76/894/EWG i 2009/470/WE. Dz.U. L 189, 27.6.2014, s. 11.</P><P>(2) decyzja Komisji z dnia 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Miejsce pracy:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Miejscem pracy będzie lokalizacja zewnętrzna (np. stały adres eksperta lub adres jego siedziby) oraz biura Komisji Europejskiej.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kryterium wykluczenia:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aby zakwalifikować się do umieszczenia na liście, wnioskodawcy muszą podpisać oświadczenia do składanego wniosku, zawarte w formularzu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kryteria wyboru</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aby zakwalifikować się do umieszczenia na liście, wnioskodawcy muszą posiadać:</P><P>— dyplom w dziedzinie medycyny weterynaryjnej,</P><P>— bardzo dobrą znajomość języka angielskiego w mowie i piśmie,</P><P>— podstawową znajomość informatyki,</P><P>— przynajmniej 5 lat doświadczenia:</P><P>—— doświadczenia zawodowego i umiejętności w zakresie realizacji programów eliminowania, zwalczania i nadzoru oraz zarządzania tymi programami w odniesieniu do co najmniej jednej z chorób wymienionych powyżej, lub</P><P>—— doświadczenie zawodowe w dziedzinie epidemiologii, w odniesieniu do co najmniej 1 z chorób zwierząt wymienionych powyżej.</P><P>Dodatkowym atutem będą publikacje naukowe związane z wyżej wymienionymi chorobami i dobra znajomość języków innych niż język angielski.</P><P>Przed podpisaniem umowy wybrani kandydaci będą zobowiązani podpisać oświadczenie, że nie zachodzi konflikt interesów w związku z daną oceną i że niezwłocznie poinformują Komisję, jeżeli taki konflikt interesów pojawi się w trakcie oceny. Konflikt interesów ma miejsce w przypadku, gdy bezstronne i obiektywne wykonywanie obowiązków podmiotu oceniającego jest niemożliwe ze względu na życie rodzinne, osobiste, przynależność polityczną lub zapatrywania narodowe, interes gospodarczy lub inny wspólny interes w związku z przedłożonymi programami. Podczas procedury oceny podmioty oceniające muszą wykazać odpowiednie zaangażowanie w wykonywanie obowiązków i przestrzegać poufności informacji i dokumentów, z którymi zapoznają się w trakcie pracy.</P><P>Od kandydatów może być wymagane przedstawienie dokumentów potwierdzających (tj. kopii dyplomu potwierdzającego wyższe wykształcenie i dowodów doświadczenia zawodowego). Brak tych dokumentów spowoduje odrzucenie wniosku.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacje dotyczące wniosku:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Formularz, który należy wypełnić, znajduje się na stronie internetowej:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Niniejszy formularz należy zapisać na twardym dysku, wypełnić i odesłać klikając w odpowiedni przycisk.</P><P>W przypadku problemów z pobraniem formularza (spowodowanych niezgodnością oprogramowania itp.) należy wysłać wiadomość pocztą elektroniczną na adres: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu.</P><P>System nie zezwoli na odesłanie niekompletnego formularza.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Inne informacje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lista wybranych ekspertów będzie ważna przez 1 rok od daty publikacji zaproszenia do wyrażenia zainteresowania w Dzienniku Urzędowym.</P><P>Wszystkie zainteresowane osoby mogą składać wnioski w każdej chwili w okresie ważności tej listy z wyjątkiem 3 ostatnich miesięcy tego okresu.</P><P>Kandydaci mogą wycofać swoje wnioski w dowolnym momencie w okresie ważności listy, wysyłając pisemne powiadomienie do instytucji zamawiającej.</P><P>Wszyscy wnioskodawcy zostaną poinformowani o uwzględnieniu bądź nieuwzględnieniu na liście.</P><P>W przypadku oceny programów na dany rok N planowane prace mają zostać zrealizowane między drugą połową czerwca a końcem lipca roku N-1. Eksperci powinni być dostępni w tym okresie przez co najmniej 2 tygodnie w celu przeprowadzenia oceny, a także dysponować czasem w celu wzięcia udziału w spotkaniu w DG ds. Zdrowia i Bezpieczeństwa Żywności w Brukseli (eksperci zaangażowani w działania dotyczące kilku chorób muszą liczyć się z pobytem w Brukseli trwającym dłużej niż 1 dzień).</P><P>Do celów oceny programów dotyczących roku 2019 będą rozpatrywane tylko wnioski złożone do 31.3.2018.</P><P>Wybrani kandydaci nie mogą ponownie złożyć wniosku.</P><P>Komisja Europejska zapewni zrównoważony sposób tworzenia paneli oceniających na podstawie listy ekspertów sporządzonej w wyniku niniejszego zaproszenia do wyrażenia zainteresowania oraz właściwą rotację ekspertów. Pod uwagę zostanie wzięte pochodzenie geograficzne wnioskodawcy, jak również doświadczenie zawodowe. Komisja Europejska poszukuje także wyważonej proporcji udziału kobiet i mężczyzn.</P><P>Działania następujące po uzyskaniu odpowiedzi na zaproszenie do wyrażenia zainteresowania będą wymagały rejestracji i dalszego przetwarzania danych osobowych (takich jak imię i nazwisko, adres i życiorys). Dane te będą przetwarzane zgodnie z wymogami rozporządzenia (WE) nr 45/2001 o ochronie osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych przez instytucje i organy wspólnotowe i o swobodnym przepływie takich danych. Jeżeli nie określono inaczej, odpowiedzi na pytania i wymagane dane osobowe są konieczne do celów oceny wniosku i będą zarządzane wyłącznie przez Dział D4 DG ds. Zdrowia i Bezpieczeństwa Żywności. Na życzenie można otrzymać informację o swoich danych osobowych, które można poprawić w razie nieprawidłowości lub uzupełnić. Pytania dotyczące przetwarzania danych osobowych należy kierować do DG ds. Zdrowia i Bezpieczeństwa Żywności, Dział D4, na następujący adres: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu W sprawach dotyczących przetwarzania danych osobowych wnioskodawcom w każdym momencie przysługuje prawo do odwołania się do Europejskiego Inspektora Ochrony Danych, na następujący adres: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Zamawiający będzie publikować okresowo w swojej witrynie internetowej listę ekspertów, którzy podpisali umowę z Komisją Europejską.</P><P>Wszystkie wnioski o dodatkowe informacje należy wysyłać na adres: sante-ami-prog-d4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data wysłania niniejszego ogłoszenia przez DG ds. Zdrowia i Bezpieczeństwa Żywności:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data otrzymania ogłoszenia przez Urząd Publikacji:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: Výzva na vyjadrenie záujmu o zostavenie zoznamu externých odborníkov na hodnotenie programov pre vyhubenie, kontrolu a sledovanie zvieracích chorôb a zoonóz.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rozhodujúci orgán:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európska komisia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgicko.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Toto oznámenie je výzva na vyjadrenie záujmu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fyzické osoby, ktoré majú záujem o uchádzanie sa o súťaž, tak môžu urobiť v súlade s ustanoveniami tohto oznámenia.</P><P>Táto výzva by mala umožniť službám Komisie, aby po preskúmaní predložených prihlášok zostavili zoznam uchádzačov, ktorým by bolo možné prideliť obstarávanie v oblastiach opísaných v bode C.</P><P>V každom prípade, keď má byť vykonané hodnotenie činnosti súvisiacej s niektorou z chorôb uvedených nižšie, obstarávateľ vyzve buď všetkých uchádzačov zaradených na zoznam, alebo len niektorých z nich na základe objektívnych a nediskriminačných výberových kritérií špecifických pre konkrétne hodnotenie.</P><P>Zaradenie do zoznamu neznamená žiadny právny záväzok zo strany Európskej komisie prideliť obstarávanie.</P><P>Zoznam odborníkov bude zostavený pre každú z uvedených chorôb.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Úplný opis záležitostí zahrnutých v tejto výzve na vyjadrenie záujmu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Článkom 9 nariadenia Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 652/2014 (1) sa stanovuje finančný podiel Únie na vykonávaní vnútroštátnych programov na vyhubenie, kontrolu a sledovanie určitých zvieracích chorôb a zoonóz.</P><P>Komisia bude hodnotiť tieto programy, každoročne predložené členskými štátmi, z veterinárneho a finančného hľadiska.</P><P>Komisia hľadá externú odbornú pomoc na vykonanie predbežného hodnotenia programov predložených členskými štátmi na rok 2019 s cieľom poskytnúť dodatočný nástroj na hodnotenie programov.</P><P>Hľadáme vonkajšiu pomoc na hodnotenie programov týkajúcich sa týchto chorôb:</P><P>africký mor ošípaných,</P><P>vtáčia chrípka,</P><P>katarálna horúčka oviec,</P><P>brucelóza hovädzieho dobytka,</P><P>tuberkulóza hovädzieho dobytka,</P><P>klasický mor ošípaných,</P><P>nodulárna dermatitída,</P><P>ovčia a kozia brucelóza,</P><P>besnota,</P><P>salmonelóza (zvieracia salmonela),</P><P>mor drobných prežúvavcov,</P><P>kiahne oviec a kôz,</P><P>prenosná spongiformná encefalopatia (TSE).</P><P>Uchádzači by mali jasne uviesť chorobu, na ktorú sú špecializovaní. Pozri bod F pre kritériá výberu.</P><P>Zmluvy, podpísané v rámci tejto výzvy na predloženie prihlášok, budú štandardné zmluvy uzatvorené s dennou sadzbou 450 EUR (štyristopäťdesiat eur). Cestovné náklady, diéty a iné náklady budú preplatené podľa štandardných pravidiel Komisie (2). Platí všeobecné pravidlo, že celkové trvanie zmlúv nebude presahovať 30 dní za rok.</P><P>Denná sadzba 450 EUR môže podliehať ročnej alebo dvojročnej úprave.</P><P>(1) Nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 652/2014 z 15.5.2014, ktorým sa stanovuje hospodárenie s výdavkami týkajúcimi sa potravinového reťazca, zdravia a dobrých životných podmienok zvierat, ako aj zdravia rastlín a rastlinného rozmnožovacieho materiálu, a ktorým sa menia smernice Rady 98/56/ES, 2000/29/ES a 2008/90/ES, nariadenia Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (ES) č. 178/2002, (ES) č. 882/2004 a (ES) č. 396/2005, smernica Európskeho parlamentu a Rady 2009/128/ES a nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (ES) č. 1107/2009 a zrušujú rozhodnutia Rady 66/399/EHS, 76/894/EHS a 2009/470/ES. Ú. v. EÚ L 189, 27.6.2014, str. 11.</P><P>(2) Rozhodnutie Komisie z 5.12.2007 [DOC C(2007) 5858].</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Miesto vykonávania práce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Miestom vykonávania prác bude vzdialené miesto (napr. stála alebo úradná adresa odborníka) a priestory Európskej komisie.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kritériá vylúčenia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aby boli uchádzači zaradení do zoznamu, musia vyplniť vyhlásenia o podaní prihlášky, ktoré nájdu vo formulári.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kritériá výberu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Na zaradenie do zoznamu musia mať uchádzači:</P><P>— diplom v oblasti veterinárneho lekárstva,</P><P>— veľmi dobrú znalosť angličtiny slovom aj písmom,</P><P>— základné znalosti v oblasti informatiky,</P><P>— minimálne 5 rokov:</P><P>—— buď odborných zručností a skúseností v oblasti riadenia a realizácie programov na kontrolu, monitorovanie a vyhubenie týkajúcich sa aspoň 1 z chorôb uvedených vyššie, alebo</P><P>—— odborných skúseností v oblasti epidemiológie, súvisiacich s aspoň 1 zo zvieracích chorôb uvedených vyššie.</P><P>Vedecké publikácie súvisiace s vyššie uvedenými chorobami a dobré znalosti ďalších jazykov okrem angličtiny predstavujú výhodu.</P><P>Pred podpísaním zmluvy musia vybraní uchádzači podpísať vyhlásenie potvrdzujúce, že sa nenachádzajú v konflikte záujmov v súvislosti s dotyčným vyhodnotením a že budú bezodkladne informovať Komisiu, ak by sa vyskytol takýto konflikt záujmov počas trvania hodnotenia. O konflikte záujmov možno hovoriť v prípade, ak sa poškodzuje nestranné a objektívne vykonávanie funkcie hodnotiteľa z dôvodov rodinných, citových, politickej alebo národnostnej spriaznenosti, ekonomických záujmov alebo akýchkoľvek iných spoločných záujmov s predloženými programami. V priebehu vyhodnotenia hodnotitelia musia preukázať primeranú oddanosť svojim povinnostiam a zachovať dôvernosť informácií a dokumentov, s ktorými sa oboznámia počas konania.</P><P>Od uchádzačov sa môže požadovať, aby predložili podporné dokumenty (t. j. kópiu univerzitného diplomu a osvedčenia o pracovných skúsenostiach). Nepredloženie týchto dokumentov bude mať za následok odmietnutie prihlášky.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informácie týkajúce sa prihláškového formulára</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Formulár, ktorý je potrebné vyplniť, je dostupný na tejto internetovej stránke:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Tento formulár je potrebné uložiť na pevný disk, dokončiť a odoslať kliknutím na príslušné tlačidlo.</P><P>Ak sa pri sťahovaní formulára vyskytne problém (pre nekompatibilitu softvéru atď.), prosíme, zašlite e-mail na adresu sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Systém neumožní odoslať predloženie, ktoré je neúplné.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ďalšie informácie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Zoznam vybraných odborníkov bude platný počas 1 roka od dátumu zverejnenia výzvy na vyjadrenie záujmu v Úradnom vestníku.</P><P>Záujemcovia môžu predložiť prihlášky kedykoľvek počas lehoty platnosti tohto zoznamu, okrem posledných 3 mesiacov tejto lehoty.</P><P>Uchádzači môžu stiahnuť svoje prihlášky kedykoľvek počas obdobia platnosti zoznamu odoslaním písomného oznámenia rozhodujúcemu orgánu.</P><P>Všetci uchádzači budú informovaní o tom, či boli zapísaní do zoznamu, alebo nie.</P><P>Pre hodnotenie programov v danom roku N sa plánovaná práca vykoná v období od druhej polovice júna do konca júla roku N-1. Odborníci by mali byť počas tohto obdobia k dispozícii minimálne 2 týždne, aby mohli vykonať hodnotenie, a mali by byť k dispozícii pre účasť na stretnutí GR SANTE v Bruseli (odborníci zapojení v rámci niekoľkých chorôb musia rátať s viac ako 1 dňom v Bruseli).</P><P>Pre hodnotenie programov z roku 2019 sa budú brať do úvahy len prihlášky predložené do 31.3.2018.</P><P>Potom, ako boli vybraní, žiadatelia nesmú žiadosť predložiť opätovne.</P><P>Európska komisia zabezpečí, aby hodnotiace výbory zostavené na základe zoznamu odborníkov z tejto výzvy na vyjadrenie záujmu mali vyvážené zloženie a aby bolo zabezpečené primerané striedanie odborníkov. Bude sa brať do úvahy zemepisný pôvod uchádzača, ako aj jeho odborné pozadie. Európska komisia má tiež záujem o vyváženú účasť mužov a žien.</P><P>Sledovanie vašej odpovede na výzvu na vyjadrenie záujmu bude vyžadovať zaznamenanie a ďalšie spracovanie osobných údajov (ako napr. vášho mena, adresy a životopisu). Tieto údaje budú spracované v súlade s požiadavkami nariadenia (ES) č. 45/2001 o ochrane osôb s ohľadom na spracovanie osobných údajov inštitúciami a orgánmi Spoločenstva a o voľnom pohybe takýchto údajov. Pokiaľ nie je uvedené inak, odpovede na otázky a požadované osobné údaje sú potrebné na účely posúdenia vašej prihlášky a bude ich spracovávať oddelenie SANTE/D4. Na požiadanie môžete získať informácie o vašich osobných údajoch a opraviť prípadné nepresnosti alebo neúplné osobné údaje. Ak máte nejaké otázky týkajúce sa spracovania vašich osobných údajov, zašlite ich na oddelenie SANTE/D4 na túto adresu: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu Čo sa týka spracovania vašich osobných údajov, máte právo kedykoľvek sa obrátiť na európskeho dozorného úradníka pre ochranu údajov na nasledujúcej e-mailovej adrese: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Rozhodujúci orgán bude pravidelne zverejňovať na svojej webovej stránke zoznam odborníkov, ktorí podpísali zmluvu s Európskou komisiou.</P><P>Všetky žiadosti o dodatočné informácie zasielajte na adresu: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dátum odoslania tohto oznámenia generálnym riaditeľstvom SANTE:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dátum doručenia tohto oznámenia ÚVÚPES:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselj: Poziv k prijavi interesa za vzpostavitev seznama zunanjih strokovnjakov za vrednotenje programov za izkoreninjenje, nadzor in spremljanje živalskih bolezni in zoonoz.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselj</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>E-pošta: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>To obvestilo je poziv k prijavi interesa.</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fizične osebe, ki se želijo prijaviti, lahko to storijo v skladu z določbami tega obvestila.</P><P>Ta poziv bo službam Komisije omogočil, da po pregledu predloženih prijav sestavijo seznam strokovnjakov, ki se jim lahko odda naročilo s področij, opisanih v točki C.</P><P>Vedno, ko bo treba izvesti dejavnost ocenjevanja v zvezi z eno od bolezni, navedenih spodaj, bo naročnik povabil vse ali le nekatere kandidate s seznama na podlagi objektivnih in nediskriminatornih meril za izbor, specifičnih za določeno oceno.</P><P>Vključitev na seznam za Evropsko komisijo ne predstavlja pravne obveze za oddajo naročila.</P><P>Za vsako od navedenih bolezni bo sestavljen seznam strokovnjakov.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popoln opis področij, na katere se nanaša ta poziv k prijavi interesa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>V členu 9 Uredbe (EU) št. 652/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta (1) je določeno, da se lahko dodeli finančni prispevek Unije za izvedbo nacionalnih programov za izkoreninjenje, obvladovanje in nadzor nekaterih bolezni živali in zoonoz.</P><P>Komisija te programe, ki jih vsako leto posredujejo države članice, oceni z veterinarskih in finančnih vidikov.</P><P>Da bi si zagotovila dodatno orodje za ocenjevanje programov, išče Komisija zunanjo tehnično pomoč za izvedbo predhodne ocene programov, ki so jih države članice posredovale za leto 2019.</P><P>Iščemo zunanjo pomoč za oceno programov, povezanih z naslednjimi boleznimi:</P><P>afriška prašičja kuga,</P><P>ptičja gripa,</P><P>bolezen modrikastega jezika,</P><P>goveja bruceloza,</P><P>goveja tuberkuloza,</P><P>klasična prašičja kuga,</P><P>vozličasti dermatitis,</P><P>ovčja in kozja bruceloza,</P><P>steklina,</P><P>salmoneloza (zoonotska salmonela),</P><P>kuga drobnice,</P><P>osepnice ovac in koz,</P><P>transmisivna spongiformna encefalopatija (TSE).</P><P>Kandidati morajo jasno navesti, za katero bolezen so specializirani. Glede meril za izbor glej točko F.</P><P>Naročila, sklenjena v okviru tega poziva k prijavi, bodo standardna naročila delovnih nalog, sklenjena z dnevno postavko 450 EUR (štiristo petdeset eurov). Potovanja, dnevnice in drugi stroški bodo povrnjeni v skladu s standardnimi pravili Komisije (2). Praviloma naročila skupno ne bodo presegala 30 dni na leto.</P><P>Dnevna postavka 450 EUR se lahko enkrat ali dvakrat letno spremeni.</P><P>(1) Uredba (EU) št. 652/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 15. maja 2014 o določbah za upravljanje odhodkov v zvezi s prehransko verigo, zdravjem in dobrobitjo živali ter v zvezi z zdravjem rastlin in rastlinskim razmnoževalnim materialom, spremembi direktiv Sveta 98/56/ES, 2000/29/ES in 2008/90/ES, uredb (ES) št. 178/2002, (ES) št. 882/2004 in (ES) št. 396/2005 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta, Direktive 2009/128/ES Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta in Uredbe (ES) št. 1107/2009 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta ter razveljavitvi sklepov Sveta 66/399/EGS in 76/894/EGS ter Odločbe Sveta 2009/470/ES. UL L 189, 27.6.2014, str. 11.</P><P>(2) Odločba Komisije z dne 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kraj dela</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kraj dela bo oddaljeni kraj (npr. uradni ali stalni naslov strokovnjaka) in pisarne Evropske komisije.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Merilo za izključitev</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Za uvrstitev na seznam morajo kandidati izpolniti izjave v okviru oddaje prijave, ki se nahajajo v obrazcu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Merila za izbor</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Za uvrstitev na seznam morajo kandidati imeti:</P><P>— diplomo s področja veterine,</P><P>— zelo dobro ustno in pisno znanje angleščine,</P><P>— osnovno znanje informatike,</P><P>— najmanj 5 let:</P><P>—— bodisi poklicnih spretnosti in izkušenj na področju vodenja in izvedbe programov za izkoreninjenje, obvladovanje in nadzor vsaj 1 od bolezni, naštetih zgoraj, ali</P><P>—— strokovne izkušnje na področju epidemiologije, povezane z najmanj1 boleznijo živali, našteto zgoraj.</P><P>Znanstvene objave v zvezi z zgoraj omenjenimi boleznimi in dobre jezikovne sposobnosti v jeziku poleg angleščine se upoštevajo kot prednost.</P><P>Pred podpisom pogodbe morajo izbrani kandidati podpisati izjavo, ki potrjuje, da pri zadevnem ocenjevanju niso predmet navzkrižja interesov in da bodo Komisijo nemudoma obvestili v primeru, da se med ocenjevanjem takšno navzkrižje interesov pojavi. Navzkrižje interesov obstaja, če je nepristransko in objektivno delovanje funkcij ocenjevalca kompromitirano iz razlogov, povezanih z družino, emotivnimi vidiki, politično ali nacionalno naklonjenostjo, ekonomskim interesom ali katerim koli drugim skupnim interesom s predloženimi programi. V celotnem poteku ocenjevalnega postopka morajo ocenjevalci izkazovati primerno predanost dolžnosti in spoštovati tajnost podatkov in dokumentov, ki so jim predloženi med postopkom.</P><P>Od kandidatov se lahko zahteva predložitev podporne dokumentacije (tj. kopija univerzitetne diplome in potrdil o delovnih izkušnjah). Če ta dokumentacija ne bo na razpolago, bo prijava zavrnjena.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacije v zvezi s prijavnim obrazcem</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Obrazec, ki ga je treba izpolniti, je na voljo na naslednjem spletnem naslovu:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Ta obrazec je treba shraniti na trdi disk, ga izpolniti in poslati s klikom ustreznega gumba.</P><P>V primeru težav s prenosom obrazca (zaradi nezdružljivosti programske opreme itd.) pišite na naslov e-pošte sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Sistem ne dovoljuje oddaje nepopolne vloge.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Druge informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Seznam izbranih strokovnjakov bo veljaven 1 leto od datuma objave poziva k prijavi interesa v Uradnem listu.</P><P>Vse zainteresirane osebe lahko oddajo prijavo kadar koli v času veljavnosti seznama, razen v zadnjih 3 mesecih tega obdobja.</P><P>Kandidati lahko umaknejo svoje prijave kadarkoli v obdobju veljavnosti seznama s pisnim obvestilom naročniku.</P><P>Vsi kandidati bodo obveščeni, ali so bili uvrščeni na seznam ali ne.</P><P>Za ocenjevanje programov danega leta N naj bi se predvideno delo opravljajo od druge polovice junija do konca julija leta N-1. Strokovnjaki morajo biti v tem obdobju na voljo vsaj 2 tedna za izvedbo ocenjevanja in udeležbo na sestankih v prostorih GD SANTE v Bruslju (strokovnjaki, vključeni v dejavnosti, ki zadevajo več bolezni, bodo morali za sestanke v Bruslju nameniti več kot 1 dan).</P><P>Za ocenjevanje programov za leto 2019 bodo upoštevane le prijave, oddane do 31.3.2018.</P><P>Po izboru kandidati prijave ne smejo oddati ponovno.</P><P>Evropska komisija bo zagotovila, da bodo ocenjevalni odbori, sestavljeni na podlagi seznama strokovnjakov, oblikovanega v skladu s tem pozivom k prijavi interesa, uravnoteženi in da bo zagotovljeno primerno kroženje strokovnjakov. Upoštevano bo geografsko poreklo in strokovno ozadje kandidata. Evropska komisija si prizadeva tudi za uravnoteženo sodelovanje moških in žensk.</P><P>Spremljanje vašega odziva na poziv k prijavi interesa bo zahtevalo beleženje in nadaljnjo obdelavo osebnih podatkov (kot so ime, naslov in življenjepis). Ti podatki bodo obdelani v skladu z zahtevami Uredbe (ES) št. 45/2001 o varstvu posameznikov pri obdelavi osebnih podatkov v institucijah in organih Skupnosti in o prostem pretoku takih podatkov. Razen če je navedeno drugače, so odgovori na vprašanja in zahtevani osebni podatki potrebni za namen ocenjevanja vaše prijave in jih bo upravljala izključno Enota SANTE/D4. Na zahtevo lahko pridobite informacije o svojih osebnih podatkih in popravite morebitne netočne ali nepopolne osebne podatke. V primeru, da imate vprašanja v zvezi z obdelavo svojih osebnih podatkov, jih naslovite na Enoto SANTE/D4 na naslednji naslov: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu V zvezi z obdelavo svojih osebnih podatkov imate pravico, da se kadar koli pritožite pri Evropskem nadzorniku za varstvo podatkov na naslednji naslov e-pošte: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Naročnik bo na svojem spletnem mestu v določenih časovnih presledkih objavljal seznam strokovnjakov, ki so podpisali pogodbo z Evropsko komisijo.</P><P>Zahtevke za dodatne informacije lahko pošljete na: sante-ami-prog-d4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum odpošiljanja tega obvestila s strani GD SANTE:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum prejema obvestila v Uradu za publikacije Evropske unije:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-An Bhruiséil: Glao ar léiriú spéise chun liosta saineolaithe seachtracha a bhunú le haghaidh cláir a mheasúnú do dhíothú, rialú agus faireachas na ngalar ainmhithe agus zónóisí.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás dámhachtana:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An Coimisiún Eorpach</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food Safety Programme, emergency funding B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Bheilg.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Ríomhphost: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Is glao ar léiriú spéise é an fógra seo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tugtar cuireadh do dhaoine nádúrtha a dteastaíonn uathu iarratas a chur isteach é sin a dhéanamh i gcomhlíonadh le forálacha an fhógra seo.</P><P>Ba cheart go ligfí leis an nglao seo do sheirbhísí an choimisiúin, tar éis scrúdú ar na hiarratais a chuirtear isteach, liosta saineolaithe a chur le chéile a bhféadfaí conradh a dhámhachtain orthu sna réimsí a bhfuil cur síos orthu i bpointe C.</P><P>Gach uair a gcaithfear gníomhaíocht mheasúnaithe a bhaineann le ceann de na galair thíosluaite a dhéanamh, tabharfaidh an t-údarás dámhachtana cuireadh do na hiarrthóirí go léir atá curtha ar an liosta, nó do roinnt acu, ar bhonn na gcritéar roghnúcháin oibiachtúil agus neamh-idirdhealaitheach atá sonrach don mheasúnú nithiúil.</P><P>Ní hionann iniamh ar an liosta agus aon cheangaltas dlíthiúil ar thaobh an Choimisiúin Eorpaigh chun conradh a dhámhachtain.</P><P>I gcás gach ceann de na galair luaite, bunófar liosta saineolaithe.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos cuimsitheach ar na hábhair a chlúdaítear sa ghlao ar léiriú spéise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Foráiltear le hAirteagal 9 de Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 652/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle (1) do ranníocaíocht airgeadais um chur chun feidhme na gclár náisiúnta do dhíothú, rialú agus faireachas roinnt galar agus zónóisí faoi leith.</P><P>Déanfaidh an Coimisiún measúnú ar na cláir sin, arna gcur isteach ag Ballstáit gach bliain, ó thaobh na tréidliachta agus an airgeadais de.</P><P>D'fhonn uirlis bhreise a sholáthar le haghaidh na cláir a mheasúnú, tá an Coimisiún ag lorg cúnaimh theicniúil sheachtraigh chun réamh-mheasúnú a dhéanamh ar na cláir arna gcur isteach ag Ballstáit le haghaidh na bliana 2019.</P><P>Tá cúnamh seachtrach á lorg againn chun meastóireacht a dhéanamh ar na cláir a bhaineann leis na galair seo a leanas:</P><P>Fiabhras Afracach na muc,</P><P>Fliú éanúil,</P><P>Galar gormtheanga,</P><P>Brúsalóis bhólachta,</P><P>Eitinn bhólachta,</P><P>Fiabhras clasaiceach na muc,</P><P>Galar an chraicinn chnapánaigh,</P><P>Brúsalóis chaorach agus ghabhair,</P><P>Confadh,</P><P>Salmanallóis (salmonella zónóiseach),</P><P>Plá caorach agus gabhar,</P><P>Bolgach caorach agus gabhar,</P><P>Einceifealapaití spúinseacha in-tarchurtha (TSEí).</P><P>Ba cheart d'iarratasóirí galar a speisialtóireachta a léiriú go soiléir. Féach pointe F le haghaidh na gcritéar roghnúcháin.</P><P>Beidh conarthaí arna síniú faoin nglao seo ar iarratais ina gconarthaí taisc caighdeánacha arna dtabhairt chun críche agus ráta laethúil 450 EUR i gceist leo (ceithre chéad is caoga Euro). Aisíocfar costais taistil, chothabhála agus eile de réir rialacha caighdeánacha an Choimisiúin (2). Ní dhéanfaidh conarthaí, mar riail ghinearálta, 30 lá in aghaidh na bliana a shárú go carnach.</P><P>D'fhéadfadh an ráta laethúil 450 EUR a bheith faoi réir ag athbhreithniú bliantúil nó leathbhliantúil.</P><P>(1) Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 652/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 15.5.2014 lena leagtar síos forálacha le haghaidh caiteachas a bhainistiú i ndáil leis an slabhra bia, leis an tsláinte ainmhithe agus le leas ainmhithe, agus i ndáil le folláine plandaí agus le hábhar atáirgthe plandaí, lena leasaítear Treoracha 98/56/CE, 2000/29/CE agus 2008/90/CE, Rialacháin 178/2002, (CE) Uimh. 882/2004 agus (CE) Uimh. 396/2005 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle, Treoir 2009/128/CE ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle agus Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 1107/2009 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle, lena n-aisghairtear Cinntí ón gComhairle 66/399/CE, 76/894/CE, agus 2009/470/CE. IO L 189, 27.6.2014, lch. 11.</P><P>(2) Cinneadh ón gCoimisiún an 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Láthair oibre</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Beidh an láthair oibre ag áit chianda (e.g. seoladh buan nó oifigiúil an tsaineolaí), agus ag oifigí an Choimisiúin Eorpaigh.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critéar eisiaimh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>D'fhonn a bheith curtha ar an liosta, ní mór d'iarratasóirí na ráitis maidir le hiarratas a chur isteach a shíniú, a gheofar san fhoirm.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Critéir roghnúcháin</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>D'fhonn a bheith curtha leis an liosta, ba cheart go mbeadh an méid seo a leanas ag iarratasóirí:</P><P>— céim i dtréidliacht,</P><P>— Béarla labhartha agus scríofa an-mhaith,</P><P>— buneolas ar fhaisnéisíocht,</P><P>— cúig bliana ar a laghad de,</P><P>—— scileanna gairmiúla agus taithí ar bhainistiú agus cur chun feidhme clár díothaithe, rialaithe agus faireachais maidir le haon cheann ar a laghad de na galair thuasliostaithe; nó,</P><P>—— taithí ghairmiúil san eipidéimeolaíocht a bhaineann le 1 cheann amháin ar a laghad de na galair thuasliostaithe.</P><P>Bheadh foilseacháin eolaíochta i ndáil leis na galair thuasluaite agus dea-scileanna teanga seachas sa Bhéarla ina bhuntáiste.</P><P>Sula síneofar an conradh, beidh ar na hiarrthóirí roghnaithe dearbhú a shíniú ag deimhniú nach bhfuil aon choinbhleacht leasa acu le haghaidh na meastóireachta atá i gceist agus go gcuirfidh siad an Coimisiún ar an eolas gan mhoill sa chás go dtiocfadh coinbhleacht leasa dá leithéid chun cinn i gcaitheamh na meastóireachta. Bíonn coinbhleacht leasa ann sa chás go gcuirtear isteach ar chleachtadh neamhchlaonta agus oibiachtúil fheidhmeanna meastóra mar gheall ar chúiseanna a bhaineann le teaghlaigh, saol mothúchánach, cleamhnacht pholaitiúil nó náisiúnta, leas eacnamaíoch nó leas comhroinnte ar bith eile leis na cláir thaiscthe. Ar feadh an phróisis mheastóireachta, ní mór do mheastóirí dúthracht chuí chun dualgais a léiriú agus rúndacht na faisnéise agus na ndoiciméad a chomhall arna gcur faoina mbráid i rith an phróisis.</P><P>D’fhéadfaí a iarraidh ar iarrthóirí doiciméid tacaíochta a chur i láthair (i.e. cóip de chéim ollscoile agus deimhnithe ar thaithí oibre). Diúltófar don iarratas mura mbíonn siad sin ar fáil.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis maidir leis an bhfoirm iarratais</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Is féidir an fhoirm atá le comhlánú a fháil ag an seoladh gréasáin seo a leanas:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Ba cheart go sábhálfaí an fhoirm sin sa tiomántán crua, arna comhlánú agus arna seoladh ach cliceáil ar an gcnaipe comhfhreagrach.</P><P>Sa chás go mbainfeadh dua le híoslódáil na foirme (mar gheall ar neamh-chomhoiriúnacht bogearraí etc.), seol ríomhphost chuig an seoladh ríomhphoist sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Ní ligfidh an córas do sheoladh aighneachta nach bhfuil comhlánaithe.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis eile</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Beidh liosta na saineolaithe roghnaithe bailí ar feadh 1 bhliain amháin ó dháta foilsithe an ghlao ar léiriú spéise san Iris Oifigiúil.</P><P>Is féidir le haon duine leasmhar iarratas a chur isteach ag am ar bith le linn tréimhse bailíochta an liosta ach amháin sna trí mhí dheireanacha den tréimhse sin.</P><P>D'fhéadfadh iarrthóirí a n-iarratas a tharraingt siar ag am ar bith i rith tréimhse bailíochta an liosta trí fhógra i scríbhinn chuig an údarás dámhachtana.</P><P>Cuirfear in iúl do na hiarratasóirí go léir an bhfuil siad curtha leis an liosta nó nach bhfuil.</P><P>Is chun meastóireacht na gclár a bhaineann le bliain N a dhéanfar an saothar réamh-mheasta idir an dara leath de mhí an Mheithimh agus deireadh mhí Iúil den bhliain N-1. Ba cheart go mbeadh na saineolaithe ar fáil le haghaidh dhá sheachtain ar a laghad i rith na tréimhse sin chun an mheastóireacht a dhéanamh, agus ba cheart go mbeidís ar fáil chun freastal ar chruinniú ag AS na Sláinte agus na Sábháilteachta Bia sa Bhruiséil (ní mór do shaineolaithe a mbíonn baint acu le roinnt galar níos mó ná 1 lá amháin sa Bhruiséil a ríomh).</P><P>Maidir le meastóireacht ar chláir 2019, ní bhreithneofar ach amháin iarratais arna gcur isteach faoin 31.3.2018.</P><P>I ndiaidh an roghnaithe, ní ceadmhach d'iarrthóirí an t-iarratas a chur isteach in athuair.</P><P>Áiritheoidh an Coimisiún Eorpach go mbunófar na painéil mheastóireachta ar bhunús an liosta saineolaithe ón nglao seo ar léiriú spéise ar bhealach cothrom agus go mbeidh sealaíocht iomchuí ann i measc na saineolaithe. Tabharfar bunadh geografach mar aon le cúlra gairmiúil na n-iarrthóirí san áireamh. Teastaíonn ón gCoimisiún Eorpach fosta go mbeadh rannpháirtíocht chothrom ann idir fir agus mná.</P><P>Teastóidh próiseáil agus taifeadadh breise a dhéanamh ar shonraí pearsanta (mar shampla d'ainm, do sheoladh agus do CV) má táthar chun athleanúint a dhéanamh ar do fhreagra ar an nglao ar léiriú spéise. Próiseálfar na sonraí sin i gcomhréir le ceanglais Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 45/2001 maidir le daoine aonair a chosaint i dtaca le sonraí pearsanta a phróiseáil le hinstitiúidí agus comhlachtaí an Chomhphobail, agus maidir le saorghluaiseacht sonraí den sórt sin. Mura luaitear a mhalairt, bíonn gá le freagairtí ar cheisteanna agus ar shonraí pearsanta chun críocha d'iarratas a mheasúnú, agus ní dhéanfar é a bhainistiú ach amháin ag AS na Sláinte agus na Sábháilteachta Bia, Aonad D4. Is féidir leat an chumarsáid de do shonraí pearsanta a fháil, ach í a iarraidh, agus aon sonraí pearsanta atá míchruinn nó neamhiomlán inti a cheartú. Má bhíonn aon cheisteanna agat maidir le próiseáil do shonraí pearsanta, seoltar iad chuig AS na Sláinte agus na Sábháilteachta Bia, Aonad D4 ag an seoladh seo a leanas: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu. Maidir le próiseáil do shonraí pearsanta, tá sé de cheart agat éisteacht a fháil ón Maoirseoir Eorpach ar Chosaint Sonraí ag an seoladh ríomhphoist seo a leanas: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Foilseoidh an t-údarás dámhachtana an liosta saineolaithe a shínigh conradh leis an gCoimisiún Eorpach ar a láithreán gréasáin go tréimhsiúil.</P><P>Is féidir gach iarratas ar fhaisnéis bhreise a sheoladh chuig: sante-ami-prog-d4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dáta seolta an fhógra le AS na Sláinte agus na Sábháilteachta Bia:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dáta fála an fhógra ag Oifig na bhFoilseachán:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Брюксел: Покана за изразяване на интерес за създаване на списък с външни експерти за оценяване на програмите за премахване, контрол и наблюдение на болести по животните и зоонози.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>А.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейска комисия</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food Safety Programme, Emergency Funding, В 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Брюксел</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Белгия.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, Електронна поща: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>Б.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Това обявление е покана за изразяване на интерес</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Физически лица, които желаят да кандидатстват, се приканват да го направят в съответствие с предписанията на настоящото обявление.</P><P>Тази покана трябва да даде възможност на службите на Комисията, след проверка на подадените заявления, да съставят списък с експерти, на които може да бъде възложена поръчка в областите, описани в точка В.</P><P>Всеки път, когато дадена дейност по оценяване, свързана с една от болестите, посочени по-долу, трябва да бъде изпълнена, възлагащият орган ще покани или всички кандидати, които са включени в списъка, или само някои от тях, въз основа на обективни и недискриминационни критерии за подбор, специфични за конкретното оценяване.</P><P>Включването в списъка не представлява какъвто е да е правен ангажимент от страна на Европейската комисия да възложи поръчка.</P><P>За всяка от посочените болести ще бъде създаден списък с експерти.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>В.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Подробно описание на областите, обхванати от поканата за изразяване на интерес</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Член 9 от Регламент (ЕС) № 652/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета (1) осигурява финансов принос на Съюза за изпълнение на национални програми за премахване, контрол и наблюдение на болести по животните и зоонози.</P><P>Комисията ще направи оценка на тези програми, които са подавани от държавите членки всяка година, от ветеринарна и от финансова гледна точка.</P><P>С цел осигуряване на допълнителен инструмент за оценката на програмите, Комисията търси външна, техническа помощ за извършване на предварителна оценка на представените от държавите членки програми за 2019 г.</P><P>Ние търсим външна подкрепа за оценяването на програмите, свързани със следните болести:</P><P>африканска чума по свинете,</P><P>птичи грип,</P><P>син език,</P><P>бруцелоза при говедата,</P><P>туберкулоза при говедата,</P><P>класическа чума по свинете,</P><P>заразен нодуларен дерматит,</P><P>бруцелоза при овце и кози,</P><P>бяс,</P><P>салмонелоза (заразна салмонела),</P><P>чума при овце и кози,</P><P>шарка при овце и кози,</P><P>трансмисивни спонгиформни енцефалопатии (TSE),</P><P>Кандидатите трябва да посочат ясно болестта, по която са специализирани. Вж. точка Е относно критериите за подбор.</P><P>Договорите, подписани по тази покана за подаване на заявления, ще бъдат договори със стандартни задачи, сключени с дневна тарифа от 450 EUR (четиристотин и петдесет евро). Пътувания, дневни и други разходи ще бъдат възстановени в съответствие със стандартните правила на Комисията (2). Поръчките, като основно правило, няма да надвишават кумулативно 30 дни годишно.</P><P>Дневната тарифа от 450 EUR може да бъде предмет на годишна проверка или проверка два пъти в годината.</P><P>(1) Регламент (ЕС) № 652/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 15.5.2014 г. за установяване на разпоредби за управлението на разходите, свързани с хранителната верига, здравеопазването на животните и хуманното отношение към тях, здравето на растенията и растителния репродуктивен материал, за изменение на Директиви 98/56/ЕО, 2000/29/ЕО и 2008/90/ЕО на Съвета, на Регламенти (ЕО) № 178/2002, (ЕО) №882/2004 и (ЕО) № 396/2005 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета, на Директива 2009/128/ЕО на Европейския парламент и на Съвета и на Регламент (ЕО) № 1107/2009 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета и за отмяна на Решения 66/399/ЕИО, 76/894/ЕИО и 2009/470/ЕО. ОВ L 189, 27.6.2014 г., стр. 11.</P><P>(2) Решение на Комисията от 5.12.2007 (ДОК В (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>Г.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Място на работата</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Мястото на работа ще бъде отдалечено място (например постоянен или официален адрес на експерта) и офисите на Европейската комисия.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>Д.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Критерий за изключване</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>За да бъдат включени в списъка, кандидатите трябва да попълнят заявленията за подаване на формуляри за участие, които те ще намерят във формуляра.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>Е.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Критерии за подбор</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>За да бъдат включени в списъка, кандидатите трябва да имат:</P><P>— диплома по ветеринарна медицина,</P><P>— много добър говорим и писмен английски език,</P><P>— основни познания в областта на информатиката,</P><P>— минимум пет години:</P><P>—— или професионални умения и опит в управлението и осъществяването на програми по контрол, мониторинг и ликвидиране за поне една от болестите, изброени по-горе, или</P><P>—— професионален опит в епидемиологията, свързан с поне една от болестите по животните, изброени по-горе.</P><P>Научни публикации, свързани с горепосочените болести и добри езикови умения, освен по английски език, ще бъдат предимство.</P><P>Преди подписване на договора, избраните кандидати ще трябва да подпишат декларация, удостоверяваща, че те нямат конфликт на интерес за съответната оценка и че те без отлагане ще информират Комисията, ако възникне такъв конфликт на интереси по време на периода на оценяването. Конфликт на интереси има тогава, когато безпристрастното и обективно изпълнение на функциите на оценяващия е изложено на риск по причини, които включват семейство, емоционален живот, политически или национални връзки, и икономически интереси или всякакви други общи интереси с подадените програми. По време на процеса на оценяване, оценяващите трябва да докажат подходящо ангажиране със задълженията и да съблюдават конфиденциалност на информацията и документите, предоставени на тяхното внимание по време на процеса.</P><P>От кандидатите може да се изисква да представят подкрепящи документи (т.е. копие на университетска диплома и сертификати за работен опит). Липсата им ще доведе до отхвърляне на заявлението.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>Ж.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Информация по отношение на формуляра за кандидатстване</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Формулярът, който трябва да бъде попълнен, може да бъде намерен на следния интернет адрес:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Формулярът трябва да бъде запазен на твърд диск, попълнен и изпратен с кликване върху съответния бутон.</P><P>В случай на проблеми при изтеглянето на формуляра (поради софтуерна несъвместимост и т.н.), изпратете писмо по електронна поща на sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Системата няма да позволи изпращане на непълна кандидатура.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>З.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Друга информация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Списъкът на избраните експерти ще бъде валиден за една година от датата на публикуване на поканата за изразяване на интерес в Официален вестник.</P><P>Всяко заинтересовано лице може да подаде заявление по всяко време през срока на валидност на списъка, с изключение на последните три месеца от този срок.</P><P>Кандидатите могат да оттеглят своето заявление по всяко време на периода на валидност на списъка с писмено обявление до възлагащия орган.</P><P>Всички кандидати ще бъдат информирани дали са включени в списъка.</P><P>За оценяване на програмите на дадена година N, предвидената работа трябва да бъде извършена между втората половина на юни и края на юли на година N-1. Експертите трябва да бъдат на разположение за най-малко поне две седмици през този период, за да извършат оценяването и следва да са на разположение да участват в заседание в ГД „SANTE“ в Брюксел (експерти, участващи за няколко болести, трябва да изчислят повече от един ден в Брюксел).</P><P>За оценяването на програми за 2019 г., само заявления, подадени до 31.3.2018 г. ще бъдат разглеждани.</P><P>Веднъж избрани, кандидатите не трябва да предоставят отново заявление.</P><P>Европейската комисия ще гарантира, че комисиите по оценяване, определени въз основа на списъка с експерти от тази покана за изразяване на интерес, са установени по балансиран начин и че се извършва съответно периодично редуване на експертите. Географският произход на кандидатите, както и професионалният опит, ще бъдат взети под внимание. Европейската комисия също търси балансирано участие на мъже и жени.</P><P>Вследствие на отговора на поканата за изразяване на интерес, ще се изисква записването и по-нататъшната обработка на лични данни (например Вашето име, адрес и автобиография). Тези данни ще бъдат обработвани в съответствие с изискванията на Регламент (EO) № 45/2001 относно защитата на лицата по отношение на обработката на лични данни от институции и органи на Общността и за свободното движение на такива данни. Освен ако не е изрично споменато, искането на отговори на въпроси и искане на лични данни са необходими за целите на оценяване на Вашето заявление и ще бъдат обработвани единствено от ГД „SANTE“, отдел D4. Вие можете, при подаване на молба, да получите информация относно Вашите лични данни и да коригирате неточни или непълни лични данни. Ако имате въпроси относно подаването на Вашите лични данни, моля, изпратете ги до ГД „SANTE“, отдел D4, на следния адрес: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu По отношение на обработването на Вашите лични данни, имате правото да се обръщате по всяко време до Европейския надзорен орган по защита на личните данни на следния имейл адрес: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Възлагащия орган ще публикува периодично на своята интернет страницата списък на експерти, които са подписали договор с Европейската комисия.</P><P>Всички заявления за допълнителна информация могат да бъдат изпращани на: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>И.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Дата на изпращане на обявлението от ГД „SANTE“:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>Й.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Дата на получаване на обявлението от OPOCE:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Cerere de scrisori de interes în vederea întocmirii unei liste de experți externi pentru evaluarea de programe de eradicare, control și supraveghere a bolilor animalelor și a zoonozelor.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea de atribuire:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Comisia Europeană</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Acest anunț reprezintă o cerere de scrisori de interes</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Persoanele fizice care doresc să depună candidaturi sunt invitate să le depună în conformitate cu dispozițiile din acest anunț.</P><P>Această cerere de scrisori de interes trebuie să permită serviciilor Comisiei ca, după examinarea candidaturilor depuse, să întocmească o listă de experți cărora le-ar putea fi atribuit un contract în domeniile descrise la punctul C.</P><P>De fiecare dată când trebuie derulată o activitate de evaluare privind una dintre bolile menționate mai jos, autoritatea de atribuire va invita toți candidații înscriși pe listă sau numai pe unii dintre aceștia, pe baza unor criterii de selecție obiective și nediscriminatorii specifice evaluării concrete.</P><P>Includerea pe listă nu constituie niciun angajament juridic din partea Comisiei Europene de a atribui un contract.</P><P>Pentru fiecare dintre bolile menționate va fi întocmită o listă de experți.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea exhaustivă a domeniilor acoperite de cererea de scrisori de interes</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Articolul 9 din Regulamentul (UE) nr. 652/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului (1) prevede contribuția financiară a Uniunii pentru punerea în aplicare a programelor naționale de eradicare, control și supraveghere a bolilor animalelor și a zoonozelor.
</P><P>Comisia evaluează aceste programe prezentate anual de către statele membre, din punct de vedere veterinar și din punct de vedere financiar.</P><P>În vederea punerii la dispoziție a unui instrument suplimentar pentru evaluarea programelor, Comisia caută asistență tehnică externă pentru realizarea unei evaluări prealabile a programelor prezentate de statele membre pentru anul 2019.</P><P>Comisia caută asistență externă pentru evaluarea programelor privind următoarele boli:</P><P>pesta porcină africană;</P><P>gripa aviară;</P><P>febra catarală ovină;</P><P>bruceloza bovină;</P><P>tuberculoza bovină;</P><P>pesta porcină clasică;</P><P>dermatoza nodulară contagioasă;</P><P>bruceloza ovină și caprină;</P><P>rabia;</P><P>salmoneloza (salmonela zoonotică);</P><P>pesta micilor rumegătoare;</P><P>variola ovină și caprină;</P><P>encefalopatiile spongiforme transmisibile (EST).</P><P>Candidații trebuie să indice în mod clar bolile în care aceștia sunt specializați. Pentru criteriile de selecție, a se vedea punctul F.</P><P>Contractele semnate în baza acestei cereri de candidaturi vor fi contracte de sarcini standard încheiate cu un tarif zilnic de 450 EUR (patru sute cincizeci de euro). Cheltuielile de deplasare, de subzistență și alte cheltuieli vor fi rambursate conform normelor standard ale Comisiei (2). Ca regulă generală, contractele nu vor depăși cumulativ 30 de zile pe an.</P><P>Tariful zilnic în valoare de 450 EUR poate face obiectul unei revizuiri anuale sau bianuale.</P><P>Articolul 1 din Regulamentul (UE) nr. 652/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 15.5.2014 de stabilire a unor dispoziții pentru gestionarea cheltuielilor privind lanțul alimentar, sănătatea și bunăstarea animalelor, precum și sănătatea plantelor și materialul de reproducere a plantelor, de modificare a Directivelor 98/56/CE, 2000/29/CE și 2008/90/CE ale Consiliului, a Regulamentelor (CE) nr. 178/2002, (CE) nr. 882/2004 și (CE) nr. 396/2005 ale Parlamentului European și ale Consiliului, a Directivei 2009/128/CE a Parlamentului European și a Consiliului și a Regulamentului (CE) nr. 1107/2009 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului și de abrogare a Deciziilor 66/399/CEE, 76/894/CEE și 2009/470/CE. JO L 189, 27.6.2014, p. 11.</P><P>(2) Decizia Comisiei din 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Locul de derulare a activităților:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Locul de derulare a activităților va fi un loc extern (de exemplu, sediul permanent sau oficial al expertului) și birourile Comisiei Europene.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criteriu de excludere:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pentru a fi incluși pe listă, candidații trebuie să semneze declarațiile de depunere a candidaturilor pe care le vor găsi în formular.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Criterii de selecție</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pentru a fi incluși pe listă, candidații trebuie să aibă:</P><P>— o diplomă în medicină veterinară;</P><P>— un nivel foarte bun de limba engleză, scris și vorbit;</P><P>— cunoștințe informatice de bază;</P><P>— un minim de 5 ani de,</P><P>—— fie competențe și experiență profesionale în domeniul gestionării și implementării de programe de control, de supraveghere și de eradicare pentru cel puțin una dintre bolile enumerate mai sus; sau</P><P>—— experiență profesională în epidemiologie legată de cel puțin 1 dintre bolile animalelor enumerate mai sus.</P><P>Publicațiile științifice privind bolile sus-menționate și competențe lingvistice bune în alte limbi decât limba engleză vor constitui un avantaj.</P><P>Înainte de semnarea contractului, candidații selectați vor trebui să semneze o declarație care să certifice că nu se află într-o situație de conflict de interese în ceea ce privește evaluarea vizată și că vor informa fără întârziere Comisia în cazul în care o astfel de situație de conflict de interese apare pe durata evaluării. Un conflict de interese survine în cazul în care exercitarea imparțială și obiectivă a funcțiilor unui evaluator este compromisă din motive care implică familia, viața sentimentală, afinitățile politice sau naționale, interesul economic sau orice alt interes comun cu programele prezentate. Pe parcursul procesului de evaluare, evaluatorii trebuie să demonstreze o dedicare corespunzătoare pentru sarcini și să respecte confidențialitatea informațiilor și a documentelor de care vor lua cunoștință pe durata acestui proces.</P><P>Candidaților li se poate solicita să prezinte documente justificative (o copie a diplomei universitare și certificate privind experiența de lucru). Neprezentarea acestor documente va avea ca rezultat respingerea candidaturii.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informații privind formularul de candidatură:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Formularul care trebuie completat poate fi găsit la următoarea adresă de internet:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Acest formular trebuie salvat pe hard disk, completat și trimis prin clic pe butonul corespunzător.</P><P>În cazul unor probleme legate de descărcarea formularului (din cauza incompatibilității software-ului etc.), candidații sunt rugați să trimită un e-mail la sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Sistemul nu va permite trimiterea unei candidaturi incomplete.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Alte informații</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lista cu experții selectați va fi valabilă pentru o perioadă de 1 an de la data publicării cererii de scrisori de interes în Jurnalul Oficial.</P><P>Orice persoană interesată poate depune o candidatură în orice moment pe parcursul perioadei de valabilitate a listei, cu excepția ultimelor 3 luni din respectiva perioadă.</P><P>Candidații își pot retrage candidatura în orice moment pe parcursul perioadei de valabilitate a listei, printr-o notificare adresată autorității de atribuire.</P><P>Toți candidații vor fi informați cu privire la includerea sau neincluderea lor pe listă.</P><P>Pentru evaluarea programelor pentru un anumit an N, activitățile prevăzute trebuie să fie realizate în perioada cuprinsă între a doua jumătate a lunii iunie și sfârșitul lunii iulie din anul N-1. În această perioadă, experții trebuie să fie disponibili timp de cel puțin 2 săptămâni pentru realizarea evaluării și trebuie să fie disponibili pentru a participa la o reuniune în cadrul Direcției Generale Sănătate și Siguranță Alimentară în Bruxelles (experții care participă la licitație pentru mai multe boli trebuie să calculeze mai mult de 1 zi în Bruxelles).</P><P>Pentru evaluarea programelor pentru anul 2019, vor fi luate în considerare numai candidaturile depuse până la 31.3.2018.</P><P>După ce au fost selectați, candidații nu trebuie să depună o altă candidatură.</P><P>Comisia Europeană va garanta că respectivele grupuri de evaluare, create pe baza listei de experți din cadrul acestei cereri de scrisori de interes, sunt alcătuite într-un mod echilibrat și că există o rotație corespunzătoare a experților. Vor fi luate în considerare originea geografică a candidaților, precum și experiența profesională a acestora. Comisia Europeană dorește, de asemenea, o participare echilibrată a bărbaților și a femeilor.</P><P>Monitorizarea răspunsului candidaților la cererea de scrisori de interes va necesita înregistrarea și prelucrarea ulterioară a datelor cu caracter personal (de exemplu, nume, adresă și CV). Aceste date vor fi prelucrate în conformitate cu Regulamentul (CE) nr. 45/2001 privind protecția persoanelor fizice cu privire la prelucrarea datelor cu caracter personal de către instituțiile și organele comunitare și privind libera circulație a acestor date. Cu excepția cazurilor în care se specifică altfel, pentru evaluarea candidaturilor sunt necesare răspunsurile la întrebări și datele cu caracter personal solicitate, acestea fiind gestionate exclusiv de Direcția Generală Sănătate și Siguranță Alimentară, Unitatea D4. Candidații pot obține, la cerere, comunicarea datelor cu caracter personal și pot rectifica eventualele date incorecte sau incomplete. Eventualele întrebări referitoare la prelucrarea datelor cu caracter personal pot fi adresate Direcției Generale Sănătate și Siguranță Alimentară, Unitatea D4, la următoarea adresă: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu. În ceea ce privește prelucrarea datelor cu caracter personal, candidații au dreptul să sesizeze în orice moment Autoritatea Europeană pentru Protecția Datelor la următoarea adresă de e-mail: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Autoritatea de atribuire va publica periodic pe site-ul său lista de experți care au semnat un contract cu Comisia Europeană.</P><P>Toate cererile de informații suplimentare pot fi trimise la: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data expedierii anunțului de către Direcția Generală Sănătate și Siguranță Alimentară :</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data primirii anunțului de către Oficiul pentru Publicații al Uniunii Europene:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Poziv na iskazivanje interesa za sastavljanje popisa vanjskih stručnjaka za ocjenjivanje programa iskorjenjivanja, kontrole i nadzora bolesti životinja i zoonoza.</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>A.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska komisija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Directorate-General for Health and Food Safety, Unit D4 Food safety programme, emergency funding, B 232 2/35, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX><FAX>Fax: +32 2 29 21879</FAX><BLK_BTX>, E-pošta: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>B.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ova je obavijest poziv za iskazivanje interesa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fizičke osobe koje se žele prijaviti pozvane su učiniti to u skladu s odredbama ove obavijesti.</P><P>Ovim se pozivom treba omogućiti službama Komisije, nakon ocjenjivanja podnesenih prijava, da sastave popis stručnjaka s kojima će ugovor moći biti sklopljen u područjima opisanim u točki C.</P><P>Svaki put kada aktivnost ocjenjivanja povezana s jednom od bolesti spomenutih u nastavku mora biti provedena, javni će naručitelj pozvati sve natjecatelje s popisa, ili samo neke od njih, na osnovi objektivnih i nediskriminatornih uvjeta sposobnosti specifičnih za predmetno ocjenjivanje.</P><P>Uključivanje na popis ne predstavlja nikakvu pravnu obvezu prema Europskoj komisiji u pogledu sklapanja ugovora.</P><P>Za svaku od spomenutih bolesti bit će sastavljen popis stručnjaka.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>C.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Detaljan opis područja obuhvaćenih ovim pozivom za iskazivanje interesa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Članak 9. Uredbe (EU) br. 652/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća (1) dodjeljuje Uniji bespovratna sredstva za provedbu nacionalnih programa iskorjenjivanja, kontrole i nadziranja određenih bolesti životinja i zoonoza.</P><P>Komisija ocjenjuje te programe koje države članice podnesu svake godine s veterinarskog i financijskog stajališta.</P><P>Radi pružanja dodatnog alata za ocjenjivanje programa, Komisija traži vanjsku, tehničku pomoć za izvršavanje prethodnog ocjenjivanja programa koje su podnijele države članice za 2019.</P><P>Tražimo vanjsku pomoć za ocjenjivanje programa povezanih sa sljedećim bolestima:</P><P>afrička svinjska kuga,</P><P>influenca ptica,</P><P>bolest plavog jezika,</P><P>bruceloza goveda,</P><P>tuberkuloza goveda,</P><P>klasična svinjska kuga,</P><P>bolest kvrgave kože,</P><P>bruceloza ovaca i koza,</P><P>bjesnoća,</P><P>salmoneloza (zoonotska salmonela),</P><P>kuga malih preživača,</P><P>ovčje i kozje boginje,</P><P>transmisivne-spongiformne encefalopatije (TSE).</P><P>Prijavitelji moraju jasno naznačiti bolest za koju su se specijalizirali. Vidi točku F uvjeta sposobnosti.</P><P>Ugovori sklopljeni prema ovom pozivu na podnošenje prijava bit će standardni ugovori o zadacima s dnevnom naknadom od 450 EUR (četiri stotine i pedeset eura). Putovanja, dnevnice i drugi troškovi bit će isplaćeni prema standardnim Komisijinim pravilima (2). Kao općenito pravilo, ugovori neće kumulativno prelaziti 30 dana godišnje.</P><P>Dnevna naknada od 450 EUR može biti podvrgnuta reviziji na godišnjoj ili dvogodišnjoj osnovi.</P><P>(1) Uredba (EU) br. 652/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 15.5.2014 o utvrđivanju odredaba za upravljanje rashodima koji se odnose na prehrambeni lanac, zdravlje i dobrobit životinja te na biljno zdravstvo i biljni reprodukcijski materijal, o izmjeni direktiva Vijeća 98/56/EZ, 2000/29/EZ i 2008/90/EZ, uredbi (EZ) br. 178/2002, (EZ) br. 882/2004 i (EZ) br. 396/2005 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća, Direktive 2009/128/EZ Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća i Uredbe (EZ) br. 1107/2009 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća te o stavljanju izvan snage odluka Vijeća 66/399/EEZ, 76/894/EEZ i 2009/470/EZ. SL L 189, 27.6.2014, str. 11.</P><P>(2) Odluka Komisije od 5.12.2007 (DOC C (2007) 5858).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>D.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Mjesto rada</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mjesto rada bit će udaljeno mjesto (primjerice, stručnjakova stalna ili službena adresa), kao i uredi Europske komisije.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>E.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kriterij za isključivanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kako bi bili uvršteni na popis, prijavitelji moraju potpisati izjavu o podnošenju podneska koju će naći u obrascu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>F.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uvjeti sposobnosti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kako bi bili uvršteni na popis, prijavitelji moraju imati:</P><P>— diplomu iz veterinarstva,</P><P>— vrlo dobar engleski u govoru i pismu,</P><P>— osnovno informatičko znanje,</P><P>— najmanje 5 godina,</P><P>—— profesionalnih vještina i iskustva u upravljanju i provedbi programa iskorjenjivanja, kontrole i nadzora za najmanje jednu prethodno navedenu bolest, ili,</P><P>—— profesionalno iskustvo u epidemiologiji povezano s najmanje 1 prethodno navedenom bolesti životinja.</P><P>Znanstvene publikacije povezane s prethodno spomenutim bolestima i dobre jezične vještine osim engleskog jezika smatrat će se prednošću.</P><P>Prije potpisivanja ugovora, odabrani natjecatelji moraju potpisati izjavu kojom dokazuju da nisu u sukobu interesa u pogledu predmetne ocjene i da će bez odgode obavijestiti Komisiju ako takav sukob interesa nastane tijekom ocjenjivanja. Sukob interesa postoji tamo gdje je nepristrano i objektivno izvršavanje funkcija ocjenjivača ugroženo iz razloga uključivanja obitelji, emocionalnog života, političkih ili nacionalnih sklonosti, gospodarskog interesa ili drugih dijeljenih interesa s podnesenim programima. Kroz postupak ocjenjivanja sami ocjenjivači moraju dokazati primjerenu odanost dužnosti i poštivati povjerljivost podataka i dokumenata na koje im je skrenuta pozornost tijekom postupka.</P><P>Od natjecatelja se može tražiti da dostave prateću dokumentaciju (primjerice, presliku sveučilišne diplome i potvrda o radnom iskustvu). Nedostupnost istih rezultirat će odbijanjem prijave.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>G.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacije koje se odnose na prijavni obrazac</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Obrazac koji mora biti ispunjen nalazi se na sljedećoj mrežnoj adresi:</P><P>https://ec.europa.eu/food/funding/procurement-contracts_en</P><P>Taj obrazac treba sačuvati na tvrdom disku, ispuniti i poslati klikom na odgovarajuću tipku.</P><P>U slučaju problema s preuzimanjem obrasca (zbog softverske nekompatibilnosti itd.), molimo pošaljite e-poštu na sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Sustav neće dopustiti slanje podneska koji je nepotpun.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>H.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ostale informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Popisa odabranih stručnjaka vrijedit će 1 godinu od dana objave poziva za iskazivanje interesa u Službenom listu.</P><P>Sve zainteresirane osobe mogu dostaviti prijavu u svakom trenutku tijekom razdoblja valjanosti ovog popisa, osim tijekom posljednja 3 mjeseca tog razdoblja.</P><P>Natjecatelji mogu povući svoju prijavu u bilo kojem trenutku tijekom razdoblja valjanosti popisa pisanom obaviješću poslanom javnom naručitelju.</P><P>Svi će prijavitelji biti obaviješteni jesu li ili nisu uvršteni na popis.</P><P>Za ocjenjivanje programa za danu godinu N, predviđeni rad treba biti izvršen u drugoj polovici lipnja i krajem srpnja godine N-1. Stručnjaci moraju biti dostupni najmanje 2 tjedna tijekom tog razdoblja za izvršavanje ocjenjivanja i moraju biti dostupni za prisustvovanje sastanku u GU za zdravlje i sigurnost hrane u Bruxellesu (stručnjaci uključeni u nekoliko bolesti moraju računati na ostanak dulji od 1 dana u Bruxellesu).</P><P>Za ocjenjivanje programa za 2019. razmatrat će se samo prijave dostavljene do 31.3.2018.</P><P>Jednom kada su odabrani, natjecatelji ne moraju ponovno dostaviti prijavu.</P><P>Europska će komisija osigurati da su ocjenjivački odbori uspostavljeni na temelju popisa stručnjaka iz ovog poziva za iskazivanje interesa uspostavljeni na uravnotežen način i da postoji primjerena rotacija stručnjaka. Geografsko podrijetlo stručnjaka, kao i profesionalna pozadina bit će uzeti u obzir. Europska komisija također nastoji uravnotežiti sudjelovanje muškaraca i žena.</P><P>Praćenje vašeg odgovora na poziv za iskazivanje interesa zahtijeva evidenciju i daljnju obradu osobnih podataka (poput imena, adrese i životopisa). Ti će podaci biti obrađeni u skladu sa zahtjevima Uredbom (EZ) 45/2001 o zaštiti osoba pri obradi osobnih podataka u institucijama i tijelima Zajednice i o slobodnom protoku takvih podataka. Osim ako nije drugačije navedeno, odgovori na pitanja i zatraženi osobni podaci potrebni su u svrhu ocjenjivanja vaše prijave i njima će raspolagati samo Odjel SANTE/D4 (Odjel za zdravlje i sigurnost hrane/D4). Možete na zahtjev dobiti obavijest o svojim osobnim podacima i ispraviti bilo koje netočne ili nepotpune osobne podatke. Ako imate pitanja u vezi s obradom vaših osobnih podataka, pošaljite ih Odjelu SANTE/D4 (Odjel za zdravlje i sigurnost hrane/D4) na sljedeću adresu: sante-ami-prog-D4@ec.europa.eu U pogledu obrade vaših osobnih podataka, u bilo kojem trenutku imate pravo obratiti se Europskom nadzorniku za zaštitu podataka na sljedeću adresu: DATA-PROTECTIONOFFICER@ec.europa.eu</P><P>Javni će naručitelj na svojoj mrežnoj stranici periodično objavljivati popis stručnjaka koji su potpisali ugovor s Europskom komisijom.</P><P>Svi zahtjevi za dodatne informacije moraju biti poslani na: sante-ami-prog-d4@ec.europa.eu</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>I.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum slanja obavijesti od strane GU-a za zdravlje i sigurnost hrane:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>J.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Datum primitka obavijesti u Uredu za publikacije Europske unije:</TI_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>