<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="006234-2018" EDITION="2018005"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-003026-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180124</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>5</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180109</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 005-006234</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:006234-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="66171000">Financial consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV><REF_NOTICE><NO_DOC_OJS>2017/S 106-211410</NO_DOC_OJS></REF_NOTICE></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180103</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180124</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="2">Additional information</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="Z">Not specified</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>BI3EC</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Luxembourg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser: for at udvælge finansielle formidlere, som skal modtage midler fra EIB's Silesia-fond over fonde til at gennemføre et finansielt instrument i Silesia Voivodeship, Polen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Aufruf zur Interessenbekundung: zwecks Auswahl von Finanzintermediären, die Mittel aus dem EIB-Dachfonds für Schlesien zur Umsetzung eines Finanzinstruments in der Woiwodschaft Schlesien, Polen, erhalten</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Luxembourg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Call for expression of interest: to select financial intermediaries that will receive resources from the EIB Fund of Funds Silesia to implement a financial instrument in the Silesia Voivodeship, Poland</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Luxemburgo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburgo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI — Convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés: selección de intermediarios financieros que recibirán recursos del Fondo de Fondos Silesia del BEI para aplicar un instrumento financiero en el Voivodato de Silesia, Polonia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIP - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIP – kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntö rahoituksen välittäjien valitsemiseksi saamaan resursseja EIP:n Sleesian rahastojen rahastosta rahoitusvälineen täytäntöönpanoa varten Sleesian voivodikunnassa Puolassa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Luxembourg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI — Appel de manifestations d'intérêt: sélection d'intermédiaires financiers qui recevront des ressources du fonds des fonds de la BEI pour la Silésie en vue de la mise en œuvre d'un instrument financier dans la voïvodie de Silésie, Pologne</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Λουξεμβούργο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Λουξεμβούργο</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΕπ - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: ΕΤΕπ — Πρόσκληση ενδιαφέροντος για την επιλογή ενδιάμεσων χρηματοπιστωτικών οργανισμών οι οποίοι θα λάβουν πόρους από το Ταμείο Συμμετοχών της ΕΤΕπ Silesia για την εφαρμογή ενός χρηματοδοτικού μέσου στο βοεβοδάτο Silesia, Πολωνία</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Lussemburgo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lussemburgo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI — Invito a manifestare interesse: per la selezione di intermediari finanziari che riceveranno risorse dal fondo di fondi «Silesia» per attuare uno strumento finanziario nel voivodato della Silesia, Polonia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling voor de selectie van financiële tussenpersonen die middelen van het EIB-fonds van fondsen voor Silezië toegewezen krijgen om een financieel instrument ten uitvoer te leggen in het woiwodschap Silezië, Polen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Luxemburgo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburgo</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI - Convite à manifestação de interesse para selecionar intermediários financeiros que receberão recursos do fundo de fundos Silésia do BEI para implementar um instrumento financeiro no Voivodado da Silésia, Polónia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Uppmaning till intresseanmälan: val av finansiella intermediärer som kommer att erhålla medel från EIB:s fondandelsfond Schlesien för att genomföra ett finansiellt instrument i regionen Schlesien, Polen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Lucembursko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lucemburk</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB – Výzva k vyjádření zájmu: s cílem vybrat finanční zprostředkovatele, kteří obdrží zdroje z Fondu fondů EIB pro region Silesia k provedení finančního nástroje ve Slezském vojvodství, Polsko</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIP - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIP - huvi väljendamise kutse, et valida finantsvahendajad, kes saavad EIP Sileesia fondifondist ressursse, et rakendada Poolas Sileesia vojevoodkonnas rahastamisvahendit</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EBB — Szándéknyilatkozati felhívás: olyan pénzügyi közvetítők kiválasztására, amelyek a Szilézia Alapok Alapja erőforrásainak felhasználásával pénzügyi eszközt hoznak létre a lengyelországi Szilézia Vajdaságban</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Liuksemburgas</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Liuksemburgas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB – kvietimas pareikšti susidomėjimą: atrinkti finansų tarpininkus, kurie iš EIB Silezijos fondų fondo gaus išteklių finansinei priemonei įgyvendinti Silezijos vaivadijoje, Lenkijoje</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Luksemburga</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luksemburga</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — uzaicinājums paust ieinteresētību: tādu finanšu starpnieku izraudzīšanās, kas saņems līdzekļus no Silēzijas fondu fonda, lai īstenotu finanšu instrumentu Silēzijas vojevodistē, Polijā</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Lussemburgu</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lussemburgu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI — Sejħa għal espressjonijiet ta' interess: biex jintgħażlu intermedjarji finanzjarji li se jirċievu riżorsi mill-Fond tal-Fondi Silesia tal-BEI biex jimplimentaw strument finanzjarju fis-Silesia Voivodeship, il-Polonja</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luksemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBI - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EBI - Zaproszenie do wyrażenia zainteresowania: wybór pośredników finansowych, którzy otrzymają środki z funduszu funduszy na rzecz województwa śląskiego w celu wdrożenia instrumentu finansowego w województwie śląskim w Polsce</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Luxembursko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB – Výzva na vyjadrenie záujmu: na výber finančných sprostredkovateľov, ktorí dostanú prostriedky z fondu fondov EIB pre región Sliezsko na vykonávanie finančného nástroja vo vojvodstve Sliezsko, Poľsko</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB - Poziv k prijavi interesa za izbor finančnih posrednikov, ki bodo prejeli sredstva iz sklada skladov EIB za Šlezijo za izvedbo finančnega instrumenta v Šlezijskem vojvodstvu, Poljska</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Lucsamburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Lucsamburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI — Glao ar léiriú spéise: idirghabhálaithe airgeadais a roghnú a bhfaighidh acmhainní ó Chiste Cistí Silesia chun ionstraim airgeadais a chur chun feidhme in Voivodeship Silesia, an Pholainn</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Люксембург</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Люксембург</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕИБ - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: ЕИБ — Покана за изразяване на интерес: за подбор на финансови посредници, които ще получат ресурси от Фонда на фондове „Silesia“ на ЕИБ за осъществяване на финансов инструмент в Силезкото войводство, Полша</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Luxemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxemburg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BEI - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI - Cerere de exprimare a interesului: selectarea intermediarilor financiari care vor primi resurse de la Fondul de Fonduri al BEI din Silezia pentru a pune în aplicare un instrument financiar în Voievodatul Silezia, Polonia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Luksemburg</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Luxembourg</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EIB - Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Poziv na iskazivanje interesa: za odabir financijskih posrednika koji će primiti sredstva iz fonda fondova EIB-a za Šlesku za provedbu financijskog instrumenta u Šleskom vojvodstvu, Poljska</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den Europæiske Investeringsbank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Investitionsbank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Investment Bank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">Banco Europeo de Inversiones</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan investointipankki (EIP)</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Banque européenne d'investissement</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Ευρωπαϊκή Τράπεζα Επενδύσεων</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Banca europea per gli investimenti</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europese Investeringsbank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">European Investment Bank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska investeringsbanken</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská investiční banka</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Investeerimispank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Európai Beruházási Bank</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos investicijų bankas</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Investīciju banka</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">Il-Bank Ewropew tal-Investiment</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Europejski Bank Inwestycyjny</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európska investičná banka</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska investicijska banka</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An Banc Eorpach Infheistíochta</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейска инвестиционна банка</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Banca Europeană de Investiții</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska investicijska banka</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Indkaldelse af interessetilkendegivelser: for at udvælge finansielle formidlere, som skal modtage midler fra EIB's Silesia-fond over fonde til at gennemføre et finansielt instrument i Silesia Voivodeship, Polen</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Reference: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Bekendtgørelse om annullering</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement til Den Europæiske Unions Tidende, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den Europæiske Investeringsbank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxembourg. E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Parti 1 — Energieffektivitet og vedvarende energikilder i SMV'er er blevet annulleret. Ingen ansøgninger blev modtaget, eller blev alle afvist,</P><P>— Parti 2 — Støtte til folk, der har besvær på arbejdsmarkedet, med det formål at starte deres egne erhvervsaktiviteter er blevet annulleret. Ingen ansøgninger blev modtaget, eller alle blev afvist.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Aufruf zur Interessenbekundung: zwecks Auswahl von Finanzintermediären, die Mittel aus dem EIB-Dachfonds für Schlesien zur Umsetzung eines Finanzinstruments in der Woiwodschaft Schlesien, Polen, erhalten</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenz: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Bekanntmachung der Annullierung</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement zum Amtsblatt der Europäischen Union, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Investitionsbank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg. E-Mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Los 1 — Energieeffizienz und erneuerbare Energiequellen bei KMUs wurde annulliert. Es sind keine Angebote eingegangen oder alle wurden abgelehnt,</P><P>— Los 2 — Unterstützung für Menschen mit Schwierigkeiten am Arbeitsmarkt, mit dem Ziel ihr eigenes Unternehmen zu eröffnen wurde annulliert. Es sind keine Angebote eingegangen oder alle wurden abgelehnt.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Call for expression of interest: to select financial intermediaries that will receive resources from the EIB Fund of Funds Silesia to implement a financial instrument in the Silesia Voivodeship, Poland</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Reference: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Cancellation Notice</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement to the Official Journal of the European Union, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Investment Bank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, LUXEMBOURG. E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Lot 1 — Energy efficiency and renewable energy sources in SMEs has been cancelled. No proposals were received or all were rejected,</P><P>— Lot 2 — Support for people experiencing difficulties in the labour market, for the purpose of starting their own business activities has been cancelled. No proposals were received or all rejected.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI — Convocatoria de manifestaciones de interés: selección de intermediarios financieros que recibirán recursos del Fondo de Fondos Silesia del BEI para aplicar un instrumento financiero en el Voivodato de Silesia, Polonia</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referencia: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anuncio de anulación</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplemento al Diario Oficial de la Unión Europea, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Banco Europeo de Inversiones</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburgo. Correo electrónico: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Se ha cancelado el lote 1: eficiencia energética y fuentes de energía renovable en las pymes. No se ha recibido ninguna propuesta o todas las que se han recibido han sido rechazadas.</P><P>— Se ha cancelado el lote 2: apoyo para las personas con dificultades en el mercado laboral para que puedan iniciar su propia actividad comercial. No se ha recibido ninguna propuesta o todas las que se han recibido han sido rechazadas.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIP – kiinnostuksenilmaisupyyntö rahoituksen välittäjien valitsemiseksi saamaan resursseja EIP:n Sleesian rahastojen rahastosta rahoitusvälineen täytäntöönpanoa varten Sleesian voivodikunnassa Puolassa</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Viite: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Peruutusilmoitus:</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Euroopan unionin virallisen lehden täydennysosa, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan investointipankki (EIP)</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg. Sähköpostiosoite: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Erä 1 – Energiatehokkuus ja uusiutuvat energianlähteet pk-yrityksissä on peruttu. Ehdotuksia ei vastaanotettu tai kaikki hylättiin.</P><P>— Erä 2 – Tuki ihmisille, joilla on vaikeuksia työmarkkinoilla ja jotka haluaisivat perustaa oman yrityksen, on peruttu. Ehdotuksia ei vastaanotettu tai kaikki hylättiin.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI — Appel de manifestations d'intérêt: sélection d'intermédiaires financiers qui recevront des ressources du fonds des fonds de la BEI pour la Silésie en vue de la mise en œuvre d'un instrument financier dans la voïvodie de Silésie, Pologne</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Référence: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avis d'annulation</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplément au Journal officiel de l'Union européenne, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Banque européenne d'investissement</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxembourg. Courriel : </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Lot 1 — Efficacité énergétique et sources d’énergie renouvelable dans les PME a été annulé. Aucune offre n’a été reçue ou elles ont toutes été rejetées,</P><P>— Lot 2 — Soutien aux personnes ayant des difficultés dans le marché du travail, dans le but de démarrer leur propre entreprise a été annulé. Aucune offre n’a été reçue ou elles ont toutes été rejetées.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: ΕΤΕπ — Πρόσκληση ενδιαφέροντος για την επιλογή ενδιάμεσων χρηματοπιστωτικών οργανισμών οι οποίοι θα λάβουν πόρους από το Ταμείο Συμμετοχών της ΕΤΕπ Silesia για την εφαρμογή ενός χρηματοδοτικού μέσου στο βοεβοδάτο Silesia, Πολωνία</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Αριθμός αναφοράς: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ακυρωτική προκήρυξη</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Συμπλήρωμα στην Επίσημη Εφημερίδα της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ευρωπαϊκή Τράπεζα Επενδύσεων</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Λουξεμβούργο. Ηλεκτρονικό Ταχυδρομείο: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Παρτίδα 1 — Για την ενεργειακή απόδοση και τις ανανεώσιμες πηγές ενέργειας στις ΜΜΕ ακυρώθηκε. Δεν παρελήφθησαν προτάσεις ή απερρίφθησαν όλες,</P><P>— Παρτίδα 2 — Για την υποστήριξη ατόμων που αντιμετωπίζουν δυσκολίες στην αγορά εργασίας με σκοπό την έναρξη επιχειρηματικών δραστηριοτήτων ακυρώθηκε. Δεν παρελήφθησαν προτάσεις ή απερρίφθησαν όλες.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI — Invito a manifestare interesse: per la selezione di intermediari finanziari che riceveranno risorse dal fondo di fondi «Silesia» per attuare uno strumento finanziario nel voivodato della Silesia, Polonia</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Riferimento: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avviso di annullamento</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplemento alla Gazzetta ufficiale dell'Unione europea, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Banca europea per gli investimenti</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Lussemburgo. E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Lotto 1 — Efficienza energetica e fonti di energia rinnovabili nelle PMI è stato annullato. Nessuna proposta è stata ricevuta o tutte sono state respinte,</P><P>— Lotto 2 — Sostegno alle persone che trovano difficoltà nel mercato del lavoro, allo scopo di iniziare la propria attività imprenditoriale è stato annullato. Nessuna proposta è stata ricevuta o tutte sono state respinte.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Oproep tot het indienen van blijken van belangstelling voor de selectie van financiële tussenpersonen die middelen van het EIB-fonds van fondsen voor Silezië toegewezen krijgen om een financieel instrument ten uitvoer te leggen in het woiwodschap Silezië, Polen</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referentie: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Annulering</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement op het Publicatieblad van de Europese Unie, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europese Investeringsbank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg. E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Perceel 1 — energie-efficiëntie en hernieuwbare energiebronnen in het mkb werd geannuleerd. Er zijn geen voorstellen ontvangen of ze werden allemaal verworpen.</P><P>— Perceel 2 — ondersteuning van mensen die moeilijkheden ondervinden op de arbeidsmarkt bij het opstarten van eigen bedrijfsactiviteiten, werd geannuleerd. Er zijn geen voorstellen ontvangen of ze werden allemaal verworpen.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI - Convite à manifestação de interesse para selecionar intermediários financeiros que receberão recursos do fundo de fundos Silésia do BEI para implementar um instrumento financeiro no Voivodado da Silésia, Polónia</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referência: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anúncio de anulação</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplemento do Jornal Oficial da União Europeia, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Investment Bank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburgo. Endereço eletrónico: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Lote 1 — Eficiência energética e fontes de energia renovável em PMEs foi cancelado. Não foram recebidas propostas ou todas foram rejeitadas,</P><P>— Lote 2 — Apoio a pessoas que sintam dificuldades no mercado de trabalho, com o intuito de iniciarem as suas próprias atividades de negócio foi cancelado. Não foram recebidas propostas ou todas foram rejeitadas.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Uppmaning till intresseanmälan: val av finansiella intermediärer som kommer att erhålla medel från EIB:s fondandelsfond Schlesien för att genomföra ett finansiellt instrument i regionen Schlesien, Polen</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referens: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Meddelande om annullering</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Tillägg till Europeiska unionens officiella tidning, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska investeringsbanken</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg. E-post: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Del 1 — Energieffektivitet och förnybara energikällor i små och medelstora företag har annullerats. Inga förslag har mottagits eller alla har avslagits,</P><P>— Del 2 — Stöd i syfte att starta eget företag, till människor som upplever svårigheter på arbetsmarknaden, har annullerats. Inga förslag har mottagits eller alla har avslagits.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB – Výzva k vyjádření zájmu: s cílem vybrat finanční zprostředkovatele, kteří obdrží zdroje z Fondu fondů EIB pro region Silesia k provedení finančního nástroje ve Slezském vojvodství, Polsko</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenční číslo: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Oznámení o zrušení</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatek k Úřednímu věstníku Evropské unie, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská investiční banka</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Lucembursko. E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Položka č.1 – Energetická účinnost a obnovitelné zdroje energie v malých a středních podnicích – byla zrušena. Nebyly obdrženy žádné návrhy, nebo byly všechny zamítnuty,</P><P>Položka č. 2 – Podpora pro osoby, které se potýkají s obtížemi na pracovním trhu při zahajování svých obchodních činností – byla zrušena. Nebyly obdrženy žádné návrhy, nebo byly všechny zamítnuty.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIP - huvi väljendamise kutse, et valida finantsvahendajad, kes saavad EIP Sileesia fondifondist ressursse, et rakendada Poolas Sileesia vojevoodkonnas rahastamisvahendit</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Viide: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tühistamisteade</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Euroopa Liidu Teataja täiendus, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Investeerimispank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luksemburg. E-post: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— 1. osa — "Energiatõhusus ja taastuvad energiaallikad VKE-des" on tühistatud. Pakkumisi ei laekunud või lükati need kõik tagasi.</P><P>— 2. osa — "Tööturul raskustes olevate inimeste toetamine eesmärgiga käivitada nende iseseisev äritegevus" on tühistatud. Pakkumisi ei laekunud või lükati need kõik tagasi.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EBB — Szándéknyilatkozati felhívás: olyan pénzügyi közvetítők kiválasztására, amelyek a Szilézia Alapok Alapja erőforrásainak felhasználásával pénzügyi eszközt hoznak létre a lengyelországi Szilézia Vajdaságban</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Hivatkozás: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Érvénytelenítés</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Kiegészítés az Európai Unió Hivatalos Lapjához, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európai Beruházási Bank</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg. E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Az energiahatékonyságra és a KKV-kra vonatkozó megújuló energiaforrásokra irányuló 1. tételt érvénytelenítették. Nem érkezett be ajánlat, vagy minden beérkezett ajánlatot elutasítottak,</P><P>— A munkaerőpiacon (saját üzleti tevékenység indítását illetően) nehézségekkel szembesülők támogatására irányuló 2. tételt érvénytelenítették. Nem érkezett be ajánlat, vagy minden beérkezett ajánlatot elutasítottak.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB – kvietimas pareikšti susidomėjimą: atrinkti finansų tarpininkus, kurie iš EIB Silezijos fondų fondo gaus išteklių finansinei priemonei įgyvendinti Silezijos vaivadijoje, Lenkijoje</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Nuoroda: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Skelbimas apie anuliavimą</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Europos Bendrijos Oficialiojo Leidinio priedas, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos investicijų bankas</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Liuksemburgas. El. p. </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>– 1 dalis „Energijos vartojimo efektyvumas ir atsinaujinantys energijos šaltiniai MVĮ“ buvo atšaukta. Nebuvo gauta jokių pasiūlymų arba visi jie buvo atmesti.</P><P>– 2 dalis „Parama žmonėms, patiriantiems sunkumų darbo rinkoje, siekiant padėti jiems įkurti savo verslą“ buvo atšaukta. Nebuvo gauta jokių pasiūlymų arba visi jie buvo atmesti.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — uzaicinājums paust ieinteresētību: tādu finanšu starpnieku izraudzīšanās, kas saņems līdzekļus no Silēzijas fondu fonda, lai īstenotu finanšu instrumentu Silēzijas vojevodistē, Polijā</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Atsauce: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Paziņojums par atcelšanu</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Eiropas Savienības Oficiālā Vēstneša pielikums, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Investīciju banka</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luksemburga. E-pasts: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— 1. daļa — energoefektivitāte un atjaunojamie energoresursi MVU — ir atcelta. Netika saņemts neviens piedāvājums vai arī tie tika noraidīti.</P><P>— 2. daļa — atbalsts savas uzņēmējdarbības uzsākšanā tiem cilvēkiem, kuri saskārušies ar grūtībām darba tirgū — ir atcelta. Netika saņemts neviens piedāvājums vai arī tie tika noraidīti.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI — Sejħa għal espressjonijiet ta' interess: biex jintgħażlu intermedjarji finanzjarji li se jirċievu riżorsi mill-Fond tal-Fondi Silesia tal-BEI biex jimplimentaw strument finanzjarju fis-Silesia Voivodeship, il-Polonja</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ir-referenza: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Avviż ta' Tħassir</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Supplement tal-Gurnal Ufficjali ta’ l-Unjoni Ewropea’, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Il-Bank Ewropew tal-Investiment</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Lussemburgu. Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— L-1 lott — L-effiċjenza fl-enerġija u s-sorsi ta' enerġija li tiġġedded fl-SMEs ġie mħassar. Ma waslu l-ebda proposti jew ġew kollha rrifjutati,</P><P>— It-2 lott — L-appoġġ lill-persuni li jgħaddu minn diffikultajiet fis-suq tax-xogħol, biex jibdew l-attivitajiet ta' negozju tagħhom ġie mħassar. Ma waslu l-ebda proposti jew ġew kollha rrifjutati.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EBI - Zaproszenie do wyrażenia zainteresowania: wybór pośredników finansowych, którzy otrzymają środki z funduszu funduszy na rzecz województwa śląskiego w celu wdrożenia instrumentu finansowego w województwie śląskim w Polsce</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Numer referencyjny: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ogłoszenie o unieważnieniu</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplement do Dziennika Urzędowego Unii Europejskiej, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europejski Bank Inwestycyjny</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luksemburg. E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Część 1 — Wydajność energetyczna i odnawialne źródła energii dla MŚP, ogłoszenie zostało unieważnione. Nie otrzymano żadnych ofert lub wszystkie zostały odrzucone.</P><P>— Część 2 — Wsparcie na rzecz osób doświadczających trudności na rynku pracy dla celów założenia działalności gospodarczej, ogłoszenie zostało unieważnione. Nie otrzymano żadnych ofert lub wszystkie zostały odrzucone.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB – Výzva na vyjadrenie záujmu: na výber finančných sprostredkovateľov, ktorí dostanú prostriedky z fondu fondov EIB pre región Sliezsko na vykonávanie finančného nástroja vo vojvodstve Sliezsko, Poľsko</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenčné číslo: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Oznámenie o zrušení obstarávania</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Príloha k Úradnému vestníku Európskej únie, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európska investičná banka</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxembursko. E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Časť 1 – Energetická účinnosť a obnoviteľné zdroje energie v MSP – bola zrušená. Neboli prijaté žiadne ponuky alebo boli všetky zamietnuté.</P><P>— Časť 2 – Podpora pre ľudí, ktorí majú ťažkosti na trhu práce, s cieľom založiť ich vlastnú podnikateľskú činnosť – bola zrušená. Neboli prijaté žiadne ponuky alebo boli všetky zamietnuté.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB - Poziv k prijavi interesa za izbor finančnih posrednikov, ki bodo prejeli sredstva iz sklada skladov EIB za Šlezijo za izvedbo finančnega instrumenta v Šlezijskem vojvodstvu, Poljska</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referenčna številka: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Obvestilo o preklicu</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatek k Uradnemu listu Evropske unije, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska investicijska banka</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luksemburg. E-pošta: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Sklop 1 – energetska učinkovitost in obnovljivi viri energije v MSP – je bil preklican. Ni bilo prejetih predlogov ali pa so bili vsi zavrnjeni.</P><P>— Sklop 2 – podpora osebam s težavami na trgu dela s ciljem zagona lastne poslovne dejavnosti – je bil preklican. Ni bilo prejetih predlogov ali pa so bili vsi zavrnjeni.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI — Glao ar léiriú spéise: idirghabhálaithe airgeadais a roghnú a bhfaighidh acmhainní ó Chiste Cistí Silesia chun ionstraim airgeadais a chur chun feidhme in Voivodeship Silesia, an Pholainn</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Tagairt: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Fógra cealúcháin</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Forlíonaidh d'Iris Oifigiúil an Aontais Eorpaigh, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An Banc Eorpach Infheistíochta</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Lucsamburg. Ríomhphost: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Beart 1 — Táthar tar éis an éifeachtúlacht fuinnimh agus foinsí fuinnimh in-athnuaite sna FBMí a chealú. Ní bhfuarthas tograí ar bith nó diúltaíodh dóibh go léir,</P><P>— Beart 2 — Tacaíocht do dhaoine a mbaineann dua dóibh sa mhargadh saothair, chun na críche a gcuid gníomhaíochtaí gnó féin a thionscnamh; táthar tar éis iad a chealú. Ní bhfuarthas tograí ar bith nó diúltaíodh dóibh go léir.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: ЕИБ — Покана за изразяване на интерес: за подбор на финансови посредници, които ще получат ресурси от Фонда на фондове „Silesia“ на ЕИБ за осъществяване на финансов инструмент в Силезкото войводство, Полша</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Справка: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Обявление за анулиране</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Приложение към Официален вестник на Европейския съюз, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейска инвестиционна банка</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Люксембург. Електронна поща: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Обособена позиция 1 — Енергийна ефективност и възобновяеми енергийни източници в МСП е отменена. Не са получени оферти или всички са били отхвърлени,</P><P>— Обособена позиция 2 — Подкрепа за хора, изпитващи трудности на трудовия пазар, с цел стартиране на собствени бизнес дейности е отменена. Не са получени оферти или всички са били отхвърлени.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: BEI - Cerere de exprimare a interesului: selectarea intermediarilor financiari care vor primi resurse de la Fondul de Fonduri al BEI din Silezia pentru a pune în aplicare un instrument financiar în Voievodatul Silezia, Polonia</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Referința: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Anunț de anulare</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Suplimentul Jurnalului Oficial al Uniunii Europene, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Banca Europeană de Investiții</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>98-100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luxemburg. E-mail: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Lotul 1 - Eficiența energetică și sursele regenerabile de energie în IMM-uri au fost anulate. Nu au fost primite propuneri sau toate au fost respinse</P><P>— Lotul 2 - Sprijinul pentru persoanele care se confruntă cu dificultăți pe piața forței de muncă, cu scopul de a-și începe propriile activități de afaceri, a fost anulat Nu au fost primite propuneri sau toate au fost respinse.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>Luxembourg-Luxembourg: EIB — Poziv na iskazivanje interesa: za odabir financijskih posrednika koji će primiti sredstva iz fonda fondova EIB-a za Šlesku za provedbu financijskog instrumenta u Šleskom vojvodstvu, Poljska</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>2017/S 106-211410</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Uputa: PC-1403</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Obavijest o otkazivanju</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P><FT TYPE="REFOJ">(Dodatak Službenom listu Europske unije, 3.6.2017, 2017/S 106-211410)</FT></P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska investicijska banka</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, 98–100, boulevard Konrad Adenauer, L-2950 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Luksemburg. E-pošta: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>CS-procurement@eib.org</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>— Grupa 1 — Energetska učinkovitost i obnovljivi izvori energije u malim i srednjim poduzećima je otkazana. Ni jedna ponuda nije zaprimljena ili su sve odbijene</P><P>— Grupa 2 — Podrška za osobe s poteškoćama na tržištu rada, radi pokretanja vlastitih poslovnih aktivnosti je otkazana. Ni jedna ponuda nije zaprimljena ili su sve odbijene.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>