<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="189091-2018" EDITION="2018084"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-187580-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180604</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>84</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180502</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 084-189091</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:189091-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="AZ"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45233121">Main road construction works</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180425</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180604 17:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>BR605</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Aserbajdsjan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Tilsyn med bygge- og anlægsarbejdet for renovering af motorvej (R42) mellem Bahramtapa og Bilesuvar (60 km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Aserbaidschan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Bau und Aufsicht von Bauarbeiten für die Sanierung der Straße von (R42) Bahramtapa nach Bilesuvar (60 km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Azerbaijan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Construction Supervision of Civil Works Contract for the Rehabilitation of (R42) Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road (60 Km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Azerbaiyán</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bakú</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 - Contrato de supervisión de obras civiles para la rehabilitación de la carretera de Bahramtapa a Bilesuvar (R42) (60 Km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Azerbaidžan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Bahramtapan ja Bilesuvarin välisen tien (60 km) kunnostus, rakennustöiden valvontasopimus (R42)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Azerbaïdjan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bakou</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 - Supervision de la création du contrat de travaux de génie civil pour la réhabilitation de la route R42 reliant Bahramtapa à Bilesuvar (60 km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Αζερμπαϊτζάν</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Μπακού</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Επίβλεψη σύμβασης για την αποκατάσταση του (R42) δρόμου Bahramtapa προς Bilesuvar (60 χλμ.)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Azerbaigian</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - CS-02-EBRD-2018 - Supervisione della costruzione di un contratto di lavori civili per la riabilitazione di (R42) da Bahramtapa a Bilesuvar Road (60 Km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Azerbeidzjan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bakoe</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Toezicht op de bouwopdracht inzake civieltechnische werkzaamheden voor het herstel aan de weg (R42) van Bahramtapa naar Bilesuvar (60 km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Azerbaijão</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Supervisão de Construção de Contrato de Empreitada de Obras para a Reabilitação da Estrada (R42) Bahramtapa a Bilesuvar (60 Km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Azerbajdzjan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 - konstruktion och övervakning av ett civilt byggentreprenadskontrakt för återuppbyggnaden av (R42) vägen Bahramtapa till Bilesuvar (60km).</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Ázerbájdžán</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Stavební dohled nad stavebními pracemi v rámci zakázky pro obnovu silnice č. R42 Bahramtapa – Bilesuvar (60 km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Aserbaidžaan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bakuu</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – (R42) Bahramtapa ja Bilesuvari vahelise maantee (60 km) ümberehitamise tsiviiltööde lepingu kohase ehituse järelevalve</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Azerbajdzsán</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – A Bahramtapa és Bilesuvar közötti (R42) útszakasz (60 km) felújítására irányuló építési beruházásra irányuló szerződés építésfelügyelete</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Azerbaidžanas</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – civilinių darbų sutarties dėl kelio R42 Bahramtapa-Bilesuvar (60 km) rekonstrukcijos statybos priežiūra</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Azerbaidžāna</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Inženiertehnisko būvdarbu līguma uzraudzība saistībā ar (R42) ceļa no Bahramtapas līdz Bilesuvarai (60 km) atjaunošanu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>l-Azerbajġan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Kuntratt għas-superviżjoni ta’ xogħlijiet ċivili ta’ kostruzzjoni għar-riabilitazzjoni ta’ (R42) it-Triq minn Bahramtapa għal Bilesuvar (60 Km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Azerbejdżan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - CS-02-EBRD-2018 - Nadzór budowlany nad realizacją umowy o roboty budowlane w zakresie renowacji drogi (R42) z Bahramtapy do Bilesuvaru (60 km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Azerbajdžan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Zmluva o stavebnom dohľade nad stavebnými prácami pri rekonštrukcii cesty (R42) Bahramtapa – Bilesuvar (60 km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Azerbajdžan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Nadzor gradenj v okviru naročila gradbeniških del za obnovo ceste Bahramtapa–Bilesuvar (R42) (60 km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Asarbaiseáin, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Maoirseacht Foirgníochta an Chonartha Oibreacha Sibhialta d’Athshlánú an Bhóthair (R42) idir Bahramtapa agus Bilesuvar (60 Km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Азербайджан</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Баку</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Строителен надзор на поръчка за строителство за рехабилитацията на път (R42) от Bahramtapa до Bilesuvar (60 Km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Azerbaidjan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Supervizarea construcțiilor Contractului de lucrări publice pentru reabilitarea Drumului (R42) de la Bahramtapa la Bilesuvar (60 Km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Azerbajdžan</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Baku</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Nadzor gradnje za ugovor o građevinskim radovima na sanaciji ceste od Bahramtape do Bilesuvara (R42) (60 km)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Tilsyn med bygge- og anlægsarbejdet for renovering af motorvej (R42) mellem Bahramtapa og Bilesuvar (60 km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Bau und Aufsicht von Bauarbeiten für die Sanierung der Straße von (R42) Bahramtapa nach Bilesuvar (60 km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Construction Supervision of Civil Works Contract for the Rehabilitation of (R42) Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road (60 Km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 - Contrato de supervisión de obras civiles para la rehabilitación de la carretera de Bahramtapa a Bilesuvar (R42) (60 Km) (AZ-Bakú)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Bahramtapan ja Bilesuvarin välisen tien (60 km) kunnostus, rakennustöiden valvontasopimus (R42) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 - Supervision de la création du contrat de travaux de génie civil pour la réhabilitation de la route R42 reliant Bahramtapa à Bilesuvar (60 km) (AZ-Bakou)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Επίβλεψη σύμβασης για την αποκατάσταση του (R42) δρόμου Bahramtapa προς Bilesuvar (60 χλμ.) (AZ-Μπακού)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - CS-02-EBRD-2018 - Supervisione della costruzione di un contratto di lavori civili per la riabilitazione di (R42) da Bahramtapa a Bilesuvar Road (60 Km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Toezicht op de bouwopdracht inzake civieltechnische werkzaamheden voor het herstel aan de weg (R42) van Bahramtapa naar Bilesuvar (60 km) (AZ-Bakoe)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Supervisão de Construção de Contrato de Empreitada de Obras para a Reabilitação da Estrada (R42) Bahramtapa a Bilesuvar (60 Km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 - konstruktion och övervakning av ett civilt byggentreprenadskontrakt för återuppbyggnaden av (R42) vägen Bahramtapa till Bilesuvar (60km). (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Stavební dohled nad stavebními pracemi v rámci zakázky pro obnovu silnice č. R42 Bahramtapa – Bilesuvar (60 km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – (R42) Bahramtapa ja Bilesuvari vahelise maantee (60 km) ümberehitamise tsiviiltööde lepingu kohase ehituse järelevalve (AZ-Bakuu)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – A Bahramtapa és Bilesuvar közötti (R42) útszakasz (60 km) felújítására irányuló építési beruházásra irányuló szerződés építésfelügyelete (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – civilinių darbų sutarties dėl kelio R42 Bahramtapa-Bilesuvar (60 km) rekonstrukcijos statybos priežiūra (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Inženiertehnisko būvdarbu līguma uzraudzība saistībā ar (R42) ceļa no Bahramtapas līdz Bilesuvarai (60 km) atjaunošanu (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Kuntratt għas-superviżjoni ta’ xogħlijiet ċivili ta’ kostruzzjoni għar-riabilitazzjoni ta’ (R42) it-Triq minn Bahramtapa għal Bilesuvar (60 Km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - CS-02-EBRD-2018 - Nadzór budowlany nad realizacją umowy o roboty budowlane w zakresie renowacji drogi (R42) z Bahramtapy do Bilesuvaru (60 km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Zmluva o stavebnom dohľade nad stavebnými prácami pri rekonštrukcii cesty (R42) Bahramtapa – Bilesuvar (60 km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Nadzor gradenj v okviru naročila gradbeniških del za obnovo ceste Bahramtapa–Bilesuvar (R42) (60 km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Maoirseacht Foirgníochta an Chonartha Oibreacha Sibhialta d’Athshlánú an Bhóthair (R42) idir Bahramtapa agus Bilesuvar (60 Km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Строителен надзор на поръчка за строителство за рехабилитацията на път (R42) от Bahramtapa до Bilesuvar (60 Km) (AZ-Баку)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Supervizarea construcțiilor Contractului de lucrări publice pentru reabilitarea Drumului (R42) de la Bahramtapa la Bilesuvar (60 Km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - CS-02-EBRD-2018 – Nadzor gradnje za ugovor o građevinskim radovima na sanaciji ceste od Bahramtape do Bilesuvara (R42) (60 km) (AZ-Baku)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Single Stage Open Competitive Selection – Request for Proposals</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9073-IFT-43094</P><P>Project name: Road Reconstruction and Upgrading Project</P><P>Location: Azerbaijan</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project number: 43094</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract Consultancy Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 25.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 4.6.2018 at 17:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>Name of Agency: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</P><P>Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district,</P><P>Country: Baku, Azerbaijan</P><P>Postal Code: AZ1117</P><P>The Client Contact Person:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ATTENTION>Marahim Alakbarov, PIU Procurement Specialist</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Block 2025, R. Ismayilovstr, Bilajari settlement, Binaqadi district, City: </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Baku</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Postal Code: AZ1117, Country: Azerbaijan, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>m.alakbarov@yahoo.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> copy to </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>vuqar.quliyev@mail.ru</E_MAIL></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>Project Description:</P><P>The Government of the Republic of Azerbaijan (the Borrower) is in receipt of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) and intends to use proceeds from the loan to undertake a project (the Project) of road rehabilitation.</P><P>The works includes the rehabilitation of 60 km Bahramtapa — Bilesuvar road section that starts at the roundabout on the M6 and ends at the junction at the end of the Bilesuvar western bypass. Reconstruction of the 2 lane single carriageway roads mainly follow the existing alignment includes earthworks, construction of pavement, drainage systems, the replacement of three bridges and the installation of road furniture and road markings. The IA intends to award one civil works contract for the rehabilitation of the R42 Bahramtapa to Bilesuvar Road.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Client now intends to select and contract a consulting company (the Consultant) to the Assignment, on the basis of the Consultancy Procurement Document (CPD) in attachment.</P><P>The expected outcome of the Assignment is for the Consultant to assist the Client in the administration of the Bank-funded works contracts (hereinafter also referred to as “the Contract”) and carry out the duties of the Engineer assigned to him in the works contracts.</P><P>The objective of the consultancy services are:</P><P>i) Review of detailed design and approve drawings for construction of the road by the civil works contractor. Revise/update Bill of Quantities on monthly basis in light of available information and report it to the client with remedial actions, if require, as part of monthly progress report.</P><P>ii) Ensure that the permanent and temporary works have been designed and are constructed in accordance with the technical specifications and standards forming part of the civil works contract with the Contractors;</P><P>iii) Advise IA on all matters concerning implementation of the civil works contracts including quality control, progress of work, arbitration or litigation, certification for payments;</P><P>iv) Ensure compliance with safeguards, including the management of environmental mitigation plans;</P><P>v) Provide the staff of the IA with on-site training in contract administration and other procedures relevant to site supervision and contract administration.</P><P>The Consultant shall ensure the timely supervision and control of the civil works and exercise all reasonable care to protect the interests of the Employer. While performing the assignment, reasonable care should be taken to minimize climatic impacts and to implement greenhouse gas reduction measures.</P><P>The Consultant shall be the Engineer under the contracts and perform the duties and authority of the Engineer as defined in the FIDIC Conditions of Contract for Construction for Works designed by the Employer (FIDIC MDB 2010).</P><P>The Consultant shall agree with the Client the duties to be delegated by the Engineer to the site supervision team. All delegations shall be in writing and observe the requirements of Sub-Clause 3.2 of the Conditions of Contract for the civil works.</P><P>The Consultant shall perform the Services in accordance with the laws and any other instruments having force of law in Azerbaijan as may be issued and in force from time to time.</P><P>The selected Consultant is expected to provide the following services:</P><P>— Pre-construction activities,</P><P>— Administration of the civil works contracts,</P><P>— Approval of contractors' materials, construction techniques and programs of works,</P><P>— Direct supervision of the works and monitoring of progress,</P><P>— Technical assistance during works execution,</P><P>— Preparation of mandatory Project reporting,</P><P>— Assisting the Client on Project closure.</P><P>Consultant Selection Procedure: Single stage open competitive selection</P><P>Interested firms of groups of firms are invited to submit a Technical and Financial Proposal.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to start in July 2018 and has an estimated overall duration of 24 months for supervision + 24 months for Defects Liability Period.</P><P>Input estimate for the Assignment: The estimated input of the key experts will be 213 Man-month and estimated input of the non-key experts will be 144 Man-months.</P><P>Subject to availability of funding, the performance of the selected Consultant and the specific needs of the Client the Assignment may be extended beyond the current scope.</P><P>Funding Source: The contract will be financed by the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD). Selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions based on the consultant's country of origin.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the Consultant shall submit a Response in accordance with the CPD.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>1) The selection will normally be made from the Proposals received in response to this notification only, on the basis of the selection criteria set out in the CPD. The highest-ranked Consultant will be selected and be invited to negotiate the contract, subject to availability of funding.</P><P>2) Any updates of and clarifications on this procurement notice and/or the CPD shall be announced as updates on this notice, without any other notification. In the event of changes to the CPD, consultants will need to download the updated version of the CPD. Consultants are required to periodically check the notice for updates. Failure to take the updates into account while preparing the Proposal may result in disqualification or penalties to the scores in the evaluation.</P><P>3) The CPD may be obtained from the office at the address below upon payment of a non-refundable fee of AZN 500 or USD 300 or equivalent in a convertible currency. The method of payment will be cash or by bank transfer to:</P><P>Beneficiary: State Agency of Azerbaijan Automobile Roads, ID No.: 9900013141</P><P>Bank: Azerbaijan International Bank, “Nagliyyat” Branch</P><P>SWIFT: IBAZAZ2X</P><P>Account Number: AZ21IBAZ38050019449345490205 AZN</P><P>AZ11IBAZ38150018409345490205 USD</P><P>Bank Identification Number: 9900001881</P><P>Upon receipt of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the CPD will promptly be dispatched by courier arranged by the Consultant; however, no liability can be accepted for their loss or late delivery.</P><P>If requested, instead of a hard copy the CPD can be dispatched electronically in PDF format. If so, the Consultant is required to send an email requesting documents electronically. Please attach a copy of the receipt issued by the bank for payment made to the bank as described above.</P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s Procurement Policies and Rules (PP&amp;R, Rev. November 2017) which can be located at: http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-andrules.html</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>