<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="073588-2018"
            EDITION="2018034">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-074667-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180320</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>34</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180217</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 034-073588</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:073588-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.regioner.dk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=204941&amp;B=AMGROS</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="22455000">ID cards</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="30160000">Magnetic cards</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="DK">DANMARK</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="DK">DANMARK</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="DKK">55000000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180215</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180320 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="3">Regional or local authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="H">Health</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01B02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Дaния</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Лични карти</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Osobní průkazy</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Id-kort</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Dänemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Personalausweise</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Δανία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ταυτότητες</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Denmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>ID cards</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Carnés de identidad</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Taani</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Isikutunnistused (ID-kaardid)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Tanska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Henkilötodistukset</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Danemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Cartes d'identité</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Danmhairg, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>ID cards</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Osobne iskaznice</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Dánia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Személyi igazolvány</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Danimarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Carte di identità</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Danija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Identifikavimo dokumentai</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Dānija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Personas identifikācijas kartes</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>id-Danimarka</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Karti ta' l-identità</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Denemarken</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Identiteitskaarten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Dania</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dowody tożsamości</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Bilhetes de identidade</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Danemarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Cărţi de identitate</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Identifikačné karty</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Osebne izkaznice</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>ID-kort</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Danske Regioner</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>fe774ffb-40ca-43c6-9fca-7f05f981ec82</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Danske Regioner</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Dampfærgevej 22</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Copenhagen Ø</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2100</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Sarah Maria Friis Steine</CONTACT_POINT>
               <E_MAIL>ssh@amgros.dk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.regioner.dk</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://eu.eu-supply.com/ctm/Company/CompanyInformation/Index/284126</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=204941&amp;B=AMGROS</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=204941&amp;B=AMGROS</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="REGIONAL_AUTHORITY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="HEALTH"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Production and delivery of Health Insurance Cards</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="22455000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SUPPLIES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Production and delivery of Health Insurance Cards.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="DKK">55000000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30160000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>All over Denmark.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Danske Regioner (an interest organisation for the 5 regions in Denmark) wishes to invite interested card suppliers to tender for the production and delivery of health insurance cards and letters to 15-years-olds in Denmark. Danske Regioner is assisted in this process by Amgros I/S (a partnership owned by the regions which consolidates the purchases of the regions).</P>
                  <P>The production and delivery regards the following:</P>
                  <P>1. The National Health Insurance Card:</P>
                  <P>All citizens with permanent residence in Denmark are covered under the public health insurance scheme. As documentation of the right to benefits under the scheme, the Insured must produce a Health Insurance Card when contacting the health care system. The annual production of the Health Insurance Card is approx. 2 000 000.</P>
                  <P>2. The Special Health Insurance Card:</P>
                  <P>The Special Health Insurance Card serves as documentation that persons, despite having no permanent address in Denmark — are entitled to benefits under the Danish Health Act while staying in Denmark on the same terms as people residing in Denmark. An annual production of approx. 15 000-20 000 cards is expected.</P>
                  <P>3. The European Health Insurance Card:</P>
                  <P>The European health insurance covers expenses for necessary medical and hospital treatment, medicine, etc., for temporary stays (i.e. up to 1 year) in an EU member state or EEC member state, e.g. vacations, traineeships, studies or work abroad. An annual production of approx. 900 000 cards are expected.</P>
                  <P>4. Distribution of letters to 15-year-olds:</P>
                  <P>Children who are 15 years of age have a free choice of GP, and are informed of this by letter. Some 68 000 letters are annually distributed to 15-year-olds.</P>
                  <P>The Health Insurance Cards and the letters to 15-year-olds are issued in accordance with Order nº 566 of 29/04/2015. The Special Health Insurance Cards and the European Health Insurance Cards are issued by Udbetaling Danmark in accordance with the Danish Health Act, Chapter 3. The contract is concluded with Danske Regioner as a contracting party and includes the purchase of all of the above mentioned cards and letters.</P>
                  <P>The supplier will be provided with data and shall thereafter be responsible for the production, enveloping, stamping and delivery of cards/letters to the citizens of Denmark. The supplier shall deliver the cards and the letters as general contractor and shall in this capacity be responsible for taking all such action and meet such obligations as are necessary for the delivery. Danske Regioner reserves the right to replace the distribution solution with a solution based on a contract between Danske Regioner and a delivery service.</P>
                  <P>Production and delivery of the card is very important to the Danish society. It is therefore of vital interest to Danske Regioner to ensure that the production and delivery of the cards and letters is professional, efficient and reliable.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">48</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>The 48 months are calculated from the operation date, 1.10.2018. The contract starts with an implementation phase, cf. Appendix 4.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>The tenderer must submit the European Single Procurement Document (“ESPD”) with the following information:</P>
               <P>— the tenderer's equity ratio in the last financial year available,</P>
               <P>— the tenderer's total annual turnover in the last 2 financial years available.</P>
               <P>The ESPD serves as provisional documentation that the tenderer fulfils the minimum suitability requirements in respect of economic and financial capacity.</P>
               <P>Before the decision to award the contract is made, the tenderer to whom the Contracting Authority intends to award the contract must submit documentation that the information stated in the ESPD is accurate.</P>
               <P>When required by the Contracting Authority, the tenderer must submit the following documentation of economic and financial capacity:</P>
               <P>— a statement regarding the operator's equity and assets in the last financial year available, depending on the date on which the operator was established, as far as the figures for equity and assets are available. For groups of operators (e.g. a consortium), the information must be submitted for each participating operator in the group. If the operator relies on the economic and financial capacity of other entities (e.g. a parent company, sister company or a subcontractor), the information must be submitted for these entities also,</P>
               <P>— a statement regarding the operator's overall turnover in the last 2 financial years available, depending on the date when the operator was set up or started trading, as far as the information on these turnovers is available. For groups of operators (e.g. a consortium), the information must be submitted for each participating operator in the group. Where an operator relies on the economic and financial capacity of other entities (e.g. a parent company, sister company or a subcontractor), the information must be submitted for these entities also.</P>
               <P>Where an operator relies on the capacity of other entities (e.g. a parent company, sister company or a subcontractor), regardless of the legal nature of the links between the operator and such other entities, the operator must include documentation in its tender that it will have at its disposal the resources necessary for the performance of the contract by producing an undertaking of support or other documentation that the tenderer has in fact at its disposal the required economic and financial capacity. It must be documented that the entity in question is legally obliged to the tenderer. The Contracting Authority has drawn up a template for the undertaking of support for the candidate to use. Note that the operator and the entity on which the operator relies its capacity on must commit to be jointly and severally liable for the performance of the contract.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>— as a minimum requirement, an equity ratio is required of at least 5 % in the last financial year available. The equity ratio is calculated as the operator’s total equity divided by the operator’s total assets, calculated in per cent. The equity ratio is thus calculated as (total equity/total assets) x 100 = equity ratio. If the tenderer relies on the capacity of other entities, the equity ratio is calculated as the tenderer's and such other entities’ total equity divided by their total assets, calculated in per cent. For groups of operators (e.g. a consortium), the equity ratio is calculated as the total equity of the operators divided by their total assets, calculated in per cent. The information is to be stated in section IV.B of the ESPD. Reference is made to The Danish Competition and Consumer Authority's guide to the ESPD,</P>
               <P>— as a minimum requirement, a total annual turnover of at least DKK 10 000 000 is required in each of the 2 last financial years available. If the tenderer relies on the capacity of other entities, the turnover is to be calculated as the total turnover of the tenderer and such other entities in each of the 2 last financial years available. For groups of operators (e.g. a consortium), the turnover is calculated as the total turnover of the operators in each of the 2 last financial years available. The information is to be stated in Section IV.B of the ESPD. Reference is made to The Danish Competition and Consumer Authority's guide to the ESPD.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>The tenderer must submit the ESPD with the following information:</P>
               <P>— a list of the most significant comparable supplies, see Sections II.1.4) and II.2.4) that the tenderer has carried out in the last 3 years before the expiry of the tender deadline depending on when the tenderer was set up or started trading.</P>
               <P>Only references relating to supplies carried out at the time of submission of tender will be given importance in the evaluation. Hence, in the case of an ongoing task, only the part of the supplies already having been performed at the time of submission of tender will be included in the evaluation of the reference.</P>
               <P>Each reference is requested to include a brief description of the delivery performed. The delivery description should include a clear description of the supplies set out in Sections II.1.4) and II.2.4) to which the delivery related and the tenderer's role(s) in the performance of the delivery. The delivery description should moreover include the financial value of the delivery (amount), the date of the delivery, and the name of the customer (recipient).</P>
               <P>When indicating the date of the delivery, the tenderer is requested to indicate the date when the delivery was commenced and finalized. If that is not possible, e.g. if the tasks were performed on an on-going basis under a framework agreement, the tenderer is asked to indicate in the description of the delivery how the date is specified.</P>
               <P>The ESPD serves as provisional documentation that the tenderer fulfils the minimum suitability requirements in respect of technical and professional capacity, see Section III.1.3).</P>
               <P>Before the decision to award the contract is made, the tenderer to whom the contracting authority intends to award the contract must submit documentation that the information stated in the ESPD is accurate.</P>
               <P>No additional documentation of technical and professional capacity will be required from the tenderer. However, the Contracting Authority reserves the right to contact the tender or the customer indicated in the reference for confirmation of the information stated in the reference, including the dates of the reference indicated.</P>
               <P>Where an operator relies on the capacity of other entities (e.g. a parent company, sister company or a subcontractor) regardless of the legal nature of the links between the operator and such other entities, the operator must include documentation in its tender that it will have at its disposal the resources necessary for the performance of the contract by producing an undertaking of support or other documentation that the candidate or tenderer has in fact at its disposal the required technical and professional capacity. It must be documented that the entity in question is legally bound towards the tenderer. The Contracting Authority has drawn up a template for the undertaking of support that the tenderer may use.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>— as a minimum requirement, the tenderer shall demonstrate that they during the past 3 years have had experience with at least 2 similar deliveries, e.g. production of personalized identity cards or bank/credit card.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>The contract lays down requirements on compliance with the law on processing of personal data.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <FRAMEWORK>
               <SINGLE_OPERATOR/>
            </FRAMEWORK>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-03-20</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="DA"/>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DATE_TENDER_VALID>2018-10-01</DATE_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-03-20</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>12:01</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <ESTIMATED_TIMING>
               <P>2.2022.</P>
            </ESTIMATED_TIMING>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Participation in the tendering procedure may only take place by electronic means via the electronic tendering system used by the Contracting Authority, see the address set out in Section I.3). The tendering procedure is accessed under the tab “Ongoing public procedures”. For access to the tender documents, the tenderer must be registered or register as a user.</P>
               <P>If the tender contains several versions of the same document, the latest uploaded version will apply.</P>
               <P>All communication in connection with the tender procedure, including questions and answers, must be through the electronic tendering system. Questions must be submitted not later than 6.3.2018 at 23:59. Questions asked after this date will be answered if they are received in time for the contracting authority to provide the information required and communicate the answers not later than 6 days before expiry of the application deadline. Questions received later than 6 days before expiry of the deadline cannot expect to be answered.</P>
               <P>Interested operators are requested to keep updated via the electronic tendering system. If the tenderer encounters problems with the system, please contact support by e-mail: dksupport@eu-supply.com or telephone (+45) 70 20 80 14.</P>
               <P>The tenderer must submit as its application an ESPD as preliminary documentation of the circumstances set out in Section 148(1)(i-iii) of the Danish Public Procurement Act (udbudsloven). For groups of operators (e.g. a consortium), a separate ESPD must be submitted for each participating operator. If the tenderer relies on the capacity of other entities, an ESPD must be submitted for each of the entities on which the tenderer relies. Reference is made to The Danish Competition and Consumer Authority's ESPD guide.</P>
               <P>The tenderer will be excluded from participation in the tender procedure if the tenderer is subject to the compulsory grounds for exclusion set out in Sections 135 and 136 of the Danish Public Procurement Act, unless the tenderer has submitted sufficient documentation of its reliability in accordance with section 138 of the Danish Public Procurement Act.</P>
               <P>Before the decision to award the contract is made, the tenderer to whom the contracting authority intends to award the contract must provide documentation of the information submitted in the ESPD pursuant to Sections 151-152, cf. Section 153 of the Danish Public Procurement Act, and Section III.1.2 and III.1.3 of this contract notice.</P>
               <P>The contract value is an estimate based on the costs for production and delivery of the 3 insurance cards and letters to 15-year-olds during the last 4-year-contract period. Note that postage represents a significant part of the contract value. The actual contract value for the coming contract period may vary depending on the actual demand on both cards and letters and whether Danske Regioner choose to make use of the Tender's distribution solution.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Klagenævnet for Udbud (The Compliants Board for Public Procurement)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Nævnenes Hus, Toldboden 2</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Viborg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>8800</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 35291095</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>klfu@erst.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.erhvervsstyrelsen.dk/klagenaevnet-for-udbud</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Pursuant to the Danish Act on the Complaints Board for Public Procurement, etc. (lov om Klagenævnet for Udbud m.v.) (the Act is available (in Danish) at www.retsinformation.dk), the following deadlines apply to the lodging of complaints:</P>
               <P>— before the expiry of 6 months after the Contracting Authority entered into a framework agreement calculated from the day after the day when the Contracting Authority notified the candidates and tenderers concerned, see Section 2(2) of the Act and Section 171(4) of the Danish Public Procurement Act.</P>
               <P>Not later than at the time of lodging a complaint with the Danish Complaints Board for Public Procurement, the complainant must notify the contracting authority in writing that a complaint has been lodged with the Danish Complaints Board for Public Procurement and whether the appeal was lodged during the standstill period, see Section 6(4) of the Act. In cases where the complaint was not lodged during the standstill period, the complainant must furthermore indicate whether a suspensory effect of the complaint has been requested, see Clause 12(1) of the Act.</P>
               <P>The email address of the Complaints Board for Public Procurement is set out in Section VI.4.1).</P>
               <P>The complaints board’s own complaints procedure is available at www.erhvervsstyrelsen.dk</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Konkurrence- og Forbrugerstyrelsen (The Danish Competition and Consumer Authority)</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Carl Jacobsens Vej 35</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Valby</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2500</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 41715000</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>kfst@kfst.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.kfst.dk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-15</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
