<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="075196-2018" EDITION="2018034"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-074622-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180309</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>34</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180217</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 034-075196</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:075196-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="MK"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>http://mtc.gov.mk</IA_URL_GENERAL><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45000000">Construction work</ORIGINAL_CPV><VALUES_LIST><VALUES TYPE="GLOBAL"><SINGLE_VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="MKD">93 280 000,00</VALUE></SINGLE_VALUE></VALUES></VALUES_LIST><REF_NOTICE><NO_DOC_OJS>2017/S 196-404019</NO_DOC_OJS></REF_NOTICE></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180215</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DD_DATE_REQUEST_DOCUMENT>20180309 10:00</DD_DATE_REQUEST_DOCUMENT><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180309 10:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="8">Other</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="1">Lowest price</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>02102</HEADING><DIRECTIVE VALUE="2004/18/EC"/></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бивша югославска република Македония</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Скопие</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Строителни и монтажни работи</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Bývalá jugoslávská republika Makedonie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Stavební práce</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Tidligere Jugoslaviske Republik Makedonien, Den</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bygge- og anlægsarbejder</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>die ehemalige jugoslawische Republik Mazedonien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bauarbeiten</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>πρώην Γιουγκοσλαβική Δημοκρατία της Μακεδονίας</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Σκόπια</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Κατασκευαστικές εργασίες</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Construction work</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Antigua República Yugoslava de Macedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopie</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Trabajos de construcción</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>endine Jugoslaavia Makedoonia Vabariik</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ehitustööd</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>entinen Jugoslavian tasavalta Makedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Rakennustyöt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Ancienne République yougoslave de Macédoine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Travaux de construction</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Poblacht iar-Iúgslavach na Macadóine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Scóipé</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Construction work</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>bivša jugoslavenska Republika Makedonija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Građevinski radovi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Macedónia Volt Jugoszláv Köztársaság</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Szkopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Építési munkák</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>ex Repubblica iugoslava di Macedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lavori di costruzione</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>buvusioji Jugoslavijos Respublika Makedonija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopjė</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Statybos darbai</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>bijusī Dienvidslāvijas Maķedonijas Republika</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Celtniecības darbi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>Dik li kienet ir-Repubblika Jugoslava tal-Maċedonja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Xogħol tal-kostruzzjoni</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>voormalige Joegoslavische Republiek Macedonië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bouwwerkzaamheden</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Była jugosłowiańska republika Macedonii</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Roboty budowlane</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>antiga República jugoslava da Macedónia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Construção</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>fosta Republică iugoslavă a Macedoniei</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lucrări de construcţii</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>bývalá Juhoslovanská republika Macedónsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Stavebné práce</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Nekdanja jugoslovanska republika Makedonija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Gradbena dela</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>F. d. jugoslaviska republiken Makedonien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anläggningsarbete</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Ministry of transport and comunication — Macedonia</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><CONTRACT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="2" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"><CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION><NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of transport and comunication — Macedonia</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>str. Dame Gruev no.6</ADDRESS><TOWN>Skopje</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>1000</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="MK"/><CONTACT_POINT>+38923145557</CONTACT_POINT><PHONE>+389 23145557</PHONE><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>aleksandar.popkostoski@mtc.gov.mk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><URL_GENERAL>http://mtc.gov.mk</URL_GENERAL><URL_BUYER>http://mtc.gov.mk</URL_BUYER></INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><FURTHER_INFORMATION><IDEM/></FURTHER_INFORMATION><SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><IDEM/></SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO><IDEM/></TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO></NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY VALUE="MINISTRY"/><TYPE_OF_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF_NO/></PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION><OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><TITLE_CONTRACT><P>The subject of the contract is the procurement of works for construction of a pipeline in Gostivar, Municipality of Gostivar</P></TITLE_CONTRACT><TYPE_CONTRACT_LOCATION><TYPE_CONTRACT VALUE="WORKS"/></TYPE_CONTRACT_LOCATION><LOCATION_NUTS><LOCATION><P>Municipality of Gostivar</P></LOCATION></LOCATION_NUTS><NOTICE_INVOLVES><PUBLIC_CONTRACT/></NOTICE_INVOLVES><SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><P>all details are given at the tender documentation</P></SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><CPV><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="45000000"/></CPV_MAIN></CPV><F02_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><DIV_INTO_LOT_NO/></F02_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><ACCEPTED_VARIANTS VALUE="NO"/></DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><QUANTITY_SCOPE><NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><TOTAL_QUANTITY_OR_SCOPE><P>104.472.292,00 mkd</P></TOTAL_QUANTITY_OR_SCOPE><COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY CURRENCY="MKD"><VALUE_COST FMTVAL="93280000.00">93 280 000,00</VALUE_COST></COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY></NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><NO_OPTIONS/><NO_RECURRENT_CONTRACT/></QUANTITY_SCOPE><PERIOD_WORK_DATE_STARTING><MONTHS>9</MONTHS></PERIOD_WORK_DATE_STARTING></OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><LEFTI_CONTRACT><CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><P>As part of the bid, it is mandatory for the economic operator to submit a guarantee for the bid in the amount of 3 % of the total value of the bid, VAT excluded.</P><P>The bid guarantee shall be in form of a bank guarantee.</P><P>The bid guarantee should be submitted in original form and in the procedures conducted electronically. Copies shall not be accepted.</P><P>The bank guarantee should be issued from a bank acceptable for the Contracting Authority, using the bid guarantee form for such purpose which is provided in Annex 6 to the tender documentation. The Contracting Authority can charge the bid guarantee if the economic operator:</P><P>— withdraws its bid prior to the expiry of the validity period thereof,</P><P>— does not accept the correction of the arithmetical errors by the commission,</P><P>— does not sign the public procurement contract; and,</P><P>— fails to provide the guarantee for qualitative contract performance.</P><P>The guarantee must have validity period of at least 14 days from the day of expiry of the bid validity. Any bid that does not include a bid guarantee, or contains a guarantee for the bid that is not in accordance with the conditions stipulated in the tender documentation, such bid will be discarded by the Contracting Authority.</P><P>As unacceptable.</P><P>In extraordinary cases, the Contracting Authority can request the bidders to prolong the validity period of the bid guarantee.</P><P>The bid guarantee of the unsuccessful economic operators shall be returned within 7 days upon the conclusion of the public procurement contract with the most advantageous economic operator. The bid guarantee of the economic operator whose bid is selected as most advantageous shall be returned there to upon the signing of the public procurement contract and submitting of a guarantee for qualitative performance of the contract.</P><P>The bid guarantee shall be submitted in the archive of the Ministry of Transport and Communications by the day and hour determined as a bid submission deadline at the latest. Guarantee for high-quality performance of the Contract.</P><P>The condition for signing a contract with the most advantageous economic operator is the provisioning of a guarantee for high-quality performance of the contract in the amount of 10 % of the value of the Public procurement contract.</P><P>The guarantee for high-quality performance of the contract shall be in form of a bank guarantee.</P><P>The guarantee for high-quality performance of the contract should be submitted in original form. Copies shall not be accepted.</P><P>The guarantee for high-quality performance of the contract shall be valid until the full contract implementation.</P><P>Upon the selection of most advantageous bidder, the Contracting Authority shall additionally determine the final date of the guarantee validity.</P><P>The bidder selected as most advantageous one shall submit the guarantee for high-quality performance of the contract to the Contracting Authority within 10 working days upon the contract conclusion. The guarantee for High-quality performance of the contract shall be submitted within the determined period, as follows: by mail or personally in the headquarters of the Contracting Authority.</P><P>The guarantee for high-quality performance of the contract shall be charged if the Contractor fails to fulfil any.</P><P>Of the obligations from the public procurement contract within the due date.</P><P>The guarantee for high-quality performance of the contract shall be returned to the Contractor within 14 days.</P><P>As of the day of the full implementation of the public procurement contract and after the Contractor submits the Bank guarantee for guarantee term to the Contracting Authority.The performance guarantee shall be returned by the Contracting Authority to the Contractor by mail or in person in the head office of the Contracting Authority.</P><P>Guarantee for a guarantee period.</P><P>As a requirement for execution of the public procurement contract, the Contractor shall be obliged to secure a guarantee for a guarantee period in amount of 5 % of the public procurement contract value, VAT included, by which the one shall be obliged, on own expense, to remove all shortcomings occurring as a consequence of substandard execution of works or substandard implementation of material and equipment, as well as for other Shortcomings occurring within the guarantee period and attributed to the Contractor.</P><P>The guarantee for a guarantee period shall be in the form of a bank guarantee.</P></DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><P>The payment shall be effectuated as follows:</P><P>— the payment shall be effectuated via signed and verified temporary situations or via signed and verified situation by the authorized person of the Contractor and the supervisory engineer, submitted to the Contracting Authority upon actually performed work; and</P><P>— the payment shall be effectuated within 360 days upon receiving signed and verified temporary situations or via signed and verified completed situation by authorized person of the contractor and the supervisory engineer, Submitted tin the archive of the contracting authority upon actually performed work.</P></MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><LEGAL_FORM><P>Group of tenderers shall also have the right to submit a tender without the obligation to be associated in the appropriate legal form.</P></LEGAL_FORM><NO_EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS/></CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><F02_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><P>Information and formalities necessary for evaluating if the requirements are met:</P><P>Information and formalities necessary for evaluating if the requirements are met: — statement of the economic operator that, within the last 5 years, it has not had any legally effective judgment for participation in a criminal organization, corruption, fraud or money laundering, pronounced against it;</P><P>— confirmation that it is not subject to an open bankruptcy procedure by a competent authority of the country of registration of the economic operator,</P><P>— confirmation that it is not subject to an open liquidation procedure by a competent authority of the country of registration of the economic operator,</P><P>— confirmation for paid taxes, contributions and other public dues issued by a competent authority in the country where the economic operator is registered,</P><P>— confirmation from the Registry of penalties for committed criminal acts of the legal entities that it was not pronounced with a second penalty prohibiting the participation in the public procedures, the public procurement contract award procedures and the public private partnership procedures,</P><P>— confirmation from the Registry of penalties for committed criminal acts of the legal entities that they were not pronounced with a second penalty for temporary or permanent prohibiting for performing certain activity, and,</P><P>— confirmation that there is no legally effective judgment imposing a misdemeanour sanction involving prohibition to perform a profession, activity or duty, or prohibition to perform a specific activity, imposed against it from the country of registration of the economic operator.</P><P>The statement referred to in indent 1, sub-item 2.5.1 is prepared in an electronic form and signed with an electronic signature by the economic operator, and the same should not be verified by a competent authority.</P><P>The confirmation referred to in indent 2, sub-item 2.5.1, that there are is open bankruptcy procedure, and</P><P>The confirmation referred to indent 3 of sub-item 2.5.1, that there is no open liquidation procedure, as well as the confirmations of the registry of penalties for committed criminal acts referred to in indents 5 and 6 of sub-item 2.5.1, are issued by competent authorities in the country where the economic operator is registered.</P><P>The Central Registry of RM is the competent authority for issuing such confirmations in the Republic of Macedonia. The confirmation referred to in indent 4, sub-item 2.5.1. for paid taxes, contributions and other public dues is issued by a competent authority in the country of registration of the economic operator. The Public Revenues Office is the competent authority in the Republic of Macedonia for issuing of this confirmation. The confirmation referred to in indent 7, sub-item 2.5.1. is issued by the competent authority of the country where.</P><P>The economic operator is registered. The Central Registry of RM is the competent authority for issuing of this confirmation in the Republic of Macedonia.</P><P>The documents referred to in sub-item 2.5.1 must not be older than 6 months counted backwards from the final deadline for submission of the tenders.</P><P>The documents proving the personal standing are submitted in original or a copy verified by the economic operator.</P><P>If the Contracting Authority has any doubts regarding the documents proving the personal standing of the economic operator, it can request information directly from the competent bodies that have issued the documents proving the personal standing.</P><P>If the country where the economic operator is registered does not issue the documents referred to in sub-item 2.5.1 or if the documents do not include all cases stipulated above, the economic operator shall be obliged to submit a statement, verified with a competent authority, declaring that: there are no open bankruptcy procedures.</P><P>Against it; there are no open liquidation procedures, that the economic operator has paid all taxes, contributions.</P><P>And other public dues to the state; that no second penalty prohibiting the participationin public procurement.</P><P>Procedures, contract award procedures or public private partnership procedures was pronounced against the economic operator; that no second penalty for temporary or permanent prohibition for performing a certain activity was pronounced against the economic operator; and that no legally effective judgment for a misdemeanour sanction — prohibition to perform a profession, activity, or duty, that is, a temporary prohibition to perform a certain activity in the country of registration of the tenderer was pronounced against the economic operator.</P><P>The Contracting Authority shall exclude from the procedure for awarding a public procurement contract, any economic operator that:</P><P>— within the last 5 years has had a legally effective judgment pronounced against it for participation in a criminal organization, corruption, fraud or money laundering;</P><P>— is subject to a bankruptcy procedure or a liquidation procedure,</P><P>— has unpaid taxes, contributions or other public dues,</P><P>— has been pronounced with a second penalty prohibiting the participation in public procedures, public procurement contract awarding and public private partnership contracts;</P><P>— has been pronounced with a second penalty for temporary or permanent prohibition for performing of a certain activity;</P><P>— has a misdemeanor sanction involving prohibition to perform a profession, activity or duty, or temporary prohibition to perform a specific activity, and.</P><P>— gives false information or fails to submit the data requested by the Contracting Authority.</P><P>The criteria for proving the capability to perform a professional activity of the economic operators are as follows:</P><P>— The economic operator shall be registered as a natural or a legal entity for performing the activity related to the contract subject or to be part of a relevant professional association in accordance with the regulations of the country of registration and.</P><P>— The economic operator shall possess a License B for construction of category two buildings.</P><P>In accordance with the Law on Construction (Official Gazette of the Republic of Macedonia No 130/09,</P><P>124/10,18/2011,36/2011, 54/2011, 13/2012, 144/2012, 25/2013, 79/2013, 137/2013, 163/2013, 27/2014,</P><P>28/2014 and42/2014)</P></ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><F02_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>ITo qualify as capable of performing the specific contract for public procurement in terms of its economic and financial status, the economic operator must meet the following minimum requirements:</P><P>— minimum total revenue of MKD 120 000 000.00 in the past 3 years (2014, 2015, 2016) and financial status, the economic operator must meet the following minimum requirements:</P><P>— balance sheet statement certified by the competent authority, i.e. audited balance sheet or extracts from the balance sheet statement in cases when the publication.</P><P>Of the balance sheet has been prescribed by law in the country where the economic operator is registered, and</P><P>— extract of the overall turnover of the economic operator- enterprise (data from the income statement issued by a competent authority, i.e. audited income statement) for the last 3 years if the balance sheet and the income statement have been subject to commercial audit, the economic operator shall submit them as evidence that it meets.</P><P>The minimum requirement for establishing the economic and financial status without them being additionally verified by a competent authority.</P><P>If the balance sheet and the income statement have not been subject to commercial audit, the economic operator shall submit them verified, i.e. issued by the competent authority as evidence that it meets the minimum requirement for establishing the economic and financial status. The competent authority in the Republic of Macedonia is the Central Register of the Republic of Macedonia.</P><P>The economic and financial status of the economic operator can be supported by another entity, regardless of the legal connections between the economic operator and the aforementioned entity. If the economic operator proves its economic and financial eligibility referring to the support of another entity, the economic operator shall validate that support by evidence stating that the aforementioned entity shall make available to the economic operator the adequate financial resources.</P><P>No effective court decision for participation in a criminal organization, corruption, fraud or money laundering should be rendered against the entity providing the financial support.</P><P>If the economic operators submit a bid in a group of economic operators, the economic and financial status shall be established by considering the resources of all members of the group. If the group of economic operators acts by the financial support of a third entity, the economic and financial status shall be established in accordance with the aforementioned, i.e. pursuant to Article.</P></EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><EAF_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL><P>In order to qualify as capable of carrying out the relevant public procurement contract in terms of its economic and financial status, the economic operator must fulfill the following minimum requirements:</P><P>— minimum total revenue of MKD 120 000 000.00 in the past 3 years (2014, 2015, 2016).</P></EAF_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL></F02_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI><T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>N order to qualify as capable of carrying out the relevant public procurement contract in terms of its technical or professional ability, the economic operator must fulfill the following minimum requirements:</P><P>— At least three (3) implemented contracts for performed same or similar activities in the past 5 years, of which at least one (1) signed and implemented contract for performed same or similar activity in the past 5 years in an amount not less than MKD 25 000 000.00 including VAT;</P><P>— The economic operator should have at least ten (10) full-time employees (40 hours per week), of whom at least two (2) civil engineers holding B authorization for Engineer for performance in the field of "construction."</P><P>— The economic operator should have employed or engaged at least one (1) expert for safety at work Holding a Certificate for passing a professional exam.</P><P>— Proof that the economic operator should have at its disposal the following minimum required technical equipment: 2 (two) dredgers with a long spoon with a capacity of 0.6-1.0 m<FT TYPE="SUP">3</FT>, 2 (two) pick hammers, 1 (one) movable compressor, 1 (one) vibrating roller, 2 (two) vibro frog-boards, 2 (two) pervibrators and 2 (two) Tippers with minimum capacity of 8m<FT TYPE="SUP">3</FT>.</P></T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><T_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL><P>The economic operator must fulfill the following minimum requirements:</P><P>— At least three (3) implemented contracts for performed same or similar activities in the past 5 years, of which at least one (1) signed and implemented contract for.</P><P>Performed same or similar activity in the past 5 years in an amount not less than MKD 25 000 000.00 including VAT;</P><P>— The economic operator should have at least ten (10) full-time employees (40 hours per week), of whom at least two (2) civil engineers holding B authorization for.</P><P>Engineer for performance in the field of "construction."</P><P>— The economic operator should have employed or engaged at least one (1) expert for safety at work holding a certificate for passing a professional exam.</P><P>— Proof that the economic operator should have at its disposal the following minimum required technical equipment: 2 (two) dredgers with a long spoon with a capacity of 0.6-1.0 m<FT TYPE="SUP">3</FT>, 2 (two) pick hammers, 1 (one) movable compressor, 1 (one) vibrating roller, 2 (two) vibro frog-boards, 2 (two) pervibrators a.</P></T_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL></TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI></F02_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION></LEFTI_CONTRACT><PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE><PT_OPEN/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE><AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><LOWEST_PRICE/></AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE><USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION><P>Additional information about electronic auction: Additional information about electronic auction: The Contracting Authority shall use the electronic auction as the final phase in the open procedure. The subject of the auction is the total price of the public contract subject, that is, the lowest price out of the acceptable tenders submitted in the initial phase of the procedure. The request for participation at the auction shall be electronically delivered through the ESPP following the complete evaluation of the initial tenders, to all economic operators who have submitted acceptable tenders in the first phase of the procedure. Following the complete evaluation of the initial tenders and the approval of the initial ranking list, an automatic notification shall be sent through the ESPP to the registered e-mail address of each economic operator who isnot qualified for participation at the electronic auction, whereas the qualified tenderers for participation at the auction shall be directly submitted with a request for participation at the auction. The request for participation at the auction shall contain the following data: initial auction price, that is the lowest price of the initially submitted tenders; date and hour of commencement and closing of the auction; the interval within which the negative bidding shall be carried out</P><P>(minimal and maximal difference in offered prices); as well as the current rank of the tenderer made on the basis of the initially submitted price. The reached total price at the electronic auction, including all costs and discounts, VAT excluded, for the contract subject, shall involve proportional reduction of prices for each position of the public procurement contract subject.</P></USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION></IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE></AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><P>09/2018</P></FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F2><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_EXISTS_F2><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_NOTICE_F2><PRIOR_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F2 CHOICE="PRIOR_INFORMATION_NOTICE"/><NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 196-404019</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ><DATE_OJ><DAY>12</DAY><MONTH>10</MONTH><YEAR>2017</YEAR></DATE_OJ></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_NOTICE_F2><NO_OTHER_PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION/></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_EXISTS_F2></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F2><CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><TIME_LIMIT><DAY>09</DAY><MONTH>03</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>10:00</TIME></TIME_LIMIT><NO_PAYABLE_DOCUMENTS/></CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><DAY>09</DAY><MONTH>03</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>10:00</TIME></RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><CONDITIONS_FOR_OPENING_TENDERS><DATE_TIME><DAY>09</DAY><MONTH>03</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>10:00</TIME></DATE_TIME><EXISTENCE_AUTHORISED_PERSONS><P>Only the authorised representatives of the tenderers may participate in the procedure for public opening of tenders with providing their own remarks registered in the minutes for the tender opening. At the public opening of tenders, authorised representatives of economic operators must present an authorisation signed by the authorised person of the economic operator. All authorised representatives of the economic operators present at the public opening of tenders should sign an attendance list. The tender opening shall be electronic, via the ESPP, and shall be public.</P><P>The public opening of tenders shall take place on 9.3.2018, at 10:00 hours, in the Ministry of Transport and communications, Skopje.</P><P>All submitted tenders shall be opened in line with the Law on Public Procurement, as follows: one at a time, by reading the name of each economic operator, followed by establishing whether the tenders have been submitted.</P><P>Pursuant to item 7.1 of the tender documentation and whether all tenders have been signed electronically,</P><P>Followed by a reading of tenders respecting the same order of opening. The tenderers which shall fail to meet the requirements referred to in the tender documentation shall be excluded from the further procedure, that is, they shall not be invited to the electronic auction. None of the tenders shall be rejected at the opening of the tenders,</P><P>except for the late tenders the public procurement commission shall open the tenders even if only one tender is received. In that case, there shall be no electronic auction. The condition for having an electronic auction is to receive at least 2 acceptable tenders in the procedure during the public opening of tenders and evaluation of the initially submitted tenders, minutes shall be kept inline with the rule book for the procedure for tenders opening and the form for minutes keeping at tenders opening ('Official Gazette of the Republic of Macedonia' Nº 154/07), as well as a Report on the</P><P>conducted procedure prior to evaluating the tenders, the commission shall check whether a negative reference was publishedtill</P><P>The expiry of the deadline for submission of tenders and shall verify the completeness and validity of the documentation proving the tenderer's capability. Unacceptable tenders shall not be evaluated by the Commission.</P></EXISTENCE_AUTHORISED_PERSONS></CONDITIONS_FOR_OPENING_TENDERS></ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/><ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><P>The procurement holder is obliged to perform the planned works within a period of 9 (nine) calendar months.The period for performance of the works starts with the day of introducing the Procurement Holder with the work.</P><P>The performance of the works will be done in accordance with the dynamic plan for performance of the works, proposed by the economic operator, whereby Form for the proposed dynamic plan, specified in Part II.6 of the tender documentation shall be used.</P><P>The deadline for performance of the works, subject of the public procurement contract shall be mandatory for the selected procurement holder.</P><P>For each delay with the deadline for performance of the works, subject of the public procurement contract,</P><P>The economic operator agrees to pay the Contracting Authority a contractual penalty of 1 % (one percent) of the total agreed price for the works for each day of delay if the works are not completed within the planned period, whereby the amount of the contractual penalty agreed in such manner must not exceed 5 % (five percent) of the total agreed price for the works.</P><P>Each bid containing deadline for performance of the works different from the planned deadline referred to in sub-item 2.2.3. of the tender documentation shall be deemed unacceptable and it shall be rejected by the public Procurement Commission. Deadline, method and terms of payment The payment shall be effectuated as follows:</P><P>— the payment shall be effectuated via signed and verified temporary situations or via signed and verified situation by the authorized person of the Contractor and the Supervisory Engineer, submitted to the Contracting Authority upon actually performed work; and</P><P>— the payment shall be effectuated within 360 days upon receiving signed and verified temporary situations or via signed and verified completed situation by authorized person of the Contractor and the supervisory engineer, submitted tin the archive of the Contracting Authority upon actually performed work.</P></ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>State Appeals Commission</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>bul.Ilinden 63A</ADDRESS><TOWN>Skopje</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>1000</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="MK"/><PHONE>+389 23251251</PHONE><URL>http://dkzjn.mk</URL></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><LODGING_OF_APPEALS><LODGING_OF_APPEALS_PRECISION><P>The appeal shall be submitted within eight days starting from the day of:</P><P>— publication of the contract award notice with reference to the data, actions or failure to undertake actions related to the notice;</P><P>— opening of the tenders reference to the data, actions or failure to undertake actions related to the tender documentation, that is, the tender opening procedure;</P><P>— expiry of the time frame for adoption of a decision for selection or cancellation of the procedure pursuant to Article 162 paragraph 2 of the Public Procurement Law regarding the failure to make a decision for selection or cancellation of the procedure in the relevant time frame;</P><P>— receiving of the decision for selection of the most advantageous tender or the decision for cancellation of the procedure, or</P><P>— findings about irregularities in the management of the contract award procedure, within 1 year at the latest starting from the day of the termination of the implemented procedure.</P><P>The timeframe to lodge an appeal regarding the determining of the tenderers' capability and the overall evaluation of the initial tenders shall be counted from the date of receipt of the decision deciding on the individual right from the contract award procedure following the electronic auction completion.</P><P>8.3.4 The economic operator that failed to lodge an appeal with respect to the provisions stipulated in sub-item.</P><P>8.3.2 shall not have a right to an appeal in a later stage of the procedure for the same legal basis.</P><P>8.3.5. The appeal should contain the following elements:</P><P>— data on the submitter of the appeal (name, surname, name of the economic operator, address of residence and registered address);</P><P>— data on the representative or the proxy,</P><P>— name and registered address of the Contracting Authority,</P><P>— number and date of the contract award procedure and data on the contract notice,</P><P>— number and date of the decision for selection of the most advantageous tender, cancellation of the procedure or other decisions of the Contracting Authority;</P><P>— data on the actions or failure to undertake actions by the Contracting Authority,</P><P>— description of the factual situation,</P><P>— description and explanation of the irregularities,</P><P>— appeal and/or claim for compensation of procedure costs; and -signature and seal of an authorised person.</P><P>8.3.6. The submitter of the appeal shall be obliged to submit a proof of payment of the fee for procedure implementation.</P><P>8.3.7. The submitter of the appeal whose registered address is not on the territory of the Republic of Macedonia shall be obliged to determine a proxy to receive writs.</P><P>8.3.8. The appeal shall be lodged with the State Appeals Commission. The appeal shall be submitted in person or by registered mail to both the contracting authority and the state appeals commission. The day when the appeal is sent by registered mail shall be deemed as the day when the appeal was submitted. In case the appeal is submitted in person, the contracting authority shall be obliged to issue a confirmation of the time of the receipt to the submitter.8.3.9. In the procedure before the state appeals commission, the appellant shall, in addition to the administrative fee, be liable to pay a fee for implementing the procedure depending on the amount of the tender, as follows:</P><P>— up to 20 000 EUR in MKD counter-value, a fee of 100 EUR in MKD counter-value,</P><P>— from 20 000 to 100 000 EUR in MKD counter-value, a fee of 200 EUR in MKD counter-value,</P><P>— from 100 000 to 200 000 EUR in MKD counter-value, a fee of 300 EUR in MKD counter-value, or,</P><P>— over 200 000 EUR in MKD counter-value, a fee of 400 EUR in MKD counter-value 8.3.10. In case when there is no tender, the amount of the fee for procedure implementation shall be calculated on the basis of the estimated value of the public procurement contract, and the state appeals commission shall inform the appellant about the amount of the fee and the deadline in which the appellant needs to submit prooffor payment of the fee</P><P>8.3.11. The procedure implementation fee shall be revenue of the Budget of the Republic of Macedonia.</P></LODGING_OF_APPEALS_PRECISION></LODGING_OF_APPEALS><LODGING_INFORMATION_FOR_SERVICE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>State Appeals Commission</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>bul.Ilinden 63A</ADDRESS><TOWN>Skopje</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>1000</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="MK"/><PHONE>+389 23251251</PHONE><URL>http://dkzjn.mk</URL></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></LODGING_INFORMATION_FOR_SERVICE></PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE><DAY>15</DAY><MONTH>02</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR></NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></FD_CONTRACT></CONTRACT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>