<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="008461-2018"
            EDITION="2018006">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-007955-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20190108</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>6</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180110</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 006-008461</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:008461-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.testvalley.gov.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45000000">Construction work</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="70110000">Development services of real estate</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71000000">Architectural, construction, engineering and inspection services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKJ3">Hampshire and Isle of Wight</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKJ3">Hampshire and Isle of Wight</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180108</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="3">Regional or local authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01A01</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Строителни и монтажни работи</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Stavební práce</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Bygge- og anlægsarbejder</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Bauarbeiten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Κατασκευαστικές εργασίες</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Construction work</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Trabajos de construcción</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ehitustööd</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Rakennustyöt</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Travaux de construction</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Construction work</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Građevinski radovi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Építési munkák</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Lavori di costruzione</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Statybos darbai</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Celtniecības darbi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Xogħol tal-kostruzzjoni</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Bouwwerkzaamheden</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Roboty budowlane</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Construção</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Lucrări de construcţii</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Stavebné práce</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Gradbena dela</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Andover</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Anläggningsarbete</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Test Valley Borough Council</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F01_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F01" LG="EN">
         <NOTICE TYPE="PRI_ONLY"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Test Valley Borough Council</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Beech Hurst, Weyhill Road</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Andover</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>SP10 3AJ</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <E_MAIL>marketengagement@testvalley.gov.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKJ3"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.testvalley.gov.uk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="REGIONAL_AUTHORITY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Redevelopment Site in Andover</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="45000000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The Council wishes to explore the opportunities to undertake a mixed redevelopment with a partner to deliver on its aspirations for a cultural quarter in Andover and is seeking responses as follows:</P>
               <P>— Option A: the sites owned by the Council comprising the Magistrates Court, adjacent car park and The Lights Theatre.</P>
               <P>— Option B: all of the Council owned sites in Option A above plus the Council owned car park adjacent to the new leisure centre, the site owned by Andover College and the site of Anton House owned by Simplyhealth. Any redevelopment should allow for the ongoing provision of the type of facilities currently provided by The Lights Theatre, accommodation for Andover College and to maintain at least the same number of pay and display car parking spaces. Simplyhealth are interested in all potential opportunities which could include a reprovision on site or meeting their requirements at another site in Andover.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="70110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="71000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKJ3"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Andover, Hampshire, UK.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Option A.</P>
                  <P>Test Valley Borough Council acquired the Andover Magistrates Court site when the building ceased to be used as a Magistrates Court together with the adjacent 51 space car park which has latterly been operated as a pay and display car park though it is currently in temporary use as a building site compound.</P>
                  <P>The property is situated in an area that the Council has an aspiration to become a “cultural quarter”. Adjacent to the Magistrates Court building is The Lights theatre, a Council owned and operated facility. A new Leisure Centre to be operated for the Council by Places for People is also under construction in close proximity (being constructed on the site of the old leisure centre that is being demolished) and is due to be completed in 2019.</P>
                  <P>Option B.</P>
                  <P>To include all of Option A above and 2 adjacent sites owned by Andover College (largely a 16-18-year-old college) and Simplyhealth (Anton House) which are in close proximity and may be included in the redevelopment site along with the Council owned 40 space Car Park for Andover Leisure Centre (ALC).</P>
                  <P>The Magistrates Court, Theatre, Leisure Centre and College all form part of an open quarter (respecting the necessity for college safeguarded zones) with public footpaths through the grounds with Simplyhealth and the ALC Car Park adjacent. The area of the new quarter is located opposite a Lidl supermarket with The Chantry shopping centre, bus station and multi storey car park beyond, just over 100 metres to the south.</P>
                  <P>The quarter is readily accessible from Andover’s inner ring road, with part of the site fronting Western Avenue and surrounding roadways.</P>
                  <P>Andover is one of the main commercial centres of North Hampshire and currently has a population in the region of 47 000 which is planned to substantially increase over the coming years. Several large organisations and companies are based in the town including Simplyhealth, Stannah Lifts, Twinings, Co-Op, Ocado and The British Army’s Land Forces Administrative HQ.</P>
                  <P>Andover benefits from excellent road communications with the A303 Exeter to Basingstoke trunk road passing along the southern edge of the town and linking to the motorway at junction 8 of the M3 at Basingstoke and also via the A34 interchange at Bullington Cross (7 miles east of Andover) to the M4 at Newbury. Approximate distances to nearby towns include Basingstoke 22 miles, Newbury 17 miles, Salisbury 18 miles, Winchester 16 miles, Southampton 29 miles and London 68 miles.</P>
                  <P>Andover is also served by a mainline railway station on the London Waterloo to Exeter line. The station is just under half a mile from the site.</P>
                  <P>The Council wishes to explore the opportunities to undertake a mixed redevelopment with a partner to deliver on its aspirations for a cultural quarter in Andover, potentially to include the Magistrates Court and The Lights buildings with the option to extend this area to include the sites of Andover College, Simplyhealth and the ALC Car Park. Any redevelopment should allow for the ongoing provision of the type of facilities currently provided by The Lights Theatre, The Andover College Campus and car parking provision. Simplyhealth are interested in all potential opportunities which could include a reprovision on site or meeting their requirements at another site in Andover.</P>
                  <P>Developer Days are scheduled for 28 February and 01, 12, 13, 14, 19, 20 and 22 March 2018. We are proposing meetings of around 2 hours for developers interested in Option A or 3 hours for those interested in Option B that also includes Andover College, Anton House (Simplyhealth) and the ALC Car Park.</P>
                  <P>The first phase of work will be to engage the appropriate professional advice to assist the Council in:</P>
                  <P>— understanding what options the market is likely to identify for the site.</P>
                  <P>— how the Council could set about structuring any partnership arrangement.</P>
                  <P>— how best to go about taking the site to market.</P>
                  <P>— the tendering arrangements to bring forward proposals for a scheme on the site.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>The market engagement exercise will seek the views of potential developers through 1-to-1 meetings in Andover and will be used to inform the design of the commercial arrangements, understand what options the market is likely to identify for the sites and inform the procurement strategy.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>2018-06-01</DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>For further details regarding Test Valley Borough Council, to request a plan of the site or to arrange a meeting please contact marketengagement@testvalley.gov.uk</P>
               <P>For further details regarding Andover College please contact Suzanne Grant suzanne.grant@sparsholt.ac.uk</P>
               <P>For further details regarding Simplyhealth please contact Gareth Williams Gareth.Williams@simplyhealth.co.uk</P>
               <P>This Prior Information Notice is not a call for competition. Participating in this market engagement exercise is not a pre-requisite to participating in any procurement activity that may arise in relation to this opportunity.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-01-08</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F01_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
