<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="192514-2018" EDITION="2018085"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-195571-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180531</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>85</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180503</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 085-192514</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:192514-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>https://www.gov.uk/government/organisations/ministryofdefence/about/procurement</IA_URL_GENERAL><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="50111000">Fleet management, repair and maintenance services</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="42418500">Mechanical handling equipment</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="43300000">Construction machinery and equipment</ORIGINAL_CPV><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="00">Not specified / Other</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS><VALUES_LIST><VALUES TYPE="GLOBAL"><RANGE_VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="GBP">450 000 000</VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="GBP">600 000 000</VALUE></RANGE_VALUE></VALUES></VALUES_LIST></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180501</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180531 17:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="4">Negotiated procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>01317</HEADING><DIRECTIVE VALUE="2009/81/EC"/></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Бристол</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Услуги по управление, техническо обслужване и ремонт на автомобилния парк</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Řízení vozového parku, opravy a údržba</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Forvaltning af bilpark, reparations- og vedligeholdelsestjenesteydelser</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Verwaltung, Reparatur und Wartung von Fahrzeugparks</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Μπρίστολ</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Υπηρεσίες διαχείρισης, επισκευής και συντήρησης στόλου οχημάτων</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Fleet management, repair and maintenance services</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Servicios de administración, reparación y mantenimiento de parque de vehículos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Sõidukipargi haldamis-, remondi- ja hooldusteenused</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ajokaluston hoito, korjaus ja huolto</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Services de gestion, de réparation et d'entretien de parc de véhicules</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Briostó</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Fleet management, repair and maintenance services</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Usluge upravljanja voznim parkom, usluge popravaka i usluge održavanja voznog parka</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Járműállomány-javítási és karbantartási szolgáltatások</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Gestione del parco macchine, servizi di riparazione e di manutenzione</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristolis</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Parko valdymo, remonto ir priežiūros darbai</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristole</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Autoparka vadības, remonta un apkopes pakalpojumi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Amministrazzjoni tal-flotta tal-vetturi, servizzi ta’ tiswija u manutenzjoni</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Beheer, reparatie en onderhoud van wagenpark</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Zarządzanie flotą pojazdów; usługi konserwacyjne i naprawcze</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Serviços de gestão, reparação e manutenção de frota de veículos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Servicii de gestionare, de reparare şi de întreţinere a parcurilor de vehicule</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Správa, opravy a údržba vozového parku</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Storitve upravljanja, popravila in vzdrževanja voznega parka</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Skötsel, reparation och underhåll av bilpark</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Ministry of Defence, Land Equipment, OSP Programme Management Office (PGMO)</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><CONTRACT_DEFENCE CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="17" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE CTYPE="SERVICES"><CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, Land Equipment, OSP Programme Management Office (PGMO)</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Spruce 3c, #1309</ADDRESS><TOWN>Bristol</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>BS34 8JH</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><CONTACT_POINT>MITER Commercial Team</CONTACT_POINT><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>DESLELCA-Comrcl-MITER@mod.gov.uk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><URL_GENERAL>https://www.gov.uk/government/organisations/ministryofdefence/about/procurement</URL_GENERAL></INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><FURTHER_INFORMATION><IDEM/></FURTHER_INFORMATION><SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><CONTACT_DATA><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, Land Equipment, OSP Programme Management Office (PGMO)</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS/><TOWN>Bristol</TOWN><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>DESLELCA-Comrcl-MITER@mod.gov.uk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CONTACT_DATA></SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO><IDEM/></TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO></NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY VALUE="MINISTRY"/><TYPE_OF_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF_NO/></PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><TITLE_CONTRACT><P>Project MITER: Service Provision Arrangement For Military Construction and Mechanical Handling Capability</P></TITLE_CONTRACT><TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><TYPE_CONTRACT VALUE="SERVICES"/><SERVICE_CATEGORY_DEFENCE>26</SERVICE_CATEGORY_DEFENCE></TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><LOCATION_NUTS><LOCATION><P>Not specified / Other.</P></LOCATION><n2016:NUTS CODE="00"/></LOCATION_NUTS><SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><P>Fleet management, repair and maintenance services. Mechanical handling equipment. Construction machinery and equipment. The Authority has a requirement for the fleet management of earth-moving, engineer construction and materiel handling capabilities required to undertake tasks in the United Kingdom (UK), on deployed operations and overseas.</P><P>A Dynamic Pre-Qualification Questionnaire has been published on Defence Contracts Online for interested parties to complete and submit by 17:00 on Wednesday 31.5.2018. The requirement is currently delivered through the following three contracts:</P><P>CVehicles (EVP/7) – Comprises of engineering, construction and plant equipment to enable manoeuvre, construction, logistics, force protection engineering and life support. Provided under a Private Finance Initiative contract ending in 2021, whereby the current equipment fleet is.</P><P>Owned by the contractor and loaned to MOD on demand.</P><P>Protected Plant (OSVP/0011) – Engineering Plant protected against a range of blast and ballistic threats. The small protected construction plant fleet is owned by MOD and supported by industry under a contract also ending in 2021.</P><P>Defence Mechanical Handling Equipment (DMHE) (SPPT/0015) – Pure Commercial off the Shelf mechanical handling equipment across Defence and as part of the logistic supply chain. It is currently almost entirely provided under the DMHE contract, ending in 2020. The equipment fleet is owned by the contractor and provided to MOD on a period lease basis.</P><P>MITER seeks to bring these 3 separate arrangements together under a single fleet management and support/service provision arrangement from 2020. The primary role of the MITER contractor will be to manage and sustain the combined construction and mechanical handling equipment.</P><P>Fleet in the United Kingdom (UK), on deployed operations and overseas environments. As the existing arrangements have different expirations date, a transition approach into project MITER may be required.</P><P>Currently, this combined activity consists of approximately 4 600 pieces of equipment at approximately 300 locations in 14 countries. The future scenario is expected to be broadly similar, although work is underway to establish the scope for rationalisation and efficiencies and.</P><P>The effect of the recent Strategic Defence and Security Review.</P></SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><CPV><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="50111000"/></CPV_MAIN><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="42418500"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="43300000"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL></CPV><SUBCONTRACTING><INDICATE_ANY_SHARE VALUE="YES"/><INDICATE_ANY_CHANGE VALUE="YES"/><SUBCONTRACT_AWARD_PART VALUE="NO"/><IDENTIFY_SUBCONTRACT VALUE="NO"/></SUBCONTRACTING><F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><DIV_INTO_LOT_NO/></F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS></DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><QUANTITY_SCOPE><NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><TOTAL_QUANTITY_OR_SCOPE><P>MITER is required to support operations in 3 operational environments:</P><P>Firm Base — This represents enduring UK forces locations, currently still including Germany and Cyprus.</P><P>Deployed Benign — Operations, which can be temporary or semi-permanent in nature, in low threat and potentially remote and/or environmentally testing conditions. This environment includes places such as Permanent Joint Operating Bases (PJOBs), overseas training areas e.g. Canada (BATUS), Kenya (BATUK), Brunei and other enduring but non-permanent deployments where combat operations are not being conducted. Assets at sea are also included.</P><P>Deployed Tactical - Overseas military operations involving armed conflict which constitute a contingent commitment and are temporary in nature. Sponsored Reserves (SRs) may be appropriate. This environment gives rise to the need for equipment to be held at readiness and ‘train as you fight’ activity conducted in other environments.</P><P>As the MITER requirement relates to the provision of services used for military purposes the Authority will follow the Defence and security public contract regulations in respect of this procurement.</P><P>The Authority has conducted previous industry engagement using Defence Contracts Online(DCO) and has communicated previous Industry Briefing Events by Prior Information Notices (PIN). Previous Industry Briefing events were held in October 2017 and March 2018.</P><P>Information provided at the Industry Briefing events is available on the MITER Award Data room.</P><P>Reverse auctions and Lots will not be used for the procurement of MITER.</P><P>MITER will utilise the Whole Force Approach (WFA) Initiative.</P><P>The intent of Whole Force Approach is to create an effective, agile and resilient capability delivered by an integrated, pre-planned and affordable mix of regular and reserve military, civilian and industry resources to meet Defence Outputs.</P><P>Any military capability which has components delivered by anything other than Regular military manpower, is a WFA capability. WFA will normally encompass the means chosen to deliver capabilities (both in terms of the make-up of the solution and the contracting mechanisms put in place) in benign or semi-benign environments; however, recent performance of Contractor Support to Operations (CSO) demonstrates that there is industry appetite and capability to also operate in non-benign environments.</P><P>Any service which is routinely offered in the commercial market can be defined as ‘commoditised’; if components of a military capability include routinely commoditised services, an assessment must be made as to whether industry resource may be more effective and / or efficient than military resource.</P><P>WFA seeks to balance delivery risk between the MOD (as the customer) and industry (as the supplier). The challenge is to develop WFA capabilities that explicitly explore and exploit every opportunity to optimise the benefits for every Defence line of development (DLOD) at the outset, including training, equipment, infrastructure and personnel.</P><P>The capability supports military task achievement across the range of MITER environments through the provision of non-military (Civil servants, contractors) / military (Regulars, Regular reserves (RR), Sponsored reserves (SR) Operators that are appropriate to task, the operating environment and most attractive in terms of value for money and risk.</P><P>Operator provisioning:</P><P>— Firm Base - non-military/ military personnel,</P><P>— Deployed Benign - non-military/ military personnel,</P><P>— Deployed Tactical - military personnel.</P><P>The contracting Authority will be using the Award system to conduct the competition, the system will be used to issue any invitations to negotiate and to manage the tender evaluation process. Although Award access is not required to complete the Dynamic pre-qualification questionnaire it is recommended that access is requested via e-mail (DESLELCA-Comrcl-MITER@mod.gov.uk). Please ensure any e-mail requests include a contact name, company name and e-mail address.</P><P>The Authority will trade using the electronic ‘Contracting, purchasing and finance system (CP &amp; F). Before partaking in the DPQQ any interested parties should ensure that they have the future ability to trade electronically and connect to the CP and F System in the event of being successful.</P><P>The closing date for DPQQ Submissions will be Thursday 31st 30.5.2018 (17:00). 30 calendar days after online publication of the DPQQ.</P><P>Following down selection, the Authority intends to invite 3 preferred bidders to negotiate. Following negotiations, the preferred bidders will be requested to submit best and final offers for consideration.</P><P>The Authority expects to issue Invitations to negotiate (ITN) in mid July 2018. A bidder’s conference is expected to be held in August 2018, after the ITN documents have been issued.</P></TOTAL_QUANTITY_OR_SCOPE><COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY CURRENCY="GBP"><RANGE_VALUE_COST><LOW_VALUE FMTVAL="450000000">450 000 000</LOW_VALUE><HIGH_VALUE FMTVAL="600000000">600 000 000</HIGH_VALUE></RANGE_VALUE_COST></COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY></NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><OPTIONS><OPTION_DESCRIPTION><P>The duration of the contract is 7 years (2020-2027). The Authority is seeking the option to extend the Contract by a maximum of 3 years.</P><P>— Option 1: Option to extend contract for 1 year (2027 - 2028).</P><P>— Option 2: Option to extend contract for 1 year (2028 - 2029).</P><P>— Option 3: Option to extend contract for 1 year (2029 - 2030).</P></OPTION_DESCRIPTION></OPTIONS></QUANTITY_SCOPE></OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><P>The Authority will apply all the offences listed in Article 39(1) of Directive 2009/81/EC (implemented as Regulation 23(1) of the Defence and Security Public Contract Regulations (DSPCR) 2011 in the UK) and all of the professional misconducts listed at Article 39(2) of Directive 2009/81/EC (see also Regulation 23(2) in the DSPCR 2011) to the decision of whether a Candidate is eligible to be invited to tender.</P><P>A full list of the Regulation 23(1) and 23(2) criteria are at http://www.contracts.mod.uk/delta/project/reasonsForExclusion.html#dspr</P><P>Candidates will be required to sign a declaration confirming whether they do or do not have any of the listed criteria as part of the pre-qualification process.</P><P>Candidates who have been convicted of any of the offences under Article 39(1) are ineligible and will not be selected to bid, unless there are overriding requirements in the general interest (including defence and security factors) for doing so.</P><P>Candidates who are guilty of any of the offences, circumstances or misconduct under Article 39(2) may be excluded from being selected to bid at the discretion of the Authority.</P></ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION></F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION></LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><PT_NEGOTIATED_CHOICE/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED><OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA/></MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><P>OSP/0080</P></FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><DAY>31</DAY><MONTH>05</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>17:00</TIME></RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><LANGUAGE><LANGUAGE_EC VALUE="EN"/></LANGUAGE></ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE></PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/><RELATES_TO_EU_PROJECT_NO/><ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><P>The Contracting Authority considers that this contract may be suitable for economic operators that are small or medium enterprises (SMEs). However, any selection of tenderers will be based solely on the criteria set out for the procurement. The Authority reserves the right to amend any condition related to security of information to reflect any changes in national law or government policy. If any contract documents are accompanied by instructions on safeguarding classified information (e.g. a Security aspects letter), the Authority reserves the right to amend the terms of these instructions to reflect any changes in national law or government policy, whether in respect of the applicable protective marking scheme, specific protective markings given, the aspects to which any protective marking applies, or otherwise. The link below to the Gov.uk website provides information on the Government security classification.</P><P>https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/government-security-classifications</P><P>Advertising Regime OJEU: — This contract opportunity is published in the Official Journal of the European Union (OJEU),the MoD Defence Contracts Bulletin and www.contracts.mod.uk</P><P>Suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P><P>The information and/or documents for this opportunity are available on http://www.contracts.mod.uk</P><P>You must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password. Please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P><P>Suppliers must log in, go to your Response manager and add the following Access Code: 363ZM4429G.</P><P>Please ensure you follow any instruction provided to you here.</P><P>The deadline for submitting your response(s) is detailed within this contract notice, you will also have visibility of the deadline date, once you have added the Access code via DCO as the opening and closing date is visible within the opportunity.</P><P>Please ensure that you allow yourself plenty of time when responding to this opportunity prior to the closing date and time, especially if you have been asked to upload documents.</P><P>If you experience any difficulties please refer to the online Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ&#x92;s) or the User Guides or contact the MOD DCO Helpdesk by emailing support@contracts.mod.uk or Telephone 0800 282 324.</P><P>GO Reference: GO-201851-DCB-12338543.</P></ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, Land Equipment, Operational Support Programmes (OSP)</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><TOWN>Bristol</TOWN><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>DESLELCA-Comrcl-MITER@mod.gov.uk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><MEDIATION_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, Land Equipment, Operational Support Programmes (OSP)</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><TOWN>Bristol</TOWN><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>DESLELCA-Comrcl-MITER@mod.gov.uk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></MEDIATION_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><LODGING_INFORMATION_FOR_SERVICE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, Land Equipment, OSP Programme Management Office (PGMO)</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><TOWN>Bristol</TOWN><COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>DESLELCA-Comrcl-MITER@mod.gov.uk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></LODGING_INFORMATION_FOR_SERVICE></PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE><DAY>01</DAY><MONTH>05</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR></NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE></CONTRACT_DEFENCE></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>