<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="163369-2018" EDITION="2018074"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-159245-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180503</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>74</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180417</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 074-163369</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:163369-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="RO"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71356200">Technical assistance services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180410</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180503 15:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>BR605</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Rumænien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - Vandforsyning i Constanta — Udarbejdelse af en resultatbaseret tjenesteydelsesaftale
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Rumänien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - Constanta Water — Anfertigung einer erfolgsabhängigen Dienstleistungsvereinbarung
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Romania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Rumanía</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Agua de Constanta: preparación de un contrato de servicios basado en el rendimiento
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Romania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Constanțaa koskeva vesihanke – suorituskykyyn perustuvan palvelusopimuksen valmistelu
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Roumanie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Eau de Constanta - Préparation de résultats basés sur l'accord de services
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Ρουμανία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - Εταιρεία Ύδρευσης της Constanta — Προετοιμασία σύμβασης παροχής υπηρεσιών με βάση την καλή εκτέλεση
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Romania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - Rete idrica di Costanza — Preparazione di un accordo di servizi basato sulle prestazioni
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Roemenië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - Watervoorziening in Constanta — voorbereiding van een prestatiegerelateerde dienstenovereenkomst
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Roménia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Águas de Constanta — Preparação de um acordo de serviço baseado em desempenho
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Rumänien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Constanta Water - förberedelse av ett prestationsbaserat tjänsteavtal
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Rumunsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Voda ve městě Constanta – příprava servisní smlouvy založené na výkonu
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Rumeenia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Constanta vesi – tulemuspõhise teenuslepingu ettevalmistamine
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Románia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Konstancai vízügyi vállalat — Teljesítményalapú szolgáltatási megállapodás elkészítése
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Rumunija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - Konstancos vanduo – rezultatais pagrįstos paslaugų pirkimo sutarties parengimas
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Rumānija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - Konstancas ūdens — uz rezultātiem balstīta pakalpojumu līguma sagatavošana
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>ir-Rumanija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - Ilma ta' Constanta — It-Tħejjija ta' Ftehim għal Servizz Ibbażat fuq il-Prestazzjoni
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Rumunia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt wodny w Konstancy — przygotowanie umowy o usługi uzależnionej od wyników
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Rumunsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Vodovodná sieť v meste Constanta – príprava zmluvy o poskytovaní služieb založenej na výkonnosti
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Romunija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt oskrbe z vodo za Constanto – Priprava sporazuma o storitvah na podlagi uspešnosti
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Rómáin, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Uisce Constanța — Comhaontú seirbhíse bunaithe ar fheidhmíocht a ullmhú
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Pyмъния</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - Водоснабдяване в Констанца — Изготвяне на споразумение за услуги въз основа на изпълнението
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>România</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Alimentarea cu apă în Constanța — Pregătirea unui contract de prestări servicii bazat pe performanță
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Rumunjska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Constanta</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Vodoopskrba Constante — priprema sporazuma o uslugama temeljenog na učinkovitosti
			</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">S.C. RAJA S.A.</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - Vandforsyning i Constanta — Udarbejdelse af en resultatbaseret tjenesteydelsesaftale
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - Constanta Water — Anfertigung einer erfolgsabhängigen Dienstleistungsvereinbarung
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Agua de Constanta: preparación de un contrato de servicios basado en el rendimiento
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Constanțaa koskeva vesihanke – suorituskykyyn perustuvan palvelusopimuksen valmistelu
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Eau de Constanta - Préparation de résultats basés sur l'accord de services
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - Εταιρεία Ύδρευσης της Constanta — Προετοιμασία σύμβασης παροχής υπηρεσιών με βάση την καλή εκτέλεση
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - Rete idrica di Costanza — Preparazione di un accordo di servizi basato sulle prestazioni
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - Watervoorziening in Constanta — voorbereiding van een prestatiegerelateerde dienstenovereenkomst
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Águas de Constanta — Preparação de um acordo de serviço baseado em desempenho
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Constanta Water - förberedelse av ett prestationsbaserat tjänsteavtal
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Voda ve městě Constanta – příprava servisní smlouvy založené na výkonu
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Constanta vesi – tulemuspõhise teenuslepingu ettevalmistamine
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Konstancai vízügyi vállalat — Teljesítményalapú szolgáltatási megállapodás elkészítése
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - Konstancos vanduo – rezultatais pagrįstos paslaugų pirkimo sutarties parengimas
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - Konstancas ūdens — uz rezultātiem balstīta pakalpojumu līguma sagatavošana
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - Ilma ta' Constanta — It-Tħejjija ta' Ftehim għal Servizz Ibbażat fuq il-Prestazzjoni
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt wodny w Konstancy — przygotowanie umowy o usługi uzależnionej od wyników
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Vodovodná sieť v meste Constanta – príprava zmluvy o poskytovaní služieb založenej na výkonnosti
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt oskrbe z vodo za Constanto – Priprava sporazuma o storitvah na podlagi uspešnosti
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Uisce Constanța — Comhaontú seirbhíse bunaithe ar fheidhmíocht a ullmhú
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - Водоснабдяване в Констанца — Изготвяне на споразумение за услуги въз основа на изпълнението
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Alimentarea cu apă în Constanța — Pregătirea unui contract de prestări servicii bazat pe performanță
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Vodoopskrba Constante — priprema sporazuma o uslugama temeljenog na učinkovitosti
			 (RO-Constanta)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Procurement Notice</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Procurement reference: 9053-EOI-41177</P><P>Project number: 41177</P><P>Assignment name: Constanta Water — Preparation of a Performance Based Service Agreement</P><P>Business sector: Municipal and Environmental Infrastructure</P><P>Funding source: EBRD Shareholder Special Fund</P><P>Type of contract: Consultancy Services</P><P>Issue date: 9.4.2018</P><P>Closing date: 3.5.2018, 15:00 local time</P><P>Executing Agency (Client):</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>The Client Contact Person: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Stelian Budes</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>S.C. RAJA S.A.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Călăraşi 22-24 Street, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Constanţa</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, ROMANIA, Email: </BLK_BTX><E_MAIL>bstellis@gmail.com</E_MAIL><BLK_BTX> — Phone: </BLK_BTX><PHONE>+40 754 073 217</PHONE></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The EBRD Contact Person: William Power, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, One Exchange Square, London EC2A 2JN, Tel: + 44 20 7338 7123 — E-mail: powerw@ebrd.com</P><P>Background:</P><P>The City of Constanta (the “City”), the second largest metropolitan area with over 425 000 population, is the largest port of the country to the Black Sea and a major commercial, trading and touristic center.</P><P>SC RAJA SA Constanta (the “Company”, “RAJA”) is the Country‘s largest public water and wastewater utility and the regionalized water and wastewater provider for the City of Constanta, the County of Constanta and several other localities in seven adjacent counties in Romania, serving a total population of over 3 000 000.</P><P>RAJA approached the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (“EBRD”, the “Bank”) with a request to explore the involvement of private sector in decreasing Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) in the City’s water distribution network (the “Project”). RAJA requested the Bank to explore the involvement of a Private Partner under a Performance-Based Service Agreement (“PBSA”) between RAJA and the Private Partner, whereby the payment mechanism to the Private Partner contains certain parts linked to performance as defined in a number of Key Performance Indicators (“KPIs”).</P><P>The Company now requires a consultant (the “Consultant”) to provide assistance with the preparation of the tender documentation, the tender, the evaluation and contract of a private partner (the “Private Partner”) under a single PBSA (the “Assignment”).</P><P>The Private Partner will subsequently assist the Company in 2 areas:</P><P>1. Part 1: assist the Company in understanding the Company’s base water network performance in terms of NRW and Infrastructure Leakage Index (“ILI”) and other relevant business critical metrics by reviewing the Network Inventory, developing a hydraulic model, installing reliable measurement equipment to calibrate the hydraulic model, assessment of the customers water meters, design of the network sectorization, define the baseline proposal, extend the SCADA system, and other measures the Private Partner will deem appropriate. The baseline proposed, which will include certain baseline data in relation to NRW, will then be agreed with the Company and will subsequently be used to measure the Private Partner’s performance [the KPIs, the KPIs measurement mechanism and the incentive / disincentive mechanism will be as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The agreed baseline will be validated by a third party consultant.</P><P>2. Part 2: the Private Partner will implement the measures required to reduce NRW efficiently. In this Part, the Private Partner will be paid partly a fixed fee and a variable fee which will be subject to its performance and achievement of the KPIs [as defined by the Consultant under the scope of this assignment]. The measures to be implemented should take fully into account the investments being made in RAJA’s water network under the EU Large Infrastructure Operational Programme (“LIOP”) 2014-2020.</P><P>Assignment Description:</P><P>The Consultant will draft the PBSA, prepare and launch the tender. The key objectives of the assignment are as follows:</P><P>— develop the PBSA taking into account the two areas of support (as outlined above) and procurement documents in implementation thereof, based on the best international practices and standards in the area of water and wastewater services and with due regard to the requirements of PBSA and structured accordingly to take into account the existing legislation, current shareholding structure and ownership of assets,</P><P>— prepare the tender documentation and assist the Company in successfully launching the tender of the Project,</P><P>— assist the Company in the evaluation of the Expressions of Interest received from the bidders,</P><P>— assist the Company in the contracting of the winning bidder,</P><P>— ensure, throughout the assignment, appropriate transfer of skills via regular updates, provision of formal presentations and trainings to the Company and, as appropriate, other stakeholders.</P><P>Full Terms of Reference are can be accessed through the following link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/work-with-us/procurement/p-pn-180409c.html</P><P>Status of Selection Process: Interested firms or group of firms are hereby invited to submit Expressions of Interest.</P><P>Assignment Start Date and Duration: The Assignment is expected to begin in the second quarter of 2018 and have an estimated overall duration of ten months.</P><P>Cost Estimate for the Assignment: 300 000 EUR (exclusive of VAT).</P><P>The Consultant must determine whether any indirect taxes / VAT are chargeable on the proposed services and state the basis for such. If any indirect taxes / VAT are payable, the Client will have to pay indirect taxes / VAT element to the services directly to the Consultant unless otherwise agreed.</P><P>Funding Source: It is anticipated that the contract will be financed by the EBRD Shareholder Special Fund. Final selection and contracting is subject to the availability of funding.</P><P>Eligibility: There are no eligibility restrictions.</P><P>Consultant Profile: Corporate services are required.</P><P>The Consultant will be the firm / group of firms with previous project experience related to:</P><P>1. legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures;</P><P>2. leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water (“NRW”) collection;</P><P>3. consultancy on the operation of municipal water service networks, including operational performance improvement.</P><P>The Consultant’s expert team is expected to include the following Key Experts:</P><P>1. Key Expert nº 1 (Team Leader): engineer or project manager with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in water sector, including successful implementation of private sector participation projects and at least 1 recent (less than 5 years ago) performance-based contracts. Relevant experience in NRW projects will be an asset.</P><P>2. Key Expert nº 2 (Legal Expert): lawyer with preferably 10 years of previous professional experience in drafting and implementation of service and performance-based contracts with experience in the procurement of PBC. Knowledge and experience in the Romanian legal framework will be an asset.</P><P>3. Key Experts nº 3 (Pool of Additional Experts) consisting of procurement expert, regulatory reform expert, institutional expert and other technical experts.</P><P>Submission Requirements: In order to determine the capability and experience of Consultants seeking to be selected, the information submitted should include the following:</P><P>1. company / group of firms’ profile, organisation and staffing (max. 2-4 pages);</P><P>2. details of previous project experience or similar assignments particularly undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contract value, contracting entity / client, project location/country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided (if different from duration), main activities, objectives;</P><P>3. CVs of Experts that will be responsible for executing the Assignment detailing qualifications, relevant experience and role in similar assignments, particularly assignments undertaken in the previous 5 years, including information on contracting entity / client, project location / country, duration (mm/yy to mm/yy), expert months provided, assignment budget, main activities, objectives. The person who will take overall responsibility of the Assignment as well as the individuals who would lead and individual work stream should be identified;</P><P>4. completed Consultant Declaration Form and Contact Sheet, the template for which is available from the following web-link:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/pages/workingwithus/procurement/notices/csu/contact_sheet.doc</P><P>The Expression of Interest shall not exceed 25 pages (excluding CVs Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet). The complete Expression of Interest (including CVs, Consultant Declaration and Contact Sheet) should be submitted, in English via email (pdf) to the Client’s Contact Person, to reach the Client not later than the closing date. The Executing Agency reserves the right to reject applications of firms submitting more than 1 file.</P><P>An electronic copy of the Expression of Interest shall reach the Bank’s Contact Person by the same due in the form of a single pdf file.</P><P>Important Notes:</P><P>The selection will normally be made from responses to this notification only.</P><P>The Executing Agency intends to mobilise the services as soon as possible following competitive selection process and CVs of the proposed experts will form basis for contract negotiations. The Executing Agency reserves the right to terminate negotiations with the highest-ranked Consultant if Key Experts proposed in the competitive selection process are not available for this Assignment.</P><P>The weighted evaluation criteria will be as follows:</P><P>1. firm’s experience in legal and contract design, tendering and implementation of performance-based contracts in the water sector, including effective monitoring, verification and remuneration procedures: 20 %;</P><P>2. firm’s experience in leakage detection and improvement in Non-Revenue Water collection: 15 %;</P><P>3. firm’s experience in providing advisory services in relation to municipal water service networks, including in regards to operational performance improvements: 15 %;</P><P>4. skills and experience of key expert 1: 18 %;</P><P>5. skills and experience of key expert 2: 16 %;</P><P>6. skills and experience of key expert 3: 16 %.</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>