<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="100083-2018"
            EDITION="2018046">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-094665-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180608</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>46</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180307</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 046-100083</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC>
            <URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100083-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="92521100">Museum-exhibition services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79930000">Specialty design services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45212313">Museum construction work</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="31500000">Lighting equipment and electric lamps</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="39100000">Furniture</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="44523200">Mountings</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="32322000">Multimedia equipment</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="72212520">Multimedia software development services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="30200000">Computer equipment and supplies</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="32320000">Television and audio-visual equipment</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="32340000">Microphones and loudspeakers</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79822500">Graphic design services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="92110000">Motion picture and video tape production and related services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="BE100">Arr. de Bruxelles-Capitale / Arr. van Brussel-Hoofdstad</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="BE100">Arr. de Bruxelles-Capitale / Arr. van Brussel-Hoofdstad</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <n2016:TENDERER_NUTS CODE="NL310">Utrecht</n2016:TENDERER_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="PROCUREMENT_TOTAL" CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
         <REF_NOTICE>
            <NO_DOC_OJS>2017/S 154-318476</NO_DOC_OJS>
         </REF_NOTICE>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180228</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="7">Contract award notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>PAA03</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>PA</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Projektering, fremstilling, installering, vedligeholdelse og demontering af den midlertidige udstilling »Rastløse unge: opvækst i Europa igennem 70 år«</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Planung, Herstellung, Aufbau, Instandhaltung und Abbau der Wechselausstellung „Rastlose Jugend: 70 Jahre Aufwachsen in Europa“</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brussels</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Design, production, installation, maintenance and dismantling of the Temporary Exhibition "Restless Youth: 70 Years of Growing Up in Europe"</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruselas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Diseño, producción, instalación, mantenimiento y desmantelamiento de la exposición temporal «Juventud inquieta: 70 años de crecimiento en Europa»</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Vaihtuvan näyttelyn ”Levoton nuoruus: 70 vuotta varttumista Euroopassa” suunnittelu, tuotanto, pystytys, ylläpito ja purkaminen </P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Belgique</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Conception, production, installation, maintenance et démontage de l'exposition temporaire «Jeunesse agitée: grandir en Europe depuis 70 ans»</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Βέλγιο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Σχεδιασμός, παραγωγή, εγκατάσταση, συντήρηση και αποσυναρμολόγηση της προσωρινής έκθεσης «Ανήσυχη νεολαία: μεγαλώνοντας εδώ και 70 χρόνια στην Ευρώπη»</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Belgio</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Progettazione, produzione, allestimento, manutenzione e smantellamento della mostra temporanea «Gioventù inquieta: crescere in Europa lungo 70 anni»</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>België</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brussel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ontwerp, productie, installatie, onderhoud en afbraak van de tijdelijke tentoonstelling „Rusteloze jeugd: 70 jaar opgroeien in Europa”.</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Conceção, produção, instalação, manutenção e desmontagem da exposição temporária «Juventude inquieta: 70 anos de crescimento na Europa»</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Utformning, framtagande, installation, underhåll och nedmontering av den tillfälliga utställningen ”Rastlös ungdom: att växa upp i Europa under 70 år”</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Belgie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Návrh, výroba, instalace, údržba a demontáž dočasné expozice: „Neklidné mládí: 70 let dospívání v Evropě“</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ajutise näituse „Rahutu noorus: 70 aastat Euroopas üles kasvamist“ kavandamine, tootmine, paigaldamine ning selle hooldamine ja demonteerimine </P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brüsszel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>A „Nyugtalan ifjúság: a felnövekedés 70 éve Európában” időszakos kiállítás megtervezése, létrehozása, a telepítési, a karbantartási és a leszerelési munkák elvégzése </P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Briuselis</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Laikinos parodos „Neramus jaunimas: 70 metų augimo Europoje“ projektavimas, gamyba, įrengimas, priežiūra ir išmontavimas </P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Beļģija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brisele</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pagaidu ekspozīcijas “Nemierīgā jaunatne: 70 gadi pieaugot Eiropā” plānošana, sagatavošana, ierīkošana, uzturēšana un novākšana </P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>il-Belġju</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brussell</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Id-disinn, il-produzzjoni, l-installazzjoni, il-manutenzjoni u ż-żarmar tal-wirja temporanja ‘Żgħażagħ mingħajr kwiet: 70 sena ta' tkabbir fl-Ewropa’</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruksela</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Projekt, produkcja, montaż, utrzymanie i demontaż wystawy czasowej „Niespokojna młodzież: 70 lat dorastania w Europie”</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Belgicko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Návrh, výroba, inštalácia, údržba a demontáž v súvislosti s dočasnou výstavou „Nepokojná mládež: 70 rokov dospievania v Európe“</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruselj</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Načrtovanje, izdelava, namestitev, vzdrževanje in odstranitev začasne razstave „Nemirna mladost: 70 let odraščanja v Evropi“</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Bheilg, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Taispeántas sealadach 'Óige neamhshocair' a dhearadh, a tháirgeadh, a shuiteáil, a chothabháil agus a dhíchóimeáil: 70 bliain d'fhás aníos san Eoraip'. </P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Бeлгия</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Брюксел</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Проектиране, производство, монтаж, поддръжка и демонтаж на временната изложба „Неспокойна младост: 70 години на порастване в Европа“</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Conceperea, realizarea, instalarea, întreținerea și demontarea expoziției temporare „Tinerețe neliniștită: 70 de ani de creștere în Europa”</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Osmišljavanje, izrada, postavljanje, održavanje i rasklapanje privremene izložbe „Nemirna mladež: 70 godina odrastanja u Europi”</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="DA">Europa-Parlamentet, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäisches Parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">European Parliament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="ES">Parlamento Europeo, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan parlamentti, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers – PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="FR">Parlement européen, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="EL">Ευρωπαϊκό Κοινοβούλιο, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="IT">Parlamento europeo, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="NL">Europees Parlement, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="PT">Parlamento Europeu, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="SV">Europaparlamentet, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropský parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers – PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers – PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="HU">Európai Parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos Parlamentas, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers – PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Parlaments, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="MT">Il-Parlament Ewropew, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="PL">Parlament Europejski, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="SK">Európsky parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropski parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="GA">Parlaimint na hEorpa, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейски парламент, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="RO">Parlamentul European, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
         <AA_NAME LG="HR">Europski parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="DA">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Europa-Parlamentet, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Projektering, fremstilling, installering, vedligeholdelse og demontering af den midlertidige udstilling »Rastløse unge: opvækst i Europa igennem 70 år«</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Europa-Parlamentet har besluttet at iværksætte dette udbud om design, produktion, installering, vedligeholdelse og nedtagning af den midlertidige udstilling »Rastløs ungdom: 70 års opvækst i Europa« i Huset for Europæisk Historie i Bruxelles.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Kontrahentens lokaler og Bruxelles - Huset for Europæisk Historie.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Genstanden for dette udbud er at levere tjenesteydelser inden for design, produktion, installering, vedligeholdelse og nedtagning af den midlertidige udstilling »Rastløs ungdom: 70 års opvækst i Europa« i Huset for Europæisk Historie i Bruxelles. Tjenesteydelserne/arbejderne omfatter:</P>
                  <P>1. Design af den midlertidige udstilling;</P>
                  <P>2. Indretning af eksisterende rum, fremstilling, levering og montering af skillevægge, møbler, udstillingsmontrer og -skabe samt opsatser til genstande, herunder håndtering og installering af genstande, grafik og scenografiske elementer;</P>
                  <P>3. Levering og installering af belysningsarmaturer, av- og multimedieudstyr samt alle andre nødvendige tekniske installationer, herunder et kontrolsystem for udstillinger, med henblik på genbrug af dele af det eksisterende belysningssystem (»Medialon«) og net fastgjort til loftet;</P>
                  <P>4. Udvikling og implementering af al av- og multimediesoftware;</P>
                  <P>5. Vedligeholdelse af den midlertidige udstilling på et fornuftigt driftsniveau og dermed minimere nedbrud, herunder lejlighedsvis udskiftning af genstande i udstillingsmontrer;</P>
                  <P>6. Demontering, sortering og bortskaffelse af den midlertidige udstilling;</P>
                  <P>7. Indhold, billeder, filmoptagelser og musikforskning og -erhvervelse, herunder nødvendige rettigheder til udstillingen samt online og trykte anvendelser;</P>
                  <P>8. Opstilling af palisade.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Se venligst udbudsmaterialet.</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Projektering, fremstilling, installering, vedligeholdelse og demontering af den midlertidige udstilling »Rastløse unge: opvækst i Europa igennem 70 år«</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Der vil være et frivilligt besøg på stedet den 30.8.2017. For yderligere oplysninger se betingelserne.</P>
               <P>Europa-Parlamentet forbeholder sig retten til at anvende et udbud efter forhandling uden forudgående offentliggørelse af en udbudsbekendtgørelse i overensstemmelse med artikel 134, stk. 1, litra e) den delegerede forordning (EU) nr. 1268/2012 af 966/2012 om gennemførelsesbestemmelser til Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU, Euratom) nr. 2015/2462 om de finansielle regler vedrørende Unionens almindelige budget, som senest ændret ved Kommissionens delegerede forordning (EU) nr. 30.10.2015 af 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Retten ved Den Europæiske Unions Domstol</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Kontakt venligst organet med ansvar for klager for at få oplysninger om fristen/fristerne for indgivelse af klager.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Retten ved Den Europæiske Unions Domstol</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="DE">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Europäisches Parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Planung, Herstellung, Aufbau, Instandhaltung und Abbau der Wechselausstellung „Rastlose Jugend: 70 Jahre Aufwachsen in Europa“</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Das Europäische Parlament hat beschlossen, diese Ausschreibung einzuleiten für den Entwurf, die Erstellung, den Aufbau, die Instandhaltung und den Abbau der temporären Ausstellung „Rastlose Jugend: 70 Jahre Aufwachsen in Europa“ im Haus der Europäischen Geschichte in Brüssel.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Räumlichkeiten der Auftragnehmer und Brüssel — Haus der Europäischen Geschichte.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Das Europäische Parlament hat beschlossen, einen Bauauftrag einzuleiten für den Entwurf, die Erstellung, den Aufbau, die Instandhaltung und den Abbau der temporären Ausstellung „Rastlose Jugend: 70 Jahre Aufwachsen in Europa“ im Haus der Europäischen Geschichte in Brüssel. Diese Dienstleistungen/Arbeiten umfassen:</P>
                  <P>1. Entwurf der temporären Ausstellung;</P>
                  <P>2. Ausstattung der vorhandenen Räume, Herstellung, Lieferung und Aufbau von Trennwänden, Möbeln, Schaukästen, Ausstellungsunterlagen und Stützen für Gegenstände, einschließlich Behandlung und Installation von Gegenständen, Grafiken und szenografische Elemente;</P>
                  <P>3. Lieferung und Installation der Beleuchtungsanlagen, audiovisueller und multimedialer Hardware sowie alle anderen erforderlichen technischen Installationen, einschließlich des Ausstellungskontrollsystems; dabei ist die Wiederverwendung von Teilen des bestehenden Beleuchtungssystems („Medialon“) und der an der Decke angebrachten Netze zu berücksichtigen;</P>
                  <P>4. Entwicklung und Implementierung sämtlicher audiovisueller und multimedialer Software;</P>
                  <P>5. Pflege der Wechselausstellung, um sie in gutem Zustand zu erhalten, und infolge dessen Ausfallzeiten zu minimieren, einschließlich gelegentlichem Wechsel der Gegenstände in den Schaukästen;</P>
                  <P>6. Abbau, Ordnen und Abtransport der Wechselausstellung;</P>
                  <P>7. Recherche und Erwerb von Inhalten, Bildern, Filmmaterial und Musik, einschließlich der erforderlichen Rechte für Ausstellung sowie Online- und Print-Verwendung;</P>
                  <P>8. Anbringen einer Palisade.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Siehe Ausschreibungsunterlagen.</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Planung, Herstellung, Aufbau, Instandhaltung und Abbau der Wechselausstellung „Rastlose Jugend: 70 Jahre Aufwachsen in Europa“</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Es wird eine fakultative Ortsbesichtigung der Räumlichkeiten am 30.8.2017 durchgeführt. Weitere Einzelheiten siehe Bedingungen.</P>
               <P>Das Europäische Parlament behält sich das Recht vor, auf ein Verhandlungsverfahren ohne vorherige Veröffentlichung einer Auftragsbekanntmachung gemäß Artikel 134 Absatz 1 Buchstabe e der delegierten Verordnung (EU) Nr. 1268/2012 über die Anwendungsbestimmungen für die Verordnung (EU, Euratom) Nr. 966/2012 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates über die Haushaltsordnung für den Gesamthaushaltsplan der Union mit Änderung durch die delegierte Verordnung (EU) 2015/2462 der Kommission vom 30.10.2015 zurückzugreifen.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Gericht des Gerichtshofs</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Um Informationen zu der/den Frist(en) für die Einlegung von Rechtsbehelfen zu erhalten, ist die für Rechtsbehelfe zuständige Stelle zu kontaktieren.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Gericht des Gerichtshofs</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F03" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>European Parliament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Design, production, installation, maintenance and dismantling of the Temporary Exhibition "Restless Youth: 70 Years of Growing Up in Europe"</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>European Parliament has decided to issue this invitation to tender for the design, the production, the installation, the maintenance and the dismantling of the temporary exhibition "Restless Youth: 70 Years of Growing Up in Europe" at the House of European History in Brussels.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Contractors’ premises and Brussels - House of European History.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The invitation to tender aims at establishing a works contract for the design, the production, the installation, the maintenance and the dismantling of the temporary exhibition "Restless Youth: 70 Years of Growing Up in Europe” at the House of European History in Brussels. Those services/works include:</P>
                  <P>1. Design of the temporary exhibition;</P>
                  <P>2. Fit-out of the existing spaces, production, delivery and installation of partition walls, furniture, showcases, display bases and mounting supports for objects including handling and installation of the objects, graphics and scenographic elements;</P>
                  <P>3. Supply and installation of the lighting equipment, audiovisual and multimedia hardware and all other necessary technical installations, including exhibition control system, bearing in mind the reuse of parts of the existing lighting system (“Medialon”) and grids fixed to the ceiling;</P>
                  <P>4. Development and implementation of all the audiovisual and multimedia software;</P>
                  <P>5. Maintenance of the temporary exhibition in good operating level and consequently minimization of downtime, including occasional change of objects in showcases;</P>
                  <P>6. Dismantling, sorting and disposal of the temporary exhibition;</P>
                  <P>7. Content, image, footage, and music research and acquisition, including necessary rights, for exhibition, online and print use;</P>
                  <P>8. Placing a palisade</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>See Specifications document</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Design, production, installation, maintenance and dismantling of the Temporary Exhibition "Restless Youth: 70 Years of Growing Up in Europe"</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>There will be an optional visit to the premises on 30.8.2017. Further details please see conditions.</P>
               <P>The European Parliament reserves the right to use a negotiated procedure without prior publication of a contract notice, according to Article 134.1 (e) of Delegated Regulation (EU) Nº 1268/2012 on the rules of application of Regulation (EU, Euratom) Nº 966/2012 of the European Parliament and of the Council on the financial rules applicable to the general budget of the Union as last amended by Commission delegated regulation (EU) 2015/2462 of 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>General Court of the Court of Justice of the European Union</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Please contact the body responsible for appeals for information concerning the deadline(s) for lodging appeals.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>General Court of the Court of Justice of the European Union</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="ES">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Parlamento Europeo, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Diseño, producción, instalación, mantenimiento y desmantelamiento de la exposición temporal «Juventud inquieta: 70 años de crecimiento en Europa»</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>El Parlamento Europeo ha decidido emitir esta invitación a licitar para el diseño, la producción, la instalación, el mantenimiento y el desmantelamiento de la exposición temporal «Juventud inquieta: 70 años creciendo en Europa» en la Casa de la Historia Europea en Bruselas.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Las instalaciones de los contratistas y Bruselas - Casa de la Historia Europea.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>La invitación a licitar tiene como objetivo celebrar un contrato para el diseño, la producción, la instalación, el mantenimiento y el desmantelamiento de la exposición temporal «Juventud inquieta: 70 años creciendo en Europa» en la Casa de la Historia Europea en Bruselas. Estos servicios/trabajos incluyen:</P>
                  <P>1. Diseño de la exposición temporal.</P>
                  <P>2. Equipamiento de los espacios existentes, producción, suministro e instalación de tabiques, mobiliario, vitrinas, peanas y soportes de montaje para objetos, incluido el manejo y la instalación de estos objetos, gráficos y elementos escenográficos.</P>
                  <P>3. Suministro e instalación de equipos de iluminación, «hardware» multimedia y audiovisual y todas las demás instalaciones técnicas necesarias, como el sistema de control de la exposición, teniendo en cuenta la reutilización de partes del sistema y las redes de iluminación existentes («Medialon») fijadas al techo.</P>
                  <P>4. Desarrollo y aplicación de todo el «software» audiovisual y multimedia.</P>
                  <P>5. Mantenimiento de la exposición temporal en un buen estado de funcionamiento reduciendo al mínimo el tiempo de inactividad, incluidos los cambios ocasionales de objetos de las vitrinas.</P>
                  <P>6. Desmantelamiento, clasificación y retirada de la exposición temporal.</P>
                  <P>7. Búsqueda y adquisición de contenidos, imágenes, vídeos y música, con sus respectivos derechos, para la exposición y para su uso en línea y en formato impreso.</P>
                  <P>8. Instalación de una cerca.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Véase el pliego de condiciones.</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Diseño, producción, instalación, mantenimiento y desmantelamiento de la exposición temporal «Juventud inquieta: 70 años de crecimiento en Europa»</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Se celebrará una visita opcional a las instalaciones el 30.8.2017. Para más detalles, consúltense las condiciones.</P>
               <P>El Parlamento Europeo se reserva el derecho a recurrir a un procedimiento negociado, sin publicación previa de un anuncio de contrato, de acuerdo con el artículo 134, apartado 1, letra e), del Reglamento Delegado (UE) n.º 1268/2012 sobre las normas de desarrollo del Reglamento (UE, Euratom) n.º 966/2012 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, sobre las normas financieras aplicables al presupuesto general de la Unión, modificado en última instancia por el Reglamento Delegado (UE) 2015/2462 de la Comisión, de 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal General del Tribunal de Justicia de la Unión Europea</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Póngase en contacto con el organismo responsable de los recursos para obtener información relativa al (a los) plazo(s) de presentación de recursos.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal General del Tribunal de Justicia de la Unión Europea</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="FI">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Euroopan parlamentti, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers – PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Vaihtuvan näyttelyn ”Levoton nuoruus: 70 vuotta varttumista Euroopassa” suunnittelu, tuotanto, pystytys, ylläpito ja purkaminen </P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Euroopan parlamentti on päättänyt käynnistää tämän tarjouspyyntömenettelyn seuraavan vaihtuvan näyttelyn suunnittelua, tuotantoa, pystytystä, ylläpitoa ja purkamista varten: ”Levoton nuoruus: 70 vuotta varttumista Euroopassa”. Näyttely toteutetaan Euroopan historian talossa Brysselissä. </P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>sopimusosapuolen toimitilat ja Euroopan historian talo Brysselissä.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Tarjouspyyntömenettelyn tavoitteena on urakkasopimuksen tekeminen vaihtuvan näyttelyn ”Levoton nuoruus: 70 vuotta varttumista Euroopassa” suunnittelua, tuotantoa, pystytystä, ylläpitoa ja purkamista varten. Näyttely toteutetaan Euroopan historian talossa Brysselissä.  Kyseessä oleviin palveluihin/töihin sisältyvät seuraavat:</P>
                  <P>1. vaihtuvan näyttelyn suunnittelu,</P>
                  <P>2. nykyisten tilojen varustelu sekä väliseinien, kalusteiden, näyttelyvitriinien, näyttelyalustojen ja kiinnitystukien tuotanto, toimitus ja asennus esineitä varten, mukaan luettuina esineiden, grafiikan ja perspektiivisten elementtien käsittely ja asennus,</P>
                  <P>3. valaistuslaitteiden, audiovisuaalisten laitteistojen ja multimedialaitteistojen sekä kaikkien muiden tarvittavien teknisten laitteiden (mukaan luettuna näyttelyn valvontajärjestelmä) toimitus ja asennus siten, että otetaan huomioon tällä hetkellä käytössä olevan valaistusjärjestelmän (Medialon) osien uudelleenkäyttö ja kattoon kiinnitetyt ristikot,</P>
                  <P>4. kaikkien audiovisuaalisten ohjelmistojen ja multimediaohjelmistojen kehittäminen ja toteutus,</P>
                  <P>5. vaihtuvan näyttelyn ylläpito hyvässä toimintakunnossa, minkä ansiosta hukka-ajan määrä voidaan vähimmäistää, mukaan luettuna ajoittainen näyttelyvitriineissä olevien esineiden vaihtaminen,</P>
                  <P>6. vaihtuvan näyttelyn purkaminen, lajittelu ja poistaminen,</P>
                  <P>7. sisältöjä, kuvia, filmiaineistoja ja musiikkia koskeva tutkimus ja niiden hankinta, mukaan luettuina tarvittavat oikeudet, niiden käyttöä varten näyttelyssä, verkossa ja painetuissa materiaaleissa,</P>
                  <P>8. palisadin asettaminen.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>katso eritelmäasiakirjat</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Vaihtuvan näyttelyn ”Levoton nuoruus: 70 vuotta varttumista Euroopassa” suunnittelu, tuotanto, pystytys, ylläpito ja purkaminen </P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Toimitiloihin järjestetään vapaaehtoinen tutustumiskäynti 30.8.2017. Katso tarkemmat tiedot ehdoista.</P>
               <P>Euroopan parlamentti varaa oikeuden käyttää neuvottelumenettelyä julkaisematta hankintailmoitusta etukäteen unionin yleiseen talousarvioon sovellettavista varainhoitosäännöistä annetun Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetuksen (EU, Euratom) N:o 966/2012 soveltamissäännöistä annetun delegoidun asetuksen (EU) N:o 1268/2012, sellaisena kuin se on viimeksi muutettuna 30.10.2015 annetulla komission delegoidulla asetuksella (EU) 2015/2462, 134 artiklan 1 kohdan e alakohdan mukaisesti.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Euroopan unionin tuomioistuimeen kuuluva unionin yleinen tuomioistuin</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>tarjoajia pyydetään ottamaan yhteyttä muutoksenhakuelimeen tietojen saamiseksi muutoksenhaun määräajoista.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Euroopan unionin tuomioistuimeen kuuluva unionin yleinen tuomioistuin</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="FR">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Parlement européen, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Conception, production, installation, maintenance et démontage de l'exposition temporaire «Jeunesse agitée: grandir en Europe depuis 70 ans»</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Le Parlement européen a décidé de lancer le présent appel d'offres en vue de la conception, de la production, de l'installation, de la maintenance et du démontage de l'exposition temporaire «Jeunesse agitée: grandir en Europe depuis 70 ans» à la Maison de l'histoire européenne à Bruxelles.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Dans les locaux du contractant et à Bruxelles — Maison de l'histoire européenne.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Le Parlement européen a décidé de lancer le présent appel d'offres en vue de la conception, de la production, de l'installation, de la maintenance et du démontage de l'exposition temporaire «Jeunesse agitée: grandir en Europe depuis 70 ans» à la Maison de l'histoire européenne à Bruxelles. Ces services/travaux comprennent :</P>
                  <P>1. La conception de l'exposition temporaire ;</P>
                  <P>2. L'aménagement des espaces existants ainsi que la production, la livraison et l'installation des cloisons de séparation, du mobilier, des vitrines, des bases de présentation et des supports de montage pour les objets, incluant la manipulation et l'installation des objets, des éléments graphiques et scénographiques ;</P>
                  <P>3. La fourniture et la mise en place des dispositifs d'éclairage, du matériel audiovisuel et multimédia ainsi que de toutes les autres installations techniques nécessaires, y compris le système de contrôle de l'exposition, en tenant compte de la réutilisation de composants du système d'éclairage actuellement en place (« Medalion ») et des grilles fixées au plafond ;</P>
                  <P>4. Le développement et l'implémentation de tous les logiciels audiovisuels et multimédias ;</P>
                  <P>5. Le maintien de l'exposition temporaire à un bon niveau de fonctionnement et, en conséquence, la limitation des temps d'arrêt, y compris le changement occasionnel des objets dans les présentoirs ;</P>
                  <P>6. Le démontage, le triage et l'enlèvement de l'exposition temporaire ;</P>
                  <P>7. La recherche et l'acquisition de contenu, d'images, de séquences et de musique, y compris des droits requis pour une exposition en ligne et une utilisation en version papier ;</P>
                  <P>8. L'installation d'une palissade</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Voir cahier des charges</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Conception, production, installation, maintenance et démontage de l'exposition temporaire «Jeunesse agitée: grandir en Europe depuis 70 ans»</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Une visite des lieux facultative sera organisée le 30.8.2017. Voir conditions pour plus d'informations.</P>
               <P>Le Parlement européen se réserve le droit de recourir à une procédure négociée sans publication préalable d'un avis de marché, conformément à l'article 134, paragraphe 1, point e), du Règlement délégué (UE) no 1268/2012 de la Commission relatif aux règles d'application du règlement (UE, Euratom) no 966/2012 du Parlement européen et du Conseil relatif aux règles financières applicables au budget général de l'Union, tel que modifié par le règlement délégué (UE) 2015/2462 de la Commission du 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal de la Cour de justice de l'Union européenne</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Prière de contacter l'organe responsable des recours pour de plus amples renseignements concernant le(s) délai(s) d'introduction des recours.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal de la Cour de justice de l'Union européenne</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="EL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ευρωπαϊκό Κοινοβούλιο, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Σχεδιασμός, παραγωγή, εγκατάσταση, συντήρηση και αποσυναρμολόγηση της προσωρινής έκθεσης «Ανήσυχη νεολαία: μεγαλώνοντας εδώ και 70 χρόνια στην Ευρώπη»</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Το Ευρωπαϊκό Κοινοβούλιο έχει αποφασίσει να εκδώσει την παρούσα πρόσκληση υποβολής προσφορών για τον σχεδιασμό, την παραγωγή, την εγκατάσταση, τη συντήρηση και την αποσυναρμολόγηση της προσωρινής έκθεσης «Ανήσυχη νεολαία: μεγαλώνοντας εδώ και 70 χρόνια στην Ευρώπη» στο Σπίτι της Ευρωπαϊκής Ιστορίας στις Βρυξέλλες.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Εγκαταστάσεις του αναδόχου και Βρυξέλλες — Σπίτι της Ευρωπαϊκής Ιστορίας.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Η πρόσκληση υποβολής προσφορών στοχεύει στη σύναψη μιας σύμβασης έργων για τον σχεδιασμό, την παραγωγή, την εγκατάσταση, τη συντήρηση και την αποσυναρμολόγηση της προσωρινής έκθεσης «Ανήσυχη νεολαία: μεγαλώνοντας εδώ και 70 χρόνια στην Ευρώπη» στο Σπίτι της Ευρωπαϊκής Ιστορίας στις Βρυξέλλες.Οι εν λόγω υπηρεσίες/εργασίες περιλαμβάνουν: </P>
                  <P>1. το σχεδιασμό της προσωρινής έκθεσης,</P>
                  <P>2. τη διαμόρφωση των υφιστάμενων χώρων, την παραγωγή, την παράδοση και εγκατάσταση διαχωριστικών τοίχων, επίπλων, προθηκών, βάσεων προβολής και στηριγμάτων στερέωσης αντικειμένων, συμπεριλαμβανομένης της διαχείρισης και εγκατάστασης των αντικειμένων, καθώς και γραφικών και σκηνογραφικών στοιχείων,</P>
                  <P>3. την προμήθεια και εγκατάσταση του εξοπλισμού φωτισμού, των οπτικοακουστικών υλικών και των υλικών πολυμέσων, καθώς και όλων των λοιπών απαραίτητων τεχνικών εγκαταστάσεων, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του συστήματος ελέγχου της έκθεσης, λαμβάνοντας υπόψη την επαναχρησιμοποίηση εξαρτημάτων του υφιστάμενου συστήματος φωτισμού («Medialon») και των σκελετών που στερεώνονται στην οροφή,</P>
                  <P>4. την ανάπτυξη και υλοποίησηόλων των λογισμικών οπτικοακουστικών μέσων και πολυμέσων,</P>
                  <P>5. τη συντήρηση της προσωρινής έκθεσης σε καλό επίπεδο λειτουργίας και, κατά συνέπεια, την ελαχιστοποίηση του χρόνου διακοπής της λειτουργίας της, συμπεριλαμβανομένης της περιστασιακής αλλαγής των αντικειμένων στις προθήκες,</P>
                  <P>6. την αποσυναρμολόγηση, ταξινόμηση και απομάκρυνση της προσωρινής έκθεσης,</P>
                  <P>7. την έρευνα και απόκτηση περιεχομένου, εικόνων, ανεπεξέργαστου υλικού και μουσικής, συμπεριλαμβανομένων των απαραίτητων δικαιωμάτων, για χρήση στην έκθεση, στο διαδίκτυο και σε έντυπα μέσα,</P>
                  <P>8. την τοποθέτηση περίφραξης.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Ανατρέξτε στο έγγραφο συγγραφής υποχρεώσεων</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Σχεδιασμός, παραγωγή, εγκατάσταση, συντήρηση και αποσυναρμολόγηση της προσωρινής έκθεσης «Ανήσυχη νεολαία: μεγαλώνοντας εδώ και 70 χρόνια στην Ευρώπη»</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Θα πραγματοποιηθεί προαιρετική επίσκεψη στις εγκαταστάσεις στις 30.8.2017. Για περισσότερες λεπτομέρειες, βλέπε όρους.</P>
               <P>Το Ευρωπαϊκό Κοινοβούλιο διατηρεί το δικαίωμα να προσφύγει σε διαδικασία με διαπραγμάτευση χωρίς να προηγηθεί δημοσίευση προκήρυξης σύμβασης, σύμφωνα με το άρθρο 134 παράγραφος 1, στοιχείο ε) του κατ’ εξουσιοδότηση κανονισμού (ΕΕ) αριθ. 1268/2012 σχετικά με τους κανόνες εφαρμογής του κανονισμού (ΕΕ, Ευρατόμ) αριθ. 966/2012 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου σχετικά με τον δημοσιονομικό κανονισμό που εφαρμόζεται στον γενικό προϋπολογισμό της Ένωσης, όπως τροποποιήθηκε τελευταία με τον κατ’ εξουσιοδότηση κανονισμό (ΕΕ) 2015/2462 της Επιτροπής, της 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Γενικό Δικαστήριο του Δικαστηρίου της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Οι υποψήφιοι καλούνται να επικοινωνήσουν με τον αρμόδιο φορέα υποβολής προσφυγών για πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις προθεσμίες υποβολής προσφυγών.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Γενικό Δικαστήριο του Δικαστηρίου της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="IT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Parlamento europeo, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Progettazione, produzione, allestimento, manutenzione e smantellamento della mostra temporanea «Gioventù inquieta: crescere in Europa lungo 70 anni»</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Il Parlamento europeo ha deciso di indire il presente bando di gara per la progettazione, la produzione, l'allestimento, la manutenzione e lo smantellamento della mostra temporanea «Gioventù inquieta: crescere in Europa lungo 70 anni» presso la Casa della Storia europea a Bruxelles.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>nei locali del contraente e a Bruxelles — Casa della Storia europea.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Il bando di gara prevede la conclusione di un appalto di lavori per la progettazione, la produzione, l'allestimento, la manutenzione e lo smantellamento della mostra temporanea «Gioventù inquieta: crescere in Europa lungo 70 anni» presso la Casa della Storia europea a Bruxelles. Questi servizi/lavori comprendono:</P>
                  <P>1. la progettazione della mostra temporanea;</P>
                  <P>2. la disposizione degli spazi esistenti, la produzione, la consegna e l'allestimento di pareti divisorie, mobili, vetrine, basi espositive e supporti di montaggio per oggetti, compresi il maneggio e l'installazione di oggetti, elementi grafici e scenografici;</P>
                  <P>3. la fornitura e l'installazione di apparecchiature di illuminazione, hardware audiovisivo e multimediale e di tutti gli altri impianti tecnici necessari, incluso il sistema di controllo della mostra, tenendo presente il riutilizzo di parti del sistema e della rete di illuminazione esistenti («Medialon») fissati al soffitto;</P>
                  <P>4. lo sviluppo e l'implementazione di tutti i software audiovisivi e multimediali;</P>
                  <P>5. il mantenimento in buono stato operativo della mostra temporanea e, di conseguenza, la riduzione di guasti, compreso il cambiamento occasionale di oggetti nelle vetrine;</P>
                  <P>6. lo smantellamento, l'ordinamento e la disposizione della mostra temporanea;</P>
                  <P>7. la ricerca e l'acquisizione di contenuto, immagini, riprese e musica per la mostra, sia online che su supporto stampato, inclusi i necessari diritti;</P>
                  <P>8. la posa di una recinzione</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>cfr. capitolato d'oneri</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Progettazione, produzione, allestimento, manutenzione e smantellamento della mostra temporanea «Gioventù inquieta: crescere in Europa lungo 70 anni»</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Una visita dei luoghi opzionale è prevista per il 30.8.2017. Per ulteriori dettagli consultare le condizioni.</P>
               <P>Il Parlamento europeo si riserva il diritto di ricorrere a una procedura negoziata non preceduta dalla pubblicazione di un bando di gara, ai sensi dell'articolo 134, paragrafo 1, lettera e), del regolamento delegato (UE) n. 1268/2012 recante le modalità di applicazione del regolamento (UE, Euratom) n. 966/2012 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio che stabilisce le regole finanziarie applicabili al bilancio generale dell'Unione, come modificato da ultimo dal regolamento delegato (UE) 2015/2462 della Commissione, del 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunale della Corte di giustizia dell'Unione europea</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>si prega di contattare l'organo responsabile dei ricorsi per informazioni concernenti i termini di scadenza per presentare ricorsi.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunale della Corte di giustizia dell'Unione europea</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="NL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Europees Parlement, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Ontwerp, productie, installatie, onderhoud en afbraak van de tijdelijke tentoonstelling „Rusteloze jeugd: 70 jaar opgroeien in Europa”.</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Het Europees Parlement heeft beslist deze uitnodiging tot inschrijving uit te schrijven voor het ontwerp, de productie, de installatie, het onderhoud en de ontmanteling van de tijdelijke tentoonstelling „Rusteloze jeugd: 70 jaar opgroeien in Europa” in het Huis van de Europese geschiedenis in Brussel.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>kantoren van de contractant en Brussel — Huis van de Europese geschiedenis.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>De uitnodiging tot inschrijving beoogt het opzetten van een opdracht voor werken voor het ontwerp, de productie, de installatie, het onderhoud en de ontmanteling van de tijdelijke tentoonstelling „Rusteloze jeugd: 70 jaar opgroeien in Europa” in het Huis van de Europese geschiedenis in Brussel. De diensten/werkzaamheden omvatten:</P>
                  <P>1. ontwerp van de tijdelijke tentoonstelling;</P>
                  <P>2. inrichting van de bestaande ruimten, vervaardiging, levering en installatie van scheidingswanden, meubilair, toonbanken, uitstalkasten en montagebevestigingen voor objecten, met inbegrip van de hantering en installatie van de objecten, grafische kunstwerken en scenografische elementen;</P>
                  <P>3. levering en installatie van de verlichtingsinstallatie, audiovisuele en multimediahardware en alle andere noodzakelijke technische installaties, met inbegrip van een tentoonstellingscontrolesysteem, rekening houdend met het hergebruik van delen van het bestaande verlichtingssysteem („Medialon”) en roosters die zijn vastgemaakt aan het plafond;</P>
                  <P>4. ontwikkeling en tenuitvoerlegging van alle audiovisuele en multimediasoftware;</P>
                  <P>5. onderhoud van de tijdelijke tentoonstelling zodat de systemen goed werken en zo min mogelijk defect zijn, met inbegrip van occasionele verandering van objecten in toonbanken;</P>
                  <P>6. afbreken, sorteren en verwijderen van de tijdelijke tentoonstelling;</P>
                  <P>7. onderzoek naar inhoud, beeld, film en muziek en aankoop, met inbegrip van noodzakelijke rechten, voor tentoonstelling, online- en gedrukt gebruik;</P>
                  <P>8. plaatsing van een palissade.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>zie de aanbestedingsstukken</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60.</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40.</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Ontwerp, productie, installatie, onderhoud en afbraak van de tijdelijke tentoonstelling „Rusteloze jeugd: 70 jaar opgroeien in Europa”.</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Op 30.8.2017 vindt een optioneel bezoek plaats aan de kantoren. Zie voorwaarden voor meer details.</P>
               <P>Het Europees Parlement behoudt zich het recht voor om gebruik te maken van een onderhandelingsprocedure zonder voorafgaande publicatie van een aankondiging van opdracht, overeenkomstig artikel 134, lid 1, onder e), van de Gedelegeerde Verordening (EU) nr. 1268/2012 van de Commissie houdende uitvoeringsvoorschriften voor Verordening (EU, Euratom) nr. 966/2012 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad tot vaststelling van de financiële regels van toepassing op de algemene begroting van de Unie, zoals laatst gewijzigd bij Gedelegeerde Verordening (EU) 2015/2462 van de Commissie van 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Gerecht van het Hof van Justitie van de Europese Unie</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>gelieve contact op te nemen met de instantie die verantwoordelijk is voor beroep voor meer informatie over de termijn(en) voor het instellen van beroep.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Gerecht van het Hof van Justitie van de Europese Unie</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="PT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Parlamento Europeu, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Conceção, produção, instalação, manutenção e desmontagem da exposição temporária «Juventude inquieta: 70 anos de crescimento na Europa»</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>O Parlamento Europeu decidiu publicar o presente convite à apresentação de propostas para a conceção, produção, instalação, manutenção e desmontagem da exposição temporária «Juventude inquieta: 70 anos de crescimento na Europa» na Casa da História Europeia em Bruxelas.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Instalações do contratante e Bruxelas - Casa da História Europeia.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>O anúncio de concurso visa estabelecer um contrato de obras para a conceção, produção, instalação, manutenção e desmontagem da exposição temporária «Juventude inquieta: 70 anos de crescimento na Europa» na Casa da História Europeia em Bruxelas. Os referidos serviços/obras incluem:</P>
                  <P>1. Conceção da exposição temporária;</P>
                  <P>2. Adaptação dos espaços existentes, produção, entrega e instalação de paredes divisórias, mobiliário, expositores, bases para expositores e suportes de montagem para objetos, incluindo manipulação e instalação dos objetos, elementos gráficos e cenográficos;</P>
                  <P>3. Fornecimento e instalação do equipamento de iluminação, de hardware audiovisual e multimédia e de todas as outras instalações técnicas necessárias, incluindo um sistema de controlo da exposição, tendo em conta a reutilização de partes do sistema de iluminação existente («Medialon») e grelhas de iluminação instaladas no teto;</P>
                  <P>4. Desenvolvimento e implementação de todo o software multimédia e audiovisual;</P>
                  <P>5. Manutenção da exposição temporária num bom nível operacional e consequente minimização de tempo de inatividade, incluindo mudança ocasional de objetos em expositores;</P>
                  <P>6. Desmontagem, seleção e eliminação da exposição temporária;</P>
                  <P>7. Pesquisa e aquisição de conteúdos, imagens, vídeos e músicas, incluindo direitos necessários, para exposição e utilização impressa e em linha;</P>
                  <P>8. Instalação de uma cerca</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Consultar o caderno de encargos</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Conceção, produção, instalação, manutenção e desmontagem da exposição temporária «Juventude inquieta: 70 anos de crescimento na Europa»</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Será realizada uma visita opcional às instalações em 30.8.2017. Para mais informações, ver condições.</P>
               <P>O Parlamento Europeu reserva-se o direito de recorrer a um procedimento por negociação sem publicação prévia de um anúncio de concurso, de acordo com o artigo 134.º, n.º 1, alínea e), do Regulamento Delegado (UE) n.º 1268/2012 sobre as regras de aplicação do Regulamento (UE, Euratom) N.º 966/2012 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho sobre as regras financeiras aplicáveis ao orçamento geral da União consoante a sua correção mais recente, regulamento delegado (UE) 2015/2462 da Comissão, de 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal Geral do Tribunal de Justiça da União Europeia</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Para informações sobre o(s) prazo(s) para interposição de recursos, contactar o órgão responsável pelos recursos.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunal Geral do Tribunal de Justiça da União Europeia</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="SV">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Europaparlamentet, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Utformning, framtagande, installation, underhåll och nedmontering av den tillfälliga utställningen ”Rastlös ungdom: att växa upp i Europa under 70 år”</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Europaparlamentet har beslutat att utfärda denna anbudsinfordran för utformning, utarbetande, installation, underhåll och nedmontering av den temporära utställningen ”Rastlös ungdom: att växa upp i Europa under 70 år” i Europeiska historiens hus i Bryssel.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Uppdragstagarens lokaler och Bryssel – Europeiska historiens hus.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Anbudsinfordran syftar till att etablera ett byggentreprenadkontrakt för utformning, utarbetande, installation, underhåll och nedmontering av den temporära utställningen ”Rastlös ungdom: att växa upp i Europa under 70 år” i Europeiska historiens hus i Bryssel. Dessa tjänster/arbeten omfattar:</P>
                  <P>1. Utformning av den temporära utställningen;</P>
                  <P>2. Utrustning av de befintliga utrymmena, framtagande, leverans och installation av skiljeväggar, möbler, skyltskåp, utställningsfundament och monteringsstöd för föremål, inklusive hantering och installation av föremålen, grafiken och de scenografiska beståndsdelarna;</P>
                  <P>3. Leverans och installation av belysningsutrustning, audiovisuell maskinvara och multimediemaskinvara och alla andra nödvändiga tekniska installationer, inbegripet utställningskontrollsystem, med beaktande av att delar av det befintliga systemet och de befintliga näten för belysning (Medialon) som är fastsatta i taket kan återanvändas;</P>
                  <P>4. Utveckling och implementering av all audiovisuell programvara och multimedieprogramvara;</P>
                  <P>5. Underhåll av den temporära utställningen på god driftsnivå och följaktligen minimering av spilltid, inbegripet att föremålen i skyltskåpen ibland byts ut;</P>
                  <P>6. Nedmontering, sortering och bortskaffande av den temporära utställningen;</P>
                  <P>7. Letande och förvärv av innehåll, bilder, filmsekvenser och musik, inklusive nödvändiga rättigheter, för visning online och i tryckt form;</P>
                  <P>8. Uppförande av en palissad</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Se förfrågningsunderlaget</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Utformning, framtagande, installation, underhåll och nedmontering av den tillfälliga utställningen ”Rastlös ungdom: att växa upp i Europa under 70 år”</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Ett frivilligt besök kommer att äga rum i lokalerna 30.8.2017. Se villkoren för ytterligare uppgifter.</P>
               <P>Europaparlamentet förbehåller sig rätten att använda ett förhandlat förfarande, utan att tidigare offentliggöra ett meddelande om upphandling, i enlighet med artikel 134.1 (e) i delegerade förordningen (EU) nr 1268/2012 om tillämpningsföreskrifterna för Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU, Euratom) nr 966/2012 om de finansiella reglerna för unionens allmänna budget, senast ändrad genom kommissionens delegerade förordning (EU) 2015/2462 av den 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Europeiska unionens domstols tribunal</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Information om tidsfrist(er) för inlämning av begäran om överprövning kan fås från det organ som ansvarar för överprövning.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Europeiska unionens domstols tribunal</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="CS">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Evropský parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers – PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Návrh, výroba, instalace, údržba a demontáž dočasné expozice: „Neklidné mládí: 70 let dospívání v Evropě“</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Evropský parlament se rozhodl vypsat výzvu k účasti v nabídkovém řízení týkající se návrhu, výroby, instalace, údržby a demontáže dočasné expozice s názvem „Neklidná mládež: 70 let dospívání v Evropě“ v Domě evropských dějin v Bruselu.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Prostory poskytovatele služeb a Brusel – Dům evropských dějin.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Výzva k účasti v nabídkovém řízení týkající se návrhu, výroby, instalace, údržby a demontáže dočasné expozice s názvem „Neklidná mládež: 70 let dospívání v Evropě“ v Domě evropských dějin v Bruselu. Tyto služby / stavební práce zahrnují:</P>
                  <P>1. návrh dočasné expozice;</P>
                  <P>2. vybavení stávajících prostor, výroba, dodání a instalace dělících stěn, nábytku, vitrín, výstavních soklů a připevňovacích podpěr objektů včetně manipulace a instalace objektů, grafiky a scénografických prvků;</P>
                  <P>3. dodání a instalace osvětlovacích zařízení, audiovizuálního a multimediálního hardwaru a dalších nezbytných technických zařízení, včetně kontrolního systému výstavy, s přihlédnutím k možnosti opětovnému použití částí stávajícího osvětlovacího systému („Medialon“) a mříží připevněných ke stropu;</P>
                  <P>4. vypracování a provedení veškerého audiovizuálního a multimediálního softwaru;</P>
                  <P>5. údržba dočasné expozice na dobré provozní úrovni, a také minimalizace odstávky včetně příležitostných výměn objektů ve vitrínách;</P>
                  <P>6. demontáž, třídění a likvidace dočasné expozice;</P>
                  <P>7. obsah, obraz, stopáž a rešerše a pořízení hudby, včetně potřebných práv, pro výstavní, on-line a tiskové využití;</P>
                  <P>8. umístění palisády</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Viz specifikace dokumentu.</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Návrh, výroba, instalace, údržba a demontáž dočasné expozice: „Neklidné mládí: 70 let dospívání v Evropě“</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Bude se konat nepovinná návštěva prostor dne 30.8.2017. Další podrobnosti viz podmínky.</P>
               <P>Evropský parlament si vyhrazuje právo použít jednacího řízení bez předchozího zveřejnění oznámení o zakázce v souladu s článkem 134 odst. 1 písm. e) nařízení Komise v přenesené pravomoci (EU) č. 1268/2012 o prováděcích pravidlech k nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU, Euratom) č. 966/2012, kterým se stanoví finanční pravidla o souhrnném rozpočtu Unie, ve znění nařízení Komise v přenesené pravomoci (EU) 2015/2462 ze dne 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunál Soudního dvora Evropské unie</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Ohledně lhůt(y) pro podání odvolání kontaktujte prosím instituci odpovědnou za odvolání.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunál Soudního dvora Evropské unie</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="ET">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Euroopa Parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers – PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Ajutise näituse „Rahutu noorus: 70 aastat Euroopas üles kasvamist“ kavandamine, tootmine, paigaldamine ning selle hooldamine ja demonteerimine </P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Euroopa Parlament on otsustanud avaldada selle pakkumuskutse, et kavandada, toota ja paigaldada ajutine näitus ning seda hooldada ja see demonteerida. Näituse teema on „Rahutu noorus: 70 aastat Euroopas üles kasvamist“ ja see asub Brüsselis Euroopa Ajaloo Majas. </P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Töövõtjate ruumid ja Brüssel – Euroopa Ajaloo Maja.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Pakkumuskutse eesmärk on sõlmida ehitustööde leping Euroopa Ajaloo Majas Brüsselis ajutise näituse „Rahutu noorus: 70 aastat Euroopas üles kasvamist“ kavandamiseks, tootmiseks, paigaldamiseks ning selle hooldamiseks ja demonteerimiseks.  Need teenused/tööd hõlmavad järgmist:</P>
                  <P>1) ajutise näituse kavandamine; </P>
                  <P>2) olemasolevate ruumide sisustamine, eksponaatide paigaldustugede ja eksponeerimisaluste, vaheseinte, mööbli ja vitriinide tootmine, kohaletoimetamine ja paigaldamine, sh eksponaatide, graafika ja lavaelementide paigaldamine ja käsitsemine; </P>
                  <P>3) valgustusseadmete, audiovisuaal- ja multimeediariistvara ning kõigi muude vajalike tehniliste paigaldiste (sh väljapaneku juhtsüsteemi) tarne ja paigaldamine, pidades silmas olemasoleva valgustussüsteemi (Medialon) osade ja lakke kinnitatud võrkude taaskasutamist; </P>
                  <P>4) kogu audiovisuaal- ja multimeediatarkvara väljatöötamine ja kasutuselevõtt; </P>
                  <P>5) ajutise näituse hooldamine (sh aeg-ajalt vitriinides olevate eksponaatide vahetamine), et hoida see heas töökorras ja vähendada sellega seisakuaega; </P>
                  <P>6) ajutise näituse demonteerimine, sorteerimine ja kõrvaldamine; </P>
                  <P>7) sisu, pildimaterjali, filmimaterjali ja muusika otsimine ja omandamine, sh vajalikud õigused näituste jaoks, veebipõhise ja trükimaterjalina kasutamiseks; </P>
                  <P>8) palissaadi paigaldamine. </P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>vt tehnilise kirjelduse dokumenti</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Ajutise näituse „Rahutu noorus: 70 aastat Euroopas üles kasvamist“ kavandamine, tootmine, paigaldamine ning selle hooldamine ja demonteerimine </P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Ruumides toimub vabatahtlik asukoha külastus 30.8.2017. Lisateavet vt tingimustest.</P>
               <P>Euroopa Parlament jätab endale delegeeritud määruse (EL) nr 1268/2012 (millega kehtestatakse Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu määruse (EL, Euratom) nr 966/2012 (mis käsitleb Euroopa Liidu üldeelarve suhtes kohaldatavaid finantseeskirju) kohaldamise eeskirjad), mida on viimati muudetud komisjoni 30.10.2015 delegeeritud määrusega (EL) 2015/2462, artikli 134 lõike 1 punkti e kohaselt õiguse kasutada läbirääkimistega menetlust hanketeate eelneva avaldamiseta.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Euroopa Liidu Kohtu Üldkohus</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Vaidlustuste esitamise tähtaja/tähtaegade kohta teabe saamiseks palume võtta ühendust vaidlustuste eest vastutava asutusega.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Euroopa Liidu Kohtu Üldkohus</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="HU">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Európai Parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>A „Nyugtalan ifjúság: a felnövekedés 70 éve Európában” időszakos kiállítás megtervezése, létrehozása, a telepítési, a karbantartási és a leszerelési munkák elvégzése </P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Az Európai Parlament úgy döntött, hogy elindítja a brüsszeli Európai Történelem Házában lebonyolítandó „Nyugtalan ifjúság: a felnövekedés 70 éve Európában” című időszakos kiállítás megtervezésére, létrehozására, a telepítési, karbantartási és leszerelési munkák elvégzésére irányuló jelen ajánlati felhívást. </P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>A nyertes ajánlattevő helyszíne és Brüsszel – az Európai Történelem Háza.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Az ajánlati felhívás célja egy építési beruházási szerződés megkötése a brüsszeli Európai Történelem Házában lebonyolítandó „Nyugtalan ifjúság: a felnövekedés 70 éve Európában” című időszakos kiállítás megtervezésére, létrehozására, a telepítési, karbantartási és leszerelési munkák elvégzésére irányulóan.  A szolgáltatások/munkák a következőket foglalják magukban:</P>
                  <P>1. Az időszakos kiállítás megtervezése;</P>
                  <P>2. A már létező terek berendezése, válaszfalaknak, bútorzatnak, bemutatószekrényeknek, kiállító talapzatoknak és a tárgyak szerelési támasztékainak gyártása, leszállítása és telepítése, ideértve a tárgyak, grafikák és díszletfestészeti elemek kezelését és felállítását;</P>
                  <P>3. A világítóberendezések, az audiovizuális és multimédiás hardverek, valamint minden egyéb szükséges műszaki berendezés beszerzése és telepítése, ideértve a kiállítás vezérlőrendszerét is, szem előtt tartva a jelenleg használt világítási rendszer („Medialon”) részeinek és a mennyezethez rögzített rácsok újrafelhasználását;</P>
                  <P>4. Az összes audiovizuális és multimédiás szoftver kifejlesztése és megvalósítása;</P>
                  <P>5. Az időszakos kiállítás megfelelő működési szintjének fenntartása, és ebből kifolyólag az állásidő minimalizálása, ideértve a bemutatószekrényekben kiállított tárgyak esetleges cseréjét;</P>
                  <P>6. Az időszakos kiállítás szétszerelése, szortírozása és elszállítása;</P>
                  <P>7. Tartalom-, kép-, bemutatófilm- és zenekutatás és -beszerzés, ideértve a szükséges jogokat is, kiállítás, online és nyomtatott formában történő felhasználás céljára;</P>
                  <P>8. Egy paliszád elhelyezése</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Lásd a pályázati dokumentációt</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>A „Nyugtalan ifjúság: a felnövekedés 70 éve Európában” időszakos kiállítás megtervezése, létrehozása, a telepítési, a karbantartási és a leszerelési munkák elvégzése </P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>A 2017. augusztus 30-án megrendezendő helyszíni szemlén a részvétel opcionális. A további részleteket lásd a feltételekben.</P>
               <P>Az Európai Parlament fenntartja a jogot arra, hogy ajánlati felhívás előzetes közzététele nélküli tárgyalásos eljárást alkalmazzon a legutóbb a 2015. október 30-i keltezésű (EU) 2015/2462 bizottsági felhatalmazáson alapuló rendelettel módosított, az Unió általános költségvetésére alkalmazandó pénzügyi szabályokról szóló 966/2012/EU, Euratom európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet alkalmazási szabályairól szóló, 1268/2012/EU felhatalmazáson alapuló bizottsági rendelet 134. cikke (1) bekezdése e) pontjának megfelelően.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Az Európai Unió Bíróságának Törvényszéke</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Kérjük, a fellebbezési határidők ügyében vegye fel a kapcsolatot a fellebbezésekért felelős szervvel.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Az Európai Unió Bíróságának Törvényszéke</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="LT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Europos Parlamentas, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers – PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Laikinos parodos „Neramus jaunimas: 70 metų augimo Europoje“ projektavimas, gamyba, įrengimas, priežiūra ir išmontavimas </P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Europos Parlamentas nusprendė paskelbti šį kvietimą pateikti pasiūlymus dėl projektavimo, rengimo, įrengimo, priežiūros ir išmontavimo darbų, susijusių su laikinąja paroda „Nerimastingas jaunimas: 70 metų augant Europoje“ Europos istorijos namuose Briuselyje.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Rangovų patalpos ir Briuselis – Europos istorijos namai.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Kvietimo pateikti pasiūlymus tikslas – sudaryti darbų pirkimo sutartį dėl projektavimo, rengimo, įrengimo, priežiūros ir išmontavimo darbų, susijusių su laikinąja paroda „Nerimastingas jaunimas: 70 metų augant Europoje“ Europos istorijos namuose Briuselyje. Šios paslaugos / darbai apima:</P>
                  <P>1. Laikinosios parodos projektavimą;</P>
                  <P>2. Esamų erdvių įrengimą, pertvarų, baldų, vitrinų, stendų pagrindų ir montuojamų atramų, skirtų objektams, gamybą, pristatymą ir įrengimą, įskaitant objektų, grafikos ir scenografinių elementų tvarkymą ir įrengimą;</P>
                  <P>3. Apšvietimo įrangos, garso ir vaizdo bei daugialypės terpės aparatinės įrangos ir visų kitų būtinų techninių įrenginių tiekimą ir įrengimą, įskaitant parodos valdymo sistemą, atsižvelgiant į esamos apšvietimo įrangos sistemos („Medialon“) dalių pakartotinį panaudojimą ir groteles, pritvirtintas prie lubų;</P>
                  <P>4. Visos audiovizualinės ir daugialypės terpės programinės įrangos kūrimą ir įgyvendinimą;</P>
                  <P>5. Gero laikinosios parodos veikimo lygio palaikymą, taigi, prastovų sumažinimą, įskaitant retkarčiais vykdomą vitrinose esančių objektų pakeitimą;</P>
                  <P>6. Laikinosios parodos išmontavimą, rūšiavimą ir pašalinimą;</P>
                  <P>7. Turinio, vaizdų, filmuotos medžiagos ir muzikos mokslinius tyrimus ir įsigijimą, įskaitant reikalingas teises eksponuoti, naudoti internete ir spausdinti;</P>
                  <P>8. Apsauginės sienelės pastatymą.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Žr. specifikacijų dokumentą.</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Laikinos parodos „Neramus jaunimas: 70 metų augimo Europoje“ projektavimas, gamyba, įrengimas, priežiūra ir išmontavimas </P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Bus neprivalomas apsilankymas patalpose 30.8.2017. Išsamesnę informaciją žr. sąlygose.</P>
               <P>Europos Parlamentas turi teisę naudoti derybų procedūrą be išankstinio skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo, vadovaujantis deleguotojo reglamento (ES) Nr. 1268/2012 dėl Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamento (ES, Euratomas) Nr. 966/2012 dėl Sąjungos bendrajam biudžetui taikomų finansinių taisyklių taikymo taisyklių su paskutiniais pakeitimais, padarytais 2015.10.30 Komisijos deleguotuoju reglamentu (ES) 2015/2462, 134 straipsnio 1 dalies e punktu.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Europos Sąjungos Teisingumo Teismo Bendrasis Teismas</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Informacijos apie apeliacijų pateikimo terminą (-us) prašome kreiptis į įstaigą, atsakingą už apeliacijas.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Europos Sąjungos Teisingumo Teismo Bendrasis Teismas</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="LV">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Eiropas Parlaments, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Pagaidu ekspozīcijas “Nemierīgā jaunatne: 70 gadi pieaugot Eiropā” plānošana, sagatavošana, ierīkošana, uzturēšana un novākšana </P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Eiropas Parlaments ir nolēmis izsludināt šo uzaicinājumu uz konkursu par pagaidu ekspozīcijas “Nemierīgā jaunatne: 70 gadi pieaugot Eiropā” plānošanu, sagatavošanu, uzstādīšanu, uzturēšanu un novākšanu Briselē esošajā Eiropas vēstures namā.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>darbuzņēmēju telpas un Eiropas vēstures nams Briselē</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Uzaicinājuma uz konkursu mērķis ir noslēgt būvdarbu līgumu par pagaidu ekspozīcijas “Nemierīgā jaunatne: 70 gadi pieaugot Eiropā” plānošanu, sagatavošanu, ierīkošanu, uzturēšanu un novākšanu Briselē esošajā Eiropas vēstures namā. Šie pakalpojumi/būvdarbi ietver:</P>
                  <P>1. pagaidu ekspozīcijas plānošanu;</P>
                  <P>2. esošo telpu aprīkošanu, starpsienu, mēbeļu, vitrīnu, eksponātu statīvu un priekšmetu balsta elementu izgatavošanu, piegādi un uzstādīšanu, tostarp priekšmetu, attēlu un scenogrāfijas elementu pārvietošanu un uzstādīšanu;</P>
                  <P>3. apgaismes iekārtu, audiovizuālās un multivides aparatūras un visu pārējo nepieciešamo tehnisko iekārtu, tostarp ekspozīcijas kontroles sistēmas, piegādi un uzstādīšanu, ņemot vērā iespēju izmantot esošās apgaismes sistēmas (“Medialon”) daļas un griestiem piestiprinātos režģus;</P>
                  <P>4. visas audiovizuālās un multivides programmatūras izstrādi un ieviešanu;</P>
                  <P>5. pagaidu ekspozīcijas uzturēšanu labā darba kārtībā (tostarp vitrīnās izvietoto priekšmetu periodisku nomaiņu), tādējādi samazinot dīkstāves laiku;</P>
                  <P>6. pagaidu ekspozīcijas novākšanu, tās materiālu šķirošanu un likvidēšanu;</P>
                  <P>7. ekspozīcijā, internetā un drukātos materiālos izmantojama satura, attēlu, video materiālu un mūzikas meklēšanu un ieguvi, tostarp nepieciešamo tiesību ieguvi;</P>
                  <P>8. aizsargsienas uzstādīšanu.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>lūdzam skatīt specifikāciju dokumentu</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Pagaidu ekspozīcijas “Nemierīgā jaunatne: 70 gadi pieaugot Eiropā” plānošana, sagatavošana, ierīkošana, uzturēšana un novākšana </P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>30.8.2017 notiks neobligāts telpu apmeklējums. Sīkāku informāciju lūdzam skatīt nosacījumos.</P>
               <P>Saskaņā ar 134. panta 1. punkta e) apakšpunktu Komisijas Deleģētajā regulā (ES) Nr. 1268/2012 (2012. gada 29. oktobris) par Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regulas (ES, Euratom) Nr. 966/2012 par finanšu noteikumiem, ko piemēro Savienības vispārējam budžetam, piemērošanas noteikumiem, kurā jaunākie grozījumi izdarīti ar Komisijas Deleģēto regulu (ES) 2015/2462 (2015. gada 30. oktobris), Eiropas Parlaments saglabā tiesības izmantot sarunu procedūru bez iepriekšējas paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Eiropas Savienības Tiesas Vispārējā tiesa</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>lūdzam sazināties ar struktūru, kas atbildīga par pārsūdzības procedūrām, lai iegūtu informāciju par pārsūdzību iesniegšanas termiņu(-iem).</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Eiropas Savienības Tiesas Vispārējā tiesa</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="MT">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Il-Parlament Ewropew, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Id-disinn, il-produzzjoni, l-installazzjoni, il-manutenzjoni u ż-żarmar tal-wirja temporanja ‘Żgħażagħ mingħajr kwiet: 70 sena ta' tkabbir fl-Ewropa’</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Il-Parlament Ewropew iddeċieda li joħroġ din l-istedina għall-offerti għad-disinn, il-produzzjoni, l-installazzjoni, il-manutenzjoni u ż-żarmar tal-wirja temporanja ‘Żgħażagħ mingħajr kwiet: 70 sena ta' tkabbir fl-Ewropa’ fid-Dar tal-Istorja Ewropea fi Brussell.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Fil-bini tal-kuntrattur u fi Brussell — id-Dar tal-Istorja Ewropea.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>L-istedina għall-offerti għandha l-għan li tistabbilixxi kuntratt ta' xogħlijiet għad-disinn, il-produzzjoni, l-installazzjoni, il-manutenzjoni u ż-żarmar tal-wirja temporanja ‘Żgħażagħ mingħajr kwiet: 70 sena ta' tkabbir fl-Ewropa’ fid-Dar tal-Istorja Ewropea fi Brussell. Dawk is-servizzi/ix-xogħlijiet jinkludu:</P>
                  <P>1. Id-disinn tal-wirja temporanja;</P>
                  <P>2. It-tgħammir bażiku tal-ispazji li hemm, il-produzzjoni, il-kunsinna u l-installazzjoni ta' ħitan għat-tqassim f'partijiet, għamara, vetrini, bażijiet ta' wiri u appoġġi għall-immuntar għal oġġetti inkluż it-tqandil u l-installazzjoni tal-oġġetti, elementi grafiċi u xenografiċi;</P>
                  <P>3. Il-provvista u l-installazzjoni tat-tagħmir ta' tidwil, ħardwer awdjoviżiv u tal-multimedja u installazzjonijiet tekniċi oħra neċessarji, inkluża sistema ta' kontroll tal-wiri, filwaqt li jitqies l-użu mill-ġdid ta' partijiet tas-sistema ta' tidwil li qed tintuża ("Medialon") u grilji fissi mas-saqaf;</P>
                  <P>4. L-iżvilupp u l-implimentazzjoni tas-softwer kollu tal-awdjoviżiv u l-multimidja;</P>
                  <P>5. Il-manutenzjoni tal-wirja temporanja fuq livell operazzjonali tajjeb u bħala riżultat it-tnaqqis ta' perijodi ta' waqfien, inkluż il-bdil ta' oġġetti b'mod okkażjonali fil-vetrini;</P>
                  <P>6. Iż-żarmar, l-issortjar u t-tneħħija tal-wirja temporanja;</P>
                  <P>7. Ir-riċerka u l-akkwist tal-kontenut, l-immaġini, il-vidjow, u l-mużika, inkluż id-drittijiet meħtieġa, għall-wirja, l-użu onlajn u stampat;</P>
                  <P>8. It-tqegħid ta' barrieri</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Ara d-dokument tal-ispeċifikazzjonijiet</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Id-disinn, il-produzzjoni, l-installazzjoni, il-manutenzjoni u ż-żarmar tal-wirja temporanja ‘Żgħażagħ mingħajr kwiet: 70 sena ta' tkabbir fl-Ewropa’</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Se jkun hemm żjara mhux obbligatorja fuq il-post nhar it-30.8.2017. Għal aktar dettalji jekk jogħġbok ara l-kundizzjonijiet.</P>
               <P>Il-Parlament Ewropew jirriżerva d-dritt li juża l-proċedura nnegozjata mingħajr il-pubblikazzjoni ta' avviz ta' kuntratt minn qabel, skont l-Artiklu 134.1(e) tar-Regolament ta' Delega tal-Kummissjoni (UE) Nru 1268/2012 tat-29 ta’ Ottubru 2012 dwar ir-regoli tal-applikazzjoni tar-Regolament (UE, Euratom) Nru 966/2012 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill dwar ir-regoli finanzjarji applikabbli għall-baġit ġenerali tal-Unjoni kif emendati l-aħħar mir-Regolament Delegat tal-Kummissjoni (UE) 2015/2462 tat-30 ta' Ottubru 2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Il-Qorti Ġenerali tal-Qorti tal-Ġustizzja tal-Unjoni Ewropea</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Jekk jogħġbok ikkuntattja lill-korp responsabbli għall-appelli għat-tagħrif dwar id-data(i) tal-għeluq għat-tressiq tal-appelli.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Il-Qorti Ġenerali tal-Qorti tal-Ġustizzja tal-Unjoni Ewropea</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="PL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Parlament Europejski, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Projekt, produkcja, montaż, utrzymanie i demontaż wystawy czasowej „Niespokojna młodzież: 70 lat dorastania w Europie”</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Parlament Europejski postanowił wystąpić z niniejszym zaproszeniem do składania ofert na projekt, produkcję, montaż, utrzymanie oraz demontaż tymczasowej ekspozycji „Niespokojna młodzież: 70 lat dorastania w Europie” w Domu Historii Europejskiej w Brukseli.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>siedziba instytucji zamawiającej w Brukseli – Dom Historii Europejskiej.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Parlament Europejski postanowił wystąpić z niniejszym zaproszeniem do składania ofert na projekt, produkcję, montaż, utrzymanie oraz demontaż tymczasowej ekspozycji „Niespokojna młodzież: 70 lat dorastania w Europie” w Domu Historii Europejskiej w Brukseli. Usługi/roboty obejmują:</P>
                  <P>1. zaprojektowanie tymczasowej ekspozycji;</P>
                  <P>2. aranżację istniejących przestrzeni, wyprodukowanie, dostawę i montaż ścian działowych, mebli, gablot, stojaków ekspozycyjnych i wsporników montażowych dla eksponatów, w tym obsługę i montaż eksponatów, prac graficznych i elementów scenograficznych;</P>
                  <P>3. dostawę i montaż urządzeń oświetleniowych, sprzętu audiowizualnego i multimedialnego oraz wszelkich innych koniecznych instalacji technicznych, w tym systemu kontroli wystawy, z uwzględnieniem ponownego wykorzystania części istniejącego systemu oświetlenia („Medialon”) i kratek zamocowanych do sufitu;</P>
                  <P>4. stworzenie i wdrożenie całego oprogramowania audiowizualnego i multimedialnego;</P>
                  <P>5. utrzymanie wystawy czasowej w dobrym stanie technicznym, a co za tym idzie minimalizacja czasu przestoju, w tym okazjonalna wymiana eksponatów w gablotach;</P>
                  <P>6. demontaż, posortowanie i usunięcie tymczasowej ekspozycji;</P>
                  <P>7. analiza i pozyskanie treści, obrazów, materiału filmowego i muzyki, w tym koniecznych praw, do użytku na wystawie, w internecie i w druku;</P>
                  <P>8. ustawienie palisady.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>zob. specyfikację istotnych warunków zamówienia.</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Projekt, produkcja, montaż, utrzymanie i demontaż wystawy czasowej „Niespokojna młodzież: 70 lat dorastania w Europie”</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>W dniu 30.8.2017 odbędzie się nieobowiązkowa wizyta w pomieszczeniach. Więcej szczegółów – zob. warunki.</P>
               <P>Parlament Europejski zastrzega sobie prawo do zastosowania procedury negocjacyjnej bez uprzedniej publikacji ogłoszenia o zamówieniu zgodnie z art. 134 ust. 1 lit. e) rozporządzenia delegowanego (UE) nr 1268/2012 w sprawie zasad stosowania rozporządzenia Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE, Euratom) nr 966/2012 w sprawie zasad finansowych mających zastosowanie do budżetu ogólnego Unii, ostatnio zmienionego rozporządzeniem delegowanym Komisji (UE) 2015/2462 z 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Sąd Trybunału Sprawiedliwości Unii Europejskiej</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>zapytania o informacje dotyczące terminów składania odwołań należy kierować do organu odpowiedzialnego za odwołania.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Sąd Trybunału Sprawiedliwości Unii Europejskiej</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="SK">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Európsky parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Návrh, výroba, inštalácia, údržba a demontáž v súvislosti s dočasnou výstavou „Nepokojná mládež: 70 rokov dospievania v Európe“</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Európsky parlament rozhodol o vypísaní tejto výzvy na súťaž na návrh, výrobu, inštaláciu, údržbu a demontáž dočasnej výstavy s názvom „Nepokojná mládež: 70 rokov dospievania v Európe“ v Dome európskej histórie v Bruseli.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>priestory dodávateľov a Brusel – Dom európskej histórie.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Výzva na predkladanie ponúk sa zameriava na uzatvorenie zmluvy o vykonaní prác na návrh, výrobu, inštaláciu, údržbu a demontáž dočasnej výstavy s názvom „Nepokojná mládež: 70 rokov dospievania v Európe“ v Dome európskej histórie v Bruseli. Tieto služby/práce zahŕňajú:</P>
                  <P>1. návrh dočasnej výstavy;</P>
                  <P>2. vybavenie existujúcich priestorov, výrobu, dodanie a montáž deliacich priečok, nábytku, vitrín, podstavcov pre exponáty a upevňovacích podpier pre predmety vrátane manipulácie s predmetmi a ich inštalácie, grafiky a scénografických prvkov;</P>
                  <P>3. dodávku a inštaláciu osvetlenia, audiovizuálneho a multimediálneho hardvéru a všetkých ostatných potrebných technických zariadení vrátane systému kontroly výstavy so zohľadnením opätovného využitia prvkov existujúceho systém osvetlenia („Medialon“) a vedení pripevnených na strop;</P>
                  <P>4. vývoj a implementáciu všetkých audiovizuálnych a multimediálnych softvérov;</P>
                  <P>5. údržbu dočasnej výstavy na dobrej prevádzkovej úrovni a následné minimalizovanie prestojov vrátane občasnej výmeny predmetov vo vitrínach;</P>
                  <P>6. demontáž, roztriedenie a odstránenie dočasnej výstavy;</P>
                  <P>7. výskum a získanie obsahov, snímok, fotiek vrátane potrebných práv pre výstavu na online a tlačené použitie;</P>
                  <P>8. umiestnenie palisády.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Pozri súťažné podklady</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Návrh, výroba, inštalácia, údržba a demontáž v súvislosti s dočasnou výstavou „Nepokojná mládež: 70 rokov dospievania v Európe“</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Organizuje sa nepovinná prehliadka miesta 30.8.2017. Ďalšie podrobnosti nájdete v podmienkach.</P>
               <P>Európsky parlament si vyhradzuje právo na využitie rokovacieho konania bez predchádzajúceho zverejnenia oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania v zmysle článku 134 ods. 1 písm. e) delegovaného nariadenia (EÚ) č. 1268/2012 o pravidlách uplatňovania nariadenia Európskeho parlamentu a Rady č. 966/2012 o rozpočtových pravidlách, ktoré sa vzťahujú na všeobecný rozpočet Únie, naposledy zmeneného delegovaným nariadením Komisie (EÚ) 2015/2462 z 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Všeobecný súd Súdneho dvora Európskej únie</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Na získanie informácií o konečnom termíne na podávanie odvolaní kontaktujte orgán zodpovedný za odvolania.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Všeobecný súd Súdneho dvora Európskej únie</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="SL">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Evropski parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Načrtovanje, izdelava, namestitev, vzdrževanje in odstranitev začasne razstave „Nemirna mladost: 70 let odraščanja v Evropi“</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Evropski parlament se je odločil za objavo tega javnega razpisa z namenom načrtovanja, izdelave, namestitve, vzdrževanja in odstranitve začasne razstave „Nemirna mladost: 70 let odraščanja v Evropi“ v Hiši evropske zgodovine v Bruslju.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>prostori izvajalca in Bruselj – Hiša evropske zgodovine.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Namen javnega razpisa je oddaja naročila gradenj za načrtovanje, izdelavo, namestitev, vzdrževanje in odstranitev začasne razstave „Nemirna mladost: 70 let odraščanja v Evropi“ v Hiši evropske zgodovine v Bruslju. Te storitve/gradnje vključujejo:</P>
                  <P>1. načrtovanje začasne razstave;</P>
                  <P>2. opremljanje obstoječih prostorov, izdelavo, dostavo in namestitev pregradnih sten, pohištva, vitrin, razstavnih podstavkov in vgradnih opornikov za predmete, vključno z upravljanjem in namestitvijo predmetov, grafik in scenografskih elementov;</P>
                  <P>3. dobavo in namestitev opreme za razsvetljavo, avdiovizualne in multimedijske strojne opreme in drugih potrebnih tehničnih napeljav, vključno s sistemom za nadzor razstave, ob upoštevanju ponovne uporabe delov obstoječega sistema za razsvetljavo („Medialon“) in omrežij, pritrjenih na strop;</P>
                  <P>4. razvoj in namestitev vse avdiovizualne in multimedijske programske opreme;</P>
                  <P>5. vzdrževanje začasne razstave na dobri operativni ravni in posledično čim večjo omejitev izpadov, vključno z občasno zamenjavo predmetov v vitrinah;</P>
                  <P>6. demontažo, sortiranje in odstranitev začasne razstave;</P>
                  <P>7. raziskavo in pridobitev vsebine, slik, posnetkov in glasbe za razstavo v spletni in tiskani obliki, vključno s potrebnimi pravicami;</P>
                  <P>8. postavitev pregrade.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Glej dokument s specifikacijami</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Načrtovanje, izdelava, namestitev, vzdrževanje in odstranitev začasne razstave „Nemirna mladost: 70 let odraščanja v Evropi“</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Neobvezni obisk prostorov bo potekal 30.8.2017. Nadaljnje informacije so na voljo v pogojih.</P>
               <P>Evropski parlament si pridržuje pravico do uporabe postopka s pogajanji brez predhodne objave obvestila o naročilu v skladu s členom 134.1(e) Delegirane uredba Komisije (EU) št. 1268/2012 z dne 29.10.2012 o pravilih uporabe Uredbe (EU, Euratom) št. 966/2012 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta o finančnih pravilih, ki se uporabljajo za splošni proračun Unije, kakor je bila nazadnje spremenjena z Delegirano uredbo Komisije (EU) 2015/2462 z dne 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Splošno sodišče Sodišča Evropske unije</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Za informacije v zvezi s časovnimi roki za vložitev pritožb se obrnite na organ, pristojen za pritožbe.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Splošno sodišče Sodišča Evropske unije</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="GA">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Parlaimint na hEorpa, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Taispeántas sealadach 'Óige neamhshocair' a dhearadh, a tháirgeadh, a shuiteáil, a chothabháil agus a dhíchóimeáil: 70 bliain d'fhás aníos san Eoraip'. </P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Tá sé socraithe ag Parlaimint na hEorpa an cuireadh seo chun tairisceana a eisiúint chun dearadh, táirgeadh, suiteáil, cothabháil agus díchóimeáil a dhéanamh i leith an taispeántais shealadaigh 'Óige ghiodamach: 70 bliana d'fhás aníos san Eoraip' ag Áras Stair na hEorpa sa Bhruiséil.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Áitreabh na gConraitheoirí agus sa Bhruiséil - Áras Stair na hEorpa.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Is éard is aidhm leis an gcuireadh seo chun tairisceana conradh oibreacha a bhunú chun dearadh, táirgeadh, suiteáil, cothabháil agus díchóimeáil a dhéanamh i leith an taispeántais shealadaigh 'Óige ghiodamach: 70 bliana d'fhás aníos san Eoraip' ag Áras Stair na hEorpa sa Bhruiséil. Áirítear leis na seirbhísí/na hoibreacha úd:</P>
                  <P>1. Taispeántas sealadach a dhearadh;</P>
                  <P>2. Feistiú na spásanna reatha, spiaraí, troscán, sárthaispeántais, boinn taispeána agus tacaí gléasta le haghaidh nithe, láimhseáil agus suiteáil na nithe san áireamh, grafaic agus gnéithe grafaíochta radhairc a tháirgeadh, a sheachadadh agus a shuiteáil;</P>
                  <P>3. An trealamh soilsithe, crua-earraí closamhairc agus ilmheán a sholáthar agus a shuiteáil mar aon leis na suiteálacha teicniúla riachtanacha go léir eile, lena n-áirítear córas rialaithe taispeántais, ag tabhairt san áireamh athúsáid chodanna an chórais soilsithe reatha (“Medialon”) agus na ngreillí atá feistithe leis an tsíleáil;</P>
                  <P>4. Na bogearraí closamhairc agus ilmheán uile a fhorbairt agus a chur chun feidhme;</P>
                  <P>5. An taispeántas sealadach a chothabháil ar leibhéal dea-oibriúcháin agus dá réir sin aga neamhfhónaimh a íoslaghdú, lena n-áireofar athrú ócáideach nithe i sárthaispeántais;</P>
                  <P>6. An taispeántas sealadach a dhíchóimeáil, a shórtáil agus a dhiúscairt;</P>
                  <P>7. Taighde agus fáil maidir le hinneachar, íomhá, píosa scannánaíochta, agus ceol, lena n-áireofar na cearta riachtanacha, le haghaidh taispeántais, úsáid ar líne agus i gcló;</P>
                  <P>8. Sonnach a chur</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Féach doiciméad na Sonraíochtaí</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Taispeántas sealadach 'Óige neamhshocair' a dhearadh, a tháirgeadh, a shuiteáil, a chothabháil agus a dhíchóimeáil: 70 bliain d'fhás aníos san Eoraip'. </P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Beidh cuairt roghnach ar an áitreabh an 30.8.2017. Le haghaidh tuilleadh sonraí féach na coinníollacha.</P>
               <P>Forchoimeádann Parlaimint na hEorpa an ceart leas a bhaint as nós imeachta idirbheartaithe gan fógra conartha a fhoilsiú roimh ré, de réir Airteagal 134.1(e) de Rialachán Tarmligthe (AE) Uimh. 1268/2012 um rialacha maidir le cur i bhfeidhm Rialachán (AE, Euratom) Uimh. 966/2012 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle maidir leis na rialacha airgeadais is infheidhme ar bhuiséad ginearálta an Aontais de réir mar a leasaíodh go deireanach ag rialachán tarmligthe (AE) 2015/2462 ón gCoimisiún an 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Cúirt Ghinearálta Chúirt Bhreithiúnais an Aontais Eorpaigh</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Déan teagmháil leis an gcomhlacht atá freagrach as achomhairc maidir le faisnéis a bhaineann le spriocdháta(í) le haghaidh achomhairc a dhéanamh.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Cúirt Ghinearálta Chúirt Bhreithiúnais an Aontais Eorpaigh</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="BG">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Европейски парламент, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Проектиране, производство, монтаж, поддръжка и демонтаж на временната изложба „Неспокойна младост: 70 години на порастване в Европа“</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Европейският парламент реши да публикува тази покана за участие в търг за проектирането, производството, монтажа, поддръжката и демонтажа на временната изложба „Неспокойна младост: 70 години на порастване в Европа“ в Дома на европейската история в Брюксел.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Помещенията на изпълнителя и в Брюксел — Дом на европейската история.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Поканата за участие в търг цели да установи работна поръчка за проектирането, производството, монтажа, поддръжката и демонтажа на временната изложба „Неспокойна младост: 70 години на порастване в Европа“ в Дома на европейската история в Брюксел. Тези услуги/дейности включват:</P>
                  <P>1. Проектиране на временната изложба;</P>
                  <P>2. Основно оборудване на съществуващите помещения, изготвяне, доставка и монтаж на преградни стени, обзавеждане, витрини, поставки за излагане и монтажни опори за предмети, включително работа с и монтаж на предмети, графики и сценографски елементи;</P>
                  <P>3. Доставка и монтаж на осветително оборудване, аудиовизуален и мултимедиен хардуер и всички други необходими технически инсталации, включително система за управление на изложбата, като се има предвид повторната употреба на части от съществуващата осветителна система („Medialon“) и мрежите, фиксирани към тавана;</P>
                  <P>4. Разработване и прилагане на целия аудиовизуален и мултимедиен софтуер;</P>
                  <P>5. Поддръжка на временната изложба на добро работно ниво и следователно свеждане до минимум на прекъсванията, включително при смяна на предмети във витрините;</P>
                  <P>6. Демонтаж, сортиране и отстраняване на временната изложба;</P>
                  <P>7. Проучване и придобиване на съдържание, изображения, кадри и музика, включително необходимите права за използване за изложби, онлайн или печат;</P>
                  <P>8. Поставяне на палисада</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Вижте документа със спецификациите</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Проектиране, производство, монтаж, поддръжка и демонтаж на временната изложба „Неспокойна младост: 70 години на порастване в Европа“</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>На 30.8.2017 г. ще се проведе незадължително посещение на помещенията. За допълнителна информация, моля, вж. условията.</P>
               <P>Европейският парламент си запазва правото да използва процедура на договаряне, без предварително публикуване на обявление за поръчка, съгласно член 134, параграф 1, буква д) от Делегиран регламент (ЕС) № 1268/2012 относно правилата за прилагане на Регламент (ЕС, Евратом) № 966/2012 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета относно финансовите правила, приложими за общия бюджет на Съюза, последно изменен от Делегиран регламент (ЕС) № 2015/2462 на Комисията от 30.10.2015 г.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Общ съд на Съда на Европейския съюз</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Моля, свържете се с органа, който отговоря за подаване на жалби, за информация относно крайния/те срок/ове за подаване на жалби.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Общ съд на Съда на Европейския съюз</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="RO">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Parlamentul European, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Conceperea, realizarea, instalarea, întreținerea și demontarea expoziției temporare „Tinerețe neliniștită: 70 de ani de creștere în Europa”</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Parlamentul European a decis să lanseze această invitație la licitație pentru conceperea, producția, instalarea, întreținerea și demontarea expoziției temporare „Tinerețe neliniștită: 70 de ani de creștere în Europa” la Casa Istoriei Europene din Bruxelles.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Sediul contractanților și Bruxelles – Casa Istoriei Europene.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Invitația de participare la licitație urmărește stabilirea unui contract de lucrări pentru conceperea, producția, instalarea, întreținerea și demontarea expoziției temporare „Tinerețe neliniștită: 70 de ani de creștere în Europa” la Casa Istoriei Europene din Bruxelles. Respectivele servicii/lucrări includ:</P>
                  <P>1. Conceperea expoziției temporare;</P>
                  <P>2. Amenajarea spațiilor existente, producția, livrarea și instalarea de pereți despărțitori, de mobilier, de vitrine, de baze de prezentare și de suporturi de montare pentru obiecte, inclusiv manipularea și instalarea obiectelor, elementelor grafice și scenografice;</P>
                  <P>3. Furnizarea și instalarea echipamentului de iluminat, hardware-ului audiovizual și multimedia și a tuturor celorlalte instalații tehnice necesare, inclusiv a sistemului de control al expoziției, ținând cont de reutilizarea unor piese ale sistemului de iluminat existent („Medialon”) și a grilajelor fixate de plafon;</P>
                  <P>4. Dezvoltarea și implementarea întregului software audiovizual și multimedia;</P>
                  <P>5. Menținerea expoziției temporare în stare bună de funcționare și, prin urmare, reducerea la minimum a perioadei de nefuncționare, inclusiv schimbarea ocazională a obiectelor din vitrine;</P>
                  <P>6. Demontarea, sortarea și îndepărtarea expoziției temporare;</P>
                  <P>7. Căutarea și achiziționarea de conținut, imagini, fotografii și muzică, inclusiv a drepturilor necesare, pentru expoziție și utilizarea în format tipărit și online;</P>
                  <P>8. Amplasarea unei palisade</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>A se vedea caietul de sarcini</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Conceperea, realizarea, instalarea, întreținerea și demontarea expoziției temporare „Tinerețe neliniștită: 70 de ani de creștere în Europa”</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Va fi organizată o vizită opțională la sediu la data de 30.8.2017. Pentru detalii suplimentare, a se vedea condițiile.</P>
               <P>Parlamentul European își rezervă dreptul de a utiliza o procedură de negociere fără publicarea în prealabil a unui anunț de participare, conform articolului 134 alineatul (1) litera (e) din Regulamentul delegat (UE) nr. 1268/2012 privind normele de aplicare a Regulamentului (UE, Euratom) nr. din 966/2012 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului privind normele financiare aplicabile bugetului general al Uniunii, astfel cum a fost modificat ultima dată prin Regulamentul delegat (UE) 2015/2462 al Comisiei din 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunalul Curții de Justiție a Uniunii Europene</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Pentru precizări privind termenul-limită (termenele-limită) de exercitare a căilor de atac, a se contacta organismul competent pentru căile de atac.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Tribunalul Curții de Justiție a Uniunii Europene</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
      <F03_2014 CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" FORM="F03" LG="HR">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Europski parlament, Directorate-General for Communication, Directorate for Relations with the Citizens, House of European History, FAO Mr. R. Evers — PHS00A77</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>60 rue Wiertz</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Brussels</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>1047</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/>
               <E_MAIL>hehtenders@ep.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.europarl.europa.eu/tenders/invitations.htm</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="EU_INSTITUTION"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Osmišljavanje, izrada, postavljanje, održavanje i rasklapanje privremene izložbe „Nemirna mladež: 70 godina odrastanja u Europi”</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>COMM/DG/AWD/2017/772</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="92521100"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Europski je parlament odlučio objaviti ovaj poziv na nadmetanje za osmišljavanje, produkciju, postavljanje, održavanje i rasklapanje privremene izložbe „Nemirna mladež: 70 godina odrastanja u Europi” u Domu europske povijesti u Bruxellesu.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79930000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="45212313"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="31500000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="39100000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="44523200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32322000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72212520"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="30200000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32320000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="32340000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79822500"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="92110000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="BE100"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Prostori ugovaratelja i Bruxelles — Dom europske povijesti.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Cilj je ovog poziva na dostavu ponuda uspostava ugovora o radovima za osmišljavanje, produkciju, postavljanje, održavanje i rasklapanje privremene izložbe „Nemirna mladež: 70 godina odrastanja u Europi” u Domu europske povijesti u Bruxellesu. Te usluge/radovi obuhvaćaju:</P>
                  <P>1. osmišljavanje privremene izložbe;</P>
                  <P>2. temeljno uređenje postojećih prostora, izradu, isporuku i postavljanje pregradnih zidova, namještaja, vitrina, podnožja i potpornja za postavljanje za predmete, grafike, scenografske elemente;</P>
                  <P>3. nabava i postavljanje rasvjetne opreme, audiovizualne i multimedijske strojne opreme i ostalih nužnih tehničkih instalacija, uključujući sustav kontrole za izložbu, uzimajući u obzir dijelove postojećeg sustava rasvjete („Medialon”) i mreže koja je pričvršćena na strop;</P>
                  <P>4. razvoj i primjenu cjelokupnog audiovizualnog i multimedijskog softvera;</P>
                  <P>5. održavanje privremene izložbe na dobroj operativnoj razini te time i smanjenje sati nedostupnosti, uključujući povremenu izmjenu predmeta u izložbenim vitrinama;</P>
                  <P>6. rasklapanje, razvrstavanje i odlaganje privremene izložbe;</P>
                  <P>7. istraživanje i nabava sadržaja, slika, snimljenog materijala, uključujući nužna prava, za izložbu te mrežnu i tiskanu upotrebu;</P>
                  <P>8. postavljanje palisada.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_QUALITY>
                  <AC_CRITERION>Vidjeti dokument sa specifikacijama</AC_CRITERION>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>60</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_QUALITY>
               <AC_PRICE>
                  <AC_WEIGHTING>40</AC_WEIGHTING>
               </AC_PRICE>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 154-318476</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <AWARD_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Osmišljavanje, izrada, postavljanje, održavanje i rasklapanje privremene izložbe „Nemirna mladež: 70 godina odrastanja u Europi”</P>
            </TITLE>
            <AWARDED_CONTRACT>
               <DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>2018-02-02</DATE_CONCLUSION_CONTRACT>
               <NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>4</NB_TENDERS_RECEIVED>
               <NO_AWARDED_TO_GROUP/>
               <CONTRACTOR>
                  <ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                     <OFFICIALNAME>TINKER Imagineers BV</OFFICIALNAME>
                     <TOWN>Utrecht</TOWN>
                     <COUNTRY VALUE="NL"/>
                     <n2016:NUTS CODE="NL310"/>
                  </ADDRESS_CONTRACTOR>
                  <NO_SME/>
               </CONTRACTOR>
               <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
               <VAL_TOTAL CURRENCY="EUR">1200000.00</VAL_TOTAL>
            </AWARDED_CONTRACT>
         </AWARD_CONTRACT>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Bit će organiziran opcionalni posjet prostorima dana 30.8.2017. Za pojedinosti vidi uvjete.</P>
               <P>Europski parlament zadržava pravo korištenja pregovaračkog postupka, bez prethodne objave poziva na nadmetanje, sukladno članku 134. stavku 1. točki (e) Delegirane uredbe (EU) br. 1268/2012 o pravilima za primjenu Uredbe (EU, Euratom) br. 966/2012 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća o financijskim pravilima koja se primjenjuju na opći proračun Unije kako je zadnje izmijenjena Delegiranom uredbom Komisije (EU) 2015/2462 od 30.10.2015.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Opći sud Suda Europske unije</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Za informacije o roku(ovima) podnošenja žalbe obratite se tijelu nadležnom za žalbe.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Opći sud Suda Europske unije</OFFICIALNAME>
               <TOWN>Luxembourg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>L-2925</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="LU"/>
               <PHONE>+352 4303-1</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>GeneralCourt.Registry@curia.europa.eu</E_MAIL>
               <FAX>+352 4303-2600</FAX>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-28</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F03_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
