<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="100067-2018" EDITION="2018046"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-085247-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20190222</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>46</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180307</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 046-100067</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:100067-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71248000">Supervision of project and documentation</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71322000">Engineering design services for the construction of civil engineering works</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71323100">Electrical power systems design services</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71520000">Construction supervision services</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79418000">Procurement consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180222</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>AP301</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Renoveringsprojekt vedrørende transmission og forsyning i Lusaka (LTDRP) — lavspændingsforsyningsnet: Tekniske revisionstjenester</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Projekt zur Sanierung des Versorgungs- und Verteilernetzes in Lusaka — Niederspannungsverteilernetz: Dienstleistungen zum technischen Audit</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussels</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lusaka Transmission Distribution Rehabilitation Project (LTDRP) – Low Voltage Distribution Network: Technical Audit Services</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Proyecto de rehabilitación de la transmisión y la distribución en Lusaka; red de distribución de baja tensión: servicios de auditoría técnica</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lusakan voimansiirto- ja jakelujärjestelmän kunnostushanke – pienjännitteinen jakeluverkko: teknistä tarkastusta koskevat palvelut</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Belgique</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Projet de rénovation du réseau de transport et de distribution d'électricité à Lusaka (LTDRP) — réseau de distribution basse tension: Services d'audit technique</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Βέλγιο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Σχέδιο αποκατάστασης της μεταφοράς και διανομής στη Λουσάκα (LTDRP) — Δίκτυο Διανομής Χαμηλής Τάσης: Υπηρεσίες Τεχνικού Ελέγχου</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Belgio</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Progetto di riattamento della trasmissione e distribuzione a Lusaka — rete di distribuzione a bassa tensione: servizi di audit tecnico</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>België</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Project voor herstel van het transmissie- en distributienetwerk in Lusaka (LTDRP) — laagspanningsdistributienetwerk: Technische auditdiensten</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Projeto de reabilitação de distribuição e transmissão de Lusaca (LTDRP) — Rede de distribuição de baixa tensão: Serviços de auditoria técnica</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Återuppbyggnadsprojekt i Lusaka avseende överföring och distribution (LTDRP) – Distributionsnät för lågspänning: Tekniska granskningstjänster</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Belgie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Projekt obnovy přenosové a distribuční sítě v lokalitě Lusaka (LTDRP) – nízkonapěťová distribuční síť: Služby technického auditu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lusaka ülekande jaotamise uuendustööde projekt (Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project (LTDRP)) – madalpinge jaotusvõrk: tehnilise auditi teenused</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüsszel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>A lusakai átviteli és elosztó hálózat felújítására irányuló projekt (LTDRP) – kisfeszültségű elosztó hálózat: műszaki ellenőrzési szolgáltatások</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Briuselis</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lusakos perdavimo paskirstymo atnaujinimo projektas (LTDRP) – žemosios įtampos skirstomasis tinklas: Techninio audito paslaugos</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Beļģija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brisele</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lusakas pārvades un sadales atjaunošanas projekts (Lusaka Transmission Distribution Rehabilitation Project – LTDRP) – zemsprieguma sadales tīkls: tehniskā audita pakalpojumi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Belġju</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussell</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Proġett ta' Riabilitazzjoni tad-Distribuzzjoni tat-Trażmissjoni f'Lusaka (LTDRP) – Netwerk tad-Distribuzzjoni b'Vultaġġ Baxx: Servizzi ta' Verifika Teknika</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruksela</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Projekt dotyczący modernizacji sieci przesyłowej i rozdzielczej w Lusace (LTDRP) – sieć rozdzielcza niskiego napięcia: usługi audytu technicznego</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Belgicko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Projekt obnovy rozvodnej a prenosovej siete v Lusake (LTDRP) – nízkonapäťová rozvodná sieť: Služby technického auditu</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselj</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Projekt obnove prenosa in distribucije v Lusaki (LTDRP) – nizkonapetostno distribucijsko omrežje: storitve tehnične revizije</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Bheilg, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tionscadal Athshlánaithe um Dháileadh Tarchuir Lusaka (LTDRP) — Líonra Dáilte Ísealvoltais: Seirbhísí Iniúchóireachta Teicniúla</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бeлгия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Брюксел</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Проект за реконструкция на пренос и разпределение в Лусака (LTDRP) — нисковолтова разпределителна мрежа: Услуги за технически одит</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Proiect privind reabilitarea rețelei de transport și de distribuție a energiei electrice din Lusaka (Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project – LTDRP) – rețeaua de distribuție de joasă tensiune: Servicii de audit tehnic</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Projekt obnove za prijenos i distribuciju u Lusaki (LTDRP) — niskonaponska distribucijska mreža: Usluge tehničke revizije</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den Europæiske Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">La Unión Europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan unioni</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Union européenne</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Unione europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europese Unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">União Europeia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska unionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Liit</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Az Európai Unió</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos Sąjunga</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Savienība</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">L-Unjoni Ewropea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Unia Europejska</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európska únia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska unija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An tAontas Eorpach</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейски съюз</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Uniunea Europeană</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska unija</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Renoveringsprojekt vedrørende transmission og forsyning i Lusaka (LTDRP) — lavspændingsforsyningsnet: Tekniske revisionstjenester</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambia, det sydlige Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FORHÅNDSMEDDELELSE OM TJENESTEYDELSER</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udbudsreference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Begrænset</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programtitel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Renoveringsprojekt vedrørende transmission og forsyning i Lusaka (LTDRP) — lavspændingsforsyningsnet</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finansieringsaftale nr.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den Europæiske Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, repræsenteret ved Europa-Kommissionen, for og på vegne af Republikken Zambia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontraktens art</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Honorarbaseret</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivelse af kontrakten</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Formålet med tjenesteydelseskontrakten er at levere tekniske revisionstjenester og sikring til den tilsynsførende, den ordregivende myndighed og den Europæiske Unions delegation i Zambia af, at renoveringsprojektet vedrørende transmission og forsyning i Lusaka (LTDRP) — projektet om lavspændingsforsyningsnet er blevet gennemført i henhold til de fastsatte kontraktmæssige og tekniske specifikationskrav. Tjenesteydelserne vil også dække verificering af det aktuelle antal ny forbindelser, der leveres i henhold til el-producenten (ZESCO Limited), og overvågning af de socioøkonomiske virkningers fremskridt og grundlæggende data.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vejledende budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Foreløbig dato for offentliggørelse af udbudsbekendtgørelsen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yderligere oplysninger</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>En grundlæggende socioøkonomisk undersøgelse med henblik på at formulere de grundlæggende data vil blive udført af kontrahenten for planlægning og overvågning, der vil blive ansat via udbudsproceduren med referencenummer EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Mulige ansøgerne bedes bemærke, at den valgte tilbudsgiver eller samtlige dennes deltagere i eventuelle konsortier i forbindelse med ovenstående tjenesteydelseskontrakt vil blive udelukket fra tildeling af nærværende tjenesteydelseskontrakt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Retsgrundlag (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bilag IV til partnerskabsaftalen mellem medlemmerne af gruppen af stater i Afrika, Vestindien og Stillehavet, som den ene part, og EU og dets medlemsstater, som den anden, underskrevet i Cotonou 23.6.2000, som ændret i Luxembourg 25.6.2005 og i Ouagadougou 22.6.2010. Der henvises til bilag IV som ændret ved AVS-EU-Ministerrådets afgørelse nr. 1/2014 af 20.6.2014.</P><P>Vær opmærksom på, at efter Det Forenede Kongeriges udtræden af EU vil reglerne om adgang til EU's udbudsprocedurer for økonomiske aktører, der er etableret i tredjelande, gælde for ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige, alt afhængigt af resultatet af forhandlingerne. Hvis en sådan adgang ikke gives ved retlige bestemmelser, der er gældende på tidspunktet for kontrakttildelingen, vil ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige kunne blive udelukket fra udbudsproceduren.</P><P>(1) Angiv venligst enhver specificitet, der kan have indflydelse på reglerne for deltagelse (såsom geografiske eller tematiske eller lang-/kortsigtede).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Bemærkninger:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Der skal være en periode på mindst 30 kalenderdage mellem offentliggørelsen af denne forhåndsmeddelelse og offentliggørelsen af den tilsvarende udbudsbekendtgørelse. Der kan ikke fremsendes ansøgninger eller anmodninger om oplysninger på nuværende tidspunkt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: Projekt zur Sanierung des Versorgungs- und Verteilernetzes in Lusaka — Niederspannungsverteilernetz: Dienstleistungen zum technischen Audit</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sambia, südliches Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VORINFORMATION FÜR EINEN DIENSTLEISTUNGSAUFTRAG</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verfahren</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nichtoffen</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmbezeichnung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt zur Sanierung des Versorgungs- und Verteilernetzes in Lusaka (Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project — LTDRP) — Niederspannungsverteilernetz</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanzierung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finanzierungsabkommen Nr.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Öffentlicher Auftraggeber</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertreten durch die Europäische Kommission im Auftrag und für Rechnung der Republik Sambia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Art des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>auf Honorarbasis</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Der beabsichtigte Dienstleistungsvertrag muss der Aufsicht, dem öffentlichen Auftraggeber und der Delegation der Europäischen Union in Sambia technische Dienstleistungen in Bezug auf Audit bieten und soll gewährleisten, dass das Projekt zur Sanierung des Versorgungs- und Verteilernetzes in Lusaka (Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project — LTDRP) – Niederspannungsverteilernetz in Übereinstimmung mit den festgelegten vertraglichen und technischen Spezifikationen umgesetzt wurde. Die Dienstleistungen umfassen auch die Überprüfung der tatsächlichen Anzahl der vom Stromversorgungsunternehmen gemeldeten neuen Verbindungen (ZESCO Limited) sowie die Überwachung der Fortschritte der sozioökonomischen Auswirkungen und der Ausgangsdaten.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veranschlagtes Budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Geplanter Zeitpunkt für die Veröffentlichung der Auftragsbekanntmachung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sonstige Informationen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eine sozioökonomische Grundlagenstudie zur Formulierung der Ausgangsdaten wird von dem Auftragnehmer für Planung und Überwachung durchgeführt, der im Rahmen des Beschaffungsverfahrens unter der Referenznummer EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM beauftragt wird. Die potenziellen Bewerber müssen sich dessen bewusst sein, dass ein erfolgreicher Bieter bzw. bei Konsortien eines der Mitglieder, der/das für einen der oben genannten Dienstleistungsauftrag den Zuschlag erhält, von der Vergabe dieses Dienstleistungsauftrags ausgeschlossen wird.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsgrundlage (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anhang IV des Partnerschaftsabkommens zwischen den Mitgliedern der Gruppe der Staaten in Afrika, im Karibischen Raum und im Pazifischen Ozean einerseits und der Europäischen Gemeinschaft und ihren Mitgliedstaaten andererseits, unterzeichnet in Cotonou am 23.6.2000, mit den Änderungen vom 25.6.2005 in Luxemburg und vom 22.6.2010 in Ouagadougou. Siehe Anhang IV in der geänderten Fassung gemäß Beschluss 1/2014 des AKP-EU-Ministerrates vom 20.6.2014.</P><P>Es gilt zu beachten, dass für Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich nach dem Austritt des Vereinigten Königreichs aus der EU in Abhängigkeit des Ausgangs der Verhandlungen die Bestimmungen über den Zugang zu Beschaffungsverfahren der EU für in Drittländern ansässige Wirtschaftsteilnehmer gelten werden. Falls dieser Zugang gemäß den bei Auftragsvergabe geltenden Bestimmung nicht gewährt wird, können Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich vom Beschaffungsverfahren ausgeschlossen werden.</P><P>(1) Bitte geben Sie alle Besonderheiten an, die sich auf die Regeln für die Teilnahme auswirken könnten (z. B. geographisch oder thematisch oder kurz-/mittelfristig).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Hinweise:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Es muss ein Zeitraum von mindestens 30 Kalendertagen zwischen der Veröffentlichung der Vorinformation und der Veröffentlichung der entsprechenden Auftragsbekanntmachung liegen. Derzeit ist von der Einreichung von Bewerbungen oder weiteren Anfragen abzusehen.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussels: Lusaka Transmission Distribution Rehabilitation Project (LTDRP) – Low Voltage Distribution Network: Technical Audit Services</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambia, Southern Africa</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SERVICE PRIOR INFORMATION NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publication reference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programme title</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project (LTDRP) — Low voltage distribution network</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financing</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Financing agreement No.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contracting Authority</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, represented by the European Commission on behalf of and for the account of the Republic of Zambia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussels</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, BELGIUM</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature of contract</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fee-based</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contract description</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The purposed service contract shall provide technical audit services and assurance to the supervisor, the Contracting Authority and the European Union Delegation to Zambia that the Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project (LTDRP) – Low voltage distribution network project has been implemented in accordance with the laid down contractual and technical specification requirements. The services will also cover verification of the actual number of new connections provided as reported by the electricity utility (ZESCO Limited) and monitoring of progress on social-economic impact and baseline data.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicative budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EUR 1 000 000</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intended timing of publication of the contract notice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Additional information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A socio-economic baseline study to formulate the baseline data will be carried out by the design and supervision contractor that will be contracted through the procurement procedure with reference number EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Prospective candidates must be aware that the successful tenderer, or any of its members if a consortium, of the above-mentioned service contract will be excluded from the award of this service contract.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal basis(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Annex IV to the Partnership agreement between the members of the African, Caribbean and Pacific Group of States of the one part, and the European Community and its member states, of the other part, signed in Cotonou on 23.6.2000 as amended in Luxembourg on 25.6.2005 and in Ouagadougou on 22 June 2010. Reference is made to Annex IV as revised by Decision 1/2014 of the ACP-EU Council of Ministers of 20.6.2014.</P><P>Please be aware that after the United Kingdom's withdrawal from the EU, the rules of access to EU procurement procedures of economic operators established in third countries will apply to candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom depending on the outcome of negotiations. In case such access is not provided by legal provisions in force at the time of contract award, candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom could be rejected from the procurement procedure.</P><P>(1) Please state any specificity that might have an impact on rules on participation (such as geographic or thematic or long/short term).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarks:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>There must be a minimum period of 30 calendar days between the publication of this prior information notice and the publication of the corresponding contract notice. No applications or requests for information should be sent at this stage.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselas: Proyecto de rehabilitación de la transmisión y la distribución en Lusaka; red de distribución de baja tensión: servicios de auditoría técnica</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambia, África Meridional</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNCIO DE PREVISIÓN DE CONTRATO DE SERVICIOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referencia de publicación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedimiento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restringido</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Denominación del programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proyecto de rehabilitación de la transmisión y la distribución en Lusaka; red de distribución de baja tensión</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Convenio de financiación n.º: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de contratación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>La Unión Europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada por la Comisión Europea, en nombre y por cuenta de la República de Zambia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naturaleza del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Honorarios</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El contrato de servicios propuesto deberá prestar servicios de auditoría técnica y dar garantía al supervisor, al órgano de contratación y a la Delegación de la Unión Europea en Zambia de que el proyecto de rehabilitación de la transmisión y de la distribución de Lusaka, red de distribución de baja tensión, ha sido ejecutado de acuerdo con los requisitos del contrato y las especificaciones técnicas establecidas. Los servicios también cubrirán la verificación del número exacto de nuevas conexiones de las que ha informado la compañía eléctrica (ZESCO Limited) y el seguimiento del progreso del impacto socioeconómico y de los datos de referencia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Presupuesto indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha prevista de publicación del anuncio de contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información adicional</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>El contratista para el diseño y la supervisión llevará a cabo un estudio socioeconómico preliminar para formular los datos de referencia, contratado a través del procedimiento de contratación con número de referencia EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Los candidatos potenciales deberán tener en cuenta que el licitador adjudicatario, o cualquiera de sus miembros si se trata de un consorcio, de los contratos de servicios mencionados anteriormente quedará excluido de la adjudicación de este contrato de servicios.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fundamento jurídico (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anexo IV del Acuerdo de Asociación entre los miembros de los Estados de África, del Caribe y del Pacífico, por una parte, y la Comunidad Europea y sus Estados miembros por otra, firmado en Cotonú el 23.6.2000, modificado en Luxemburgo el 25.6.2005 y en Uagadugu el 22.6.2010. Se hace referencia aquí al anexo IV en su versión enmendada por la Decisión n.° 1/2014 del Consejo de Ministros ACP-UE, de 20.6.2014.</P><P>Téngase en cuenta que tras la salida del Reino Unido de la Unión Europea, las normas de acceso a los procedimientos de contratación pública de la Unión Europea de los operadores económicos establecidos en terceros países se aplicarán a candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido en función del resultado de las negociaciones. En caso de que dicho acceso no se prevea en las disposiciones legales en vigor, los candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido podrán ser excluidos del proceso de contratación.</P><P>(1) Mencione cualquier aspecto específico que podría repercutir en las normas de participación (por ejemplo, aspectos geográficos, temáticos o de corto/largo plazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observaciones:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deben pasar al menos 30 días naturales desde la publicación de esta previsión de contrato hasta la publicación del correspondiente anuncio de contrato. Por el momento, no deben enviarse solicitudes ni peticiones de información complementaria.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: Lusakan voimansiirto- ja jakelujärjestelmän kunnostushanke – pienjännitteinen jakeluverkko: teknistä tarkastusta koskevat palvelut</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sambia, Eteläinen Afrikka</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PALVELUJA KOSKEVA ENNAKKOTIETOILMOITUS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen viite</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menettely</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rajoitettu menettely</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ohjelman nimi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lusakan voimansiirto- ja jakelujärjestelmän kunnostushanke (Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project – LTDRP) – pienjännitteinen jakeluverkko</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahoitus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rahoitussopimus nro: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan unioni</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, jota edustaa Euroopan komissio, Sambian tasavallan puolesta, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuslaji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Palkkiopohjainen</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuksen kuvaus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ehdotetulla palvelusopimuksella toimitetaan teknistä tarkastusta koskevia palveluja sekä taataan valvojalle, hankintaviranomaiselle ja Euroopan unionin Sambian-edustustolle, että Lusakan voimansiirto- ja jakelujärjestelmän kunnostushankkeen pienjännitteistä jakeluverkkoa koskeva hanke on toteutettu määritettyjen sopimusta koskevien ja teknisten eritelmien vaatimusten mukaisesti. Palveluihin sisältyy myös sähkölaitoksen (ZESCO Limited) ilmoittaman toteutettujen uusien liitäntöjen todellisen määrän tarkistaminen sekä sosioekonomisen vaikutuksen ja perustietojen edistymisen valvonta.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Alustava budjetti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintailmoituksen ennakoitu julkaisemisajankohta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisätiedot</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Perustietojen laatimiseksi suoritettavasta sosioekonomisen tutkimuksen suorittaa suunnittelusta ja valvonnasta vastaava sopimusosapuoli. Tutkimuksesta tehdään sopimus hankintamenettelyn EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM perusteella. Mahdollisten hakijoiden on oltava tietoisia siitä, että tätä palvelusopimusta ei tehdä sellaisen tarjoajan (tai sen jonkin jäsenen, mikäli kyseessä on konsortio) kanssa, joka on valittu edellä mainitun palvelusopimuksen sopimusosapuoleksi.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oikeusperusta (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cotonoussa 23.6.2000 allekirjoitetun Afrikan, Karibian ja Tyynenmeren valtioiden ryhmän jäsenten sekä Euroopan yhteisön ja sen jäsenvaltioiden välisen kumppanuussopimuksen liite IV, sellaisena kuin sopimus on muutettuna Luxemburgissa 25.6.2005 ja Ouagadougoussa 22.6.2010. Viitataan liitteeseen IV, sellaisena kuin se on muutettuna 20.6.2014 annetulla AKT–EU-ministerineuvoston päätöksellä 1/2014.</P><P>On syytä ottaa huomioon, että Yhdistyneen kuningaskunnan EU:sta irtautumisen jälkeen kolmansiin maihin sijoittautuneisiin talouden toimijoihin sovellettavia EU:n hankintamenettelyihin osallistumista koskevia sääntöjä sovelletaan Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin oleviin hakijoihin tai tarjoajiin neuvottelujen lopputuloksesta riippuen. Mikäli sopimuksenteon hetkellä voimassa olevassa lainsäädännössä ei anneta lupaa tällaiseen osallistumiseen, Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin olevat hakijat tai tarjoajat voidaan hylätä hankintamenettelystä.</P><P>(1) Tarjoajia pyydetään mainitsemaan erityisolosuhteista, jotka voivat vaikuttaa osallistumissääntöihin (esimerkiksi maantieteelliset tai aihekohtaiset tai pitkä-/lyhytkestoiset erityisolosuhteet).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Huom.</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Tämän ennakkotietoilmoituksen ja vastaavan hankintailmoituksen julkaisemisen välillä on oltava vähintään 30 kalenteripäivää. Hakemuksia tai lisätietopyyntöjä ei pidä lähettää tässä vaiheessa.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Projet de rénovation du réseau de transport et de distribution d'électricité à Lusaka (LTDRP) — réseau de distribution basse tension: Services d'audit technique</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambie, Afrique australe</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVIS DE PRÉINFORMATION RELATIF À UN MARCHÉ DE SERVICES</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Référence de la publication</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restreinte</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intitulé du programme</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projet de rénovation du réseau de transport et de distribution d'électricité à Lusaka (LTDRP) — réseau de distribution basse tension</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financement</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Convention de financement N°: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pouvoir adjudicateur</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Union européenne</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, représentée par la Commission européenne, agissant au nom et pour le compte de la République de Zambie, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgique.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>À prix unitaires.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le marché de service proposé est destiné à fournir des services d’audit technique et une assurance au superviseur, le pouvoir adjudicateur et la délégation de l’union européenne pour la Zambie que le projet de rénovation du réseau de transport et de distribution d'électricité à Lusaka (LTDRP) — projet du réseau de distribution basse tension a été exécuté conformément aux exigences et spécifications techniques contractuelles fixées. Les services comprendront également la vérification du nombre réel de nouveaux raccordements fournis par la compagnie d'électricité (ZESCO Limited) et le suivi de l'évolution de l'impact socio-économique et des données de base.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Budget indicatif</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date prévue pour la publication de l'avis de marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Renseignements complémentaires</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Une étude socio-économique de base visant à formuler les données de référence sera réalisée par le maître d'œuvre chargé de la conception et de la supervision, qui passera un contrat dans le cadre de la procédure de passation des marchés portant le numéro de référence EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Les candidats potentiels doivent avoir connaissance du fait que, le soumissionnaire retenu, ou un de ses membres s'il s'agit d'un consortium, du marché de services susmentionné, sera exclu de l'attribution du présent marché de services.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base juridique (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Annexe IV de l'accord de partenariat entre les membres du groupe des États d'Afrique, des Caraïbes et du Pacifique, d'une part, et la Communauté européenne et ses États membres, d'autre part, signé à Cotonou le 23.6.2000, tel que modifié au Luxembourg le 25.6.2005 et à Ouagadougou le 22.6.2010. Il est fait référence à l'annexe IV telle que révisée par la décision n° 1/2014 du Conseil des ministres ACP-UE du 20.6.2014.</P><P>Il convient de noter qu'à la suite du retrait du Royaume-Uni de l'UE, les règles d'accès aux procédures de passation des marchés de l'UE pour les opérateurs économiques établis dans des pays tiers s'appliqueront aux candidats ou aux soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni, en fonction du résultat des négociations. Si les dispositions légales en vigueur au moment de l'attribution du contrat ne prévoient pas un tel accès, les candidats ou les soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni pourraient être exclus de la procédure de passation des marchés.</P><P>(1) Veuillez indiquer toute spécificité susceptible d’avoir un impact sur les règles en matière de participation (par exemple géographique ou thématique ou à cours/long terme).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarques :</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Un délai minimal de 30 jours calendaires doit être respecté entre la publication du présent avis de pré information et celle de l'avis de marché correspondant. Aucune candidature ni demande de renseignements complémentaires ne sera envoyée à ce stade de la procédure.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Βρυξέλλες: Σχέδιο αποκατάστασης της μεταφοράς και διανομής στη Λουσάκα (LTDRP) — Δίκτυο Διανομής Χαμηλής Τάσης: Υπηρεσίες Τεχνικού Ελέγχου</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ζάμπια, νότια Αφρική</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ΠΡΟΚΑΤΑΡΚΤΙΚΗ ΑΝΑΚΟΙΝΩΣΗ ΓΙΑ ΥΠΗΡΕΣΙΕΣ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αριθ. αναφοράς δημοσίευσης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Διαδικασία</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κλειστή</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τίτλος προγράμματος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Σχέδιο αποκατάστασης της μεταφοράς και διανομής στη Λουσάκα (LTDRP) — Δίκτυο Διανομής Χαμηλής Τάσης</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Χρηματοδότηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Χρηματοδοτική συμφωνία αριθ.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα αρχή</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, εκπροσωπούμενη από την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή, εξ ονόματος και για λογαριασμό της Δημοκρατίας της Ζάμπιας, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Βέλγιο.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τύπος της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Βάσει αμοιβής</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Περιγραφή της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Η εν λόγω σύμβαση παροχής υπηρεσιών θα παρέχει υπηρεσίες τεχνικού ελέγχου και διασφαλίσεις στον επόπτη, την Αναθέτουσα Αρχή και την Αντιπροσωπεία της Ευρωπαϊκής Ένωσης στη Ζάμπια ότι το Σχέδιο αποκατάστασης της μεταφοράς και διανομής στη Λουσάκα ( LTDRP) — σχέδιο για δίκτυο διανομής χαμηλής τάσης έχει υλοποιηθεί σύμφωνα με τις καθορισμένες συμβατικές και τεχνικές απαιτήσεις προδιαγραφών. Οι υπηρεσίες θα καλύπτουν ακόμη την εξακρίβωση του πραγματικού αριθμού των νέων συνδέσεων που πραγματοποιήθηκαν σύμφωνα με την έκθεση της επιχείρησης ηλεκτροδότησης (ZESCO Limited) και την επίβλεψη της εξέλιξης του κοινωνικοοικονομικού αντικτύπου και των βασικών στοιχείων αναφοράς.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ενδεικτικός προϋπολογισμός</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης της προκήρυξης σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Θα πραγματοποιηθεί μια κοινωνικοοικονομική βασική μελέτη με σκοπό τη συλλογή των βασικών στοιχείων αναφοράς υπό τον σχεδιασμό και την επίβλεψη του αναδόχου που θα ανακηρυχθεί μέσω της διαδικασίας σύναψης συμβάσεων με αριθμό αναφοράς EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Οι υποψήφιοι πρέπει να γνωρίζουν ότι ο επιτυχής υποψήφιος, ή οποιοδήποτε από τα μέλη του εάν πρόκειται για κοινοπραξία, αναφορικά με τις συμβάσεις παροχής υπηρεσιών που αναγράφονται ανωτέρω, θα αποκλειστούν από την ανάθεση της παρούσας σύμβασης υπηρεσιών.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Νομική βάση (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Παράρτημα IV της συμφωνίας Εταιρικής Σχέσης μεταξύ των μελών της ομάδας των κρατών της Αφρικής, της Καραϊβικής και του Ειρηνικού, αφενός, και της Ευρωπαϊκής Κοινότητας και των κρατών μελών αυτής, αφετέρου, η οποία υπογράφηκε στην Κοτονού στις 23.6.2000 όπως τροποποιήθηκε στο Λουξεμβούργο στις 25.6.2005 και στην Ουαγκαντούγκου στις 22.6.2010. Γίνεται αναφορά στο Παράρτημα IV όπως αναθεωρήθηκε με την απόφαση 1/2014 του Συμβουλίου των Υπουργών ΑΚΕ-ΕΕ στις 20.6.2014.</P><P>Πρέπει να ληφθεί υπόψη ότι μετά την αποχώρηση του Ηνωμένου Βασιλείου από την ΕΕ, οι κανόνες πρόσβασης σε διαδικασίες σύναψης συμβάσεων της ΕΕ για οικονομικούς φορείς που είναι εγκατεστημένοι σε τρίτες χώρες θα ισχύουν για τους υποψήφιους ή προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο ανάλογα με το αποτέλεσμα των διαπραγματεύσεων. Σε περίπτωση που η πρόσβαση αυτή δεν παρέχεται από νομικές διατάξεις που ίσχυαν κατά τον χρόνο ανάθεσης της σύμβασης, οι υποψήφιοι ή οι προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο θα μπορούσαν να απορριφθούν από τη διαδικασία σύναψης συμβάσεων.</P><P>(1) Παρακαλείσθε να αναφέρετε οποιαδήποτε ιδιαιτερότητα που ενδέχεται να έχει αντίκτυπο στους κανόνες συμμετοχής (όπως γεωγραφική ή θεματική ή σε μακροπρόθεσμο/βραχυπρόθεσμο επίπεδο).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Παρατηρήσεις:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Μεταξύ της δημοσίευσης της παρούσας προκαταρκτικής ανακοίνωσης και της δημοσίευσης της αντίστοιχης προκήρυξης σύμβασης θα πρέπει να παρεμβληθεί χρονικό διάστημα τουλάχιστον 30 ημερολογιακών ημερών. Κατά το παρόν στάδιο δεν πρέπει να αποστέλλονται υποψηφιότητες ή αιτήματα για παροχή πληροφοριών.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Progetto di riattamento della trasmissione e distribuzione a Lusaka — rete di distribuzione a bassa tensione: servizi di audit tecnico</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambia, Africa meridionale</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVISO DI PREINFORMAZIONE RELATIVO A SERVIZI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Riferimento della pubblicazione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titolo del programma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Progetto di riattamento della trasmissione e distribuzione a Lusaka — rete di distribuzione a bassa tensione</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanziamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Accordo di finanziamento n.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ente appaltante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unione europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, rappresentata dalla Commissione europea, in nome e per conto della Repubblica dello Zambia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgio.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contratto in base a tariffa</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il contratto di servizi proposto dovrà fornire servizi di audit tecnico e assicurare al supervisore, all'ente appaltante e alla delegazione dell'Unione europea in Zambia che il progetto di riattamento della trasmissione e distribuzione a Lusaka — rete di distribuzione a bassa tensione sia stato attuato conformemente ai requisiti specifici contrattuali e tecnici. I servizi dovranno inoltre includere la verifica del numero effettivo di nuove connessioni fornite come riportato dal produttore di elettricità (ZESCO Limited) e il monitoraggio dei progressi in merito all'impatto socio-economico e rispetto ai dati di riferimento.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Importo indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista per la pubblicazione del bando di gara</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informazioni complementari</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il contraente incaricato della progettazione e supervisione effettuerà anche uno studio di riferimento socio-economico per formulare i dati di riferimento, affidato mediante la procedura di appalto con numero di riferimento EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. I potenziali candidati dovranno essere consapevoli che l'aggiudicatario, o uno dei suoi membri in caso di consorzio, del suddetto contratto di servizi sarà escluso dall'aggiudicazione del presente contratto di servizi.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base giuridica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Allegato IV dell'accordo di partenariato tra i membri del gruppo degli Stati dell'Africa, dei Caraibi e del Pacifico da una parte e la Comunità europea e i suoi Stati membri dall'altra, firmato a Cotonou il 23.6.2000, modificato a Lussemburgo il 25.6.2005 e a Ouagadougou il 22.6.2010. Si fa riferimento all'allegato IV, modificato dalla decisione 1/2014 del Consiglio dei ministri ACP-UE del 20.6.2014.</P><P>Si prega di notare che, dopo il ritiro del Regno Unito dall'UE, ai candidati o agli offerenti provenienti dal Regno Unito si applicheranno le regole di accesso alle procedure di appalto dell'UE per gli operatori economici stabiliti nei paesi terzi, in funzione dell'esito delle negoziazioni. Nel caso in cui tale accesso non sia previsto dalle disposizioni giuridiche vigenti al momento dell'aggiudicazione del contratto, i candidati o gli offerenti del Regno Unito potranno essere esclusi dalla procedura di gara.</P><P>(1) Indicare qualsiasi specificità che possa avere un impatto sulle regole di partecipazione (come ad esempio geografica o tematica o a lungo/breve termine).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Osservazioni:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Dovrà intercorrere un periodo minimo di 30 giorni di calendario tra la pubblicazione dell'avviso di preinformazione e quella del corrispondente bando di gara. Si prega di non inviare candidature o richieste di ulteriori informazioni in questa fase della procedura.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussel: Project voor herstel van het transmissie- en distributienetwerk in Lusaka (LTDRP) — laagspanningsdistributienetwerk: Technische auditdiensten</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambia, zuidelijk Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VOORAANKONDIGING VOOR DIENSTEN</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referentie van de bekendmaking:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet-openbaar.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titel van het programma:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Project voor herstel van het transmissie- en distributienetwerk in Lusaka (LTDRP) — laagspanningsdistributienetwerk.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiering:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Financieringsovereenkomst nr.: FED/2016/038-238.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europese Unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertegenwoordigd door de Europese Commissie, ten behoeve en voor rekening van de Republiek Zambia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, België.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aard van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Opdracht op basis van vergoeding.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschrijving van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>De beoogde dienstenovereenkomst behelst technische auditdiensten en de waarborging aan de supervisor, de aanbestedende dienst en de Delegatie van de Europese Unie in Zambia dat het Project voor herstel van het transmissie- en distributienetwerk in Lusaka (LTDRP) - project betreffende laagspanningsdistributienetwerk, conform de vastgelegde contractuele en technische specificatie-eisen werd uitgevoerd. De diensten zullen ook het volgende omvatten: verificatie van het werkelijke aantal nieuwe geleverde aansluitingen, zoals blijkt uit het verslag van het elektriciteitsbedrijf (ZESCO Limited) en monitoring van vooruitgang inzake sociaal-economische impact en basisgegevens.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicatieve begroting:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beoogde datum voor bekendmaking van de aankondiging van opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nadere inlichtingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Een sociaal-economische basisstudie om basisgegevens te formuleren, zal worden uitgevoerd door de contractant verantwoordelijk voor het ontwerp en het toezicht. Met hem zal een overeenkomst worden gesloten via de aanbestedingsprocedure met referentienummer EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Gegadigden worden attent gemaakt op het feit dat de geselecteerde inschrijver (en alle leden van een eventueel consortium) voor de hierboven vermelde dienstenovereenkomst uitgesloten zal zijn van gunning van onderhavige dienstenovereenkomst.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Juridische basis (1):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bijlage IV bij de Partnerschapsovereenkomst tussen de leden van de groep van staten in Afrika, het Caribisch gebied en de Stille Oceaan enerzijds, en de Europese Gemeenschap en haar lidstaten, anderzijds, ondertekend te Cotonou op 23.6.2000, zoals gewijzigd in Luxemburg op 25.6.2005 en in Ouagadougou op 22.6.2010. Er wordt verwezen naar bijlage IV zoals gewijzigd bij Besluit 1/2014 van de ACS-EU-Raad van ministers van 20.6.2014.</P><P>Gelieve op te merken dat, na de uitstap van het Verenigd Koninkrijk uit de EU en afhankelijk van het resultaat van de onderhandelingen, de regels voor toegang tot EU-aanbestedingsprocedures voor ondernemers die gevestigd zijn in derde landen van toepassing zullen zijn op gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk. Indien dergelijke toegang niet is voorzien door de geldende wettelijke bepalingen op het tijdstip van de gunning van de opdracht, kunnen gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk worden geweigerd voor de aanbestedingsprocedure.</P><P>(1) Vermeld elke specificiteit die een effect kan hebben op de deelnameregels (zoals geografische of thematische specificiteiten op korte of lange termijn).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opmerkingen:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>er moet een minimumtermijn van 30 kalenderdagen liggen tussen de bekendmaking van deze vooraankondiging en de bekendmaking van de overeenstemmende aankondiging van een opdracht. In dit stadium mogen er geen aanvragen of verzoeken om inlichtingen worden verzonden.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelas: Projeto de reabilitação de distribuição e transmissão de Lusaca (LTDRP) — Rede de distribuição de baixa tensão: Serviços de auditoria técnica</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zâmbia, África Austral</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANÚNCIO DE PRÉ-INFORMAÇÃO DE SERVIÇOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referência da publicação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Limitado</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Título do programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projeto de reabilitação de distribuição e transmissão de Lusaca (LTDRP) — Rede de distribuição de baixa tensão</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Acordo de financiamento n.º: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>União Europeia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada pela Comissão Europeia, em nome e por conta da República da Zâmbia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natureza do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Baseado em honorários</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>O contrato de serviço proposto deve fornecer serviços de auditoria técnica e garantia ao supervisor, à entidade adjudicante e à Delegação da União Europeia na Zâmbia, de que o projeto de reabilitação de distribuição e transmissão de Lusaka (LTDRP) - Projeto de rede de distribuição de baixa tensão foi implementado de acordo com o requisitos das especificações técnicas e contratuais previstas. Os serviços também abrangerão a verificação do número real de novas conexões fornecidas conforme relatado pela empresa de eletricidade (ZESCO Limited) e monitorização do progresso no impacto socioeconómico e dados de base.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orçamento indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista para a publicação do anúncio de concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Outras informações</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Um estudo socioeconómico de base para formular os dados de base será realizado pelo contratante responsável pela conceção e supervisão que será contratado através do processo de adjudicação com o número de referência EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Os candidatos devem estar cientes de que o proponente selecionado, ou qualquer dos seus membros no caso de um consórcio, dos contratos de serviços acima mencionados serão excluídos da adjudicação do presente contrato de serviços.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base jurídica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anexo IV do Acordo de Parceria entre os membros do Grupo de Estados de África, das Caraíbas e do Pacífico, por um lado, e a Comunidade Europeia e os seus Estados-Membros, por outro lado, assinado em Cotonu a 23.6.2000, alterado no Luxemburgo em 25.6.2005 e alterado em Uagadugu em 22.6.2010. É feita referência ao anexo IV conforme revisto pela Decisão 1/2014 do Conselho de Ministros ACP-UE de 20.6.2014.</P><P>Importa notar que após a saída do Reino Unido da UE, as regras de acesso aos procedimentos de adjudicação de contratos da UE de operadores económicos estabelecidos em países terceiros aplicar-se-ão aos candidatos ou proponentes provenientes do Reino Unido consoante o resultado das negociações. Caso tal acesso não esteja previsto pelas disposições legais em vigor, os candidatos ou proponentes do Reino Unido poderão ser excluídos do concurso.</P><P>(1) Indique qualquer especificidade que possa ter impacto sobre as regras de participação (tais como geográficas ou temáticas ou a longo/curto prazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observações:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deve ser respeitado um período mínimo de 30 dias de calendário entre a publicação do presente anúncio de informação prévia e a publicação do anúncio de concurso correspondente. Não devem ser enviadas candidaturas ou efetuados pedidos de informação nesta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: Återuppbyggnadsprojekt i Lusaka avseende överföring och distribution (LTDRP) – Distributionsnät för lågspänning: Tekniska granskningstjänster</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambia, södra Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÖRHANDSMEDDELANDE OM TJÄNSTER</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publikationsreferens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Förfarande</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Selektivt</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmets namn</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Återuppbyggnadsprojekt i Lusaka avseende överföring och distribution (LTDRP) – Distributionsnät för lågspänning</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finansieringsavtal nr: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska unionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representerad av Europeiska kommissionen, till förmån för och på uppdrag av Republiken Zambia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Typ av kontrakt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Arvodesbaserat</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivning av kontraktet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Syftet med tjänstekontraktet är att tillhandahålla tekniska granskningstjänster och försäkra tillsynsmannen, den upphandlande myndigheten och Europeiska unionens delegation i Zambia att återuppbyggnadsprojektet i Lusaka avseende överföring och distribution (LTDRP) – distributionsnät för lågspänning, har genomförts i enlighet med de krav som fastställts i kontraktet och de tekniska specifikationerna. I tjänsterna ingår också verifiering av det faktiska antalet nya anslutningar som tillhandahållits av elektronikföretaget (ZESCO Limited) och bevakning av framstegen beträffande den socioekonomiska effekten samt grundläggande data.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Preliminär budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerat tidsplan för publicering av meddelandet om upphandling</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kompletterande information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>En grundläggande socioekonomisk undersökning i syfte att utarbeta grundläggande data kommer att utföras baserat på uppdragstagarens utformning och bevakning, samt kommer att kontrakteras genom upphandlingsförfarandet med referensnummer EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Observera att potentiella anbudsgivare, och alla medlemmar i ett eventuellt konsortium, som tilldelas ovanstående tjänstekontrakt inte kommer att kunna tilldelas detta tjänstekontrakt.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rättslig grund (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bilaga IV till partnerskapsavtalet mellan medlemmarna i gruppen av stater i Afrika, Västindien och Stillahavsområdet, å ena sidan, och Europeiska gemenskapen och dess medlemsstater, å andra sidan, undertecknat i Cotonou den 23.6.2000, enligt tillägg i Luxemburg den 25.6.2005 och i Ouagadougou den 22.6.2010. Hänvisning görs till bilaga IV enligt ändring genom beslut 1/2014 från AVS-EU-ministerrådet av den 20.6.2014.</P><P>Observera att efter Storbritanniens utträde ur EU kommer reglerna om tillgång till EU:s upphandlingsförfaranden för ekonomiska aktörer etablerade i tredjeländer att tillämpas på sökande eller anbudsgivare från Storbritannien beroende på resultatet av förhandlingarna. Om sådan tillgång inte tillhandahålls av rättsliga bestämmelser som gäller vid tidpunkten för kontraktstilldelningen kan sökande eller anbudsgivare från Storbritannien komma att uteslutas från upphandlingsförfarandet.</P><P>(1) Ange om det finns något som kan påverka reglerna för deltagande (såsom geografiskt läge, tema eller tid på lång eller kort sikt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Anmärkningar:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>En period på minst 30 kalenderdagar ska förflyta mellan publiceringen av detta förhandsmeddelande och publiceringen av motsvarande meddelande om upphandling. Inga ansökningar eller beställningar av information ska skickas i detta skede.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: Projekt obnovy přenosové a distribuční sítě v lokalitě Lusaka (LTDRP) – nízkonapěťová distribuční síť: Služby technického auditu</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambie, jižní Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>OZNÁMENÍ PŘEDBĚŽNÝCH INFORMACÍ O SLUŽBÁCH</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenční číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užší</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Název programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt obnovy přenosové a distribuční sítě v lokalitě Lusaka (LTDRP) – nízkonapěťová distribuční síť</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financování</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Dohoda o financování č.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veřejný zadavatel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastoupená Evropskou komisí jménem a ve prospěch Zambijské republiky, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgie.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Povaha zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Placená</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popis zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Účelem zakázky na služby je poskytnutí služeb technického auditu a záruky vůči dohlížiteli, veřejnému zadavateli a delegaci Evropské unie v Zambii, že realizace projektu obnovy a přenosové a distribuční sítě v lokalitě Lusaka (LTDRP) – projekt nízkonapěťové distribuční sítě probíhá v souladu se stanovenými smluvními a technickými požadavky na specifikace. Služby budou dále pokrývat ověřování skutečného počtu nových připojení poskytovaných na základě zpráv od poskytovatele elektrické energie (ZESCO Limited) a monitorování pokroku v oblasti sociálně ekonomického dopadu a základních dat.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Směrný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zamýšlené datum zveřejnění oznámení o zakázce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Další informace</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sociálně ekonomická základní studie s cílem zformulovat základní údaje bude provedena poskytovatelem návrhu a dohledu, který vzejde jako smluvní partner ze zadávacího řízení s referenčním číslem EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Potenciální uchazeči musí vzít na vědomí, že úspěšný uchazeč, nebo kterýkoli z jeho členů v případě konsorcia v případě výše uvedené zakázky na služby, bude vyloučen ze zadávání této zakázky na služby.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právní základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Příloha IV k dohodě o partnerství mezi členy skupiny afrických, karibských a tichomořských států na jedné straně a Evropským společenstvím a jeho členskými státy na straně druhé, podepsané v Cotonou dne 23.6.2000 a pozměněné v Lucemburku dne 25.6.2005 a v Ouagadougou dne 22.6.2010. Odkazujeme na přílohu IV pozměněnou rozhodnutím Rady ministrů AKT–EU č. 1/2014 ze dne 20.6.2014.</P><P>Připomínáme, že po vystoupení Spojeného království z EU se na zájemce nebo uchazeče ze Spojeného království, v závislosti od výsledku jednání, budou uplatňovat pravidla přístupu k postupům výběrového řízení EU ze strany hospodářských subjektů se sídlem ve třetích zemích. V případě, že takový přístup není zabezpečen právními předpisy platnými v době zadání zakázky, mohli by být uchazeči nebo účastníci ze Spojeného království vyloučeni z výběrového řízení.</P><P>(1) Uveďte prosím jakoukoli specifičnost, která by mohla mít dopad na pravidla účasti (např. zeměpisnou, tematickou nebo dlouhodobou/krátkodobou).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Mezi zveřejněním těchto předběžných informací o zakázce a zveřejněním odpovídajícího oznámení o zakázce musí uplynout minimálně 30 kalendářních dnů. V této fázi nesmí být zasílány žádné přihlášky ani žádosti o informace.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: Lusaka ülekande jaotamise uuendustööde projekt (Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project (LTDRP)) – madalpinge jaotusvõrk: tehnilise auditi teenused</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sambia, Lõuna-Aafrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>TEENUSTE EELTEADE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaldamise viide</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menetlus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Piiratud</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmi nimetus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lusaka ülekande jaotamise uuendustööde projekt (Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project (LTDRP)) – madalpinge jaotusvõrk</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahastamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rahastamisleping nr FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaliku sektori hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Liit</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, keda esindab Euroopa Komisjon, Sambia Vabariigi eest ja nimel, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu laad</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tasupõhine</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Kavandatud teenuslepingu eesmärk on tehnilise auditi teenuste osutamine ja kindluse andmine järelevalveasutusele, avaliku sektori hankijale ja Euroopa Liidu delegatsioonile Sambias selle kohta, et Lusaka ülekande jaotamise uuendustööde projekt (LTDRP)) – madalpinge jaotusvõrk on teostatud vastavalt kehtestatud lepingulistele ja tehnilise kirjelduse nõuetele. Teenused hõlmavad ühtlasi elektrivõrgu (ZESCO Limited) teatatud uute ühenduste tegeliku arvu kontrollimist ning edusammude jälgimist seoses sotsiaalmajandusliku mõju ja lähteandmetega.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Soovituslik eelarve</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hanketeate avaldamise esialgne aeg</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisateave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekteerimise ja järelevalve eest vastutav töövõtja, kellega sõlmitakse leping hankemenetluses viitenumbriga EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM, teostab sotsiaalmajandusliku alusuuringu lähteandmete määratlemiseks. Võimalikud kandidaadid peavad arvestama, et eespool nimetatud teenushangete edukas pakkuja või eduka konsortsiumi mis tahes liige jäetakse kõnealuse teenuslepingu sõlmimisest kõrvale.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Õiguslik alus (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Aafrika, Kariibi mere ja Vaikse ookeani piirkonna riikide rühma ning Euroopa Ühenduse ja selle liikmesriikide vahel sõlmitud koostöölepingu (mis allkirjastati 23.6.2000. aastal Cotonous ning mida muudeti 25.6.2005. aastal Luxembourgis ja 22.6.2010. aastal Ouagadougous) IV lisa. Siinkohal viidatakse IV lisale, nagu seda on muudetud AKV-ELi ministrite nõukogu 20.6.2014 otsusega 1/2014.</P><P>Palume tähele panna, et olenevalt läbirääkimiste tulemustest kehtivad pärast Ühendkuningriigi EList lahkumist Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaatidele või pakkujatele kolmandates riikides asutatud ettevõtjatele kehtivad ELi hankemenetlustele juurdepääsu käsitlevad eeskirjad. Juhul, kui selline juurdepääs ei ole tagatud lepingu sõlmimise ajal kehtivate õiguslike sätete kaudu, võidakse Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaadid või pakkujad hankemenetlusest kõrvale jätta.</P><P>(1) Märkige kõik erijooned, mis võivad mõjutada osalemise tingimusi (näiteks geograafilised erijooned, valdkond, lühike või pikk tähtaeg).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Märkused:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Eelteate ja vastava hanketeate avaldamise vahele peab jääma vähemalt 30 kalendripäeva. Taotlusi ega teabenõudeid ei või selles etapis veel saata.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüsszel: A lusakai átviteli és elosztó hálózat felújítására irányuló projekt (LTDRP) – kisfeszültségű elosztó hálózat: műszaki ellenőrzési szolgáltatások</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambia, Dél-Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SZOLGÁLTATÁSRA IRÁNYULÓ ELŐZETES TÁJÉKOZTATÓ HIRDETMÉNY</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A közzététel hivatkozási száma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Eljárás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Meghívásos</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A program címe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A lusakai átviteli és elosztó hálózat felújítására irányuló projekt (LTDRP) – kisfeszültségű elosztó hálózat</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanszírozás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finanszírozási megállapodás száma: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Az Európai Unió</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, amelyet az Európai Bizottság képvisel, a Zambiai Köztársaság nevében és megbízásából, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüsszel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés típusa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Díjalapú</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés meghatározása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A megkötni kívánt szolgáltatási szerződés tárgya műszaki ellenőrzési szolgáltatások nyújtása, valamint annak biztosítása a felügyelő, az ajánlatkérő és az Európai Unió Zambiai Delegációja számára, hogy a lusakai átviteli és elosztó hálózat felújítására irányuló projekt (LTDRP) – kisfeszültségű elosztó hálózatra irányuló projekt megvalósítása a meghatározott szerződéses és a műszaki leírásban szereplő követelmények szerint történik. A szolgáltatások magukban foglalják továbbá az új kapcsolatok villamosenergia-ellátó (ZESCO Limited) által közölt tényleges számának ellenőrzését, továbbá a társadalmi és gazdasági hatás alakulásának és az alapadatoknak a nyomon követését.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Várható költségvetés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlati felhívás közzétételének tervezett időpontja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>További információk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM hivatkozási számú közbeszerzési eljárás keretében a tervezéssel és felügyelettel megbízott nyertes ajánlattevő társadalmi-gazdasági alaptanulmányt készít az alapadatok összeállítása érdekében. A leendő jelentkezőknek figyelembe kell venniük, hogy a fenti szolgáltatási szerződést elnyert ajánlattevő – vagy konzorcium esetén annak tagja – kizárásra kerül a jelen szolgáltatási szerződésből.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Jogalap (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Az egyrészt az afrikai, karibi és csendes-óceáni államok csoportjának tagjai, másrészt az Európai Közösség, illetve annak tagállamai között létrejött partnerségi megállapodás IV. melléklete, amelyet a 23.6.2000 dátumú napon Cotonouban írtak alá, és a 25.6.2005 dátumú napon Luxembourgban, valamint a 22.6.2010 dátumú napon Ouagadougouban módosítottak. Hivatkozással az AKCS-EU Miniszteri Tanácsának 20.6.2014 keltezésű 1/2014 határozatával felülvizsgált IV. mellékletre.</P><P>Figyelembe kell venni, hogy az Egyesült Királyságnak az EU-ból való kilépése után az Egyesült Királyságból származó jelentkezőkre vagy ajánlattevőkre – a tárgyalások kimenetelétől függően – az EU közbeszerzési eljárásaihoz való hozzáférés tekintetében a harmadik országok gazdasági szereplői számára érvényes szabályok vonatkoznak. Amennyiben az ilyen eljárásokban való részvételről nem rendelkezik a szerződés odaítélésének időpontjában hatályban lévő jogszabály, az Egyesült Királyságban székhellyel rendelkező jelentkezőket, illetve ajánlattevőket kizárhatják a közbeszerzési eljárásból.</P><P>(1) Kérjük, jelezzen bármely olyan sajátosságot, amely hatással lehet a részvételi szabályokra (például földrajzi, tematikai vagy hosszú/rövid távú sajátosság).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Megjegyzések:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Legalább 30 naptári napnak kell eltelnie a jelen előzetes összesített hirdetmény megjelenése és a vonatkozó ajánlati felhívás közzététele között. Ezen időszak alatt jelentkezések benyújtásának, illetve információkérésnek nincs helye.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Briuselis: Lusakos perdavimo paskirstymo atnaujinimo projektas (LTDRP) – žemosios įtampos skirstomasis tinklas: Techninio audito paslaugos</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambija, Pietų Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IŠANKSTINIS INFORMACINIS SKELBIMAS APIE PASLAUGŲ PIRKIMĄ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nuoroda į publikaciją</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ribotas konkursas</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programos pavadinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lusakos perdavimo paskirstymo atnaujinimo projektas (LTDRP) – žemosios įtampos skirstomasis tinklas</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansavimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finansavimo susitarimas Nr. FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Perkančioji organizacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos Sąjunga</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, atstovaujama Europos Komisijos, Zambijos Respublikos vardu ir jos naudai, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Briuselis</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties pobūdis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mokama</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties apibūdinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Paslaugų pirkimo sutarties tikslas – teikti techninio audito paslaugas ir užtikrinti priežiūros institucijai, perkančiajai organizacijai ir Europos Sąjungos delegacijai Zambijoje, kad Lusakos perdavimo paskirstymo atnaujinimo projektas (LTDRP) – žemosios įtampos skirstomojo tinklo projektas – buvo įgyvendintas, vadovaujantis nustatytais sutartiniais ir techninės specifikacijos reikalavimais. Paslaugos taip pat apims faktinio naujų suteiktų jungčių skaičiaus, apie kurį pranešė elektros tiekimo įmonė (ZESCO Limited), patikrą bei pažangą socialinio ir ekonominio poveikio srityje, pradinių duomenų stebėseną.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatomas biudžetas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatoma skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo data</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildoma informacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Pagrindinį socialinį ekonominį tyrimą, skirtą pradiniams duomenims apibrėžti, atliks projektavimo ir darbų priežiūros paslaugų rangovas, su kuriuo sutartis bus sudaryta surengus pirkimo procedūrą Nr. EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Potencialūs kandidatai turi žinoti, kad konkurso dalyvis (ar bet kuris iš narių, jei dalyvauja konsorciumas), laimėjęs minėtą paslaugų pirkimo sutartį, bus pašalintas iš šios paslaugų pirkimo sutarties paskyrimo.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teisinis pagrindas (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Afrikos, Karibų jūros bei Ramiojo vandenyno grupės valstybių ir Europos Bendrijos bei jos valstybių narių partnerystės susitarimo, pasirašyto 23.6.2000 Kotonu, su pakeitimais, padarytais 25.6.2005 Liuksemburge ir 22.6.2010 Uagadugu, IV priedas. Pateikiama nuoroda į IV priedą, iš dalies pakeistą 20.6.2014 AKR ir ES Ministrų Tarybos sprendimu 1/2014.</P><P>Atkreipkite dėmesį, kad Jungtinei Karalystei pasitraukus iš ES, trečiųjų šalių ekonominės veiklos vykdytojų, įsikūrusių trečiosiose šalyse, prieigos prie ES pirkimo procedūrų taisyklės bus taikomos kandidatams ar konkurso dalyviams iš Jungtinės Karalystės, atsižvelgiant į derybų rezultatus. Jeigu tokia prieiga nebus suteikta galiojančiomis teisinėmis nuostatomis, kandidatai arba konkurso dalyviai iš Jungtinės Karalystės gali būti pašalinti iš pirkimo procedūros.</P><P>(1) Nurodykite bet kokias aplinkybes, galinčias turėti įtakos dalyvavimo taisyklėms (pvz., geografines ar temines, ilgalaikes ar trumpalaikes).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Pastabos:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Nuo šio išankstinio informacinio skelbimo publikavimo iki atitinkamo skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo turi praeiti mažiausiai 30 kalendorinių dienų. Šiuo etapu negalima siųsti paraiškų ar kreiptis dėl informacijos.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brisele: Lusakas pārvades un sadales atjaunošanas projekts (Lusaka Transmission Distribution Rehabilitation Project – LTDRP) – zemsprieguma sadales tīkls: tehniskā audita pakalpojumi</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambija, Āfrikas dienvidi</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IEPRIEKŠĒJS INFORMATĪVS PAZIŅOJUMS PAR PAKALPOJUMU LĪGUMU</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsauce uz publikāciju</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Slēgta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmas nosaukums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Lusakas pārvades un sadales atjaunošanas projekts (LTDRP) – zemsprieguma sadales tīkls</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansējums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finansēšanas līgums Nr. FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Savienība</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ko Zambijas Republikas vārdā un interesēs pārstāv Eiropas Komisija, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brisele</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Beļģija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma veids</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Līgums, kura pamatā ir samaksa par pakalpojumiem</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Šim pakalpojumu līgumam jānodrošina tehniskā audita pakalpojumi un apliecinājums uzraudzītājam, līgumslēdzējai iestādei un Eiropas Savienības delegācijai Zambijā, ka Lusakas pārvades un sadales atjaunošanas projekts (LTDRP — Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project) – zemsprieguma sadales tīkla projekts ir ticis īstenots atbilstoši līgumtiesiskajām un tehniskās specifikācijas prasībām. Pakalpojumi ietvers arī tā faktiskā jauno nodrošināto pieslēgumu skaita pārbaudi, ko paziņojis elektrības apgādes uzņēmums (ZESCO Limited), un progresa uzraudzību attiecībā uz sociālekonomisko ietekmi un pamatdatiem.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Provizoriskais budžets</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paziņojuma par līgumu paredzamais publicēšanas datums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildu informācija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sociālekonomisko pamatdatu pētījumu, lai sagatavotu pamatdatus, veiks izstrādes un uzraudzības līgumslēdzējs, ar kuru līgums tiks noslēgts iepirkuma procedūras ar atsauces numuru EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM ietvaros. Iespējamajiem kandidātiem jāņem vērā, ka veiksmīgais pretendents (vai, konsorcija gadījumā, jebkurš tā dalībnieks), kas noslēdzis iepriekš minēto pakalpojumu līgumu, tiks izslēgts no šā pakalpojumu līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tiesiskais pamats (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IV pielikums Partnerattiecību nolīgumam starp Āfrikas, Karību jūras reģiona un Klusā okeāna valstu grupas locekļiem, no vienas puses, un Eiropas Kopienu un tās dalībvalstīm, no otras puses, kas parakstīts Kotonū 2000. gada 23. jūnijā, kā tas grozīts Luksemburgā 2005. gada 25. jūnijā un kā tas grozīts Vagadugu 2010. gada 22. jūnijā. Atsauce sniegta uz IV pielikumu, kas pārskatīts ar ĀKK un ES Ministru padomes Lēmumu Nr. 1/2014 (2014. gada 20. jūnijs).</P><P>Lūdzam ņemt vērā, ka pēc Apvienotās Karalistes izstāšanās no ES uz kandidātiem un pretendentiem no Apvienotās Karalistes atkarībā no sarunu iznākuma attieksies noteikumi par trešo valstu uzņēmēju tiesībām piedalīties ES iepirkuma procedūrās. Ja līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas brīdī spēkā esošajās tiesību normās šāda piekļuve nebūs paredzēta, kandidāti vai pretendenti no Apvienotās Karalistes var tikt izslēgti no iepirkuma procedūras.</P><P>(1) Lūdzam norādīt visus specifiskos iemeslus (piemēram, ģeogrāfiskus, tematiskus, īstermiņa vai ilgtermiņa), kas var ietekmēt dalības noteikumus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Piezīmes</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Starp šā iepriekšējā informatīvā paziņojuma un attiecīgā paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datumiem jāpaiet vismaz 30 kalendārajām dienām. Šajā posmā nekādus pieteikumus vai informācijas pieprasījumus nesūtīt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussell: Proġett ta' Riabilitazzjoni tad-Distribuzzjoni tat-Trażmissjoni f'Lusaka (LTDRP) – Netwerk tad-Distribuzzjoni b'Vultaġġ Baxx: Servizzi ta' Verifika Teknika</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Iż-Żambja, l-Afrika t'Isfel</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVIŻ TA' TAGĦRIF MINN QABEL DWAR SERVIZZ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-proċedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-titlu tal-programm</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proġett ta' riabilitazzjoni tad-distribuzzjoni tat-trażmissjoni f'Lusaka (LTDRP) — Netwerk tad-distribuzzjoni b'vultaġġ baxx</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-iffinanzjar</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-ftehim dwar l-iffinanzjar Nru: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>L-Unjoni Ewropea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, irrappreżentata mill-Kummissjoni Ewropea f'isem u għar-Repubblika taż-Żambja, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussell</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Belġju.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-tip ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bil-ħlas ta' miżata</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-deskrizzjoni tal-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-kuntratt ta' servizz propost se jipprovdi servizzi ta' verifika teknika u garanzija lis-superviżur, lill-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt u lid-Delegazzjoni tal-Unjoni Ewropea fiż-Żambja li l-proġett ta' riabilitazzjoni tad-distribuzzjoni tat-trażmissjoni f'Lusaka (LTDRP) – Netwerk tad-distribuzzjoni b'vultaġġ baxx ġie implimentat skont ir-rekwiżiti tal-ispeċifikazzjoni kuntrattwali u teknika stabbiliti. Is-servizzi se jkopru wkoll il-verifika tan-numru attwali ta' konnessjonijiet ġodda pprovduti kif irrapportat mill-kumpanija tal-elettriku (ZESCO Limited) u l-monitoraġġ tal-progress fuq l-impatt soċjoekonomiku u d-dejta bażika.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-baġit indikattiv</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Iż-żmien maħsub għall-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif addizzjonali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Studju bażiku soċjoekonomiku li jifformula d-dejta bażika se jitwettaq mill-kuntrattur tad-disinn u s-sorveljanza li se jiġi kkuntrattat permezz tal-proċedura tal-ksib bin-numru ta' referenza EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Il-kandidati prospettivi jridu jkunu konxji li dak li jirbaħ l-offerta, jew xi wieħed mill-membri tiegħu jekk konsorzju, tal-kuntratt ta' servizzi msemmi hawn fuq se jkun imwarrab mill-għoti ta' dan il-kuntratt ta' servizz.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-bażi legali (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>L-Anness IV tal-Ftehim ta' Sħubija bejn il-membri tal-Grupp tal-Istati Afrikani, tal-Karibew u l-Paċifiku bħala l-ewwel parti, u l-Komunità Ewropea u l-Istati Membri tagħha, bħala l-parti l-oħra, iffirmat f'Cotonou nhar it-23.6.2000, kif emendat fil-Lussemburgu nhar il-25.6.2005 u f'Ouagadougou nhar it-22.6.2010. Qed issir referenza għall-Anness IV kif riveduta mid-Deċiżjoni 1/2014 tal-Kunsill tal-Ministri bejn l-AKP u l-UE tal-20.6.2014.</P><P>Jekk jogħġbok kun af li wara l-irtirar tar-Renju Unit mill-UE, ir-regoli tal-aċċess għall-proċeduri ta' ksib tal-UE ta' operaturi ekonomiċi mwaqqfa f'pajjiżi terzi se japplikaw għall-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit skont ir-riżultat tan-negozjati. F'każ li tali aċċess mhux ipprovdut minn dispożizzjonijiet legali fis-seħħ fil-ħin tal-għoti tal-kuntratt, il-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit jistgħu jiġu mwarrba mill-proċedura tal-ksib.</P><P>(1) Jekk jogħġbok niżżel kwalunkwe speċifiċità li jista' jkollha impatt fuq ir-regoli għas-sehem (bħal dik ġeografika jew tematika jew fuq żmien qasir jew fit-tul).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Kummenti:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Irid ikun hemm perijodu minimu ta' 30 jum kalendarju bejn il-pubblikazzjoni ta' dan l-avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel u l-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt li għandu x'jaqsam miegħu. M'għandhomx jintbagħtu applikazzjonijiet jew talbiet għal tagħrif f'dan l-istadju.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruksela: Projekt dotyczący modernizacji sieci przesyłowej i rozdzielczej w Lusace (LTDRP) – sieć rozdzielcza niskiego napięcia: usługi audytu technicznego</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambia, Afryka Południowa</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>WSTĘPNE OGŁOSZENIE INFORMACYJNE DOTYCZĄCE ZAMÓWIENIA NA USŁUGI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numer referencyjny publikacji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograniczona</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nazwa programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt dotyczący modernizacji sieci przesyłowej i rozdzielczej w Lusace (Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project – LTDRP) – sieć rozdzielcza niskiego napięcia</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansowanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Porozumienie finansowe nr FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Instytucja zamawiająca</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unia Europejska</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentowana przez Komisję Europejską, w imieniu i na rzecz Republiki Zambii, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruksela</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rodzaj zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Według stawek jednostkowych</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Celem zamówienia jest podpisanie umowy o świadczenie usług audytu technicznego oraz zapewnienie instytucji nadzorującej, jaką jest instytucja zamawiająca oraz delegatura Unii Europejskiej w Zambii, że projekt dotyczący modernizacji sieci przesyłowej i rozdzielczej w Lusace (LTDRP) został wdrożony zgodnie z ustanowionymi wymogami zawartymi w specyfikacji kontraktowej i technicznej. Usługi obejmą również weryfikację faktycznej liczby nowych połączeń dostarczonych zgodnie z informacjami przekazanymi przez przedsiębiorstwo energetyczne (ZESCO Limited) oraz monitorowanie postępów w zakresie skutków społeczno-gospodarczych i danych wyjściowych.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orientacyjny budżet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planowana data publikacji ogłoszenia o zamówieniu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacje dodatkowe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Badanie stanu wyjściowego o charakterze społeczno-ekonomicznym w celu sformułowania danych wyjściowych zostanie przeprowadzone przez projektanta i przedsiębiorstwo sprawujące nadzór, którzy zostaną wyłonieni w ramach procedury udzielania zamówienia o numerze referencyjnym EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Przyszli kandydaci muszą mieć świadomość, że oferent lub członek konsorcjum wybrany do realizacji zamówień na usługi, o których mowa powyżej, zostanie wyłączony z postępowania o udzielenie niniejszego zamówienia.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Podstawa prawna (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Załącznik IV do Umowy o partnerstwie między członkami grupy państw Afryki, Karaibów i Pacyfiku z jednej strony a Wspólnotą Europejską i jej państwami członkowskimi z drugiej strony, podpisanej w Kotonu dnia 23.6.2000, zmienionej w Luksemburgu dnia 25.6.2005 oraz w Wagadugu dnia 22.6.2010. Odniesienia do załącznika IV dotyczą jego wersji zmienionej decyzją Rady Ministrów AKP–UE nr 1/2014 z dnia 20.6.2014.</P><P>Należy mieć świadomość, że po wystąpieniu Zjednoczonego Królestwa z UE brytyjscy kandydaci i oferenci będą podlegać zasadom dostępu do unijnych procedur udzielania zamówień podmiotom gospodarczym w państwach trzecich w zależności od wyniku negocjacji. W sytuacji gdy przepisy prawa obowiązujące w chwili udzielenia zamówienia nie będą przewidywać takiego dostępu, kandydaci lub oferenci ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa mogą zostać wykluczeni z postępowania o udzielenie zamówienia.</P><P>(1) Uprasza się o wskazanie wszelkich okoliczności, które mogą mieć wpływ na warunki udziału (takie jak uwarunkowania geograficzne, tematyczne lub kwestie długo- lub krótkoterminowe).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Uwagi:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Między publikacją niniejszego wstępnego ogłoszenia informacyjnego a publikacją odpowiedniego ogłoszenia o zamówieniu musi upłynąć co najmniej 30 dni kalendarzowych. Na tym etapie nie należy przesyłać wniosków ani zapytań o informacje.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: Projekt obnovy rozvodnej a prenosovej siete v Lusake (LTDRP) – nízkonapäťová rozvodná sieť: Služby technického auditu</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambia, južná Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDBEŽNÉ OZNÁMENIE O OBSTARÁVANÍ SLUŽIEB</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčné číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Konanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užšia súťaž</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Názov programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt obnovy rozvodnej a prenosovej siete v Lusake (LTDRP) – nízkonapäťová rozvodná sieť</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zdroj financovania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Finančná dohoda č.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verejný obstarávateľ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európska únia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastúpená Európskou komisiou v mene a záujme Zambijskej republiky, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgicko.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Charakter verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Odplatné</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Zamýšľaná zmluva o poskytovaní služieb poskytne dozornému pracovníkovi, verejnému obstarávateľovi a delegácii Európskej únie v Zambii služby technického auditu a záruku, že projekt obnovy rozvodnej a prenosovej siete v Lusake (LTDRP) – projekt nízkonapäťovej rozvodnej siete sa vykonal v súlade so stanovenými požiadavkami zmluvných a technických špecifikácií. Služby budú zahŕňať aj overenie skutočného počtu nových pripojení poskytnutých podľa informácií od elektrárne (ZESCO Limited) a monitorovania pokroku v oblasti sociálno-ekonomického vplyvu a základných údajov.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predbežný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plánovaný dátum zverejnenia oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatočné informácie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sociálno-ekonomickú základnú štúdiu na vypracovanie základných údajov zrealizuje dodávateľ pre projektovanie a dozor, s ktorým sa uzavrie zmluva prostredníctvom obstarávacieho konania s referenčným číslom EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Potenciálni uchádzači si musia uvedomiť, že úspešný uchádzač (alebo ktorýkoľvek člen v prípade konzorcia) o vyššie uvedenú zmluvu o poskytovaní služieb bude vylúčený z uzatvorenia tejto zmluvy o poskytovaní služieb.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právny základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Príloha IV k Dohode o partnerstve medzi členmi skupiny afrických, karibských a tichomorských štátov na jednej strane a Európskym spoločenstvom a jeho členskými štátmi na strane druhej, podpísanej v Cotonou 23.6.2000, zmenenej v Luxemburgu 25.6.2005 a v Ouagadougou 22.6.2010. Uvádza sa odkaz na prílohu IV v znení zmien rozhodnutia Rady ministrov krajín AKT – EÚ č. 1/2014 z 20.6.2014.</P><P>Pripomíname, že po vystúpení Spojeného kráľovstva z EÚ sa na záujemcov alebo uchádzačov zo Spojeného kráľovstva, v závislosti od výsledku rokovaní, budú uplatňovať pravidlá prístupu k postupom obstarávania EÚ zo strany hospodárskych subjektov so sídlom v tretích krajinách. V prípade, že takýto prístup sa nezabezpečí ustanoveniami platnými v čase pridelenia zákazky, záujemcovia alebo uchádzači zo Spojeného kráľovstva by mohli byť vylúčení z obstarávacieho konania.</P><P>(1) Uveďte akékoľvek špecifiká, ktoré by mohli mať vplyv na pravidlá účasti (napríklad geografické alebo tematické, dlhodobé alebo krátkodobé).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Medzi uverejnením predbežného oznámenia a uverejnením príslušného oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania musí uplynúť minimálne 30 kalendárnych dní. V tomto období sa nemajú zasielať žiadne prihlášky ani žiadosti o informácie.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselj: Projekt obnove prenosa in distribucije v Lusaki (LTDRP) – nizkonapetostno distribucijsko omrežje: storitve tehnične revizije</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambija, južna Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDHODNO INFORMATIVNO OBVESTILO O NAROČILU STORITEV</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčna številka dokumenta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postopek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Omejeni</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt obnove prenosa in distribucije v Lusaki (LTDRP) – nizkonapetostno distribucijsko omrežje</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sporazum o financiranju št.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ki jo zastopa Evropska komisija, v imenu in za račun Republike Zambije, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselj</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vrsta naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Na podlagi plačila</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>V okviru predlaganega naročila storitev se bodo nadzorniku, naročniku in delegaciji Evropske unije v Zambiji zagotovili storitve tehnične revizije in jamstvo, da se projekt obnove prenosa in distribucije v Lusaki (LTDRP) – nizkonapetostno distribucijsko omrežje – izvaja v skladu z opredeljenimi pogodbenimi zahtevami in tehničnimi specifikacijami. Storitve bodo zajemale tudi preverjanje dejanskega števila novih priključkov, kot ga sporoči električno podjetje (ZESCO Limited), in spremljanje napredka na podlagi socialno-ekonomskega učinka in temeljnih podatkov.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Okvirni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predvideni datum objave obvestila o naročilu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Izvajalec načrta in nadzora, izbran v postopku javnega naročila z referenčno številko EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM, bo izvedel temeljno socialno-ekonomsko študijo, namenjeno pripravi temeljnih podatkov. Potencialni kandidati morajo upoštevati, da bo izbrani ponudnik, ali kateri koli član konzorcija v okviru naročila storitev, omenjenega zgoraj, izključen iz postopka oddaje tega naročila storitev.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravna podlaga(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Priloga IV k Sporazumu o partnerstvu med članicami skupine afriških, karibskih in pacifiških držav na eni strani ter Evropsko skupnostjo in njenimi državami članicami na drugi, podpisanemu v Cotonouju dne 23.6.2000, kakor je bil spremenjen v Luxembourgu dne 25.6.2005 in v Ouagadougouju dne 22.6.2010. Sklic se nanaša na Prilogo IV, kakor je bila revidirana s Sklepom 1/2014 Sveta ministrov AKP-EU z dne 20.6.2014.</P><P>Upoštevajte, da se bodo po izstopu Združenega kraljestva iz EU pravila za dostop do razpisnih postopkov EU s strani gospodarskih subjektov, ustanovljenih v tretjih državah, za kandidate ali ponudnike iz Združenega kraljestva uporabljala v skladu z rezultati pogajanj. V primeru, da v času oddaje naročila veljavne pravne določbe ne zagotavljajo tovrstnega dostopa, se lahko kandidatom ali ponudnikom iz Združenega kraljestva sodelovanje v razpisnem postopku zavrne.</P><P>(1) Navedite kakršno koli posebnost, ki bi lahko vplivala na pravila za sodelovanje (na primer geografsko ali tematsko ali dolgo-/kratkoročno).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opombe:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Med objavo tega predhodnega informativnega obvestila in objavo ustreznega obvestila o naročilu mora preteči vsaj 30 koledarskih dni. V tej fazi ne pošiljajte prijav ali zahtevkov za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-An Bhruiséil: Tionscadal Athshlánaithe um Dháileadh Tarchuir Lusaka (LTDRP) — Líonra Dáilte Ísealvoltais: Seirbhísí Iniúchóireachta Teicniúla</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>An tSaimbia, Deisceart na hAfraice</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÓGRA RÉAMHAISNÉISE SEIRBHÍSE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nós imeachta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Teoranta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teideal an chláir</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tionscadal athshlánaithe um dháileadh tarchuir Lusaka (LTDRP) — Líonra dáilte ísealvoltais</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Maoiniú</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Comhaontú maoinithe Uimh.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás Conarthach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An tAontas Eorpach</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, arna ionadú ag an gCoimisiún Eorpach thar ceann agus chun cuntais Phoblacht na Saimbia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>an Bhruiséil</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Bheilg.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cineál an chonartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bunaithe ar tháille</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ar an gconradh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cuirfear seirbhísí iniúchóireachta teicniúla agus dearbhú ar fáil don mhaoirseoir leis an gconradh seirbhíse beartaithe, don Údarás Conarthach agus do Thoscaireacht an Aontais Eorpaigh chuig an Saimbia; go bhfuil an tionscadal athshlánaithe um dháileadh tarchuir Lusaka (LTDRP) — an tionscadal líonra dáilte ísealvoltais tar éis a bheith curtha chun feidhme i gcomhréir leis na riachtanais a bhaineann le sonraíocht an chonartha agus le sonraíochtaí theicniúla faoi mar a bhí leagtha síos. Clúdóidh na seirbhísí freisin fíordheimhniú líon iarbhír na gceangal nua a cuireadh ar fáil faoi mar atá tuairiscithe ag an bhfóntas leictreachais (ZESCO Limited) agus monatóireacht ar dhul chun cinn um thionchar sóisialta agus eacnamaíoch agus sonraí bonnlíne.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buiséad táscach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>An sprioc atá beartaithe d'fhoilsiú an fhógra conartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis bhreise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Cuirfear i gcrích staidéar bonnlíne socheacnamaíoch chun na sonraí bonnlíne a fhoirmliú. Beidh sé seo déanta ag conraitheoir an dearaidh agus na maoirseachta a gheobhaidh conradh tríd an nós imeachta soláthair leis an uimhir thagartha EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Ní mór do na hiarrthóirí ionchasacha a thuiscint go ndéanfar eisiamh ó dhámhachtain an chonartha seirbhíse seo don tairgeoir rathúil, nó ar bhall ar bith dá chuid más cuibhreannas atá ann, i gcás na gconarthaí seirbhísí liostaithe thuas.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bunús dlí (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Iarscríbhinn IV leis an gComhaontú Comhpháirtíochta idir baill Ghrúpa na Stát san Afraic, sa Mhuir Chairib agus san Aigéan Ciúin de pháirt, agus an Comhphobal Eorpach agus a Bhallstáit, den pháirt eile, arna síniú in Cotonou an 23.6.2000, mar a leasaíodh i Lucsamburg an 25.6.2005, agus in Ouagadougou an 22.6.2010. Déantar tagairt d'Iarscríbhinn IV arna hathbhreithniú le Cinneadh 1/2014 ó Chomhairle Airí ACC-AE an 20.6.2014.</P><P>Tabhair faoi deara go gcuirfear na rialacha um rochtain ar nósanna imeachta soláthair an AE ag oibreoirí eacnamaíocha atá bunaithe i dtríú tíortha i bhfeidhm ar iarrthóirí nó ar thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe tar éis di tarraingt siar ón AE, ag brath ar thorthaí na n-idirbheartaíochtaí. Sa chás nach gcuirfear a leithéid de rochtain ar fáil trí fhorálacha dlíthiúla a bheidh i bhfeidhm an tráth a dhámhfar an conradh, d'fhéadfaí iarrthóirí nó tairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe a dhiúltú ón nós imeachta soláthair.</P><P>(1) Luaigh aon sainiúlacht a d’fhéadfadh tionchar a bheith aici ar rialacha na rannpháirtíochta (amhail sainiúlacht thíreolaíoch nó théamach, nó sainiúlacht fhadtéarmach/ghearrthéarmach).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Nótaí:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Ní mór tréimhse 30 lá féilire ar a laghad a bheith idir foilsiú an fhógra réamhaisnéise seo agus foilsiú an fhógra conartha chomhfhreagraigh. Níor cheart aon iarratais ná iarrataí ar fhaisnéis a sheoladh faoi láthair.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Брюксел: Проект за реконструкция на пренос и разпределение в Лусака (LTDRP) — нисковолтова разпределителна мрежа: Услуги за технически одит</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Замбия, Южна Африка</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ОБЯВЛЕНИЕ ЗА ПРЕДВАРИТЕЛНА ИНФОРМАЦИЯ ЗА УСЛУГИ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Референтен номер на публикация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Процедура</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ограничена</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Заглавие на програма</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Проект за реконструкция на пренос и разпределение в Лусака (LTDRP) — нисковолтова разпределителна мрежа</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Финансиране</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Споразумение за финансиране № : FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейски съюз</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, представляван от Европейската комисия, от името и за сметка на Република Замбия, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Брюксел</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Белгия.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Вид на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Комисионна поръчка</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Описание на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>По предлаганата поръчка за услуги ще се осигурят услуги за технически одит и гаранция на надзорния орган, възлагащия орган и Делегацията на Европейския съюз в Замбия, че проектът за реконструкция на пренос и разпределение в Лусака (LTDRP) — нисковолтова разпределителна мрежа е изпълнен в съответствие с определените изисквания на договорните и техническите спецификации. Услугите ще обхващат също така проверка на реалния брой осигурени нови връзки, докладван от комуналното дружество за доставка на електроенергия (ZESCO Limited), и мониторинг на напредъка въз основа на социално-икономическото въздействие и изходните данни.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Индикативен бюджет</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Очакван срок за публикуване на обявлението за поръчка</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018 г.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Допълнителна информация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Изпълнителят за проектиране и надзор, с когото ще бъде сключен договор по обществена поръчка с референтен номер EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM, ще извърши социално-икономическо основно проучване за формулиране на изходните данни. Потенциалните кандидатите трябва да са наясно, че одобреният оферент или всеки от неговите членове, в случай на консорциум, за посочената по-горе поръчка за услуги ще бъде изключен от възлагане на настоящата поръчка за услуги.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Правно основание (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Приложение IV към Споразумението за партньорство между членовете на Групата на държавите от Африка, Карибите и Тихоокеанския басейн, от една страна, и Европейската общност и нейните държави членки от друга, подписано в Котону на 23.6.2000 г., изменено в Люксембург на 25.6.2005 г. и в Уагадугу на 22.6.2010 г. Направена е препратка към приложение IV, ревизирано с Решение № 1/2014 на Съвета на министрите АКТБ-ЕС от 20.6.2014 г.</P><P>Моля, имайте предвид, че след оттеглянето на Обединеното кралство от ЕС, правилата за достъп до процедури за обществени поръчки на ЕС за икономически оператори, установени в трети държави, ще се прилагат за кандидати или оференти от Обединеното кралство, в зависимост от резултата от преговорите. В случай че такъв достъп не е предвиден в действащите правни разпоредби, които са в сила по време на възлагането на поръчката, кандидатите или оферентите от Обединеното кралство могат да бъдат отхвърлени от процедурата за обществена поръчка.</P><P>(1) Моля, посочете всяка особеност, която може да окаже въздействие върху правилата за участие (напр. географска или тематична, или кратък/дълъг срок).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Забележки:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Трябва да има минимален период от 30 календарни дни между публикуването на това обявление за предварителна информация и публикуването на съответното обявление за поръчка. На този етап не трябва да се изпращат никакви молби или искания за информация.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Proiect privind reabilitarea rețelei de transport și de distribuție a energiei electrice din Lusaka (Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project – LTDRP) – rețeaua de distribuție de joasă tensiune: Servicii de audit tehnic</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambia, Africa de Sud</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNȚ DE INTENȚIE PRIVIND UN CONTRACT DE ACHIZIȚII PUBLICE DE SERVICII</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referința publicației</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedură</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restrânsă</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titlul programului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Proiect privind reabilitarea rețelei de transport și de distribuție a energiei electrice din Lusaka (Lusaka transmission distribution rehabilitation project – LTDRP) – rețeaua de distribuție de joasă tensiune</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanțare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Acordul de finanțare nr.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea contractantă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Uniunea Europeană</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentată de Comisia Europeană, în numele și în favoarea Republicii Zambia, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bazat pe onorarii</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contractul de servicii propus va furniza servicii de audit tehnic și va oferi asigurare supraveghetorul, autorității contractante și Delegația Uniunii Europene în Zambia că servicii de audit tehnic și de asigurare că proiectul privind reabilitarea rețelei de transport și de distribuție a energiei electrice din Lusaka – rețeaua de distribuție de joasă tensiune a fost implementat în conformitate cu cerințele specificațiilor tehnice si contractuale. Serviciile vor acoperi, de asemenea, verificarea numărului efectiv de conexiuni noi furnizate, așa cum sunt raportate de către furnizorul de energie electrică (ZESCO Limited), și monitorizarea progreselor privind impactul social-economic și datele de bază.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buget indicativ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevăzută de publicare a anunțului de participare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informații suplimentare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Un studiu socio-economic de bază pentru formularea datelor de referință va fi efectuat de contractantul în domeniul proiectării și monitorizării care va fi contractat prin procedura de achiziție cu numărul de referință EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Potențialii candidați trebuie să aibă în vedere faptul că ofertantul câștigător (sau oricare dintre membrii acestuia, în cazul unui consorțiu) al contractelor de servicii menționate mai sus va fi exclus de la atribuirea acestui contract de servicii.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Temeiul juridic (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Anexa IV la Acordul de parteneriat între membrii grupului statelor din Africa, zona Caraibelor și Pacific, pe de o parte, și Comunitatea Europeană și statele membre ale acesteia, pe de altă parte, semnat la Cotonou, la 23.6.2000, astfel cum a fost modificat la Luxemburg, la 25.6.2005, și la Ouagadougou, la 22.6.2010. Se face referire la anexa IV, astfel cum a fost revizuită prin Decizia 1/2014 a Consiliului de miniștri ACP-UE din 20.6.2014.</P><P>A se avea în vedere că, după retragerea Marii Britanii din UE, normele de acces al operatorilor economici stabiliți în țări terțe la procedurile de achiziții publice ale UE se vor aplica ofertanților sau candidaților din Marea Britanie în funcție de rezultatul negocierilor. În cazul în care accesul nu este prevăzut de dispozițiile juridice în vigoare la momentul atribuirii contractului, candidații sau ofertanții din Marea Britanie ar putea fi respinși de la procedura de achiziții publice.</P><P>(1) Vă rugăm să precizați orice specificitate care ar putea avea un impact asupra regulilor de participare (cum ar fi de ordin geografic sau tematic sau pe termen lung/scurt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observații:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Trebuie respectată o perioadă de minimum 30 de zile calendaristice între publicarea prezentului anunț de intenție și publicarea anunțului de participare corespunzător. În această etapă nu se acceptă candidaturi sau cereri de informații.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: Projekt obnove za prijenos i distribuciju u Lusaki (LTDRP) — niskonaponska distribucijska mreža: Usluge tehničke revizije</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Zambija, južna Afrika</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PRETHODNA INFORMACIJSKA OBAVIJEST O USLUGAMA</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uputa na objavu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139532/DH/SER/ZM</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postupak</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograničeni</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Projekt obnove za prijenos i distribuciju u Lusaki (LTDRP) — niskonaponska distribucijska mreža</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Sporazum o financiranju br.: FED/2016/038-238</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, koju predstavlja Europska komisija u ime i za račun Republike Zambije, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Priroda ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Temeljen na naknadama</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Predloženim će se ugovorom o pružanju usluga pružiti usluge tehničke revizije i osiguranja nadzorniku, javnom naručitelju i Delegaciji Europske unije u Zambiji da je Projekt obnove za prijenos i distribuciju u Lusaki (LTDRP) — niskonaponska distribucijska mreža proveden u skladu s utvrđenim ugovornim zahtjevima i zahtjevima tehničkih specifikacija. Usluge će obuhvatiti i provjeru stvarnog broja pruženih novih veza koje je prijavilo komunalno poduzeće za električnu energiju (ZESCO Limited) i praćenje napretka socio-ekonomskog utjecaja i osnovnih podataka.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indikativni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>1 000 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predviđeni datum objave poziva na nadmetanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>10.4.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Socio-ekonomsku osnovnu studiju za izradu osnovnih podataka provest će izvoditelj za projektiranje i nadzor koji će se ugovoriti putem postupka nabave s referentnim brojem EuropeAid/138361/IH/SER/ZM. Budući natjecatelji moraju biti svjesni da će uspješni ponuditelj ili netko od njegovih članova ako se radi o konzorciju, za naveden ugovor o uslugama, biti isključen iz sklapanja ovog ugovora o uslugama.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravni temelj (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Prilog IV. Sporazumu o partnerstvu između članica afričke, karipske i pacifičke skupine država, s jedne strane, i Europske zajednice i njezinih država članica, s druge strane, potpisan u Cotonouu 23.6.2000 kako je izmijenjen u Luxembourgu 25.6.2005 i u Ouagadougouu 22.6.2010. Uputa se daje na Prilog IV. kako je revidiran Odlukom 1/2014 Vijeća ministara AKP-a i EU-a od 20.6.2014.</P><P>Napominjemo da će se nakon povlačenja Ujedinjene Kraljevine iz EU-a na natjecatelje ili ponuditelje iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine primjenjivati pravila pristupa postupcima nabave EU-a za gospodarske subjekte s poslovnim nastanom u trećim zemljama, ovisno o rezultatima pregovora. U slučaju da pristup nije omogućen putem pravnih odredbi koje su na snazi u vrijeme sklapanja ugovora, natjecatelji ili ponuditelji iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine mogu biti odbijeni iz postupka javne nabave.</P><P>(1) Molimo navedite bilo kakve pojedinosti koje bi mogle utjecati na pravila sudjelovanja (poput geografskih ili tematskih ili dugoročnih/kratkoročnih).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Napomene:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Između objave ove prethodne informacijske obavijesti i objave odgovarajućeg poziva na nadmetanje mora proći najmanje 30 kalendarskih dana. U toj se fazi ne smiju slati prijave ili zahtjevi za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>