<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="196284-2018"
            EDITION="2018087">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-199687-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180605</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>87</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180505</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 087-196284</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:196284-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.tideway.london</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="70210000">Residential property renting or leasing services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKI">LONDON</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKI">LONDON</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180503</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180605 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="4">Negotiated procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="8">Other</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01G05</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/25/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Лондон</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги по даване под наем на собствени жилищни имоти</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londýn</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Pronájem nebo leasing obytných nemovitostí</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Udlejning eller leasing af egen fast ejendom til beboelse</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dienstleistungen der Vermietung oder Verpachtung von eigenen Wohnimmobilien</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Λονδίνο</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες ενοικίασης ή χρηματοδοτικής μίσθωσης ιδιόκτητων ακινήτων που προορίζονται για κατοίκηση</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Residential property renting or leasing services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londres</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de alquiler o arrendamiento financiero relativos a bienes raíces residenciales propios</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Eluruumi üürimis- või liisimisteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Lontoo</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Omien asuinkiinteistöjen vuokraus- ja leasingpalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londres</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de crédit-bail ou de location de propriétés résidentielles propres</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londain</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Residential property renting or leasing services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge davanja stambenih nekretninau najam ili zakup</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Lakóingatlannal kapcsolatos kölcsönzési vagy lízingszolgáltatás</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londra</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di affitto o locazione finanziaria di beni immobili residenziali propri</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londonas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Gyvenamojo nekilnojamojo turto nuomos ar lizingo paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londona</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Dzīvojamā fonda īpašuma izīrēšanas vai iznomāšanas pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londra</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi tal-kiri għal żmien qasir jew fit-tul bil-proprjetà attwali residenzali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londen</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Residential property renting or leasing services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londyn</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi wynajmu lub leasingu nieruchomości mieszkalnych</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londres</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de arrendamento ou locação de propriedades residenciais próprias</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londra</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de închiriere sau de leasing de proprietăţi rezidenţiale proprii</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Londýn</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Prenájom alebo lízing obytných nehnuteľností</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve dajanja stanovanjskih nepremičnin v najem ali zakup</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>London</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Uthyrning eller leasing av bostäder</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Bazalgette Tunnel Limited</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F05_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F05" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Bazalgette Tunnel Limited</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Cottons Centre, Cottons Lane</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>London</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>SE1 2QG</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 2039346058</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>Danesh.Sharma@Tideway.London</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKI"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.tideway.london</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://thamestidewaytunnel.bravosolution.co.uk</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_RESTRICTED/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://thamestidewaytunnel.bravosolution.co.uk</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://thamestidewaytunnel.bravosolution.co.uk</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CE_ACTIVITY_OTHER>Design, finance, construct and operate the Thames Tideway Tunnel</CE_ACTIVITY_OTHER>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Temporary Accommodation Sourcing Services</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="70210000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The successful Tenderer will be responsible for sourcing temporary accommodation for residents who may be impacted by Tideway works during the construction phase of the Thames Tideway Tunnel. The accommodation to be provided will be (predominantly) serviced apartments, located within approximately 3km of Tideway’s construction sites. Details of these sites are provided in the Pre-qualification Pack (PQP).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKI"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Services to be performed in relation to the Thames Tideway Tunnel under construction in London.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>The successful Tenderer will be responsible for sourcing temporary accommodation for residents who may be impacted by Tideway works during the construction phase of the Thames Tideway Tunnel. The accommodation to be provided will be (predominantly) serviced apartments, located within approximately 3km of Tideway’s construction sites. Details of these sites are provided in the Pre-Qualification Pack (PQP).</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">36</DURATION>
               <RENEWAL/>
               <RENEWAL_DESCR>
                  <P>Further 12 month extension at discretion of Tideway.</P>
               </RENEWAL_DESCR>
               <NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>5</NB_MAX_LIMIT_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>Applicants are referred to the PQP and Pre-Qualification Questionnaire (‘PQQ’) for information on Tideway's criteria for choosing Applicants to be invited to tender for this contract. Tideway expects to select only the top Five Applicants to tender for this contact, however Tideway reserves the right in its absolute discretion to invite to tender fewer or greater than Five on the basis described in the PQP.</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>Applicants should be aware that Tideway reserves the right to extend the term of this contract by a period of up 12 months, making a maximum aggregate contract period of 4 years.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <SUITABILITY>
               <P>Applicants are referred to the PQP and PQQ for information about conditions for participation.</P>
            </SUITABILITY>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <RULES_CRITERIA>
               <P>Applicants are referred to the PQP and PQQ for information about Tideway's objective rules and criteria for participation in the contract.</P>
            </RULES_CRITERIA>
            <DEPOSIT_GUARANTEE_REQUIRED>
               <P>Tideway reserves the right to require guarantees, bonds, collateral warranties (potentially including the grant of step-in rights) and other forms of security as appropriate to be specified in the Procurement Documents to be made available at ITT stage. Applicants are referred to the PQP for relevant information available at this Contract Notice stage.</P>
            </DEPOSIT_GUARANTEE_REQUIRED>
            <MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITION>
               <P>The main financing conditions, payment mechanism and performance standards will be described in the Procurement Documents to be made available at ITT stage.</P>
            </MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITION>
            <LEGAL_FORM>
               <P>Tideway will accept expressions of interest and tenders from single entities or Consortia. Tideway does not require those Consortia who intend to form a single legal entity to do so at the PQQ stage. Tideway will consider contracting with a Consortium, providing always that the participants in any Consortium are jointly and severally liable for all of the obligations of the Supplier under this contract.</P>
            </LEGAL_FORM>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_NEGOTIATED_WITH_PRIOR_CALL/>
            <REDUCTION_RECOURSE/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-06-05</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>12:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">24</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <EORDERING/>
            <EINVOICING/>
            <EPAYMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>1) Terms in this Contract notice with initial capital letters have the meanings given in PQP Section 1.2.4(Glossary).</P>
               <P>2) To express interest in this tender, Applicants must register and complete the PQQ on the Tideway portal: https://thamestidewaytunnel.bravosolution.co.uk by the deadline for PQQs stated in the PQP.The PQQ Deadline is a precise time and Applicants must allow sufficient time to upload the PQQ.</P>
               <P>3) Section I (Contracting entity): The contracting entity is Bazalgette Tunnel Limited (‘Tideway’), the organisation responsible for delivering the Thames Tideway Tunnel. Additional information relating to this Contract Notice is available in the Procurement Documents. Further information on Tideway and the Thames Tideway Tunnel is available at www.tideway.london</P>
               <P>4) Section II.2.7 (Duration of the contract: Timescales in this Contract Notice are estimated based on the current Tideway programme but may be subject to change.</P>
               <P>5) Section IV (Procedure): Tideway is not a utility for the purpose of the Utilities Contracts Regulations 2016 (‘UCR 2016’) and accordingly the UCR 2016 do not apply to this procurement. However Tideway is required pursuant to the procurement regime in The Water Industry (Specified Infrastructure Projects) (English Undertakers) Regulations 2013 (‘SIP Regulations’) to tender certain contracts and certain categories of contracts in accordance with a modified regime set out in the SIP Regulations as amended by The Public Procurement (Amendments, Repeals and Revocations) Regulations 2016 (‘modified UCR 2016’). The procurement requirements set out in the modified UCR 2016 are broadly similar to the UCR 2016 save that certain procedures, exclusions and exemptions have been removed and Part 5 of UCR 2016 (Remedies) has been modified so that a different remedies regime applies to Tideway. Additional information in relation to the modified UCR 2016 is available at: http://www.legislation.gov.uk/cy/uksi/2016/275/schedule/2/paragraph/48/made</P>
               <P>6) Section VI.4 (Procedures for review): In accordance with the modified UCR 2016 regime, Tideway will incorporate a minimum 10 calendar day standstill period before award from the point information on award is communicated to Tenderers. Any request for further information by Tenderers pursuant to the modified UCR 2016 regime must be made in writing to the address set out in section I.1 above. The modified UCR 2016 regime provides remedies for economic operators who, in consequence of a breach of the modified UCR 2016 regime, suffer, or risk suffering, loss or damage. Proceedings must be started in the High Court of England and Wales.</P>
               <P>7) A response to this Contract Notice does not guarantee that an Applicant will be invited to tender. The award process may be terminated or suspended at any time without cost or liability to Tideway. Tideway does not bind itself to enter into any contract(s) arising out of the procedure envisaged by this Contract notice. No contractual rights express or implied arise out of this Contract Notice or the procedures envisaged by it. Tideway reserves the right to vary its requirements and the procedure relating to the conduct of the award process. Tideway reserves the right to disqualify any Applicants on terms set out in the PQP.</P>
               <P>8) Applicants/Tenderers shall be solely responsible for and liable for all costs associated with and arising out of or in connection with responding to this Contract notice, any PQQ and with submitting any tender, howsoever incurred.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>High Court</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Royal Courts of Justice, Strand</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>London</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>WC2A 2LL</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 20794760000</PHONE>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_MEDIATION_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>High Court</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Royal Courts of Justice, Strand</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>London</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>WC2A 2LL</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <PHONE>+44 20794760000</PHONE>
            </ADDRESS_MEDIATION_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-05-03</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F05_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
