<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="127234-2018"
            EDITION="2018057">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-128870-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20190320</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>57</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180322</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 057-127234</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:127234-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="US"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>http://www.c40.org</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="90713000">Environmental issues consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="90712100">Urban environmental development planning</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71356000">Technical services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="90712000">Environmental planning</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71356200">Technical assistance services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71621000">Technical analysis or consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="73210000">Research consultancy services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="00">Not specified / Other</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="00">Not specified / Other</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">6000000.00</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180320</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="8">Other</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="9">Not applicable</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="Z">Not specified</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="9">Not applicable</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="E">Environment</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>08C01</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>08</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Съединени щати</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ню Йорк</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Консултантски услуги по проблемите на околната среда</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené státy/USA</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Poradenské služby související s otázkami životního prostředí</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Stater, De</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Rådgivning i forbindelse med miljøspørgsmål</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>die Vereinigten Staaten</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Beratung in Umweltfragen</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένες Πολιτείες</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Νέα Υόρκη</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών για περιβαλλοντικά ζητήματα</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United States</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Environmental issues consultancy services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Estados Unidos</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nueva York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de asesoramiento sobre asuntos ambientales</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Ameerika Ühendriigid</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Keskkonnaküsimuste nõuandeteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdysvallat</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Ympäristöasioiden neuvontapalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>États-Unis</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de conseils environnementaux</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Stáit Aontaithe, na</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nua-Eabhrac</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Environmental issues consultancy services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Sjedinjene Američke Države</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge savjetovanja u pitanjima okoliša</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Államok</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Környezetvédelmi tanácsadási szolgáltatások</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Stati Uniti</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nuova York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di consulenza per questioni ambientali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinės Valstijos</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Niujorkas</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Konsultacijų aplinkosaugos klausimais paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>ASV</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ņujorka</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Vides jautājumu konsultāciju pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>l-Istati Uniti</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' konsulenza dwar kwistjonijiet ambjentali</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigde Staten</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Adviesdiensten inzake milieuproblematiek</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Stany Zjednoczone</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nowy Jork</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi konsultacyjne w zakresie zagadnień dotyczących środowiska</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Estados Unidos</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Nova Iorque</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de consultoria sobre questões ambientais</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Statele Unite</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de consultanţă în probleme de mediu</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené štáty</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Konzultačné služby týkajúce sa otázok životného prostredia</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združene države</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve svetovanja na področju okoljskih vprašanj</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenta staterna</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>New York</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Miljörådgivning</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">C40 Cities Climate Leadership Group, Inc.</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F01_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F01" LG="EN">
         <NOTICE TYPE="PRI_ONLY"/>
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>C40 Cities Climate Leadership Group, Inc.</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>120 Park Avenue, 23rd Floor</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>New York</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>NY 10017</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="US"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Lisa Kim</CONTACT_POINT>
               <E_MAIL>lkim@c40.org</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="00"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>http://www.c40.org</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://c40.box.com/v/c40-ojeu-procurement</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE_OTHER>non-profit organisation (non-regulated)</CA_TYPE_OTHER>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="ENVIRONMENT"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT ITEM="1">
            <TITLE>
               <P>Climate Change Action Planning – Invitation to Participate in Early Market Engagement</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="90713000"/>
               <CPV_SUPPLEMENTARY_CODE CODE="QB52"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>C40 Cities Climate Leadership Group, Inc. (C40) is a non-profit organisation which supports international cities to collaborate effectively, share knowledge and drive sustainable action on climate change. C40 expects to receive funding support from both the UK government's Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy (BEIS) and the Danish government's Ministry of Foreign Affairs, which will be used to fund the delivery of climate action plans in 15-20 cities located across South America and South East Asia (including but not limited to: Indonesia, Vietnam, Malaysia, Thailand and Philippines).</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">6000000.00</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="90712100"/>
                  <CPV_SUPPLEMENTARY_CODE CODE="QB52"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="71356000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="90712000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="71356200"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="71621000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="73210000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="00"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>South America and South East Asia.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>Through one or more procurement processes, C40 intends to procure high-quality consultancy services to deliver some or all of the following work streams in each city:</P>
                  <P>1. Climate action planning strategic review to determine the extent to which a city’s current and/or planned climate targets, policies, plans and programmes are consistent with the goals of the Paris Agreement;</P>
                  <P>2. Climate action planning workshops to include in-city workshops and regional academies to build capacity, facilitate discussions and enable peer-to-peer interaction and learning;</P>
                  <P>3. GHG emissions analysis to include GHG emissions inventory development and GHG emissions scenario modelling;</P>
                  <P>4. Climate risk assessment to include identification and assessment of current and future climate hazards, and interdependencies analysis;</P>
                  <P>5. Climate action and plan development to support development of an evidence-based, inclusive and deliverable climate action plan for achieving mitigation and adaptation consistent with the goals of the Paris Agreement;</P>
                  <P>6. Benefits and inclusivity assessment to ensure climate action plan addresses all segments of the population in cities; and achieve wider and equitably distributed benefits of climate action; and</P>
                  <P>7. Review of climate action plan against C40’s Climate Action Planning Framework;</P>
                  <P>C40 will be looking for consultants with a regional presence and experience to ensure local knowledge, and specialist consultancies or organisations to support with the more technical work streams.</P>
                  <P>C40 anticipates a need for the climate action plans to be finalised by 2020 and hopes to finalise the contracts during the second half of 2018.</P>
                  <P>The proposed procurement and delivery strategy is to structure the requirement, and the future competition into multiple lots, which will broadly be arranged according to region, language and origin of funding. Due to capacity concerns in meeting the tight deadlines, C40 envisages that some restrictions may be placed on the number of lots that one bidder can win.</P>
                  <P>Further information about this project can be found here: https://c40.box.com/v/c40-ojeu-procurement</P>
                  <P>C40 wishes to undertake early market engagement to provide further information on its likely requirements and seek feedback from the market on its proposed procurement and delivery strategy. It will therefore host 2 Supplier Market Engagement Sessions on 16.4.2018 between 9:00 and 11:00 BST, and between 15:00 and 17:00 BST at Bird and Bird LLP, 12 New Fetter Lane, London, EC4A 1JP. The sessions are intended to be identical and it is therefore not necessary for interested parties to attend both. Those outside the UK are very welcome and actively encouraged to attend via conference call. Dial-in details will be circulated shortly before the engagement day to all those who register their interest in accordance with the procedure set out below. The early market engagement will provide suppliers with an insight into C40's proposed procurement strategy, the timescales associated with the procurement and the contract as well as to invite feedback from the market on C40's current plans. C40 will use the feedback to further validate its procurement and delivery strategy.</P>
                  <P>C40 is not subject to the public procurement rules in the UK, Denmark or elsewhere and is voluntarily advertising this opportunity in the Official Journal. However, in accordance with the terms of its grant agreements, C40 intends to run an open, fair and transparent process in order to appoint consultants with a local presence in the relevant cities to deliver the work streams (in partnership with specialist consultancies or organisations to support with the more technical work streams where necessary).</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>At this stage, the estimated value of the opportunity is approximately 6 000 000 GBP. However, C40 reserves the right to revisit this figure in due course and will confirm the final estimated value at the point a contract notice is published.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>2018-04-30</DATE_PUBLICATION_NOTICE>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>Suppliers that are interested in participating in a Supplier Early Market Engagement Session are invited to register their interest via email to Lisa Kim, lkim@c40.org, responding no later than midday on 11.4.2018.</P>
               <P>Suppliers should provide their full company name, company registration number and key contact details accompanied by a short description (no more than 100 words) of their company’s capabilities in regards to the proposed work streams. This will be used by C40 for early market engagement planning purposes and will not bind suppliers going forward.</P>
               <P>C40 will manage this early market engagement process in an open and transparent manner to maximise the possible benefits, and in particular C40 will share the key outputs of all early market engagement activities, including to those who have not attended the Supplier Early Market Engagement Sessions. Participation (or non-participation) in these early market engagement activities will not preclude or disadvantage/advantage any suppliers’ ability to participate in any future procurement activity.</P>
               <P>The publication of this PIN is to commence early market engagement and is not a call for competition, nor does it bind C40 to starting a competition.</P>
               <P>Suppliers should note that the date given in the "Estimated date of publication of contract notice" is purely an estimate.</P>
               <P>C40 reserves the right to make any changes to the procurement as it may require at any time with no liability on its part (including to change, suspend, stop or terminate the process and not award a contract and/or to reject any or all bids at any time).</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-20</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F01_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
