<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="088822-2018" EDITION="2018041"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-085746-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180405</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>41</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180228</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 041-088822</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088822-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="HR"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="48810000">Information systems</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180222</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180405 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="Z">Not specified</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>BR505</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Kroatien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - Indkøb af informationssystem til energiforvaltning (EMIS, Energy Management Information System)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Kroatien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - Beschaffung des Energiemanagementinformationssystems (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Croatia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Croacia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Contratación del sistema de información para la gestión de la energía</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Kroatia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Energianhallinnan tietojärjestelmän (energy management information system, EMIS) hankinta</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Croatie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Approvisionnement du système d’information de gestion électrique (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Κροατία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - Προμήθεια του Συστήματος Διαχείρισης Πληροφοριών για την Ενέργεια (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Croazia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - Acquisto del Sistema informativo per la gestione energetica (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Kroatië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - Aankoop van het informatiesysteem voor energiebeheer (EMIS - Energy Management Information System)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Croácia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Aprovisionamento do Sistema de Informação de Gestão de Energia (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Kroatien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Upphandling av Energistyrningsinformationssystemet (Energy Management Information System - EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Chorvatsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Zajištění informačního systému pro řízení energie (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Horvaatia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Energiaseire infosüsteemi (Energy Management Information System (EMIS)) hange</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Horvátország</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Energiagazdálkodási információs rendszer (EMIS) beszerzése</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Kroatija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - Energijos valdymo informacijos sistemos (Energy Management Information System – EMIS) pirkimas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Horvātija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - Energopārvaldības informācijas sistēmas (EMIS) iepirkums</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Kroazja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - Il-ksib tas-Sistema ta' Tagħrif dwar l-Immaniġġjar tal-Enerġija (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Chorwacja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Dostawa systemu informacji dotyczących zarządzania energią</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Chorvátsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Obstaranie informačného systému hospodárenia s energiou (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Hrvaška</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Nabava informacijskega sistema za upravljanje z energijo (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Chróit, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Soláthar Córais Faisnéise um Bainistiú Fuinnimh (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Хърватска</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - Обществена поръчка за Информационна система за управление на енергетиката (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Croaţia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Achiziția Sistemului informatic de management al energiei (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Hrvatska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Nabava Informacijskog sustava za gospodarenje energijom (EMIS)</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">HŽ Infrastruktura doo</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - Indkøb af informationssystem til energiforvaltning (EMIS, Energy Management Information System) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - Beschaffung des Energiemanagementinformationssystems (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Contratación del sistema de información para la gestión de la energía (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Energianhallinnan tietojärjestelmän (energy management information system, EMIS) hankinta (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Approvisionnement du système d’information de gestion électrique (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - Προμήθεια του Συστήματος Διαχείρισης Πληροφοριών για την Ενέργεια (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - Acquisto del Sistema informativo per la gestione energetica (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - Aankoop van het informatiesysteem voor energiebeheer (EMIS - Energy Management Information System) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Aprovisionamento do Sistema de Informação de Gestão de Energia (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Upphandling av Energistyrningsinformationssystemet (Energy Management Information System - EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Zajištění informačního systému pro řízení energie (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Energiaseire infosüsteemi (Energy Management Information System (EMIS)) hange (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Energiagazdálkodási információs rendszer (EMIS) beszerzése (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - Energijos valdymo informacijos sistemos (Energy Management Information System – EMIS) pirkimas (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - Energopārvaldības informācijas sistēmas (EMIS) iepirkums (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - Il-ksib tas-Sistema ta' Tagħrif dwar l-Immaniġġjar tal-Enerġija (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Dostawa systemu informacji dotyczących zarządzania energią (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Obstaranie informačného systému hospodárenia s energiou (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Nabava informacijskega sistema za upravljanje z energijo (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Soláthar Córais Faisnéise um Bainistiú Fuinnimh (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - Обществена поръчка за Информационна система за управление на енергетиката (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Achiziția Sistemului informatic de management al energiei (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Nabava Informacijskog sustava za gospodarenje energijom (EMIS) (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8.1.2018</P><P>Closing date: 5.4.2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This Invitation for Tenders follows the General Procurement Notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22.7.2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26.1.2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS):</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS — Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE- Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of meters in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new meters or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the Bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1. a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 years to demonstrate the current soundness of the Tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long term profitability.</P><P>b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1 250 000 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2. The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(i) the following cash-flow requirement: 800 000 EUR; and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3. Experience as supplier, in at least 3 contracts within the last 5 years each with a value of at least 150 000 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, meter reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4. Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5. The tenderer shall submit with its tender the Manufacturer’s Authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6. The tenderer shall submit with its tender an Excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the abovementioned elements. The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorized to sign the tender:</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account nº HR7624020061500030910 Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank dd, Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift nº of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura doo</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00, starting from 8.1.2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a Tender Security. The Tender Security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000 EUR. Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before: 5.4.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura doo</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd floor, room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, CROATIA.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>