<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="088937-2018"
            EDITION="2018041">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-092358-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180417</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>41</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180228</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 041-088937</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:088937-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/2d4571e1-a1e3-456e-8ae1-ac604238d128/homepage</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/2d4571e1-a1e3-456e-8ae1-ac604238d128/publicMaterial</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="34963000">Instrument Landing System (ILS)</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="DK0">DANMARK</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="DK0">DANMARK</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="DKK">10000000</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180227</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180417 13:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01A02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Дaния</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Система за приземяване по прибори (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Systém pro přesné přiblížení a přistání (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Instrumentlandingssystem (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Dänemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Instrumentenlandesystem (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Δανία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Σύστημα ενόργανης προσγείωσης (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Denmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Instrument Landing System (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sistema de aterrizaje por instrumentos (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Taani</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Instrumentaalmaandumise süsteem (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Tanska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Mittarilaskeutumisjärjestelmä (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Danemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Système d'atterrissage aux instruments (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Danmhairg, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Instrument Landing System (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sustav za instrumentalno slijetanje (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Dánia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Műszeres leszállító rendszer (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Danimarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sistema di atterraggio strumentale (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Danija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tūpimo pagal prietaisus sistema (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Dānija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Instrumentālā nosēšanās sistēma (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>id-Danimarka</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sistema għall-inżul ta' l-ajruplani (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Denemarken</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Instrument Landing System (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Dania</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>System lądowania według przyrządów (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sistema de Aterragem por Instrumentos (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Danemarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Sistem de aterizare cu instrumente (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Presný pristávací rádiový systém (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Instrumentni pristajalni sistem (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Instrumentlandningssystem (ILS)</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Danish Defence Acquisition and Logistics Organizations</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Danish Defence Acquisition and Logistics Organizations</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>16-28-71-80</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>Lautrupbjerg 1-5</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Ballerup</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2750</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Denise Katarina Kirkeskov Jensen</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+45 72814272</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>fmi-ja-s112@mil.dk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK0"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/2d4571e1-a1e3-456e-8ae1-ac604238d128/homepage</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/2d4571e1-a1e3-456e-8ae1-ac604238d128/publicMaterial</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/2d4571e1-a1e3-456e-8ae1-ac604238d128/homepage</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <URL_TOOL>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/2d4571e1-a1e3-456e-8ae1-ac604238d128/homepage</URL_TOOL>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="MINISTRY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>Instrument Landing System</P>
            </TITLE>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="34963000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>The Danish Defence Acquisition and Logistics Organisation (DALO) wishes to replace the existing Instrument Landing Systems at Airbase Karup / Midtjylland airport (EKKA) with two new Instrument Landing Systems. The existing Instrument Landing Systems – runway (RWY) 27L (CAT II) and RWY 09R (CAT I) were installed and commissioned in about 1977/87. This purchase concerns the replace of these 2 Instrument Landing Systems. All other prerequisites for existing CAT II and CAT I operations will be retained.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="DKK">10000000</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK0"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Airbase Karup / Midtjylland airport.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>See description in section II.1.4.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">16</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>It shall be possible as an option for DALO to acquire training activities for DALO technical personnel (up to 8 participants) in order to give the participants the theoretical knowledge of the Instrument Landing System. The Option shall be valid until 12 months after signing the Contract.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>DALO has decided not to divide the Contract into lots due to the limited number of Instrument Landing Systems.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>The tenderer must use the European Single Procurement Document (electronic version, hereafter ESPD) and provide the following information in the ESPD:</P>
               <P>A list of the most important similar deliveries (references), cf. minimum level(s) of standards possibly required and section II.1.4) and II.2.4), carried out within the past 3 years, prior to the deadline for the submission of the offer, cf. Part IV, section C.</P>
               <P>The list should preferably include a short description of each delivery. The description should include a clear indication of which specific parts of the deliveries that are similar to the supplies as described in section II.1.4) and II.2.4). The description should also include a description of the tenderers participation/role in the performance of the deliveries. The description should contain information on the date of the deliveries, the size and value of the deliveries, the recipients of the deliveries (specific names/countries are preferred, but not necessary; if no country specific information is included, the tenderer is asked to provide as much generic information as possible about the delivery). When specifying the date for the deliveries, the tenderer should state the date of commencement and completion. If this is not possible, e.g. because the delivery in question is performed on an ongoing basis according to a framework agreement, the description of the deliveries should nonetheless contain information on how the date is set.</P>
               <P>Only the deliveries (references) performed at the time of the deadline for submission of the offer will be considered when assessing if the minimum requirement for suitability stated below is fulfilled. If the delivery in question is ongoing, it is only the part of the supplies performed and completed at the time of the deadline for the request to submission of the offer which will be included in the assessment of the delivery.</P>
               <P>A tenderer may rely on the technical and professional capacity of other entities (e.g. a parent or sister company or a sub supplier), irrespective of the legal nature of the relations between the tenderer and the entity or entities on which the tenderer relies. In this case, the tenderer shall ensure that an ESPD from the entity or entities on which the tenderer relies is submitted along with the tenderers own ESPD. The entity or entities’ ESPD must equally provide the information listed above.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
               <P>The tenderer must demonstrate experience with as a minimum 1 similar delivery within the past 3 years, prior to the deadline for the submission of the offer. By similar delivery means: a Instrument Landing System that are installed in other EU Countries, a Instrument Landing System that have been approved by the Civil Aviation Authority (CAA) in at least one of these countries, a Instrument Landing System that have accumulated data from similar installations in Europe regarding Mean Time between Failure (MTBF), so the MTBF &gt;= 50.000 hours.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_MIN_LEVEL>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>If prepayments are made, an on-demand guarantee from a recognized financial institution must be presented. The financial institution has to be approved by DALO.</P>
               <P>Note payment terms in the contract. Invoicing must be done in accordance with the applicable Danish legislation on public payments. Exact terms are stated in the contract.</P>
               <P>No particular legal form is required. If the contract is awarded to a group of suppliers (e.g. a consortium), the participants shall undertake joint and several liabilities and to appoint one supplier to represent the group. The contract must be conducted in consideration of social responsibility (CSR) and it contains a labour clause, see clause 4.11 in the Contract for further information. DALO demands that any person taking part in the performance of the contract must possess the appropriate personnel security clearance at the level required by DALO. The security clearance must be maintained throughout the term of the contract. See Annex I for details.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-04-17</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>13:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">12</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-04-17</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>13:00</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>DALO demands that the tenderer and each of the legal entities whose capacities the tenderer relies on undertake joint and several liability for the performance of the contract.</P>
               <P>The use of the ESPD is a precondition for participation in the procurement procedure, cf. § 148 of the Public Procurement Act. DALO shall require that the tenderer apply the ESPD as preliminary evidence that the tenderer is not subject to the grounds of exclusion stipulated in §§ 135 and 136 of the said Act, that the tenderer fulfils the minimum requirements for suitability fixed in accordance with § 140, cf. III.1.3), and how the candidate fulfils the objective and non-discriminatory criteria of selection, cf. § 145(2), cf. section II.2.9).</P>
               <P>The tenderers and, if relevant, the participants in the group of entities and/or supporting entities, must use the electronic version of the ESPD. DALO has prepared an ESPD (an XML-file) available at ETHICS. DALO strongly encourages the tenderer to use this XML-file when completing the ESPD. The tenderer must upload the XML-file to this website https://ec.europa.eu/growth/tools-databases/espd/welcome where the ESPD can be completed and later exported. No other versions than the EPSD must be used.</P>
               <P>Prior to decision on award of the contract, DALO shall require that the tenderer to whom DALO intends to award the contract presents documentation for the information stated in the ESPD, cf. §§ 151-155 of the said Act. If a tenderer relies on the capacity of other entities, cf. section III.1.2 and III.1.3, the tenderer shall upon request provide statements of support or other documentation proving that the tenderer has access to the necessary technical and professional capacity, and that the entity referred to has a legal obligation to the tenderer. If such documentation is not provided, DALO cannot consider the technical and professional capacity of the other entity or entities. DALO has prepared a template to be used to confirm the legal obligation which is available at ETHICS. DALO strongly encourages the tenderers to use this form. However, it is emphasized that it is the sole responsibility of the tenderer that the information provided fulfils the requirements.</P>
               <P>DALO shall exclude a tenderer from participation in the procurement procedure, if the tenderer is subject to one of the compulsory grounds for exclusion in §§ 135 and 136 of the said Act unless the tenderer has provided sufficient documentation that the tenderer is reliable in accordance to § 138 of the said Act. Please note that certain voluntary exclusion grounds in Directive 2014/24/EU on public procurement have been made compulsory in § 136 of the said Act.</P>
               <P>For further information regarding this procurement, please see the enclosed document "Additional information to Contract Notice".</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Klagenævnet for udbud</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Toldboden 2</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Viborg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>8800</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 72405708</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>klfu@naevneneshus.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>https://erhvervsstyrelsen.dk/klagenaevnet-for-udbud</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Pursuant to Section 3 of the Danish Consolidation Act nº 593 of 2.6.016 on the Complaints Board for Public Procurement (available at www.retsinformation.dk), the following time limits for filing a complaint apply:</P>
               <P>Complaints regarding public procurements and decisions subject to Chapter II or III of the Public Procurement Act, which does not concern a candidate not being invited to tender, must in accordance with § 7(2) of the Act on The Complaints Board for Public Procurement be filed with The Complaints Board for Public Procurement within:</P>
               <P>1) 45 calendar days after the contracting authority has published a contract award notice in the Official Journal of the European Union (with effect from the day following the publication date),</P>
               <P>2) 30 calendar days starting the day after the contracting authority has informed the tenderers in question, that the contracting authority has entered into a contract based on a framework agreement through reopening of competition or a dynamic purchasing system, provided that the notification includes a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision,</P>
               <P>3) 6 months starting the day after the contracting authority has sent notification to the candidates/tenderers involved that the contracting authority has entered into the framework agreement, cf. § 2(2) or § 171(4) of the Public Procurement Act, provided that the notification included a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision,</P>
               <P>4) 20 calendar days starting the day after the contracting authority has published a notice concerning his decision to uphold the contract, cf. § 185(2) of the Public Procurement Act.</P>
               <P>The complainant must inform the contracting authority of the complaint in writing at the latest simultaneously with the lodge of the complaint to The Complaints Board for Public Procurement stating whether the complaint has been lodged in the stand-still period, cf. § 6(4) of the Act on The Complaints Board for Public Procurement. If the complaint has not been lodged in the stand-still period, the complainant must also state whether it is requested that the appeal is granted delaying effect, cf. § 12(1) of the said Act.</P>
               <P>The e-mail of The Complaints Board for Public Procurement is stated in section VI.4.1.</P>
               <P>The Complaints Board for Public Procurement’s own guidance note concerning complaints is available at the internet address stated in section VI.4.1.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Konkurrence- og Forbrugerstyrelsen</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Carl Jacobsens Vej 35</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Valby</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2500</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 41715000</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>kfst@kfst.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>www.kfst.dk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-02-27</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
