<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="111963-2018" EDITION="2018050"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-112671-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180409</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>50</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180313</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 050-111963</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:111963-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/875e8908-83f4-4353-9ea7-ec394f5b259a/homepage</IA_URL_GENERAL><IA_URL_ETENDERING>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/875e8908-83f4-4353-9ea7-ec394f5b259a/homepage</IA_URL_ETENDERING><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="35000000">Security, fire-fighting, police and defence equipment</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="35513400">Auxiliary hospital; cargo; tanker; ro-ro vessel</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="34512700">Ro-Ro vessels</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="34512600">Container carriers</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="34512500">Goods vessels</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="34512400">Cargo ships</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="34512200">Cruise ships</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="34512100">Ferry boats</ORIGINAL_CPV><VALUES_LIST><VALUES TYPE="GLOBAL"><RANGE_VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="EUR">10 000 000</VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="EUR">30 000 000</VALUE></RANGE_VALUE></VALUES><VALUES TYPE="GLOBAL"><RANGE_VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="EUR">10 000 000</VALUE><VALUE CURRENCY="EUR">30 000 000</VALUE></RANGE_VALUE></VALUES></VALUES_LIST></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180309</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180409 13:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="4">Negotiated procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>01317</HEADING><DIRECTIVE VALUE="2009/81/EC"/></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Дaния</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Оборудване за безопасност, противопожарно, полицейско и отбранително оборудване</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bezpečnostní, hasičské, policejní a ochranné vybavení</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Sikkerheds-, brandbekæmpelses, politi- og forsvarsudstyr</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Dänemark</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ausrüstung für Sicherheitszwecke, Brandbekämpfung, Polizei und Verteidigung</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Δανία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Εξοπλισμός ασφαλείας και πυρόσβεσης, αστυνομικός και αμυντικός εξοπλισμός</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Denmark</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Security, fire-fighting, police and defence equipment</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Equipo de seguridad, extinción de incendios, policía y defensa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Taani</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Turva-, tuletõrje-, politsei- ja kaitseseadmed</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Tanska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Turva-, palontorjunta-, poliisi- ja maanpuolustusvälineet</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Danemark</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Équipement de sécurité, de lutte contre l'incendie, de police et de défense</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Danmhairg, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Security, fire-fighting, police and defence equipment</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Sigurnosna, vatrogasna policijska i obrambena oprema</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Dánia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Biztonsági, tűzoltó, rendőrségi és védelmi felszerelések</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Danimarca</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Attrezzature di sicurezza, antincendio, per la polizia e di difesa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Danija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Apsaugos, gaisrų gesinimo, policijos ir gynybos įrenginiai</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Dānija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Drošības, ugunsdzēsības, policijas un aizsardzības aprīkojums</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>id-Danimarka</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Tagħmir għas-sigurtà, tifi tan-nar, pulizija u difiża</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Denemarken</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Uitrusting voor veiligheid, brandweer, politie en leger</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Dania</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Sprzęt bezpieczeństwa, gaśniczy, policyjny i obronny</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Equipamento de segurança, combate a incêndios, polícia e defesa</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Danemarca</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Echipament de securitate, de luptă împotriva incendiilor, de poliţie şi de apărare</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bezpečnostné, hasičské, policajné a ochranné vybavenie</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Varnostna, gasilska, policijska in obrambna oprema</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Ballerup</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Säkerhets-, brandbekämpnings-, polis- och försvarsutrustning</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Danish Defence Acquisition and Logistics Organizations</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><CONTRACT_DEFENCE CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="17" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE CTYPE="SERVICES"><CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Danish Defence Acquisition and Logistics Organizations</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Lautrupbjerg 1-5</ADDRESS><TOWN>Ballerup</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>2750</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/><CONTACT_POINT>Martin Porsborg-Smith</CONTACT_POINT><PHONE>+45 41740616</PHONE></CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><URL_GENERAL>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/875e8908-83f4-4353-9ea7-ec394f5b259a/homepage</URL_GENERAL><URL_INFORMATION>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/875e8908-83f4-4353-9ea7-ec394f5b259a/homepage</URL_INFORMATION><URL_PARTICIPATE>https://www.ethics.dk/ethics/eo#/875e8908-83f4-4353-9ea7-ec394f5b259a/homepage</URL_PARTICIPATE></INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><FURTHER_INFORMATION><IDEM/></FURTHER_INFORMATION><SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><IDEM/></SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO><IDEM/></TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO></NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY VALUE="MINISTRY"/><TYPE_OF_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF_NO/></PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_OR_CONTRACTING_ENTITY_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><TITLE_CONTRACT><P>Framework Agreement for Chartering of Vessels</P></TITLE_CONTRACT><TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><TYPE_CONTRACT VALUE="SERVICES"/><SERVICE_CATEGORY_DEFENCE>9</SERVICE_CATEGORY_DEFENCE></TYPE_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><NOTICE_INVOLVES_DEFENCE VALUE="ESTABLISHMENT_FRAMEWORK_AGREEMENT"/><F17_FRAMEWORK><SEVERAL_OPERATORS/><DURATION_FRAMEWORK_YEAR>3</DURATION_FRAMEWORK_YEAR><TOTAL_ESTIMATED><COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY CURRENCY="EUR"><RANGE_VALUE_COST><LOW_VALUE FMTVAL="10000000">10 000 000</LOW_VALUE><HIGH_VALUE FMTVAL="30000000">30 000 000</HIGH_VALUE></RANGE_VALUE_COST></COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY></TOTAL_ESTIMATED></F17_FRAMEWORK><SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><P>Danish Defence and Logistics Organization (DALO) is putting the acquisition of a Framework Agreement for Chartering of Vessels up for tender.</P><P>DALO is in charge of entering a framework agreement that meets the Danish Defence's requirements for additional access to international strategic sealift. The Danish Defence has had its own ARK cooperation that possesses access to strategic sealift since 2003. Since 2006 the Danish Defence has been part of the Danish-German ARK project. The access to Strategic Sealift involves RORO's (Roll On, Roll Off) with special ARK features at time charter.</P><P>The Ark cooperation involves close coordination with Movement Coordination Centre Eindhoven (MCCE) and 27 others nations who have ratified the cooperation.</P><P>The objective of this framework agreement is to improve the ARK projects access to additional sea lift capacities including swift access to the civilian shipping market for chartering of primarily additional RORO vessels and occasionally other specific vessels and sea based platforms.</P><P>The framework agreement is intended to improve the access vessels for transportation of varying cargo in terms of items, size and shapes. This includes but is not limited to transportation for both national and international military purposes and support of the need for transportation of military equipment and other commodities for sustainment or in support of own and allied military operations, missions, training exercises, humanitarian disaster relief situations, routine transports and others tasks such as the use of sea based platforms for various tasks.</P><P>The chartering method will primarily be based on "Time Charter" or "Voyage Charter". Secondary chartering methods will be "Trip Time Charter", "Contract of Affreightment" and "Bareboat Charter".</P><P>The Danish Defence wants to establish a cooperation of ship brokers (contractors) with experience within the civilian RORO market including experience with chartering of RORO vessels. Hence, the contractor must be able to source and provide sealift options on request, as well as arrangement of charter agreements primarily within the RORO segment supplemented with the contractors staff's ability to support chartering of other types of vessels (e.g. ROPAX (Roll on/Roll of Passenger), Ferry, MPV (Multi Purpose Vessel), PCTC (Pure Car and Truck Carrier), CONT (Container Ship), Heavy lift, Supply vessel and tankers)).</P><P>The typical duration of Time Charters varies between 1 week and 7 months. This however, shall not exclude the possibility to arrange shorter or longer charter periods and for some occasions more vessels will be chartered for the same event.</P><P>The Danish Defence expect that the geographical area of operating will be within the European continent-area but can also be extended to world wide operations.</P><P>Features which will be made mandatory through the tendering process:</P><P>— The Contractor shall be able to act as a ship broker providing RORO vessels at Time Charter and Voyage Charter.</P><P>— The Contractor shall be accessible 24/7/365 (via switch-board).</P><P>— The Contractor shall be able to provide vessels flagged in NATO and EU countries.</P><P>— The Contractor shall have at least two employees with operational responsibility capable of conducting charter agreements.</P><P>— The Contractor shall have an office in NATO and/or EU countries.</P><P>— The Contractors key workers of the Framework Agreement shall be able to obtain security clearance within 7 months after commencement of the framework agreement.</P><P>Important features for the chartering contractor:</P><P>— Regularly issue of RORO reports describing the shipping market for RORO vessels. The reports preferably contain information regarding the actual number of RORO's and other vessels types (e.g. ROPAX or MPP), the definition of the vessel type, the composition by age and the size of the vessels, the charter rates, bunker prices and an assessment of the future development within these categories including scrapping of vessels and new buildings entering the market. The reports also preferably contain regular updates on fixtures of RORO's and other vessel types, sales and scrapping of vessels primarily within the RORO segment.</P><P>— Experience with maritime transport of military cargo including sailing in risk areas (war areas).</P><P>The framework agreement will have a duration of 3 years and there will be 4 options with renewal of 1 year.</P><P>DALO will enter into a parallel framework agreement with up to 5 (five) Tenderers. After DALO has awarded the tender to up to 5 Tenderers, DALO will initiate mini-competitions as the award model during the entire duration of the framework agreement.</P></SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><CPV><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="35000000"/></CPV_MAIN><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="35513400"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="34512700"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="34512600"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="34512500"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="34512400"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="34512200"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_ADDITIONAL><CPV_CODE CODE="34512100"/></CPV_ADDITIONAL></CPV><SUBCONTRACTING><INDICATE_ANY_SHARE VALUE="NO"/><INDICATE_ANY_CHANGE VALUE="NO"/><SUBCONTRACT_AWARD_PART VALUE="NO"/><IDENTIFY_SUBCONTRACT VALUE="NO"/></SUBCONTRACTING><F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><DIV_INTO_LOT_NO/></F17_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><ACCEPTED_VARIANTS VALUE="NO"/></DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><QUANTITY_SCOPE><NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY CURRENCY="EUR"><RANGE_VALUE_COST><LOW_VALUE FMTVAL="10000000">10 000 000</LOW_VALUE><HIGH_VALUE FMTVAL="30000000">30 000 000</HIGH_VALUE></RANGE_VALUE_COST></COSTS_RANGE_AND_CURRENCY></NATURE_QUANTITY_SCOPE><OPTIONS><OPTION_DESCRIPTION><P>The framework agreement may be extended with up to 1 year 4 times (i.e. to a maximum of 7 years in total), cf. II.2.3) below.</P></OPTION_DESCRIPTION></OPTIONS><RECURRENT_CONTRACT><NUMBER_POSSIBLE_RENEWALS>4</NUMBER_POSSIBLE_RENEWALS></RECURRENT_CONTRACT></QUANTITY_SCOPE></OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION_DEFENCE><LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><P>Reference is made to the tender documents regarding payment terms. Invoicing must be done in accordance with the applicable Danish legislation on public payments. At present, this is Danish consolidation act. nº 798 of June 2007 which requires invoicing to be done electronically. Exact terms will be stated in the framework agreement.</P></MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITIONS><LEGAL_FORM><P>No particular legal form is required. If the framework agreement is awarded to a group of suppliers (e.g. a consortium), the participants are required to undertake joint and several liabilities and to appoint one supplier to represent the group.</P></LEGAL_FORM><EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS><P>The framework agreement must be conducted in consideration of corporate social responsibility and it contains a labour clause.</P></EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS></CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><P>When submitting the offers (but not the request for participation), the tenderers must submit a solemn declaration stating to which degree the tenderer has unpaid overdue debt in relation to tax, duties or social security contributions under Danish law or under the law of the country in which the tenderer is established. A template for the declaration will be provided with the tender documents, and the tenderer is encouraged — but not obliged — to use it.</P><P>Be advised, that DALO shall exclude a tenderer which has unpaid overdue debt of 100 000 DKK  or more to public authorities in relation to tax, duties or social security contributions under Danish law or under the law of the country in which the tenderer is established.</P><P>However, DALO may not exclude a tenderer which has provided sufficient documentation that the tenderer is reliable. DALO will decide whether the documentation is sufficient, hence the tenderer is considered reliable, based on the guidelines equal to the guidelines provided for in Section 138(1-4) of the Danish Act nº 1564 of 15.12.2015 — The Public Procurement Act.</P></ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>Annual reports or excerpts hereof or other documentation stating the candidate's equity ratio (calculated by dividing the candidate’s equity with the candidate’s total assets (equity/total assets x 100) at the end of the last 3 financial years, to the extent such information is available.</P></EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><EAF_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL><P>The candidate must have had a positive equity ratio for each of the last 3 financial years. The equity ratio is calculated by dividing the candidate's equity with the candidate's total assets (equity/total assets x 100).</P><P>If the candidate is composed of a group of entities (e.g. consortium), including temporary joint ventures, the equity ratio is calculated by dividing the sum of all the participants’ equities with the sum of all the participants’ total assets (sum of equity/sum of total assets x 100) in each of the last 3 financial years available.</P><P>If the candidate relies on the economic and financial standing of an entity or entities, the equity ratio is calculated by dividing the sum of the candidate’s and the entity or entities’ equity with the sum of the candidate’s and the entity or entities’ total assets (sum of equity/sum of total assets x 100) in each of the last 3 financial years available.</P><P>Please note that a candidate may rely on the economic and financial standing of other entities (e.g. a parent or sister company or a sub supplier), irrespective of the legal nature of the relations between the candidate and the entity or entities on which the candidate relies.</P></EAF_CAPACITY_MIN_LEVEL></F17_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI><T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>The tenderer should include 2 lists (A and B) for their application:</P><P>A:</P><P>A list of the most important similar deliveries (references), cf. Section II.1.5, carried out within the past 10 (ten) years prior to the deadline for the request to participate.</P><P>Similar deliveries: Chartering tasks (preferably with RORO vessels).</P><P>Only the deliveries (references) performed at the time of the deadline for the request to participate will be considered when assessing which candidate has documented the most relevant previous deliveries, cf. Section IV.1.2). If the delivery in question is ongoing, it is only the part of the services performed and completed at the time of the deadline for the request to participate which will be included in the assessment of the delivery(reference).</P><P>The list should preferably include a short description of each delivery. The description of the deliveries should include a clear indication of which specific parts the deliveries are similar to the services, described in Section II.1.5. The description should also include a description of the candidates participation/role in the performance of the deliveries. The description should also contain information on the date of the deliveries, the size and value of the deliveries, the recipients of the deliveries (specific names/countries are preferred, but not necessary; if details are commercial confidential or if no country specific information is included, the candidate is asked to provide as much generic information as possible about the delivery). When specifying the date for the deliveries, the candidate should state the date for the commencement and completion of the deliveries. If this is not possible, e.g. because the delivery in questions performed on an ongoing basis according to a framework agreement, the description of the deliveries should nonetheless contain information on how the date is set.</P><P>The list must contain a maximum of 5 previous deliveries, whether the candidate is one entity, composed of a group of entities (e.g. consortium), including temporary joint ventures, or relies on the technical and professional capacity of other entities. If the list contains more than 5, DALO will only consider the first 5 deliveries on the list. Deliveries beyond that will be disregarded.</P><P>Please note that a candidate may rely on the technical and professional capacity of other entities (e.g. a parent or sister company or a sub supplier), irrespective of the legal nature of the relations between the candidate and the entity or entities on which the candidate relies.</P><P>B:</P><P>A list of the most important publications of RORO reports describing the shipping market for RORO vessels, cf. Section II.1.5.</P><P>The list should preferably include a short description of the produced RORO reports including the language used, frequency (weekly, monthly or annually) and an overall description of the content i.e. a description of the RORO market situation as well other vessel capacities (e.g ROPAX or MPP), the definition of the vessel type, the composition by age and the size of the vessels, the charter rates, bunker prices and an assessment of the future development within these categories including scrapping of vessels and new buildings entering the market. The list should also preferably include whether the reports contain regular updates on fixtures of RORO's and other vessel types, sales and scrapping of vessels primarily within the RORO segment.</P><P>When stating the list, the tenderers are allowed to attach a copy of the reports of the most important publications of RORO reports as documentation.</P><P>Only the RORO reports performed at the time of the deadline for the request to participate will be considered when assessing which candidate has documented the most relevant previous RORO reports, cf. Section IV.1.2). If the delivery of RORO reports in question is ongoing, it is only the part of the RORO Reports performed and completed at the time of the deadline for the request to participate which will be included in the assessment of the delivery (reference).</P><P>The description should also include a description of the candidates participation/role in the performance of the publications.</P><P>The description should contain information on the date of issuing the publications.7. The list must contain a maximum of 7 previous publications and copies, whether the candidate is one entity, composed of a group of entities (e.g. consortium), including temporary joint ventures, or relies on the technical and professional capacity of other entities. If the list contains more than 7, DALO will only consider the first 7 reports on the list. Deliveries beyond that will be disregarded.</P><P>Please note that a candidate may rely on the technical and professional capacity of other entities (e.g. a parent or sister company), irrespective of the legal nature of the relations between the candidate and the entity or entities on which the candidate relies.</P></T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION></TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI></F17_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><SERVICES_CONTRACTS_SPECIFIC_CONDITIONS><NO_EXEC_SERVICE_RESERVED_PARTICULAR_PROFESSION/><REQUESTS_NAMES_PROFESSIONAL_QUALIFICATIONS VALUE="NO"/></SERVICES_CONTRACTS_SPECIFIC_CONDITIONS></LEFTI_CONTRACT_DEFENCE><PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><PT_NEGOTIATED_CHOICE/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED><OPE_ENVISAGED_NUMBER>8</OPE_ENVISAGED_NUMBER><OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA><P>The limitation of candidates will be based on an evaluation of which candidates have documented the most relevant previous deliveries and publications in comparison to the framework agreement/purchases described in Section II.1.5) above, in terms of the nature and quantity of the previous deliveries and publications. The evaluation will be based on the list of references submitted by the candidates according to section III.2.3). Please note that any ambiguities and/or incomprehensibilities in the information submitted may be regarded negatively in the evaluation when selecting the limited numbers of candidates.</P></OPE_OBJECTIVE_CRITERIA></MAXIMUM_NUMBER_INVITED><REDUCTION_OF_THE_NUMBER VALUE="NO"/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DEFENCE><AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><MOST_ECONOMICALLY_ADVANTAGEOUS_TENDER><CRITERIA_STATED_IN_OTHER_DOCUMENT/></MOST_ECONOMICALLY_ADVANTAGEOUS_TENDER></AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE><NO_USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION/></IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE></AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17><NO_PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_EXISTS_F17/></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F17><RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><DAY>09</DAY><MONTH>04</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>13:00</TIME></RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><LANGUAGE><LANGUAGE_EC VALUE="EN"/></LANGUAGE></ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE></PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE_DEFENCE><COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/><RELATES_TO_EU_PROJECT_NO/><ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><P>This tender is conducted according to the negotiated procedure, cf. directive 2009/81/EC, article 26. The candidates who will be invited to submit tenders will receive further practical information regarding the negotiated procedure in the Instructions to Tenderers.</P><P>Tenderers are expressly made aware that DALO reserves the right to regard the INDO as a best and final offer (BAFO) and to close the tender procedure and award the Framework Agreement on the basis of the submitted INDO, ie. without conducting any negotiations.</P><P>Please note, that each candidate can only submit one request for participation. If the same legal entity is a part of or in any other way participates in several applications, e.g. submits his own application and at the same time participates in a consortium which also applies, the candidates shall ensure that the same legal entity’s participation does not provide for opportunity for mutual coordination of their applications and offers. DALO reserves the right to request the candidates to establish and reassure DALO that the same legal entity’s participation does not threaten the transparency and distort competition between the tenderers.</P><P>DALO reserves the right — but is not obliged — to use remedies equal to the remedies provided for in Section 159(5) of the Danish Act no. 1564 of 15.12.2015, the Public Procurement Act, if applications or tenders do not fulfil the formalities of the tender documents.</P><P>Candidates are asked to submit their request to participate via ETHICS. The permalink is stated in Section I.1). The request to participate cannot be submitted by e-mail.</P><P>DALO have prepared a prequalification questionnaire which candidates are strongly encouraged to use when submitting their applications. The questionnaire contains questions, forms and templates for providing information etc. in accordance with the requirements in this Contract Notice. However, it is emphasized that it is the sole responsibility of the candidate that the information provided fulfils the requirements.</P><P>The questionnaire is available via ETHICS. The permalink is stated in Section I.1).</P><P>According to the EU defence directive, a candidate may rely on the economic and financial standing and/or technical and/or professional capacity of other entities, regardless of the legal nature of the links with the entities. If a candidate wants to rely on other entities and wishes that the capacity of other entities is taken into account when DALO assesses the suitability of the candidate, the candidate must prove that the other entities will and shall put the relevant resources at the disposal of the candidate. A template for a declaration from the supporting entity to this effect is included in the pre-qualification questionnaire referred to above.</P><P>DALO demands that any person taking part in the performance of the framework agreement (the POC's), no later than 7 months after commencement of the framework agreement, must possess the appropriate personnel security clearance at the level required by DALO. The security clearance must be maintained throughout the term of the framework agreement.</P></ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Klagenævnet for udbud (The Complaints Board for Public Procurement)</OFFICIALNAME><NATIONALID>Nævnenes Hus</NATIONALID></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Toldboden 2</ADDRESS><TOWN>Viborg</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>8800</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>klfu@naeveneneshus.dk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS><PHONE>+45 72405708</PHONE><URL>http://erhvervsstyrelsen.dk/klagenaevnet-for-udbud</URL></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></APPEAL_PROCEDURE_BODY_RESPONSIBLE><LODGING_OF_APPEALS><LODGING_OF_APPEALS_PRECISION><P>Pursuant to Section 3 of the Danish Consolidation Act nº 593 of 2.6.2016 on the Complaints Board for Public Procurement (available at www.retsinformation.dk), the following time limits for filing a complaint apply:</P><P>Complaints regarding a candidate not being pre-qualified must be filed with The Complaints Board for Public Procurement within 20 calendar days starting the day after the Contracting Authority has sent notification to the candidates involved, cf. § 7(1) of the Act on the Complaints Board for Public Procurement, provided that the notification includes a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P><P>Other complaints must in accordance with § 7(2) of the Act on the Complaints Board for Public Procurement be filed with The Complaints Board for Public Procurement within:</P><P>1) 45 calendar days after the Contracting Authority has published a contract award notice in the Official Journal of the European Union (with effect from the day following the publication date).</P><P>2) 30 calendar days starting the day after the Contracting Authority has informed the tenderers in question, that the Contracting Authority has entered into a contract based on a framework agreement through reopening of competition or a dynamic purchasing system, provided that the notification includes a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P><P>3) 6 months starting the day after the Contracting Authority has sent notification to the candidates/tenderers involved that the Contracting Authority has entered into the framework agreement, provided that the notification included a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P><P>4) 20 calendar days starting the day after the Contracting Authority has published a notice concerning his decision to uphold the contract, cf. the principle in § 185(2) of the Public Procurement Act (act no. 1564 of 15.12.2015 – available at www.retsinformation.dk).</P><P>The complainant must inform the Contracting Authority of the complaint in writing at the latest simultaneously with the lodge of the complaint to The Complaints Board for Public Procurement stating whether the complaint has been lodged in the stand-still period, cf. § 6(4) of the Act on The Complaints Board for Public Procurement. If the complaint has not been lodged in the stand-still period, the complainant must also state whether it is requested that the appeal is granted delaying effect, cf. § 12(1) of the said act.</P><P>The e-mail of The Complaints Board for Public Procurement is stated in Section VI.4.1.</P><P>The Complaints Board for Public Procurement’s own guidance note concerning complaints is available at the internet address stated in section VI.4.1.</P></LODGING_OF_APPEALS_PRECISION></LODGING_OF_APPEALS><LODGING_INFORMATION_FOR_SERVICE><CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Konkurrence- og Forbrugerstyrelsen (The Danish Competition and Consumer Authority)</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Carl Jacobsens Vej 35</ADDRESS><TOWN>Valby</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>2500</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>kfst@kfst.dk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS><PHONE>+45 41715000</PHONE><URL>www.kfst.dk</URL></CONTACT_DATA_WITHOUT_RESPONSIBLE_NAME></LODGING_INFORMATION_FOR_SERVICE></PROCEDURES_FOR_APPEAL><NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE><DAY>09</DAY><MONTH>03</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR></NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></FD_CONTRACT_DEFENCE></CONTRACT_DEFENCE></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>