<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="012817-2018" EDITION="2018008"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-008085-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180222</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>8</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180112</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 008-012817</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:012817-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="HR"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="48810000">Information systems</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180108</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180222 12:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="2">Supplies</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="Z">Not specified</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>BR505</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Kroatien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - Projekt vedrørende modernisering af jernbaner i Kroatien</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Kroatien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - Projekt zur Modernisierung der kroatischen Eisenbahn</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Croatia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Croatian Railways Modernisation Project</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Croacia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Proyecto de modernización de los ferrocarriles de Croacia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Kroatia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Kroatian rautateiden uudistamishanke</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Croatie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Projet de modernisation des chemins de fer croates</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Κροατία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - Σχέδιο εκσυγχρονισμού των κροατικών σιδηροδρόμων</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Croazia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - Progetto di ammodernamento delle ferrovie croate</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Kroatië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - Moderniseringsproject voor de Kroatische spoorwegen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Croácia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Projeto de modernização das linhas férreas da Croácia</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Kroatien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Projekt för modernisering av Kroatiens järnvägar</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Chorvatsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt týkající se modernizace chorvatské železnice</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Horvaatia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Horvaatia raudteede ajakohastamise projekt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Horvátország</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - A horvát vasút modernizációjára irányuló projekt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Kroatija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - Kroatijos geležinkelių modernizavimo projektas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Horvātija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - Horvātijas dzelzceļa modernizācijas projekts</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Kroazja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - Progett ta’ Modernizzazzjoni tal-Ferroviji fil-Kroazja</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Chorwacja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt dotyczący modernizacji kolei chorwackich</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Chorvátsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt modernizácie chorvátskych železníc</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Hrvaška</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt modernizacije hrvaških železnic</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Chróit, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Tionscadal Nuachóirithe Iarnróid na Cróite</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Хърватска</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - Проект за модернизиране на хърватските железници</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Croaţia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Proiect de modernizare a căilor ferate croate</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Hrvatska</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Zagreb</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Projekt modernizacije hrvatskih željeznica</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - Projekt vedrørende modernisering af jernbaner i Kroatien (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - Projekt zur Modernisierung der kroatischen Eisenbahn (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Croatian Railways Modernisation Project (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Proyecto de modernización de los ferrocarriles de Croacia (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Kroatian rautateiden uudistamishanke (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Projet de modernisation des chemins de fer croates (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - Σχέδιο εκσυγχρονισμού των κροατικών σιδηροδρόμων (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - Progetto di ammodernamento delle ferrovie croate (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - Moderniseringsproject voor de Kroatische spoorwegen (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Projeto de modernização das linhas férreas da Croácia (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Projekt för modernisering av Kroatiens järnvägar (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt týkající se modernizace chorvatské železnice (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Horvaatia raudteede ajakohastamise projekt (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - A horvát vasút modernizációjára irányuló projekt (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - Kroatijos geležinkelių modernizavimo projektas (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - Horvātijas dzelzceļa modernizācijas projekts (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - Progett ta’ Modernizzazzjoni tal-Ferroviji fil-Kroazja (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt dotyczący modernizacji kolei chorwackich (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt modernizácie chorvátskych železníc (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt modernizacije hrvaških železnic (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Tionscadal Nuachóirithe Iarnróid na Cróite (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - Проект за модернизиране на хърватските железници (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Proiect de modernizare a căilor ferate croate (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Projekt modernizacije hrvatskih željeznica (HR-Zagreb)</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Invitation for Tenders</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><P>Project name: HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project</P><P>Country: Croatia</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 8922-IFT-44467</P><P>Funding source: EBRD</P><P>Type of contract: Goods and Related Services</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for Tenders</P><P>Issue date: 8 January 2018</P><P>Closing date: 22 February 2018 at 12:00 noon local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project which was originally published in Procurement Opportunities on the EBRD website on 22 July 2014 with reference: 7144-GPN-44467 and updated on 26 January 2017 with reference 8545-GPN-44467.</P><P>HŽ INFRASTRUKTURA d.o.o. hereinafter referred to as “the Purchaser”, intends to use part of the proceeds of a loan from the European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (the Bank) towards the cost of the HŽ Infrastructure Modernization Project.</P><P>The Purchaser now invites sealed tenders from suppliers for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (EMIS)</P><P>The scope of the purchase is an integrated Energy Consumption Monitoring System EMIS (EMIS – Energy Management Information System), which consists of CIS (Central Information System) and MRMS (Meter Reading Monitoring System), components for remote, real-time meter reading, with the goal of acquisition of data on energy consumption, data transfer to CIS, alerting subsystem in case when consumption reaches a certain threshold, processing of gathered data on consumption, drafting of special reports, and transfer service of consumption data to ISGE — Energy Management Information System of the Real Estate Agency in duration of 2 years.</P><P>The mentioned system needs to be robust (it must fulfil its purpose without malfunctions in the present working conditions of metres in question), scalable (it must be easily expanded to new metres or facilities, and integrated with other information systems); it needs to provide a constant and uninterrupted communication between all system components, and it must fulfil minimal technical requirements described in the tender documentation, as well as all the valid norms and standards in the Republic of Croatia and the European Union related to metering and communication equipment.</P><P>Tendering for contracts that are to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the bank is open to firms from any country. The proceeds of the bank's loan will not be used for the purpose of any payment to persons or entities, of for any import of goods, if such payment or import is prohibited by a decision of the United Nations Security Council taken under Chapter VII of the Charter of the United Nations.</P><P>To be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the following minimum criteria:</P><P>1.</P><P>(a) Submission of audited balance sheets, or if not required by the law of the tenderer’s country, other financial statements acceptable to the Purchaser, for the last 3 (three) years to demonstrate the current soundness of the tenderer’s financial position and its prospective long-term profitability.</P><P>(b) The tenderer must not:</P><P>— be in bankruptcy,</P><P>— be in insolvency or in liquidation proceedings,</P><P>— have the assets administered by a liquidator or by the court of law or,</P><P>— have the commercial activity suspended or in any other similar situation which results from a similar procedure according to the laws and national regulations.</P><P>(c) Tenderers shall demonstrate that they regularly meet their tax and assimilated legal contributions obligations (pensions, health fund, insurances, and other similar mandatory obligations) in the country where their business is registered or in the case they also have registered offices in the purchaser’s country, that they also meet the tax obligations assimilated legal contributions obligations in the purchaser’s country.</P><P>(d) Minimum average annual turnover of 1,250,000.00 EUR calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 3 (three) years. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the required average annual turnover, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the required average annual turnover.</P><P>2) The tenderer shall demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet:</P><P>(a) The following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>(i) 800 000,00 EUR and</P><P>(ii) the overall cash flow requirements for this contract and its current commitments.</P><P>In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfil a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfil a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>3) Experience as supplier, in at least 3 (three) contracts within the last 5 (five) years each with a value of at least 150,000.00 EUR for goods (ICT components, sensors, metre reading devices) and EMIS that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed goods. In the case of a joint venture of several companies, each partner shall fulfill a minimum 20 % of the requirement, and the leading partner shall fulfill a minimum 60 % of the requirement.</P><P>4) Demonstrate capacity to provide warranty, maintenance, repair, and spare parts-stocking obligations.</P><P>5) The tenderer shall submit with its tender the manufacturer’s authorisation for all the goods it offers, but that it does not manufacture.</P><P>6) The tenderer shall submit with its tender an excerpt from the Court Register or Company Commerce Register which confirms the tenderer’s basic business activity, dated less than 180 days before the deadline for the submission of tenders, drawn up in accordance with his national law or practice or by copies of the original documents defining the constitution and/or legal status and establishing the place of registration and/or statutory seat and, if it is different, the place of central administration. The same information shall be provided for all his sub-contractors, associates or partners, which shall be engaged as the part of the entire contract.</P><P>The successful tenderer shall be required to produce proof of the above mentioned elements.</P><P>The purchaser reserves the right to check the submitted data with the banks and the companies which are indicated in the references, or with other clients.</P><P>Qualification information and statements regarding qualification must be signed by the party authorised to sign the tender.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from and inspect the tender documents, as well as acquire the tender documents, upon payment of a non-refundable fee of 150 EUR or an equivalent in a convertible currency, at the following office:</P><P>Contact name: Iva Mršo Nastić</P><P>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Address: Mihanovićeva 12</P><P>Floor/Room number: 2nd floor, room 105</P><P>Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Telephone number: +385 1 453 4058, Facsimile number: +385 1 457 7587</P><P>Electronic mail address: iva.mrsonastic@hzinfra.hr</P><P>Payments in euros may be made by bank transfer to the following account:</P><P>Amount: 150 EUR</P><P>Account no: HR7624020061500030910 ”Erste&amp;Steiermarkische bank d.d., Rijeka, Jadranski trg 3a, Croatia, BIC/Swift no. of bank: ESBCHR22, IBAN HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>F/O:</P><P>Purpose: Tender Documentation for the Procurement of the Energy Management Information System (Emis)</P><P>Beneficiary: HZ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</P><P>Mihanovićeva 12, Zagreb, Croatia</P><P>Upon receiving appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee, the documents will be promptly dispatched by courier or may be taken over at the address above every working day from 8:00 to 15:00 h, starting from 8 January 2018; however, no liability can be accepted for loss or late delivery. If requested, the documents can also be dispatched electronically after the presentation by the prospective tenderer of appropriate evidence of payment of the non-refundable fee. In the event of a discrepancy between electronic and hard copies of the documents, the hard copy shall prevail.</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have purchased the tender documents may be inspected at the address above.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security. The tender security shall be in Euros or an equivalent amount in a convertible currency and shall not be less than: 15 000,00 EUR</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 22.2.2018 by 12:00 noon, and they will be opened on the same day at 12:30 local time, in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>HŽ Infrastruktura d.o.o.</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Address: Mihanovićeva 12, Floor/Room number: 3rd Floor, Room 180, Postal Code, City and Country: 10000 </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Zagreb</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Croatia</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>