<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="095195-2018" EDITION="2018044"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-082244-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20190220</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>44</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180303</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 044-095195</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095195-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="BE"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="80522000">Training seminars</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180220</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="5">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="0">Prior information notice without call for competition</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="2">Restricted procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="3">European Institution/Agency or International Organisation</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="9">Not applicable</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="Z">Not specified</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>AP301</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Tilrettelæggelse af og støtte til konferencer, seminarer, møder og undervisning inden for rammerne af østpartnerskabet, sortehavssynergien og den nordlige dimension</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Organisation und Unterstützung von Konferenzen, Seminaren, Sitzungen und Schulungen im Rahmen der Östlichen Partnerschaft, der Schwarzmeersynergie und der Nördlichen Dimension</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussels</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Organisation of and support to conferences, seminars, meetings and trainings in the framework of the Eastern Partnership, Black Sea Synergy and Northern Dimension</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IEV - Organización de y apoyo a conferencias, seminarios, reuniones y sesiones formativas en el marco de la Asociación Oriental, la Sinergia del Mar Negro y la Dimensión Septentrional</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Konferenssien, seminaarien, kokousten ja koulutusten järjestäminen ja tukeminen itäisen kumppanuuden, Mustanmeren synergian ja pohjoisen ulottuvuuden yhteydessä</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Belgique</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IEV - Soutien et organisation de conférences, de séminaires, de réunions et de formations dans le cadre du partenariat oriental, de la synergie de la mer Noire et de la dimension septentrionale</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Βέλγιο</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Οργάνωση και υποστήριξη συνεδρίων, σεμιναρίων, συναντήσεων και καταρτίσεων στο πλαίσιο της Ανατολικής Εταιρικής Σχέσης, της Συνέργειας του Ευξείνου Πόντου και της Βόρειας Διάστασης</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Belgio</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Organizzazione e sostegno di conferenze, seminari, incontri e formazione nel quadro del partenariato orientale, della sinergia del Mar Nero e della dimensione nordica</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>België</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Organisatie en ondersteuning van conferenties, seminars, vergaderingen en opleidingen in het kader van het Oostelijk Partnerschap, de Synergie voor het Zwarte Zeegebied en de Noordelijke Dimensie</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Bélgica</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IEV - Organização de, e apoio a conferências, seminários, reuniões e formações no quadro da Parceria Oriental, Sinergia do Mar Negro e Dimensão Setentrional</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Belgien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bryssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Europeiska grannskapsinstrumentet - Anordnande av och stöd till konferenser, seminarier, möten och utbildning inom ramen för det östliga partnerskapet, Svartahavssynergin och den nordliga dimensionen</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Belgie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Organizace a podpora pro konference, semináře, schůze a školení v rámci Východního partnerství, součinnosti mezi oblastí Černého moře a severskými zeměmi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüssel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Konverentside, seminaride, kohtumiste ja koolituse korraldamine ja toetamine idapartnerluse, Musta mere sünergia ja põhjamõõtme raames</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Belgium</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brüsszel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Konferenciák, szemináriumok, értekezletek és képzések szervezése és támogatása a Keleti partnerség, a Fekete-tengeri szinergia és az Északi Dimenzió keretében</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Briuselis</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Konferencijų, seminarų, posėdžių ir mokymų organizavimas ir parama, remiantis Rytų partneryste, Juodosios jūros sinergija ir Šiaurės dimensija</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Beļģija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brisele</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EKI - Konferenču, semināru, sanāksmju un apmācības organizēšana un atbalsts Austrumu partnerības, Melnās jūras reģiona sinerģijas un Ziemeļu dimensijas ietvaros</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Belġju</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brussell</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Organizzazzjoni ta' u appoġġ għal konferenzi, seminars, laqgħat u taħriġ fil-qafas tal-Isħubija tal-Lvant, is-Sinerġija tal-Baħar l-Iswed u d-Dimensjoni tat-Tramuntana</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruksela</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Organizacja i wsparcie konferencji, seminariów, spotkań i szkoleń w ramach Partnerstwa Wschodniego, synergii czarnomorskiej i wymiaru północnego</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Belgicko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Brusel</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Organizácia a podpora pre konferencie, semináre, stretnutia a školenia v rámci Východného partnerstva, Čiernomorskej synergie a Severnej dimenzie</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruselj</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Organizacija in podpora za konference, seminarje, srečanja in usposabljanja v okviru vzhodnega partnerstva, sinergije Črnega morja in severne dimenzije</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Bheilg, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>An Bhruiséil</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Comhdhálacha, seimineáir, cruinnithe agus seisiúin oiliúna a eagrú agus tacú leo faoi chuimsiú Chomhpháirtíocht an Oirthir, Shineirge na Mara Duibhe agus Dhiminsean an Tuaiscirt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бeлгия</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Брюксел</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕИС - Организиране на конференции, семинари, заседания и обучения в рамките на Източното партньорство, Черноморско взаимодействие и Северно измерение</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Belgia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>IEV - Organizare și asistență pentru conferințe, seminarii, reuniuni și cursuri de formare în cadrul Parteneriatului estic, al Sinergiei Mării Negre și al Dimensiunii nordice</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Belgija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Bruxelles</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ENI - Organizacija i podrška za konferencije, seminare, sastanke i osposobljavanje u okviru Istočnog partnerstva, Crnomorske sinergije i Sjeverne dimenzije</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">Den Europæiske Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">Europäische Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">European Union</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">La Unión Europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">Euroopan unioni</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">Union européenne</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">Η Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">Unione europea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">Europese Unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">União Europeia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">Europeiska unionen</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">Evropská unie</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">Euroopa Liit</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">Az Európai Unió</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">Europos Sąjunga</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">Eiropas Savienība</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">l-Unjoni Ewropea</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">Unia Europejska</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">Európska únia</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">Evropska unija</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">An tAontas Eorpach</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">Европейски съюз</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">Uniunea Europeană</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">Europska unija</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: ENI - Tilrettelæggelse af og støtte til konferencer, seminarer, møder og undervisning inden for rammerne af østpartnerskabet, sortehavssynergien og den nordlige dimension</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sted — EU's medlemsstater, Armenien, Aserbajdsjan, Georgien, Hviderusland, Island, Republikken Moldova, Norge, Den Russiske Føderation, Tyrkiet, Ukraine</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VEJLEDENDE FORHÅNDSMEDDELELSE OM TJENESTEYDELSER</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Udbudsreference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Begrænset</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programtitel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (Det europæiske naboskabsinstrument)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Det regionale handlingsprogram under ENI 2017 og 2018 (budgetpost 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ordregivende myndighed</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Den Europæiske Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, repræsenteret ved Europa-Kommissionen, for og på vegne af modtagerlandene, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kontraktens art</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Honorarbaseret kontrakt</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivelse af kontrakten</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Under østpartnerskabet, sortehavssynergien og den nordlige dimension skal afholdes en lang række konferencer, seminarer, møder og undervisningsaktiviteter (vejledende liste) som en vej til yderligere forbedring af den politiske dialog med partnerlandene og et forum til udveksling af oplysninger og erfaringer om partnerlandenes skridt imod harmonisering, reformer og modernisering. Kontraktens overordnede formål er at håndtere arrangementernes tilrettelæggelse og logistik, såvel som undersøgelser og levering af tematisk ekspertise.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vejledende budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Foreløbig dato for offentliggørelse af udbudsbekendtgørelsen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Marts 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Yderligere oplysninger</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Retsgrundlag (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 236/2014 af 11.3.2014 om fælles regler og procedurer for gennemførelse af instrumenterne til finansiering af Unionens optræden udadtil og Europa-Parlamentets og Rådets forordning (EU) nr. 232/2014 af 11.3.2014 om oprettelse af et europæisk naboskabsinstrument.</P><P>Vær opmærksom på, at efter Det Forenede Kongeriges udtræden af EU vil reglerne om adgang til EU's udbudsprocedurer for økonomiske aktører, der er etableret i tredjelande, gælde for ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige, alt afhængigt af resultatet af forhandlingerne. Hvis en sådan adgang ikke gives ved retlige bestemmelser, der er gældende på tidspunktet for kontrakttildelingen, vil ansøgere eller tilbudsgivere fra Det Forenede Kongerige kunne blive udelukket fra udbudsproceduren.</P><P>(1) Angiv venligst enhver specificitet, der kan have indflydelse på reglerne for deltagelse (såsom geografiske eller tematiske eller lang/kort-sigtede).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Bemærkninger:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Der skal være en periode på mindst 30 kalenderdage mellem offentliggørelsen af denne forhåndsmeddelelse og offentliggørelsen af den tilsvarende udbudsbekendtgørelse.</P><P>Der bør ikke fremsendes ansøgninger eller anmodninger om oplysninger på nuværende tidspunkt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: ENI - Organisation und Unterstützung von Konferenzen, Seminaren, Sitzungen und Schulungen im Rahmen der Östlichen Partnerschaft, der Schwarzmeersynergie und der Nördlichen Dimension</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Standort — Mitgliedstaaten der EU, Armenien, Aserbaidschan, Belarus, Georgien, Island, Republik Moldau, Norwegen, Russische Föderation, Türkei, Ukraine</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VORINFORMATION FÜR EINEN DIENSTLEISTUNGSAUFTRAG</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenznummer der Veröffentlichung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verfahren</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nichtoffen</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmbezeichnung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europäisches Nachbarschaftsinstrument (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanzierung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>regionales Aktionsprogramm ENI 2017 &amp; 2018 (Haushaltslinie 22.040304 )</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Öffentlicher Auftraggeber</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europäische Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertreten durch die Europäische Kommission, im Auftrag und für Rechnung der begünstigten Länder, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Art des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>auf Honorarbasis</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschreibung des Auftrags</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Im Rahmen der Östlichen Partnerschaft, der Schwarzmeersynergie und der Nördlichen Dimension werden eine Reihe von Konferenzen, Seminaren, Sitzungen und Schulungen (vorläufige Liste) zur weiteren Vertiefung des politischen Dialogs mit Partnerländern sowie ein Forum zum Informations- und Erfahrungsaustausch in Bezug auf die Fortschritte der Partnerländer bei Harmonisierung, Reform und Modernisierung organisiert. Das übergeordnete Ziel des Auftrags ist die Bewältigung der Organisation und Logistik dieser Veranstaltungen sowie Studien und Bereitstellung von thematischem Fachwissen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veranschlagtes Budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Geplanter Zeitpunkt für die Veröffentlichung der Auftragsbekanntmachung</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>März 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sonstige Informationen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rechtsgrundlage (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verordnung (EU) Nr. 236/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Festlegung gemeinsamer Vorschriften und Verfahren für die Anwendung der Instrumente der Union für die Finanzierung des auswärtigen Handelns und Verordnung (EU) Nr. 232/2014 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 11.3.2014 zur Schaffung eines Europäischen Nachbarschaftsinstruments</P><P>Es gilt zu beachten, dass für Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich nach dem Austritt des Vereinigten Königreichs aus der EU in Abhängigkeit des Ausgangs der Verhandlungen die Bestimmungen über den Zugang zu Beschaffungsverfahren der EU für in Drittländern ansässige Wirtschaftsteilnehmer gelten werden. Falls dieser Zugang gemäß den bei Auftragsvergabe geltenden Bestimmung nicht gewährt wird, können Bewerber oder Bieter aus dem Vereinigten Königreich vom Beschaffungsverfahren ausgeschlossen werden.</P><P>(1) Bitte geben Sie alle Besonderheiten an, die sich auf die Regeln für die Teilnahme auswirken könnten (z. B. geographisch oder thematisch oder kurz-/mittelfristig).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Hinweise:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Es muss ein Zeitraum von mindestens 30 Kalendertagen zwischen der Veröffentlichung der Vorinformation und der Veröffentlichung der entsprechenden Auftragsbekanntmachung liegen.</P><P>Derzeit ist von der Einreichung von Bewerbungen oder weiteren Anfragen abzusehen.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussels: ENI - Organisation of and support to conferences, seminars, meetings and trainings in the framework of the Eastern Partnership, Black Sea Synergy and Northern Dimension</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Location — EU Member States, Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Iceland, Republic of Moldova, Norway, Russian Federation, Turkey, Ukraine</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SERVICE PRIOR INFORMATION NOTICE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publication reference</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restricted</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programme title</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (European Neighbourhood Instrument)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financing</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI East Regional Action Programme 2017 &amp; 2018 (Budget line 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contracting Authority</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>European Union</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, represented by the European Commission on behalf of and for the account of the beneficiary countries, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussels</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, BELGIUM.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature of contract</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Fee-based</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Contract description</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>The Eastern Partnership, the Black Sea Synergy and the Northern Dimension provide for a whole range of conferences, seminars, meetings, training (indicative list) as a means of further deepening the political dialogue with partner countries and a forum to share information and experiences on the partner countries’ steps towards harmonisation, reform and modernisation. The overall objective of the contract is to handle the organisation and logistics of these events, as well as studies and provision of thematic expertise.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicative budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intended timing of publication of the contract notice</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>3.2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Additional information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Legal basis(1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulation (EU) nº 236/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 laying down common rules and procedures for the implementation of the Union's instruments for financing external action and Regulation (EU) nº 232/2014 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11.3.2014 establishing a European Neighbourhood Instrument.</P><P>Please be aware that after the United Kingdom's withdrawal from the EU, the rules of access to EU procurement procedures of economic operators established in third countries will apply to candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom depending on the outcome of negotiations. In case such access is not provided by legal provisions in force at the time of the contract award, candidates or tenderers from the United Kingdom, could be rejected from the procurement procedure.</P><P>(1) Please state any specificity that might have an impact on rules on participation (such as geographic or thematic or long/short term).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarks:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>There must be a minimum period of 30 calendar days between the publication of this prior information notice and the publication of the corresponding contract notice.</P><P>No applications or requests for information should be sent at this stage.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselas: IEV - Organización de y apoyo a conferencias, seminarios, reuniones y sesiones formativas en el marco de la Asociación Oriental, la Sinergia del Mar Negro y la Dimensión Septentrional</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Estados miembros de la Unión Europea, Armenia, Azerbaiyán, Bielorrusia, Federación de Rusia, Georgia, Islandia, Noruega, República de Moldavia, Turquía, Ucrania</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNCIO DE PREVISIÓN DE CONTRATO DE SERVICIOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referencia de publicación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedimiento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restringido</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Denominación del programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Instrumento Europeo de Vecindad (IEV)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de acción regional oriental del IEV para 2017 y 2018 (línea presupuestaria 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Órgano de contratación</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>La Unión Europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada por la Comisión Europea, en nombre y por cuenta de los países beneficiarios, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naturaleza del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Honorarios</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descripción del contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>La Asociación Oriental, la Sinergia del Mar Negro y la Dimensión Septentrional proporcionan un amplio abanico de conferencias, seminarios, reuniones y sesiones formativas (lista indicativa) con el objetivo de intensificar el diálogo político con los países socios y un foro para compartir información y experiencias sobre los avances de los países socios hacia la armonización, la reforma y la modernización. El objetivo global del contrato consiste en gestionar la organización y la logística de dichos eventos, así como la realización de estudios y la provisión de conocimientos específicos.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Presupuesto indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fecha prevista de publicación del anuncio de contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Marzo de 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Información adicional</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Fundamento jurídico (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Reglamento (UE) n.{^&gt;o&lt;^} 236/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establecen normas y procedimientos de ejecución comunes de los instrumentos de la Unión para la financiación de la acción exterior, y Reglamento (UE) n.{^&gt;o&lt;^} 232/2014 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 11.3.2014, por el que se establece un Instrumento Europeo de Vecindad.</P><P>Téngase en cuenta que tras la salida del Reino Unido de la Unión Europea, las normas de acceso a los procedimientos de contratación pública de la Unión Europea de los operadores económicos establecidos en terceros países se aplicarán a candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido en función del resultado de las negociaciones. En caso de que las disposiciones jurídicas en vigor en el momento de la adjudicación del contrato no faciliten dicho acceso, los candidatos o licitadores del Reino Unido podrían ser excluidos del procedimiento de contratación.</P><P>(1) Mencione cualquier aspecto específico que podría repercutir en las normas de participación (por ejemplo, aspectos geográficos, temáticos o de corto/largo plazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observaciones:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deben pasar al menos 30 días naturales desde la publicación de esta previsión de contrato hasta la publicación del correspondiente anuncio de contrato.</P><P>Por el momento, no deben enviarse solicitudes ni peticiones de información complementaria.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: ENI - Konferenssien, seminaarien, kokousten ja koulutusten järjestäminen ja tukeminen itäisen kumppanuuden, Mustanmeren synergian ja pohjoisen ulottuvuuden yhteydessä</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Sijainti – EU:n jäsenvaltiot, Armenia, Azerbaidžan, Georgia, Islanti, Moldovan tasavalta, Norja, Turkki, Ukraina, Valko-Venäjä, Venäjän federaatio</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PALVELUJA KOSKEVA ENNAKKOTIETOILMOITUS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ilmoituksen viite</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menettely</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rajoitettu menettely</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ohjelman nimi</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan naapuruusväline (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahoitus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan naapuruusvälineen (ENI) vuosien 2017 ja 2018 alueellinen itäinen toimintaohjelma (budjettikohta 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintaviranomainen</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopan unioni</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, jota edustaa Euroopan komissio, edunsaajamaiden puolesta, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuslaji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Palkkiopohjainen</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sopimuksen kuvaus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Itäisen kumppanuuden, Mustanmeren synergian ja pohjoisen ulottuvuuden yhteydessä järjestetään monia erilaisia konferensseja, seminaareja, kokouksia ja koulutustilaisuuksia (ohjeellinen luettelo). Näiden avulla syvennetään edelleen kumppanimaiden kanssa käytävää poliittista vuoropuhelua sekä tarjotaan foorumi, jolla voidaan jakaa tietoa ja kokemuksia kumppanimaiden etenemisestä kohti yhdenmukaistamista, uudistumista ja nykyaikaistamista. Sopimuksen yleistavoitteena on näihin tapahtumiin liittyvien järjestelyjen ja logistiikan hoitaminen sekä tutkimusten suorittaminen ja alakohtaisen asiantuntemuksen toimittaminen.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Alustava budjetti</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hankintailmoituksen ennakoitu julkaisemisajankohta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Maaliskuu 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisätiedot</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Oikeusperusta (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 236/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, unionin ulkoisen toiminnan rahoitusvälineiden täytäntöönpanoa koskevista yhteisistä säännöistä ja menettelyistä sekä Euroopan parlamentin ja neuvoston asetus (EU) N:o 232/2014, annettu 11.3.2014, Euroopan naapuruusvälineen perustamisesta.</P><P>On syytä ottaa huomioon, että Yhdistyneen kuningaskunnan EU:sta irtautumisen jälkeen kolmansiin maihin sijoittautuneisiin talouden toimijoihin sovellettavia EU:n hankintamenettelyihin osallistumista koskevia sääntöjä sovelletaan Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin oleviin hakijoihin tai tarjoajiin neuvottelujen lopputuloksesta riippuen. Mikäli sopimuksenteon hetkellä voimassa olevassa lainsäädännössä ei anneta lupaa tällaiseen osallistumiseen, Yhdistyneestä kuningaskunnasta peräisin olevat hakijat tai tarjoajat voidaan hylätä hankintamenettelystä.</P><P>(1) Tarjoajia pyydetään mainitsemaan erityisolosuhteista, jotka voivat vaikuttaa osallistumissääntöihin (esimerkiksi maantieteelliset tai aihekohtaiset tai pitkä-/lyhytkestoiset erityisolosuhteet).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Huom.</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Tämän ennakkotietoilmoituksen ja vastaavan hankintailmoituksen julkaisemisen välillä on oltava vähintään 30 kalenteripäivää.</P><P>Hakemuksia tai lisätietopyyntöjä ei pidä lähettää tässä vaiheessa.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: IEV - Soutien et organisation de conférences, de séminaires, de réunions et de formations dans le cadre du partenariat oriental, de la synergie de la mer Noire et de la dimension septentrionale</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lieux d'exécution : États membres de l'Union européenne, Arménie, Azerbaïdjan, Biélorussie, Géorgie, Islande, République de Moldavie, Norvège, Fédération de Russie, Turquie, Ukraine</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVIS DE PRÉINFORMATION RELATIF À UN MARCHÉ DE SERVICES</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Référence de la publication</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procédure</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restreinte</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Intitulé du programme</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IEV (Instrument européen de voisinage)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financement</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programme d'action 2017 et 2018 pour la région orientale bénéficiaire de l'IEV (ligne budgétaire 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pouvoir adjudicateur</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Union européenne</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, représentée par la Commission européenne, agissant au nom et pour le compte des pays bénéficiaires, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgique.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nature du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Marché à prix unitaires</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Description du marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Le partenariat oriental, la synergie de la mer Noire et la dimension septentrionale organisent un grand nombre de conférences, de séminaires, de réunions et de formations (liste indicative) afin d'approfondir davantage le dialogue politique avec les pays partenaires, ainsi qu'un forum en vue de partager des informations et des expériences sur les mesures prises par les pays partenaires en vue de l'harmonisation, de la réforme et de la modernisation. L'objectif global du marché est de superviser l'organisation et la logistique de ces événements, ainsi que des études et la fourniture d'expertises thématiques.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Budget indicatif</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Date prévue de publication de l'avis de marché</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mars 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Renseignements complémentaires</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base juridique (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Règlement (UE) no 236/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 fixant les règles communes et les procédures de mise en œuvre des instruments de l'Union pour le financement de l'action extérieure et règlement (UE) no 232/2014 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 11.3.2014 instituant un instrument européen de voisinage.</P><P>Il convient de noter qu'à la suite du retrait du Royaume-Uni de l'UE, les règles d'accès aux procédures de passation des marchés de l'UE pour les opérateurs économiques établis dans des pays tiers s'appliqueront aux candidats ou aux soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni, en fonction du résultat des négociations. Si les dispositions légales en vigueur au moment de l'attribution du contrat ne prévoient pas un tel accès, les candidats ou les soumissionnaires du Royaume-Uni pourraient être exclus de la procédure de passation des marchés.</P><P>(1) Veuillez indiquer toute spécificité susceptible d’avoir un impact sur les règles en matière de participation (par exemple géographique ou thématique ou à cours/long terme).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Remarques :</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Un délai minimal de 30 jours calendaires doit être respecté entre la publication du présent avis de préinformation et celle de l'avis de marché correspondant.</P><P>Aucune candidature ni demande de renseignements complémentaires ne sera envoyée à ce stade de la procédure.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Βρυξέλλες: ENI - Οργάνωση και υποστήριξη συνεδρίων, σεμιναρίων, συναντήσεων και καταρτίσεων στο πλαίσιο της Ανατολικής Εταιρικής Σχέσης, της Συνέργειας του Ευξείνου Πόντου και της Βόρειας Διάστασης</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Τόπος — κράτη μέλη της ΕΕ, Αρμενία, Αζερμπαϊτζάν, Λευκορωσία, Γεωργία, Ισλανδία, Δημοκρατία της Μολδαβίας, Νορβηγία, Ρωσική Ομοσπονδία, Τουρκία, Ουκρανία</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ΠΡΟΚΑΤΑΡΚΤΙΚΗ ΑΝΑΚΟΙΝΩΣΗ ΓΙΑ ΥΠΗΡΕΣΙΕΣ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αριθ. αναφοράς της δημοσίευσης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Διαδικασία</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κλειστή</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τίτλος προγράμματος</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ευρωπαϊκός Μηχανισμός Γειτονίας (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Χρηματοδότηση</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ανατολικό περιφερειακό πρόγραμμα δράσης ΕΝΙ 2017 &amp; 2018 (κονδύλιο προϋπολογισμού 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Αναθέτουσα αρχή</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Η Ευρωπαϊκή Ένωση</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, εκπροσωπούμενη από την Ευρωπαϊκή Επιτροπή, εκ μέρους και για λογαριασμό των δικαιούχων χωρών, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Βρυξέλλες</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Βέλγιο.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Τύπος σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Βάσει αμοιβής</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Περιγραφή της σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Η Ανατολική Εταιρική Σχέση, η Συνέργεια του Ευξείνου Πόντου και η Βόρεια Διάσταση παρέχουν ένα πλήρες φάσμα συνεδρίων, σεμιναρίων, συναντήσεων και καταρτίσεων (ενδεικτικός κατάλογος) ως μέσο περαιτέρω εμβάθυνσης του πολιτικού διαλόγου με τις χώρες εταίρους και φόρουμ για την ανταλλαγή πληροφοριών και εμπειριών σχετικά με τα βήματα των χωρών εταίρων προς την εναρμόνιση, τη μεταρρύθμιση και τον εκσυγχρονισμό. Γενικός στόχος της σύμβασης είναι η διαχείριση της οργάνωσης και της υλικοτεχνικής υποστήριξης των εν λόγω εκδηλώσεων καθώς και μελέτες και παροχή θεματικής εμπειρογνωμοσύνης.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ενδεικτικός προϋπολογισμός</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Προβλεπόμενη ημερομηνία δημοσίευσης της προκήρυξης σύμβασης</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Μάρτιος 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Συμπληρωματικές πληροφορίες</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Νομική βάση (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 236/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τον καθορισμό κοινών κανόνων και διαδικασιών για την εφαρμογή των μηχανισμών χρηματοδότησης της εξωτερικής δράσης της Ένωσης και κανονισμός (ΕΕ) αριθ. 232/2014 του Ευρωπαϊκού Κοινοβουλίου και του Συμβουλίου, της 11.3.2014, για τη θέσπιση Ευρωπαϊκού Μηχανισμού Γειτονίας.</P><P>Πρέπει να ληφθεί υπόψη ότι μετά την αποχώρηση του Ηνωμένου Βασιλείου από την ΕΕ, οι κανόνες πρόσβασης σε διαδικασίες διαγωνισμού της ΕΕ για οικονομικούς φορείς που είναι εγκατεστημένοι σε τρίτες χώρες θα ισχύουν για τους υποψήφιους ή προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο ανάλογα με το αποτέλεσμα των διαπραγματεύσεων. Σε περίπτωση που η πρόσβαση αυτή δεν παρέχεται από νομικές διατάξεις που ίσχυαν κατά τον χρόνο ανάθεσης της σύμβασης, οι υποψήφιοι ή οι προσφέροντες από το Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο θα μπορούσαν να απορριφθούν από τη διαδικασία διαγωνισμού.</P><P>(1) Παρακαλείσθε να αναφέρετε οποιαδήποτε ιδιαιτερότητα που ενδέχεται να έχει αντίκτυπο στους κανόνες συμμετοχής (όπως γεωγραφική ή θεματική ή σε μακροπρόθεσμο/βραχυπρόθεσμο επίπεδο).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Παρατηρήσεις:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Μεταξύ της δημοσίευσης της παρούσας προκαταρκτικής ανακοίνωσης και της δημοσίευσης της αντίστοιχης προκήρυξης σύμβασης θα πρέπει να παρεμβληθεί χρονικό διάστημα τουλάχιστον 30 ημερολογιακών ημερών.</P><P>Κατά το παρόν στάδιο δεν πρέπει να αποστέλλονται υποψηφιότητες ή αιτήματα για παροχή πληροφοριών.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: ENI - Organizzazione e sostegno di conferenze, seminari, incontri e formazione nel quadro del partenariato orientale, della sinergia del Mar Nero e della dimensione nordica</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Ubicazione — Stati membri dell'UE, Armenia, Azerbaigian, Bielorussia, Federazione russa, Georgia, Islanda, Norvegia, Repubblica di Moldova, Turchia, Ucraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVISO DI PREINFORMAZIONE RELATIVO A SERVIZI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Riferimento della pubblicazione</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titolo del programma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (strumento europeo di vicinato)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanziamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programma d'azione regionale orientale ENI 2017 e 2018 (linea di bilancio 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ente appaltante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unione europea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, rappresentata dalla Commissione europea, in nome e per conto dei paesi beneficiari, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgio.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Contratto in base a tariffa</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrizione dell'appalto</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il partenariato orientale, la sinergia del Mar Nero e la dimensione nordica provvedono ad un'intera gamma di conferenze, seminari, incontri e formazioni (elenco indicativo) finalizzati ad approfondire ulteriormente il dialogo politico con i paesi partner e a creare un forum per lo scambio di informazioni ed esperienze sulle azioni intraprese dai paesi partner verso l'armonizzazione, la riforma e la modernizzazione. L'obiettivo generale dell'appalto consiste nella gestione dell’organizzazione e della logistica di tali eventi e di studi e nella fornitura di competenze tematiche.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Importo indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista per la pubblicazione del bando di gara</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Marzo 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informazioni complementari</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base giuridica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regolamento (UE) n. 236/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che stabilisce norme e procedure comuni per l'attuazione degli strumenti per il finanziamento dell'azione esterna dell'Unione e regolamento (UE) n. 232/2014 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio, dell'11.3.2014, che istituisce uno strumento europeo di vicinato.</P><P>Si prega di notare che, dopo il ritiro del Regno Unito dall'UE, ai candidati o agli offerenti provenienti dal Regno Unito si applicheranno le regole di accesso alle procedure di appalto dell'UE per gli operatori economici stabiliti nei paesi terzi, in funzione dell'esito delle negoziazioni. Nel caso in cui tale accesso non sia previsto dalle disposizioni giuridiche vigenti al momento dell'aggiudicazione del contratto, i candidati o gli offerenti del Regno Unito potranno essere esclusi dalla procedura di gara.</P><P>(1) Indicare qualsiasi specificità che possa avere un impatto sulle regole di partecipazione (come ad esempio geografica o tematica o a lungo/breve termine).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Osservazioni:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Dovrà intercorrere un periodo minimo di 30 giorni di calendario tra la pubblicazione dell'avviso di preinformazione e quella del corrispondente bando di gara.</P><P>Si prega di non inviare candidature o richieste di ulteriori informazioni in questa fase della procedura.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussel: ENI - Organisatie en ondersteuning van conferenties, seminars, vergaderingen en opleidingen in het kader van het Oostelijk Partnerschap, de Synergie voor het Zwarte Zeegebied en de Noordelijke Dimensie</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Locatie — EU-lidstaten, Armenië, Azerbeidzjan, Belarus, Georgië, IJsland, Republiek Moldavië, Noorwegen, Oekraïne, Russische Federatie, Turkije</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>VOORAANKONDIGING VOOR DIENSTEN</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referentie van de bekendmaking:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedure:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Niet-openbaar.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titel van het programma:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europees nabuurschapsinstrument (ENI).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiering:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regionaal actieprogramma voor 2017 &amp; 2018 in het kader van ENI-oost (begrotingslijn 22.040304).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aanbestedende dienst:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europese Unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, vertegenwoordigd door de Europese Commissie, ten behoeve en voor rekening van de begunstigde landen, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, België.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Aard van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Opdracht op basis van vergoeding.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beschrijving van de opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Het Oostelijk Partnerschap, de Synergie voor het Zwarte Zeegebied en de Noordelijke Dimensie organiseren een brede waaier aan conferenties, seminars, vergaderingen en opleidingen (indicatieve lijst) met het oog op het verder uitdiepen van de politieke dialoog met partnerlanden, en zetten eveneens een forum op om informatie en ervaringen te delen met betrekking tot de voortgang op het gebied van harmonisatie, hervorming en modernisering in de partnerlanden. De algemene doelstelling van de opdracht is het aanpakken van de organisatie en de logistiek van deze evenementen, maar ook onderzoeken en verlening van thematische expertise.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indicatieve begroting:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beoogde datum voor bekendmaking van de aankondiging van opdracht:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Maart 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nadere inlichtingen:</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Juridische basis (1):</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Verordening (EU) nr. 236/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot vaststelling van gemeenschappelijke voorschriften en procedures voor de tenuitvoerlegging van de instrumenten van de Unie ter financiering van extern optreden en Verordening (EU) nr. 232/2014 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 11.3.2014 tot invoering van een Europees nabuurschapsinstrument.</P><P>Gelieve op te merken dat, na de uitstap van het Verenigd Koninkrijk uit de EU en afhankelijk van het resultaat van de onderhandelingen, de regels voor toegang tot EU-aanbestedingsprocedures voor ondernemers die gevestigd zijn in derde landen van toepassing zullen zijn op gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk. Indien dergelijke toegang niet is voorzien door de geldende wettelijke bepalingen op het tijdstip van de gunning van de opdracht, kunnen gegadigden of inschrijvers uit het Verenigd Koninkrijk worden geweigerd voor de aanbestedingsprocedure.</P><P>(1) Vermeld elke specificiteit die een effect kan hebben op de deelnameregels (zoals geografische of thematische specificiteiten op korte of lange termijn).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opmerkingen:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Er moet een minimumtermijn van 30 kalenderdagen liggen tussen de bekendmaking van deze vooraankondiging en de bekendmaking van de overeenstemmende aankondiging van een opdracht.</P><P>In dit stadium mogen er geen aanvragen of verzoeken om inlichtingen worden verzonden.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelas: IEV - Organização de, e apoio a conferências, seminários, reuniões e formações no quadro da Parceria Oriental, Sinergia do Mar Negro e Dimensão Setentrional</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Localização— Estados-Membros da UE, Arménia, Azerbaijão, Bielorrússia, Geórgia, Islândia, República da Moldávia, Noruega, Federação da Rússia, Turquia, Ucrânia</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANÚNCIO DE PRÉ-INFORMAÇÃO DE SERVIÇOS</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referência da publicação</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Limitado</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Título do programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IEV (Instrumento Europeu de Vizinhança)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiamento</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programa de ação regional 2017 e 2018 a favor da região leste do IEV (rubrica orçamental 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Entidade adjudicante</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>União Europeia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representada pela Comissão Europeia, em nome e por conta dos países beneficiários, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelas</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Bélgica.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natureza do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Baseado em honorários</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrição do contrato</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A Parceria Oriental, a Sinergia do Mar Negro e a Dimensão Setentrional organizam uma vasta gama de conferências, seminários, reuniões e formações (lista indicativa), de modo a aprofundar o diálogo político com países parceiros e um fórum para partilhar informação e experiências sobre as medidas adotadas pelos países parceiros com vista à harmonização, reforma e modernização. O objetivo global do contrato consiste em gerir a organização e a logística destes eventos, bem como estudos e fornecimento de especialização temática.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orçamento indicativo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevista para a publicação do anúncio de concurso</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Março de 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Outras informações</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Base jurídica (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulamento (UE) n.º 236/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que estabelece regras e procedimentos comuns para a execução dos instrumentos da União de financiamento da ação externa e Regulamento (UE) n.º 232/2014 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 11.3.2014, que cria um instrumento europeu de vizinhança.</P><P>Importa notar que após a saída do Reino Unido da UE, as regras de acesso aos procedimentos de adjudicação de contratos da UE de operadores económicos estabelecidos em países terceiros aplicar-se-ão aos candidatos ou proponentes provenientes do Reino Unido consoante o resultado das negociações. Caso tal acesso não esteja previsto pelas disposições legais em vigor, os candidatos ou proponentes do Reino Unido poderão ser excluídos do concurso.</P><P>(1) Indique qualquer especificidade que possa ter impacto sobre as regras de participação (tais como geográficas ou temáticas ou a longo/curto prazo).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observações:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Deve ser respeitado um período mínimo de 30 dias de calendário entre a publicação do presente anúncio de informação prévia e a publicação do anúncio de concurso correspondente.</P><P>Não devem ser enviadas candidaturas ou efetuados pedidos de informação nesta fase.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bryssel: Europeiska grannskapsinstrumentet - Anordnande av och stöd till konferenser, seminarier, möten och utbildning inom ramen för det östliga partnerskapet, Svartahavssynergin och den nordliga dimensionen</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Plats – EU:s medlemsstater, Armenien, Azerbajdzjan, Georgien, Island, Republiken Moldavien, Norge, Ryska federationen, Turkiet, Ukraina, Vitryssland</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÖRHANDSMEDDELANDE OM TJÄNSTER</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Publikationsreferens</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Förfarande</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Selektivt</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programtitel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeiska grannskapsinstrumentet (European Neighbourhood Instrument – ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansiering</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europeiska grannskapsinstrumentets (European Neighbourhood Instrument – ENI) regionala åtgärdsprogram för östra regionen 2017 &amp; 2018 (budgetrubrik 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Upphandlande myndighet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europeiska unionen</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, representerad av Europeiska kommissionen, till förmån för och på uppdrag av mottagarlandet, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bryssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgien.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Typ av kontrakt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Arvodesbaserat</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Beskrivning av kontraktet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Det östliga partnerskapet, Svartahavssynergin och den nordliga dimensionen står för en rad konferenser, seminarier, möten och utbildningstillfällen (preliminär förteckning) som ett sätt att ytterligare fördjupa den politiska dialogen med partnerländerna och som ett forum för att utbyta information och erfarenheter avseende partnerländernas steg mot harmonisering, reform och modernisering. Det övergripande syftet med kontraktet är att hantera anordnandet av och logistiken för dessa evenemang, samt undersökningar och tillhandahållande av tematisk sakkunskap.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Preliminär budget</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planerat datum för publicering av meddelandet om upphandling</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mars 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Kompletterande information</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rättslig grund (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 236/2014 av den 11.3.2014 om fastställande av gemensamma bestämmelser och förfaranden för genomförandet av unionens instrument för finansiering av yttre åtgärder och Europaparlamentets och rådets förordning (EU) nr 232/2014 av den 11.3.2014 om inrättande av ett europeiskt grannskapsinstrument.</P><P>Observera att efter Storbritanniens utträde ur EU kommer reglerna om tillgång till EU:s upphandlingsförfaranden för ekonomiska aktörer etablerade i tredjeländer att tillämpas på sökande eller anbudsgivare från Storbritannien beroende på resultatet av förhandlingarna. Om sådan tillgång inte tillhandahålls av rättsliga bestämmelser som gäller vid tidpunkten för kontraktstilldelningen kan sökande eller anbudsgivare från Storbritannien komma att uteslutas från upphandlingsförfarandet.</P><P>(1) Ange om det finns något som kan påverka reglerna för deltagande (såsom geografiskt läge, tema eller tid på lång eller kort sikt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Anmärkningar:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>En period på minst 30 kalenderdagar ska förflyta mellan publiceringen av detta förhandsmeddelande och publiceringen av motsvarande meddelande om upphandling.</P><P>Inga ansökningar eller beställningar av information ska skickas i detta skede.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: ENI - Organizace a podpora pro konference, semináře, schůze a školení v rámci Východního partnerství, součinnosti mezi oblastí Černého moře a severskými zeměmi</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokalita – členské státy EU, Arménie, Ázerbájdžán, Bělorusko, Gruzie, Island, Moldavská republika, Norsko, Ruská federace, Turecko, Ukrajina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>OZNÁMENÍ PŘEDBĚŽNÝCH INFORMACÍ O SLUŽBÁCH</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenční číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Řízení</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užší</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Název programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (evropský nástroj sousedství)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financování</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regionální akční program ENI východ 2017 &amp; 2018 (rozpočtová položka 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Veřejný zadavatel</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropská unie</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastoupená Evropskou komisí jménem a ve prospěch přijímajících zemí, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgie.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Povaha zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Placená</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Popis zakázky</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Východní partnerství, Černomořská synergie a Severní dimenze umožňují celou řadu konferencí, seminářů, setkání, školení (nevyčerpávající seznam) jako prostředky dalšího prohlubování politického dialogu s partnerskými zeměmi a fórum pro sdílení informací a zkušeností v rámci opatření partnerských zemí v oblasti harmonizace, reformy a modernizace. Celkovým cílem této zakázky je zvládnutí organizace a logistiky těchto akcí i studií a poskytování tematických odborných znalostí.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Směrný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zamýšlené datum zveřejnění oznámení o zakázce</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>březen 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Další informace</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právní základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 236/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se stanoví společná pravidla a postupy pro provádění nástrojů Unie pro financování vnější činnosti, a nařízení Evropského parlamentu a Rady (EU) č. 232/2014 ze dne 11. března 2014, kterým se zřizuje evropský nástroj sousedství.</P><P>Připomínáme, že po vystoupení Spojeného království z EU se na zájemce nebo uchazeče ze Spojeného království, v závislosti od výsledku jednání, budou uplatňovat pravidla přístupu k postupům výběrového řízení EU ze strany hospodářských subjektů se sídlem ve třetích zemích. V případě, že takový přístup není zabezpečen právními předpisy platnými v době zadání zakázky, mohli by být uchazeči nebo účastníci ze Spojeného království vyloučeni z výběrového řízení.</P><P>(1) Uveďte prosím jakoukoli specifičnost, která by mohla mít dopad na pravidla účasti (např. zeměpisnou, tematickou nebo dlouhodobou/krátkodobou).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Mezi zveřejněním těchto předběžných informací o zakázce a zveřejněním odpovídajícího oznámení o zakázce musí uplynout minimálně 30 kalendářních dnů.</P><P>V této fázi nesmí být zasílány žádné přihlášky ani žádosti o informace.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüssel: ENI - Konverentside, seminaride, kohtumiste ja koolituse korraldamine ja toetamine idapartnerluse, Musta mere sünergia ja põhjamõõtme raames</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Asukoht – ELi liikmesriigid, Armeenia, Aserbaidžaan, Gruusia, Island, Moldova Vabariik, Norra, Türgi, Ukraina, Valgevene, Venemaa Föderatsioon</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>TEENUSTE EELTEADE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaldamise viide</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Menetlus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Piiratud</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmi nimetus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (Euroopa naabruspoliitika rahastamisvahend)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rahastamine</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI 2017-2018. aasta idapiirkonna tegevusprogramm (eelarverida 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Avaliku sektori hankija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Euroopa Liit</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, keda esindab Euroopa Komisjon, abisaajate riikide eest ja nimel, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüssel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu laad</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Tasupõhine</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lepingu kirjeldus</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Idapartnerluse, Musta mere sünergia ja põhjamõõtme raames korraldatakse mitmesuguseid eri konverentse, seminare, kohtumisi ja koolitusi (esialgne loetelu), mille abil süvendatakse veelgi partnerriikidega peetavat poliitilist dialoogi, samuti korraldatakse foorum teabe ja kogemuste jagamiseks partnerriikide meetmete kohta harmoneerimise, reformide ja moderniseerimise vallas. Lepingu üldeesmärk on tagada nende ürituste korraldus ja logistika, samuti uuringud ja temaatiliste erialateadmiste pakkumine.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Soovituslik eelarve</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Hanketeate avaldamise esialgne aeg</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Märts 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Lisateave</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Õiguslik alus (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014. aasta määrus (EL) nr 236/2014, milles sätestatakse liidu välistegevuse rahastamisvahendite rakendamise ühiseeskirjad ja menetlused, ning Euroopa Parlamendi ja nõukogu 11.3.2014. aasta määrus (EL) nr 232/2014, millega luuakse Euroopa naabruspoliitika rahastamisvahend.</P><P>Võtke teadmiseks, et olenevalt läbirääkimiste tulemustest kohaldatakse pärast Ühendkuningriigi EList lahkumist Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaatidele või pakkujatele kolmandates riikides asutatud ettevõtjatele kehtivaid ELi hankemenetlustele juurepääsu käsitlevaid eeskirju. Juhul, kui selline juurdepääs ei ole tagatud lepingu sõlmimise ajal kehtivate õiguslike sätete kaudu, võidakse Ühendkuningriigist pärit kandidaadid või pakkujad hankemenetlusest kõrvale jätta.</P><P>(1) Märkige kõik erijooned, mis võivad mõjutada osalemise tingimusi (näiteks geograafilised erijooned, valdkond, lühike või pikk tähtaeg).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Märkused:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Eelteate ja vastava hanketeate avaldamise vahele peab jääma vähemalt 30 kalendripäeva.</P><P>Taotlusi ega teabenõudeid ei või selles etapis veel saata.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brüsszel: ENI - Konferenciák, szemináriumok, értekezletek és képzések szervezése és támogatása a Keleti partnerség, a Fekete-tengeri szinergia és az Északi Dimenzió keretében</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Helyszín – EU-tagállamok, Örményország, Azerbajdzsán, Fehéroroszország, Grúzia, Izland, Moldovai Köztársaság, Norvégia, Oroszországi Föderáció, Törökország, Ukrajna</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>SZOLGÁLTATÁSRA IRÁNYULÓ ELŐZETES ÖSSZESÍTETT HIRDETMÉNY</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A közzététel hivatkozási száma</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Eljárás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Meghívásos</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A program neve</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Európai Szomszédsági Támogatási Eszköz (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanszírozás</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI Keleti Regionális Cselekvési Program, 2017 és 2018 (22.040304. sz. költségvetési tétel)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ajánlatkérő</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Az Európai Unió</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, amelyet az Európai Bizottság képvisel, a kedvezményezett országok nevében és megbízásából, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brüsszel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgium.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés típusa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Díjalapú</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>A szerződés meghatározása</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A keleti partnerség, a fekete-tengeri szinergia és az északi dimenzió konferenciák, szemináriumok, értekezletek és képzések (tájékoztató jellegű felsorolás) széles skáláját biztosítja a partnerországokkal való politikai párbeszéd további mélyítésének, valamint a partnerországok a harmonizáció, a reformok és a modernizáció érdekében tett lépéseinek információ- és tapasztalatmegosztó fórumának eszközeként. A szerződés általános célja e rendezvények szervezésének és logisztikájának megoldása, valamint tanulmányok készítése és tematikus szakértelem biztosítása.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Várható költségvetés</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Az ajánlati felhívás közzétételének tervezett időpontja</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018. március</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>További információk</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Jogalap (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>A külső tevékenységek finanszírozására vonatkozó uniós eszközök végrehajtására vonatkozó közös szabályok és eljárások megállapításáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű 236/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet, valamint az Európai Szomszédsági és Partnerségi Támogatási Eszköz létrehozásáról szóló, 11.3.2014 keltezésű 232/2014/EU európai parlamenti és tanácsi rendelet.</P><P>Figyelembe kell venni, hogy az Egyesült Királyságnak az EU-ból való kilépése után az Egyesült Királyságból származó jelentkezőkre vagy ajánlattevőkre – a tárgyalások kimenetelétől függően – az EU közbeszerzési eljárásaihoz való hozzáférés tekintetében a harmadik országok gazdasági szereplői számára érvényes szabályok vonatkoznak. Amennyiben az ilyen eljárásokban való részvételről nem rendelkezik a szerződés odaítélésének időpontjában hatályban lévő jogszabály, az Egyesült Királyságban székhellyel rendelkező jelentkezőket, illetve ajánlattevőket kizárhatják a közbeszerzési eljárásból.</P><P>(1) Kérjük, jelezzen bármely olyan sajátosságot, amely hatással lehet a részvételi szabályokra (például földrajzi, tematikai vagy hosszú/rövid távú sajátosság).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Megjegyzések:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Legalább 30 naptári napnak kell eltelnie a jelen előzetes összesített hirdetmény megjelenése és a vonatkozó ajánlati felhívás közzététele között.</P><P>Ezen időszak alatt jelentkezések benyújtásának, illetve információkérésnek nincs helye.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Briuselis: ENI - Konferencijų, seminarų, posėdžių ir mokymų organizavimas ir parama, remiantis Rytų partneryste, Juodosios jūros sinergija ir Šiaurės dimensija</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vieta – ES valstybės narės, Armėnija, Azerbaidžanas, Baltarusija, Gruzija, Islandija, Moldovos Respublika, Norvegija, Rusijos Federacija, Turkija, Ukraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IŠANKSTINIS INFORMACINIS SKELBIMAS APIE PASLAUGŲ PIRKIMĄ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nuoroda į publikaciją</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ribotas konkursas</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programos pavadinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (Europos kaimynystės priemonė)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansavimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2017 m. ir 2018 m. Europos kaimynystės priemonės regioninė veiksmų programa Rytams (biudžeto eilutė 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Perkančioji organizacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europos Sąjunga</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, atstovaujama Europos Komisijos paramą gaunančių šalių vardu ir jų naudai, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Briuselis</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties pobūdis</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Mokama</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Sutarties apibūdinimas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rytų partneryste, Juodosios jūros sinergija ir Šiaurės dimensija numatomos įvairios konferencijos, seminarai, posėdžiai, mokymai (preliminarus sąrašas), kuriais toliau bus stiprinamas politinis dialogas su šalimis partnerėmis, bei forumas, kuriame bus keičiamasi informacija ir patirtimi dėl šalių partnerių veiksmų, susijusių su derinimu, reforma ir modernizavimu. Bendras sutarties uždavinys – vykdyti šių renginių organizavimą ir logistiką, tai pat tyrimus ir teikti teminę ekspertizę.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatomas biudžetas</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numatoma skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo data</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018 m. kovo mėn.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildoma informacija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teisinis pagrindas (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 236/2014, kuriuo nustatomos bendros Sąjungos išorės veiksmų finansavimo priemonių įgyvendinimo taisyklės ir procedūros, ir 11.3.2014 Europos Parlamento ir Tarybos reglamentas (ES) Nr. 232/2014, kuriuo sukuriama Europos kaimynystės priemonė.</P><P>Prašome atkreipti dėmesį, kad Jungtinei Karalystei pasitraukus iš ES, ekonominės veiklos vykdytojų, įsikūrusių trečiosiose šalyse, prieigos prie ES pirkimo procedūrų taisyklės bus taikomos kandidatams ar konkurso dalyviams iš Jungtinės Karalystės, priklausomai nuo derybų rezultato. Jeigu tokia prieiga nebus suteikta galiojančiomis teisinėmis nuostatomis, kandidatai arba konkurso dalyviai iš Jungtinės Karalystės gali būti pašalinti iš pirkimo procedūros.</P><P>(1) Nurodykite bet kokias aplinkybes, galinčias turėti įtakos dalyvavimo taisyklėms (pvz., geografines ar temines, ilgalaikes ar trumpalaikes).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Pastabos:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Nuo šio išankstinio informacinio skelbimo publikavimo iki atitinkamo skelbimo apie pirkimą publikavimo turi praeiti mažiausiai 30 kalendorinių dienų.</P><P>Šiuo etapu negalima siųsti paraiškų ar kreiptis dėl informacijos.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brisele: EKI - Konferenču, semināru, sanāksmju un apmācības organizēšana un atbalsts Austrumu partnerības, Melnās jūras reģiona sinerģijas un Ziemeļu dimensijas ietvaros</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Vieta – ES dalībvalstis, Armēnija, Azerbaidžāna, Baltkrievija, Gruzija, Islande, Moldovas Republika, Norvēģija, Krievijas Federācija, Turcija, Ukraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>IEPRIEKŠĒJS INFORMATĪVS PAZIŅOJUMS PAR PAKALPOJUMU LĪGUMU</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Atsauce uz publikāciju</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedūra</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Slēgta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Programmas nosaukums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EKI (Eiropas kaimiņattiecību instruments)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansējums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EKI Austrumu reģiona rīcības programma 2017. gadam un 2018. gadam (budžeta līnija 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līgumslēdzēja iestāde</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Eiropas Savienība</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ko saņēmējvalstu vārdā un interesēs pārstāv Eiropas Komisija, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brisele</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Beļģija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma veids</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Līgums, kura pamatā ir samaksa par pakalpojumiem</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Līguma apraksts</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Austrumu partnerība, Melnās jūras reģiona sinerģija un Ziemeļu dimensija paredz virkni konferenču, semināru, sanāksmju un apmācību (indikatīvs uzskaitījums) kā līdzekli turpmākai politiskā dialoga ar partnervalstīm padziļināšanai un forumu tādas informācijas un pieredzes apmaiņai, kas attiecas uz partnervalstu rīcību harmonizācijas, reformu un modernizācijas nodrošināšanai. Līguma vispārējais mērķis ir vadīt šo pasākumu organizēšanu un materiāltehnisko apgādi, kā arī pētījumus un tematiskās zinātības nodrošināšanu.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Provizoriskais budžets</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Paziņojuma par līgumu paredzamais publicēšanas datums</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>2018. gada marts</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Papildu informācija</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tiesiskais pamats (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 236/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko paredz kopīgus noteikumus un procedūras, lai īstenotu Savienības instrumentus ārējās darbības finansēšanai, un Eiropas Parlamenta un Padomes Regula (ES) Nr. 232/2014 (2014. gada 11. marts), ar ko izveido Eiropas kaimiņattiecību instrumentu.</P><P>Lūdzam ņemt vērā, ka pēc Apvienotās Karalistes izstāšanās no ES uz kandidātiem un pretendentiem no Apvienotās Karalistes atkarībā no sarunu iznākuma attieksies noteikumi par trešo valstu uzņēmēju tiesībām piedalīties ES iepirkuma procedūrās. Ja līguma slēgšanas tiesību piešķiršanas brīdī spēkā esošajās tiesību normās šāda piekļuve nebūs paredzēta, kandidāti vai pretendenti no Apvienotās Karalistes var tikt izslēgti no iepirkuma procedūras.</P><P>(1) Lūdzam norādīt visus specifiskos iemeslus (piemēram, ģeogrāfiskus, tematiskus, īstermiņa vai ilgtermiņa), kas var ietekmēt dalības noteikumus.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Piezīmes</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Starp šā iepriekšējā informatīvā paziņojuma un attiecīgā paziņojuma par līgumu publicēšanas datumiem jāpaiet vismaz 30 kalendārajām dienām.</P><P>Šajā posmā nekādus pieteikumus vai informācijas pieprasījumus nesūtīt.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brussell: ENI - Organizzazzjoni ta' u appoġġ għal konferenzi, seminars, laqgħat u taħriġ fil-qafas tal-Isħubija tal-Lvant, is-Sinerġija tal-Baħar l-Iswed u d-Dimensjoni tat-Tramuntana</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Il-post — l-Istati Membri tal-UE, l-Armenja, l-Ażerbajġan, il-Belarussja, il-Georgia, l-Iżlanda ir-Repubblika tal-Moldova, in-Norveġja, il-Federazzjoni Russa, it-Turkija, l-Ukrajna</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>AVVIŻ TA' TAGĦRIF MINN QABEL DWAR SERVIZZ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Ir-referenza tal-pubblikazzjoni</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-proċedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ristretta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-titlu tal-programm</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (Strument Ewropew tal-Viċinat)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-iffinanzjar</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Il-Programm ta' Ħidma Reġjonali tal-Lvant tal-ENI għall-2017 u l-2018 (Il-linja tal-baġit 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>L-awtorità li qiegħda toħroġ il-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>l-Unjoni Ewropea</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, irrappreżentata mill-Kummissjoni Ewropea, f'isem u għall-pajjiżi benefiċjarji, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brussell</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, il-Belġju.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>It-tip ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bil-ħlas ta' miżata</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Id-deskrizzjoni tal-kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Is-Sħubija tal-Lvant, is-Sinerġija tal-Baħar l-Iswed u d-Dimensjoni tat-Tramuntana jipprovdu firxa wiesgħa ta' konferenzi, seminars, laqgħat, taħriġ (lista indikattiva) bħala mezz ta' aktar tfannid tad-djalogu politiku ma' pajjiżi msieħba u forum biex jinqasmu t-tagħrif u l-esperjenzi dwar il-passi li qed jieħdu l-pajjiżi msieħba lejn l-armonizzazzjoni, ir-riforma u l-modernizzazzjoni. L-objettiv ġenerali tal-kuntratt huwa li jimmaniġġja l-organizzazzjoni u l-loġistika ta' dawn l-avvenimenti, kif ukoll l-istudji u l-provvista ta' kompetenza tematika.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-baġit indikattiv</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Iż-żmien maħsub għall-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Marzu tal-2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagħrif addizzjonali</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Il-bażi legali (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ir-Regolament (UE) Nru 236/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi regoli u proċeduri komuni għall-implimentazzjoni tal-istrumenti tal-Unjoni għall-finanzjament tal-azzjoni esterna u r-Regolament (UE) Nru 232/2014 tal-Parlament Ewropew u tal-Kunsill tal-11 ta' Marzu 2014 li jistabbilixxi Strument Ewropew tal-Viċinat.</P><P>Jekk jogħġbok kun af li wara l-irtirar tar-Renju Unit mill-UE, ir-regoli tal-aċċess għall-proċeduri ta' ksib tal-UE ta' operaturi ekonomiċi mwaqqfa f'pajjiżi terzi se japplikaw għall-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit skont ir-riżultat tan-negozjati. F'każ li tali aċċess mhux ipprovdut minn dispożizzjonijiet legali fis-seħħ fil-ħin tal-għoti tal-kuntratt, il-kandidati jew dawk li jitfgħu l-offerti mir-Renju Unit jistgħu jiġu mwarrba mill-proċedura tal-ksib.</P><P>(1) Jekk jogħġbok niżżel kwalunkwe speċifiċità li jista' jkollha impatt fuq ir-regoli għas-sehem (bħal dik ġeografika jew tematika jew fuq żmien qasir jew fit-tul).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Kummenti:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Irid ikun hemm perijodu minimu ta' 30 jum kalendarju bejn il-pubblikazzjoni ta' dan l-avviż ta' tagħrif minn qabel u l-pubblikazzjoni tal-avviż ta' kuntratt li għandu x'jaqsam miegħu.</P><P>M'għandhomx jintbagħtu applikazzjonijiet jew talbiet għal tagħrif f'dan l-istadju.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruksela: ENI - Organizacja i wsparcie konferencji, seminariów, spotkań i szkoleń w ramach Partnerstwa Wschodniego, synergii czarnomorskiej i wymiaru północnego</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokalizacja – państwa członkowskie UE, Armenia, Azerbejdżan, Białoruś, Federacja Rosyjska, Gruzja, Islandia, Norwegia, Republika Mołdawii, Turcja, Ukraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>WSTĘPNE OGŁOSZENIE INFORMACYJNE DOTYCZĄCE ZAMÓWIENIA NA USŁUGI</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Numer referencyjny publikacji</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedura</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograniczona</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nazwa programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Europejski Instrument Sąsiedztwa (ENI)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finansowanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regionalny program ENI Wschód 2017 i 2018 (linia budżetowa 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Instytucja zamawiająca</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Unia Europejska</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentowana przez Komisję Europejską, w imieniu i na rzecz państwa beneficjenta, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruksela</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Rodzaj zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Według stawek jednostkowych</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis zamówienia</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Partnerstwo Wschodnie, synergia czarnomorska i wymiar północny przewidują organizację różnego typu konferencji, seminariów, spotkań i szkoleń (orientacyjna lista), które służą dalszemu pogłębianiu dialogu politycznego z krajami partnerskimi oraz stanowią forum służące wymianie informacji i doświadczeń w zakresie podejmowanych przez kraje partnerskie działań na rzecz harmonizacji, reform i modernizacji. Ogólnym celem zamówienia jest organizacja i obsługa logistyczna tych wydarzeń, a także przeprowadzanie badań i świadczenie ekspertyzy w danej dziedzinie.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Orientacyjny budżet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Planowana data publikacji ogłoszenia o zamówieniu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Marzec 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informacje dodatkowe</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Podstawa prawna (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 236/2014 z dnia 11.3.2014 ustanawiające wspólne zasady i procedury wdrażania unijnych instrumentów na rzecz finansowania działań zewnętrznych i rozporządzenie Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) nr 232/2014 z dnia 11.3.2014 ustanawiające Europejski Instrument Sąsiedztwa.</P><P>Należy mieć świadomość, że po wystąpieniu Zjednoczonego Królestwa z UE brytyjscy kandydaci i oferenci będą podlegać zasadom dostępu do unijnych procedur udzielania zamówień podmiotom gospodarczym w państwach trzecich w zależności od wyniku negocjacji. W sytuacji gdy przepisy prawa obowiązujące w chwili udzielenia zamówienia nie będą przewidywać takiego dostępu, kandydaci lub oferenci ze Zjednoczonego Królestwa mogą zostać wykluczeni z postępowania o udzielenie zamówienia.</P><P>(1) Uprasza się o wskazanie wszelkich okoliczności, które mogą mieć wpływ na warunki udziału (takie jak uwarunkowania geograficzne, tematyczne lub kwestie długo- lub krótkoterminowe).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Uwagi:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Między publikacją niniejszego wstępnego ogłoszenia informacyjnego a publikacją odpowiedniego ogłoszenia o zamówieniu musi upłynąć co najmniej 30 dni kalendarzowych.</P><P>Na tym etapie nie należy przesyłać wniosków ani zapytań o informacje.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Brusel: ENI - Organizácia a podpora pre konferencie, semináre, stretnutia a školenia v rámci Východného partnerstva, Čiernomorskej synergie a Severnej dimenzie</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Miesto – členské štáty EÚ, Arménsko, Azerbajdžan, Bielorusko, Gruzínsko, Island, Moldavská republika, Nórsko, Ruská federácia, Turecko, Ukrajina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDBEŽNÉ OZNÁMENIE O OBSTARÁVANÍ SLUŽIEB</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčné číslo</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Konanie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Užšia súťaž</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Názov programu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (Nástroj európskeho susedstva)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Zdroj financovania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Východný regionálny akčný program ENI na rok 2017 a 2018 (rozpočtová položka 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Verejný obstarávateľ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Európska únia</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, zastúpená Európskou komisiou v mene a v záujme užívateľských krajín, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Brusel</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgicko.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Charakter verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Odplatné</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Východné partnerstvo, Čiernomorská synergia a Severná dimenzia poskytujú celý rad konferencií, seminárov, stretnutí, školení (orientačný zoznam) ako nástroj ďalšieho prehĺbenia politického dialógu medzi partnerskými krajinami a fórum na výmenu informácií a skúseností o krokoch partnerských krajín smerom k harmonizácii, reforme a modernizácii. Všeobecným cieľom obstarávania je riadenie organizácie a logistiky týchto podujatí, ako aj štúdií a poskytovania tematickej expertízy.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predbežný rozpočet</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Plánovaný dátum zverejnenia oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>marec 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatočné informácie</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Právny základ (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 236/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovujú spoločné pravidlá a postupy pre vykonávanie nástrojov Únie na financovanie vonkajšej činnosti, a nariadenie Európskeho parlamentu a Rady (EÚ) č. 232/2014 z 11.3.2014, ktorým sa ustanovuje nástroj európskeho susedstva.</P><P>Pripomíname, že po vystúpení Spojeného kráľovstva z EÚ sa na záujemcov alebo uchádzačov zo Spojeného kráľovstva, v závislosti od výsledku rokovaní, budú uplatňovať pravidlá prístupu k postupom obstarávania EÚ zo strany hospodárskych subjektov so sídlom v tretích krajinách. V prípade, že takýto prístup sa nezabezpečí ustanoveniami platnými v čase pridelenia zákazky, záujemcovia alebo uchádzači zo Spojeného kráľovstva by mohli byť vylúčení z obstarávacieho konania.</P><P>(1) Uveďte akékoľvek špecifiká, ktoré by mohli mať vplyv na pravidlá účasti (napríklad geografické alebo tematické, dlhodobé alebo krátkodobé).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Poznámky:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Medzi uverejnením predbežného oznámenia a uverejnením príslušného oznámenia o vyhlásení verejného obstarávania musí uplynúť minimálne 30 kalendárnych dní.</P><P>V tomto období sa nemajú zasielať žiadne prihlášky ani žiadosti o informácie.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruselj: ENI - Organizacija in podpora za konference, seminarje, srečanja in usposabljanja v okviru vzhodnega partnerstva, sinergije Črnega morja in severne dimenzije</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokacija – države članice EU, Armenija, Azerbajdžan, Belorusija, Gruzija, Islandija, Norveška, Republika Moldavija, Ruska federacija, Turčija, Ukrajina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PREDHODNO INFORMATIVNO OBVESTILO O NAROČILU STORITEV</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referenčna številka dokumenta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postopek</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Omejeni</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (evropski instrument sosedstva)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regionalni akcijski program za vzhod v okviru ENI za leti 2017 in 2018 (proračunska postavka 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naročnik</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Evropska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, ki jo zastopa Evropska komisija, v imenu in za račun držav upravičenk, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruselj</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Vrsta naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Na podlagi plačila</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis naročila</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Vzhodno partnerstvo, sinergija Črnega morja in severna dimenzija predvidevajo celoten niz konferenc, seminarjev, srečanj in usposabljanja (okvirni seznam) kot sredstvo za nadaljnjo poglobitev političnega dialoga z državami partnericami in foruma za izmenjavo informacij in izkušenj o ukrepih držav partneric na področju usklajevanja, reforme in modernizacije. Splošni cilj naročila zajema upravljanje organizacije in logistike teh dogodkov ter študije in zagotavljanje tematskega strokovnega znanja.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Okvirni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predvideni datum objave obvestila o naročilu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Marec 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravna podlaga (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uredba (EU) št. 236/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o določitvi skupnih pravil in postopkov za izvajanje instrumentov Unije za financiranje zunanjega delovanja in Uredba (EU) št. 232/2014 Evropskega parlamenta in Sveta z dne 11.3.2014 o vzpostavitvi evropskega instrumenta sosedstva.</P><P>Upoštevajte, da se bodo po izstopu Združenega kraljestva iz EU pravila za dostop do razpisnih postopkov EU s strani gospodarskih subjektov, ustanovljenih v tretjih državah, za kandidate ali ponudnike iz Združenega kraljestva uporabljala v skladu z rezultati pogajanj. V primeru, da v času oddaje naročila veljavne pravne določbe ne zagotavljajo tovrstnega dostopa, se lahko kandidatom ali ponudnikom iz Združenega kraljestva sodelovanje v razpisnem postopku zavrne.</P><P>(1) Navedite kakršno koli posebnost, ki bi lahko vplivala na pravila za sodelovanje (na primer geografsko ali tematsko ali dolgo-/kratkoročno).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Opombe:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Med objavo tega predhodnega informativnega obvestila in objavo ustreznega obvestila o naročilu mora preteči vsaj 30 koledarskih dni.</P><P>V tej fazi ne pošiljajte prijav ali zahtevkov za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-An Bhruiséil: ENI - Comhdhálacha, seimineáir, cruinnithe agus seisiúin oiliúna a eagrú agus tacú leo faoi chuimsiú Chomhpháirtíocht an Oirthir, Shineirge na Mara Duibhe agus Dhiminsean an Tuaiscirt</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Láthair — Ballstáit an AE, an Airméin, an Asarbaiseáin, an Bhealarúis, Cónaidhm na Rúise, an Iorua, an Íoslainn, Poblacht na Moldóive, an tSeoirsia, an Tuirc, an Úcráin</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>FÓGRA RÉAMHAISNÉISE SEIRBHÍSE</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Tagairt an fhoilseacháin</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Nós imeachta</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Teoranta</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Teideal an chláir</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (an Ionstraim Eorpach um Chomharsanacht)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Maoiniú</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Clár Gníomhaíochta Réigiúnach ENI an Oirthir 2017 &amp; 2018 (Líne bhuiséadach 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Údarás Conarthach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>An tAontas Eorpach</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, arna ionadú ag an gCoimisiún Eorpach, thar ceann agus chun cuntais na dtíortha is tairbhithe, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>an Bhruiséil</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, an Bheilg.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cineál an chonartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bunaithe ar tháille</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Cur síos ar an gconradh</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Déantar foráil le Comhpháirtíocht an Oirthir, le Sineirge na Mara Duibhe agus le Diminsean an Tuaiscirt do raon iomlán comhdhálacha, seimineár, cruinnithe agus oiliúna (liosta táscach) mar mhodh chun an t-idirphlé polaitiúil le tíortha is comhpháirtithe a threisiú a thuilleadh agus d'fhóram chun faisnéis agus eispéiris a chomhroinnt maidir le céimeanna na dtíortha is comhpháirtithe i dtreo comhchuibhithe, athchóirithe agus nuachóirithe. Is é cuspóir foriomlán an chonartha eagrúchán agus lóistíocht na n-imeachtaí sin a láimhseáil, i dteannta le staidéir agus soláthar saineolais théamaigh.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buiséad táscach</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>An sprioc atá beartaithe d'fhoilsiú an fhógra conartha</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Márta 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Faisnéis bhreise</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Bunús dlí (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Rialachán (CE) Uimh. 236/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 lena leagtar síos na rialacha agus na nósanna imeachta coiteanna le haghaidh ionstraimí an Aontais a chur chun feidhme chun an ghníomhaíocht sheachtrach a mhaoiniú; agus Rialachán (AE) Uimh. 232/2014 ó Pharlaimint na hEorpa agus ón gComhairle an 11.3.2014 lena mbunaítear Ionstraim Eorpach um Chomharsanacht.</P><P>Tabhair faoi deara go gcuirfear na rialacha um rochtain ar nósanna imeachta soláthair an AE ag oibreoirí eacnamaíocha atá bunaithe i dtríú tíortha i bhfeidhm ar iarrthóirí nó ar thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe tar éis di tarraingt siar ón AE, ag brath ar thorthaí na hidirbheartaíochta. Sa chás nach gcuirfear a leithéid de rochtain ar fáil trí fhorálacha dlíthiúla a bheidh i bhfeidhm nuair a dhámhfar an conradh, d'fhéadfaí diúltú do thairgeoirí ón Ríocht Aontaithe ón nós imeachta soláthair.</P><P>(1) Luaigh aon sainiúlacht a d’fhéadfadh tionchar a bheith aige ar rialacha na rannpháirtíochta (amhail sainiúlacht thíreolaíoch nó théamach, nó sainiúlacht fhadtéarmach/ghearrthéarmach).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Nótaí:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Ní mór tréimhse 30 lá féilire ar a laghad a bheith idir foilsiú an fhógra réamhaisnéise seo agus foilsiú an fhógra conartha chomhfhreagraigh.</P><P>Níor cheart aon iarratais ná iarrataí ar fhaisnéis a sheoladh faoi láthair.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Брюксел: ЕИС - Организиране на конференции, семинари, заседания и обучения в рамките на Източното партньорство, Черноморско взаимодействие и Северно измерение</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Местоположение — държави — членки на ЕС, Армения, Азербайджан, Беларус, Грузия, Исландия, Република Молдова, Норвегия, Руска федерация, Турция, Украйна</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ОБЯВЛЕНИЕ ЗА ПРЕДВАРИТЕЛНА ИНФОРМАЦИЯ ЗА УСЛУГИ</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Референтен номер на публикация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Процедура</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ограничена</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Заглавие на програма</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ЕИС (Европейски инструмент за съседство)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Финансиране</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Източна регионална програма за действие за 2017 и 2018 г. по ЕИС (бюджетен ред 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Възлагащ орган</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Европейски съюз</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, представляван от Европейската комисия, от името и за сметка на държавите-бенефициери, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Брюксел</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Белгия.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Вид на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Комисионна поръчка</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Описание на поръчката</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Източното партньорство, Черноморското взаимодействие и Северното измерение предоставят широка сфера от конференции, семинари, заседания, обучение (индикативен списък) като средства за допълнително задълбочаване на политическия диалог с държави-партньори и форум за обмен на информация и опит относно стъпките на държавите-партньори към хармонизиране, реформа и модернизация. Общата цел на поръчката е уреждане на организацията и логистиката за тези събития, както и проучвания и предоставяне на тематична експертиза.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Индикативен бюджет</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Очакван срок за публикуване на обявлението за поръчка</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>март 2018 г.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Допълнителна информация</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Правно основание (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Регламент (ЕС) № 236/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за определяне на общи правила и процедури за изпълнението на инструментите на Съюза за финансиране на външната дейност и Регламент (ЕС) № 232/2014 на Европейския парламент и на Съвета от 11.3.2014 г. за създаване на Европейски инструмент за съседство.</P><P>Моля, имайте предвид, че след оттеглянето на Обединеното кралство от ЕС, правилата за достъп до процедури за обществени поръчки на ЕС за икономически оператори, установени в трети държави, ще се прилагат за кандидати или оференти от Обединеното кралство, в зависимост от резултата от преговорите. В случай че такъв достъп не е предвиден в действащите правни разпоредби, които са в сила по време на възлагането на поръчката, кандидатите или оферентите от Обединеното кралство могат да бъдат отхвърлени от процедурата за обществена поръчка.</P><P>(1) Моля, посочете всяка особеност, която може да окаже въздействие върху правилата за участие (напр. географска или тематична, или кратък/дълъг срок).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Забележки:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Трябва да има минимален период от 30 календарни дни между публикуването на това обявление за предварителна информация и публикуването на съответното обявление за поръчка.</P><P>На този етап не трябва да се изпращат никакви молби или искания за информация.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: IEV - Organizare și asistență pentru conferințe, seminarii, reuniuni și cursuri de formare în cadrul Parteneriatului estic, al Sinergiei Mării Negre și al Dimensiunii nordice</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Locație – statele membre ale UE, Armenia, Azerbaidjan, Belarus, Federația Rusă, Georgia, Islanda, Republica Moldova, Norvegia, Turcia, Ucraina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>ANUNȚ DE INTENȚIE PRIVIND UN CONTRACT DE ACHIZIȚII PUBLICE DE SERVICII</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Referința publicației</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Procedură</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Restrânsă</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Titlul programului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>IEV (Instrumentul european de vecinătate)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Finanțare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Programul de acțiune pentru regiunea estică IEV pentru 2017 &amp; 2018 (linia bugetară 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Autoritatea contractantă</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Uniunea Europeană</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, reprezentată de Comisia Europeană, în numele și în favoarea țărilor beneficiare, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgia.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Natura contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Bazat pe onorarii</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Descrierea contractului</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Parteneriatul estic, Sinergia Mării Negre și Dimensiunea nordică asigură o gamă întreagă de conferințe, seminarii, reuniuni și cursuri de formare (listă indicativă) ca mijloc de a continua aprofundarea dialogului politic cu țările partenere și un forum pentru partajarea de informații și de experiențe privind eforturile depuse de țările partenere în scopul armonizării, reformării și modernizării. Obiectivul general al contractului este de a gestiona organizarea și logistica acestor evenimente, precum și studii și furnizarea de expertiză tematică.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Buget indicativ</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Data prevăzută de publicare a anunțului de participare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Martie 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Informații suplimentare</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Temeiul juridic (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Regulamentul (UE) nr. 236/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de stabilire a normelor și procedurilor comune pentru punerea în aplicare a instrumentelor Uniunii pentru finanțarea acțiunii externe și Regulamentul (UE) nr. 232/2014 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 11.3.2014 de instituire a unui instrument european de vecinătate.</P><P>A se avea în vedere că, după retragerea Marii Britanii din UE, normele de acces al operatorilor economici stabiliți în țări terțe la procedurile de achiziții publice ale UE se vor aplica ofertanților sau candidaților din Marea Britanie în funcție de rezultatul negocierilor. În cazul în care accesul nu este prevăzut de dispozițiile juridice în vigoare la momentul atribuirii contractului, candidații sau ofertanții din Regatul Unit ar putea fi respinși de la procedura de achiziții publice.</P><P>(1) Vă rugăm să precizați orice specificitate care ar putea avea un impact asupra regulilor de participare (cum ar fi de ordin geografic sau tematic sau pe termen lung / scurt).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Observații:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Trebuie respectată o perioadă de minimum 30 de zile calendaristice între publicarea prezentului anunț de intenție și publicarea anunțului de participare corespunzător.</P><P>În această etapă nu se acceptă candidaturi sau cereri de informații.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BE-Bruxelles: ENI - Organizacija i podrška za konferencije, seminare, sastanke i osposobljavanje u okviru Istočnog partnerstva, Crnomorske sinergije i Sjeverne dimenzije</P></TI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>Lokacija — države članice EU-a, Armenija, Azerbajdžan, Bjelarus, Gruzija, Island, Republika Moldova, Norveška, Ruska Federacija, Turska, Ukrajina</P></STI_DOC><STI_DOC><P>PRETHODNA INFORMACIJSKA OBAVIJEST O USLUGAMA</P></STI_DOC><CONTENTS><MARK_LIST><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="001"><NO_MARK>1.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Uputa na objavu</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>EuropeAid/139527/DH/SER/MULTI</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="002"><NO_MARK>2.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Postupak</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Ograničeni</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="003"><NO_MARK>3.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Naslov programa</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI (Europski instrument za susjedstvo)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="004"><NO_MARK>4.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Financiranje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ENI Regionalni istočni akcijski program 2017. i 2018. (proračunska stavka 22.040304)</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="005"><NO_MARK>5.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Javni naručitelj</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><ORGANISATION>Europska unija</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, koju predstavlja Europska komisija, u ime i za račun država korisnica, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Bruxelles</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, Belgija.</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="006"><NO_MARK>6.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Priroda ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Temeljen na naknadama</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="007"><NO_MARK>7.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Opis ugovora</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Istočno partnerstvo, Crnomorska sinergija i Sjeverna dimenzija predviđaju cijeli niz konferencija, seminara, sastanaka, osposobljavanja (indikativni popis) kao načina daljnjeg razvijanja političkog dijaloga s partnerskim državama i foruma za dijeljenje informacija i iskustava o koracima partnerskih država prema usklađivanju, reformi i modernizaciji. Ukupni je cilj ugovora pružanje usluga organizacije i logističkih usluga za navedena događanja, kao i studije i pružanje tematske stručnosti.</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="008"><NO_MARK>8.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Indikativni proračun</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>7 200 000 EUR</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="009"><NO_MARK>9.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Predviđeni datum objave poziva na nadmetanje</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>ožujak 2018</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="010"><NO_MARK>10.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Dodatne informacije</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P/></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR><MLI_OCCUR NO_SEQ="011"><NO_MARK>11.</NO_MARK><TI_MARK>Pravni temelj (1)</TI_MARK><TXT_MARK><P>Uredba (EU) br. 236/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014 o utvrđivanju zajedničkih pravila i postupaka za provedbu instrumenata Unije za financiranje vanjskog djelovanja i Uredba (EU) br. 232/2014 Europskog parlamenta i Vijeća od 11.3.2014 o uspostavi Europskog instrumenta za susjedstvo.</P><P>Napominjemo da će se nakon povlačenja Ujedinjene Kraljevine iz EU-a na natjecatelje ili ponuditelje iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine primjenjivati pravila pristupa postupcima nabave EU-a za gospodarske subjekte s poslovnim nastanom u trećim zemljama, ovisno o rezultatima pregovora. U slučaju da pristup nije omogućen putem pravnih odredbi koje su na snazi u vrijeme sklapanja ugovora, natjecatelji ili ponuditelji iz Ujedinjene Kraljevine mogu biti odbijeni iz postupka javne nabave.</P><P>(1) Molimo navedite bilo kakve pojedinosti koje bi mogle utjecati na pravila sudjelovanja (poput geografskih ili tematskih ili dugoročnih/kratkoročnih).</P></TXT_MARK></MLI_OCCUR></MARK_LIST><GR_SEQ><TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX>Napomene:</BLK_BTX></TI_GRSEQ><BLK_BTX_SEQ><P>Između objave ove prethodne informacijske obavijesti i objave odgovarajućeg poziva na nadmetanje mora proći najmanje 30 kalendarskih dana.</P><P>U toj se fazi ne smiju slati prijave ili zahtjevi za informacije.</P></BLK_BTX_SEQ></GR_SEQ></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>