<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="095206-2018" EDITION="2018044"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-093022-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180413</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>DA DE EN ES FI FR EL IT NL PT SV CS ET HU LT LV MT PL SK SL GA BG RO HR </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>44</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180303</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 044-095206</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="DA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:DA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="DE">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:DE:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ES">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:ES:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FI">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:FI:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="FR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:FR:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="EL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:EL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="IT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:IT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="NL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:NL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:PT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:SV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="CS">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:CS:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="ET">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:ET:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HU">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:HU:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:LT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="LV">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:LV:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="MT">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:MT:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="PL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:PL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SK">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:SK:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="SL">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:SL:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="GA">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:GA:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="BG">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:BG:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="RO">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:RO:HTML</URI_DOC><URI_DOC LG="HR">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:095206-2018:TEXT:HR:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="MD"/><IA_URL_GENERAL/><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45233120">Road construction works</ORIGINAL_CPV><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="71520000">Construction supervision services</ORIGINAL_CPV></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180227</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180413 10:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="2">European Investment Bank, European Investment Fund, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="8">Other</AC_AWARD_CRIT><HEADING>BR405</HEADING></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBGU - Projekt til støtte af vejsektorprogram</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>Moldau</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWE - Unterstützungsprojekt für das Programm für Straßensektoren</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Road Sector Program Support Project</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Moldavia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Proyecto de apoyo al programa del sector viario</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Tiealaa koskevan ohjelman tukihanke</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Moldavie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Projet de soutien au programme du secteur routier</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>Μολδαβία</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Κισινάου</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ΕΤΑΑ - Σχέδιο υποστήριξης προγράμματος για τον οδικό τομέα</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERS - Progetto di sostegno al programma relativo al settore stradale</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>Moldavië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBWO - Project ter ondersteuning van het programma voor de wegensector</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>Moldávia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Projeto de apoio ao programa relativo ao setor rodoviário</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>Moldavien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Stödprojekt till program för vägsektorn</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Moldavsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kišiněv</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt na podporu programu silničního sektoru</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chişinău</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Maanteesektori programmi tugiprojekt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - A közúti ágazati programot támogató projekt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>Moldavija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kišiniovas</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERPB - Kelių sektoriaus programos rėmimo projektas</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kišiņeva</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ERAB - Ceļu nozares programmas atbalsta projekts</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>il-Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERŻ - Proġett ta' Appoġġ għall-Programm tas-Settur tat-Toroq</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Mołdawia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kiszyniów</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt wsparcia programu na rzecz sektora drogowego</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>Moldavsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kišiňov</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt podpory programu cestného sektora</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Moldavija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBOR - Projekt podpore programa za cestni sektor</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Mholdóiv, an</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Tionscadal Tacaíochta do Chlár na hEarnála Bóithre</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Молдова</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Кишинев</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>ЕБВР - Проект за подпомагане на програмата за пътния сектор</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Chisinau</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>BERD - Proiectul de Sprijin al Programului din Sectorul Rutier</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>Moldova</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Kišinjev</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>EBRD - Projekt podrške programu cestovnog sektora</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="DA">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="DE">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EN">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ES">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FI">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="FR">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="EL">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="IT">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="NL">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PT">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SV">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="CS">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="ET">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HU">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LT">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="LV">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="MT">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="PL">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SK">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="SL">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="GA">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="BG">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="RO">State Road Administration</AA_NAME><AA_NAME LG="HR">State Road Administration</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBGU - Projekt til støtte af vejsektorprogram (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="DE" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWE - Unterstützungsprojekt für das Programm für Straßensektoren (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Road Sector Program Support Project (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ES" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Proyecto de apoyo al programa del sector viario (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FI" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Tiealaa koskevan ohjelman tukihanke (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="FR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Projet de soutien au programme du secteur routier (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="EL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ΕΤΑΑ - Σχέδιο υποστήριξης προγράμματος για τον οδικό τομέα (MD-Κισινάου)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="IT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERS - Progetto di sostegno al programma relativo al settore stradale (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="NL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBWO - Project ter ondersteuning van het programma voor de wegensector (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Projeto de apoio ao programa relativo ao setor rodoviário (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Stödprojekt till program för vägsektorn (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="CS" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt na podporu programu silničního sektoru (MD-Kišiněv)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="ET" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Maanteesektori programmi tugiprojekt (MD-Chişinău)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HU" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - A közúti ágazati programot támogató projekt (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERPB - Kelių sektoriaus programos rėmimo projektas (MD-Kišiniovas)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="LV" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ERAB - Ceļu nozares programmas atbalsta projekts (MD-Kišiņeva)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="MT" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERŻ - Proġett ta' Appoġġ għall-Programm tas-Settur tat-Toroq (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="PL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt wsparcia programu na rzecz sektora drogowego (MD-Kiszyniów)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SK" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt podpory programu cestného sektora (MD-Kišiňov)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="SL" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBOR - Projekt podpore programa za cestni sektor (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="GA" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Tionscadal Tacaíochta do Chlár na hEarnála Bóithre (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="BG" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>ЕБВР - Проект за подпомагане на програмата за пътния сектор (MD-Кишинев)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="RO" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>BERD - Proiectul de Sprijin al Programului din Sectorul Rutier (MD-Chisinau)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT><OTH_NOT CATEGORY="TRANSLATION" LG="HR" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_OTH_NOT><TI_DOC><P>EBRD - Projekt podrške programu cestovnog sektora (MD-Kišinjev)</P></TI_DOC><CONTENTS><P/><P>Project name: Road Sector Program Support Project</P><P>Country: Republic of Moldova</P><P>Business sector: Transport</P><P>Project ID: 41442</P><P>Funding source: EBRD and the client</P><P>Type of contract: Works</P><P>Type of notice: Invitation for tenders</P><P>Issue date: 27.2.2018</P><P>Closing date: 13.4.2018, 10am local time</P><P>This invitation for tenders follows the general procurement notice for this project nº 8857-GPN-41442 which was published on European bank for reconstruction and development (the Bank) website, procurement notices (www.ebrd.com) on 20.10.2017.</P><P>The Ministry of Economy and Infrastructure, represented by the State road administration, hereinafter referred to as “the employer”, intends using part of the proceeds of a loan from the European bank for reconstruction and development towards the cost of Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The employer now invites sealed tenders from contractors for the following contract to be funded from part of the proceeds of the loan:</P><P>Contract RSP/W10/01: “Rehabilitation of M3 Chisinau-Giurgiulesti road, km 96+800 — km 171+290 and km 179+650 — km 190+750.</P><P>The M3 corridor connects Chisinau, the capital of Moldova, with Giurgiulesti in the very south of Moldova.</P><P>The contract comprises two sections of M3 Road from Municipality of comrat (km 96+800) to the south of Svetlii village at km 122+800 to km 151+200 at Ciumai village and further to the start of a newly designed bypass for Slobozia Mare village.</P><P>The works under Section 1 (km 96+800 to km 151+200) include the completion of the followings works:</P><P>1. Earthworks: finishing of minor works to access road adjustments, shoulder filling and finishing of fill and shaping of batter slopes;</P><P>2. Pavement: asphalt pavement milling of damaged asphalt layer and replacement, crack sealing, asphalt paving works;</P><P>3. Shoulder protection, execution of sidewalks, construction of bus stops and arrangement and construction of one parking area and a roundabout;</P><P>4. Completion of minor works on superstructure and pavement for 9 bridges;</P><P>5. Rearrangement of power lines and road illuminations;</P><P>6. Implementation of road traffic organization (road marking and signs).</P><P>The rehabilitation works under Section 2 (km 151+200 – km 171+290 and km 179+650 – km 190+750) will follow the existing road alignment with the exception of some minor road realignment work to improve the geometric characteristics of the road, minimise safety hazards, or to avoid areas subject to severe soil erosion.</P><P>The work includes earthworks — embankment construction, cement stabilised pavement construction, drainage structures, asphalt pavement work including overlays and the replacement of one bridge with a new bridge of length 59.20 metres and width 13 metres using precast pre-stressed concrete T-beam elements. Other work includes the rehabilitation of one bridge of length 26.27 m and width of 11 m and the construction of two roundabouts. Slight realignments are foreseen to improve the road safety conditions in Ciumai and Burlăceni villages according to the tender drawings.</P><P>The main works under Section 2 consist of approximately the following:</P><P>— Construction of 1 bridge of 59.20 m long and 13 m wide,</P><P>— Construction of 2 roundabout,</P><P>— Rehabilitation of one bridge,</P><P>— &gt; 150 000 m3 of earthworks,</P><P>— &gt; 115 000 m3 cement-stabilized works,</P><P>— &gt; 18 000 m3 of cold in-place recycled asphalt layers,</P><P>— &gt;275 000 m2 of dense asphalt concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 275 000 m2 of Stone Mastic Asphalt Concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 330 linear meter of pipe and box culverts in different diameters,</P><P>— &gt; 14 000 linear meter of lined side drain or waterway with precast or in situ concrete,</P><P>— &gt; 3 500 m of guardrails.</P><P>The scope of works is estimated and mentioned for guidance only, as the final scope will be determined based on the measured quantities of implemented works.</P><P>The overall time for completion of the works under the contract is 3 years, with the works on Section 1 to be completed within first 500 days. The defect notification period is envisaged to be 12 months.</P><P>In order to be qualified for the award of a contract, tenderers must satisfy the criteria specified in the tender documents. The summary of criteria is provided for information in the table below:</P><P>Criteria: Minimum average annual construction turnover, calculated as total certified payments received for contracts in progress or completed, within the last 5 years.</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 25 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: The tenderer must demonstrate access to, or availability of, financial resources such as liquid assets, unencumbered real assets, lines of credit, and other financial means, other than any contractual advance payments to meet the following cash-flow requirement:</P><P>Qualification requirement: EUR 4 500 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a contractor or management contractor in at least 1 contract within the last 5 years, that have been successfully and substantially completed and that are similar to the proposed works. The referred contract shall include:</P><P>Qualification requirement: Road construction works for flexible pavement, including production and laying of asphalt concrete, production and laying of cement stabilized base, earthworks, recycling of asphalt etc.</P><P>Criteria: Successful experience as a contractor (prime or subcontractor) in the execution of at least 2 contracts of a magnitude comparable to the proposed contract within the last 5 years. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Participation as a main contractor on 1 contract of a similar magnitude. The values of the referred contracts shall be not less than the equivalent of:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: EUR 20 000 000 equivalent</P><P>Criteria: Production and laying asphalt concrete on a single contract in at least 1 year in the past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification requirement: 67 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Annual average asphalt concrete production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 22 000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Cold recycling of asphalt pavement on a single contract executed within the last 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 25.000 tonnes/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course production in 1 contract in at least 1 year in past 3 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 51 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Stabilised Base Course average annual production and laying over the past 5 years at a rate not less than:</P><P>Qualification Requirement: 17 000 m3/year</P><P>Criteria: Bridge construction works executed within the last 5 years with demonstrated completion of two concrete pre-stressed bridges of multi-spans 10m or greater.</P><P>Qualification Requirement: two bridges</P><P>Tendering for contracts to be financed with the proceeds of a loan from the Bank is open to firms from any country who, in order to receive any amendments or clarifications to the Tender Documents, should register by completing the Registration Form available at the Employer’s website:</P><P>http://files.asd.md/Directia_investitii\PROCUREMENT\RSP\Works\W10_02_M3_Road/Registration_Form_W10_01.pdf</P><P>Completed registration form shall be submitted to employer’s project officer via fax or email provided below. Registration will be completed when a potential tenderer receives a registration number from the employer. The potential tenderer may elect on the Registration form to receive the tender documents or any amendments or clarifications to the tender documents, in the following manner:</P><P>(i) free of charge via e-mail on submission of a request at the address below, and</P><P>(ii) free of charge in electronic format at the address below.</P><P>All tenders must be accompanied by a tender security of EUR 500 000,00 or its equivalent in a convertible currency.</P><P>Tenders must be delivered to the office at the address below on or before 10:00 a.m. (Local Time), 13.4.2018, at which time they will be opened in the presence of those tenderers’ representatives who choose to attend.</P><P>The Employer’s address is:</P><P><ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT><BLK_BTX>Attention: </BLK_BTX><ATTENTION>Mr. Gheorghe Curmei</ATTENTION><BLK_BTX>, General Director, Address: </BLK_BTX><ORGANISATION>State Road Administration</ORGANISATION><BLK_BTX>, Bucuriei str. 12A, </BLK_BTX><TOWN>Chisinau</TOWN><BLK_BTX>, MD 2004, Republic of MOLDOVA</BLK_BTX></ADDRESS_NOT_STRUCT></P><P>The applicable procurement rules are the Bank’s procurement policies and rules (PP&amp;R) which can be located at:</P><P>http://www.ebrd.com/news/publications/policies/procurement-policies-and-rules.html</P><P>A register of potential tenderers who have requested the tender documents may be inspected at the address below.</P><P>Prospective tenderers may obtain further information from the following office:</P><P>Attention: Mr. Serghei POLIȘCIUC, Deputy Director of State Road Administration</P><P>Address: str. Bucuriei 12A, office 401</P><P>Fax: 022 74 12 19</P><P>E-mail: procurement@asd.md</P></CONTENTS></FD_OTH_NOT></OTH_NOT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>