<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="121996-2018"
            EDITION="2018055">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-125840-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180424</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>55</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180320</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 055-121996</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:121996-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>www.contractsfinder.service.gov.uk</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>www.contractsfinder.service.gov.uk</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="79600000">Recruitment services</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="UKK1">Gloucestershire, Wiltshire and Bristol/Bath area</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="UKK1">Gloucestershire, Wiltshire and Bristol/Bath area</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <VALUES>
            <VALUE TYPE="ESTIMATED_TOTAL" CURRENCY="GBP">8500000</VALUE>
         </VALUES>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180319</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180424 10:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="1">Ministry or any other national or federal authority</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="4">European Union</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="D">Defence</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01C02</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/24/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Обединено кралство</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Бристол</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Услуги по набиране на персонал</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Spojené království/Velká Británie</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Nábor zaměstnanců</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Forenede Kongerige, Det</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Rekrutteringstjenester</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>das Vereinigte Königreich</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Personaleinstellung</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Ηνωμένο Βασίλειο</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Μπρίστολ</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες πρόσληψης</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>United Kingdom</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Recruitment services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios de contratación</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Suurbritannia / Ühendkuningriik</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Värbamisteenistus</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Yhdistynyt kuningaskunta</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Työhönottopalvelut</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Royaume-Uni</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de recrutement</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Ríocht Aontaithe, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Briostó</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Recruitment services</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Ujedinjena Kraljevina</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge zapošljavanja</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Egyesült Királyság</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Munkaerő-toborzási szolgáltatás</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Regno Unito</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi di assunzione</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Jungtinė Karalystė, Didžioji Britanija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristolis</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Darbo jėgos atrankos paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Apvienotā Karaliste</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristole</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Darbinieku pieņemšanas pakalpojumi</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>Ir-Renju Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' reklutaġġ</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Verenigd Koninkrijk</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Recruteringsdiensten</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Zjednoczone Królestwo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi rekrutacyjne</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Reino Unido</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de recrutamento</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Regatul Unit</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii de recrutare</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Spojené kráľovstvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Náborové služby</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Združeno kraljestvo</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve zaposlovanja</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Förenade kungariket</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Bristol</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Rekryteringstjänster</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Ministry of Defence, Agencies/Misc, Other</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <F02_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F02" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, Agencies/Misc, Other</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>MOD Abbey Wood, Elm 1c, #4135</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bristol</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>BS34 8JH</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Mr Shaun Brill</CONTACT_POINT>
               <E_MAIL>shaun.brill100@mod.gov.uk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK1"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>www.contractsfinder.service.gov.uk</URL_GENERAL>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>www.contractsfinder.service.gov.uk</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CA_TYPE VALUE="MINISTRY"/>
            <CA_ACTIVITY VALUE="DEFENCE"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>DE and S executive recruitment support</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>CCDT/399</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="79600000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>DE and S has a requirement to establish a framework of Executive Search partners for 6 distinct Lots, who can help us attract and hire the best talent in the market for the top levels of our management structure, in both permanent and interim roles. We need to get access to top talent, build our brand in the senior marketplace and use our freedoms around pay and reward to secure the very best individuals.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL CURRENCY="GBP">8500000</VAL_ESTIMATED_TOTAL>
            <LOT_DIVISION>
               <LOT_ALL/>
               <LOT_COMBINING_CONTRACT_RIGHT>
                  <P>For Lot 1 only, and as detailed in SC2 Contract Conditions Annex A to Schedule 5, submissions will only be accepted from multi practice executive search firms with more than 5% of market share of net fee income as identified by Executive Grapevine annual market share rankings of UK Executive Search Market 2016-2017.</P>
               </LOT_COMBINING_CONTRACT_RIGHT>
            </LOT_DIVISION>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <TITLE>
                  <P>Leadership Premium</P>
               </TITLE>
               <LOT_NO>1</LOT_NO>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79600000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK1"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Gloucestershire, Wiltshire and Bristol / Bath area.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>DE and  S has a requirement to establish a multi-supplier framework of Executive Search Support for 6 distinct Lots, who can help us attract and hire the best talent in the market for the top levels of our management structure, in both permanent and interim roles. We need to get access to top talent, build our brand in the senior marketplace and use our freedoms around pay and reward to secure the very best individuals. We want to build relationships with external suppliers so they get to know DE and S and understand our business, our culture and senior leaders.</P>
                  <P>The role of the Executive Search Framework Contractor for each of the 6 framework Lots, will be to work face to face with HR, the business and key stakeholders, including our Chief Executives Committee and Senior Leadership Group to define and advise the correct person specification for each role, utilising market data to advise potential candidate sources that will provide access to the most relevant and high quality candidates per role. For permanent recruitment, it is expected that in-depth research based market mapping will be conducted to identify and approach potential candidates, introducing DE and S in a compelling way in order to attract them to the opportunity on offer. Framework Contractors will conduct a thorough assessment of all candidates before recommending the most suitable individuals to DE and S, and subsequently managing these individuals through the selection process of shortlist and interview stages before securing the preferred candidate.</P>
                  <P>Lot 1.</P>
                  <P>Lot 1 is reserved for the highest profile roles at DE and S. Typically these roles will be the most senior at DE and S, but not exclusively. All roles will be of the most reputational and strategic importance to the organisation. Roles that present an opportunity for business critical succession planning are also included. The emphasis is on management and leadership as opposed to technical expertise. Typical remits include General Management, Executive and Director level leadership.</P>
                  <P>Timescales.</P>
                  <P>The Contract duration for each Lot is expected to be 2 years from the framework establishment, with a further 2 option years anticipated. The Framework Contract will run for an initial period of 2 years from contract award, which the Authority may wish to extend for further period or periods dependent on forecasted recruitment demand and Contractor-success and performance in each Lot.</P>
                  <P>Pricing.</P>
                  <P>Firm prices are sought for all permanent recruitment work under the Contract. nterim recruitment will be subject to Firm daily rate price bandings.</P>
                  <P>The competition is being conducted under the PCR 2015 Open Procedure. This is a live Invitation to Tender and Bidders must respond directly to this ITT by obtaining the ITT documents published on the Government’s Contracts Finder website (www.gov.uk/contracts-finder) and completing the Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) on the Contract Notice for this requirement on Defence Contracts Online (DCO) (https://www.contracts.mod.uk/).</P>
                  <P>This Cyber Risk classification of this requirement is defined as Low. Tenderers wishing to tender for this requirement are required to complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire.</P>
                  <P>There will not be a separate pre-qualification stage, bidders conference or any further publication/issue of these ITT documents. The full ITT document set is only available through the Contracts Finder website.</P>
                  <P>Tenderers must:</P>
                  <P>— complete the Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) within this Contract Notice by the due date/time. Access Code: Y966BX5GJU,</P>
                  <P>— complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire by registering on https://supplier-cyber-protection.service.gov.uk/ and entering the reference: RAR-Y9ZF5MPY,</P>
                  <P>— download the published ITT Documents for this requirement from Contracts finder and complete and submit postal tenders through the MOD Abbey Wood Tender board by the due date / time. All required information is given in this documentation.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">2705333</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">24</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>The Authority retains Options to proceed to each of the Contract Years 3 and 4 of each Contract Lot, subject to the Authority’s continued requirement for the Framework Contractors’ services under the Framework Agreement following completion of each Contract Year. The Framework Contractors hereby grant to the Authority irrevocable Options to proceed to future Contract Years at the firm prices stated in the Schedule of Requirements (Schedule 2). The Authority will not be obliged to take up the Option(s) and if the Authority elects not to take up the Option(s), the Framework Agreement will be deemed to have expired at the end of Contract Year 2 or Contract Year 3 if Contract Year 4 is not taken up.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>No business whatsoever is guaranteed under any resulting framework agreement indeed there is no guarantee that any framework agreement or contract will be put in place in relation to this notice. No compensation will be paid if a resulting framework agreement is withdrawn for any reason. Bidders should take part in this process only on the basis that they fully understand and accept this position.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="2">
               <TITLE>
                  <P>Leadership Standard</P>
               </TITLE>
               <LOT_NO>2</LOT_NO>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79600000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK1"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Gloucestershire, Wiltshire and Bristol / Bath area.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>DE and S has a requirement to establish a multi-supplier framework of Executive Search Support for 6 distinct Lots, who can help us attract and hire the best talent in the market for the top levels of our management structure, in both permanent and interim roles. We need to get access to top talent, build our brand in the senior marketplace and use our freedoms around pay and reward to secure the very best individuals. We want to build relationships with external suppliers so they get to know DE&amp;S and understand our business, our culture and senior leaders.</P>
                  <P>The role of the Executive Search Framework Contractor for each of the 6 framework Lots, will be to work face to face with HR, the business and key stakeholders, including our Chief Executives Committee and Senior Leadership Group to define and advise the correct person specification for each role, utilising market data to advise potential candidate sources that will provide access to the most relevant and high quality candidates per role. For permanent recruitment, it is expected that in-depth research based market mapping will be conducted to identify and approach potential candidates, introducing DE and S in a compelling way in order to attract them to the opportunity on offer. Framework Contractors will conduct a thorough assessment of all candidates before recommending the most suitable individuals to DE and S, and subsequently managing these individuals through the selection process of shortlist and interview stages before securing the preferred candidate.</P>
                  <P>Lot 2.</P>
                  <P>Lot 2 contains general leadership roles at DE and S. The emphasis is on management and leadership as opposed to technical expertise. Typical remits include General and Function Management, Operating Centre Director level leadership and Operations.</P>
                  <P>Timescales.</P>
                  <P>The Contract duration for each Lot is expected to be 2 years from the framework establishment, with a further 2 option years anticipated. The Framework Contract will run for an initial period of 2 years from contract award, which the Authority may wish to extend for further period or periods dependent on forecasted recruitment demand and Contractor-success and performance in each Lot.</P>
                  <P>Pricing.</P>
                  <P>Firm prices are sought for all permanent recruitment work under the Contract. Interim recruitment will be subject to Firm daily rate price bandings.</P>
                  <P>The competition is being conducted under the PCR 2015 Open Procedure. This is a live Invitation to Tender and Bidders must respond directly to this ITT by obtaining the ITT documents published on the Government’s CONTRACTS FINDER website (www.gov.uk/contracts-finder) and completing the Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) on the Contract Notice for this requirement on Defence Contracts Online (DCO) (https://www.contracts.mod.uk/).</P>
                  <P>This Cyber Risk classification of this requirement is defined as Low. Tenderers wishing to tender for this requirement are required to complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire.</P>
                  <P>There will not be a separate pre-qualification stage, bidders conference or any further publication/issue of these ITT documents. The full ITT document set is only available through the Contracts finder website.</P>
                  <P>Tenderers must:</P>
                  <P>— complete the online Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) within this DCO Contract Notice by the due date/time. Access Code: Y966BX5GJU,</P>
                  <P>— complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire by registering on https://supplier-cyber-protection.service.gov.uk/ and entering the reference: RAR-Y9ZF5MPY,</P>
                  <P>— download the published ITT Documents for this requirement from Contracts finder and complete and submit postal tenders through the MOD Abbey Wood Tender board by the due date/time. All required information is given in this documentation.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">1665333</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">24</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>The Authority retains Options to proceed to each of the Contract Years 3 and 4 of each Contract Lot, subject to the Authority’s continued requirement for the Framework Contractors’ services under the Framework Agreement following completion of each Contract Year. The Framework Contractors hereby grant to the Authority irrevocable Options to proceed to future Contract Years at the firm prices stated in the Schedule of Requirements (Schedule 2). The Authority will not be obliged to take up the Option(s) and if the Authority elects not to take up the Option(s), the Framework Agreement will be deemed to have expired at the end of Contract Year 2 or Contract Year 3 if Contract Year 4 is not taken up.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>No business whatsoever is guaranteed under any resulting framework agreement indeed there is no guarantee that any framework agreement or contract will be put in place in relation to this notice. No compensation will be paid if a resulting framework agreement is withdrawn for any reason. Bidders should take part in this process only on the basis that they fully understand and accept this position.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="3">
               <TITLE>
                  <P>Engineering and Logistics</P>
               </TITLE>
               <LOT_NO>3</LOT_NO>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79600000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK1"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Gloucestershire, Wiltshire and Bristol / Bath area.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>DE and S has a requirement to establish a multi-supplier framework of Executive Search Support for 6 distinct Lots, who can help us attract and hire the best talent in the market for the top levels of our management structure, in both permanent and interim roles. We need to get access to top talent, build our brand in the senior marketplace and use our freedoms around pay and reward to secure the very best individuals. We want to build relationships with external suppliers so they get to know DE and S and understand our business, our culture and senior leaders.</P>
                  <P>The role of the Executive Search Framework Contractor for each of the 6 framework Lots, will be to work face to face with HR, the business and key stakeholders, including our Chief Executives Committee and Senior Leadership Group to define and advise the correct person specification for each role, utilising market data to advise potential candidate sources that will provide access to the most relevant and high quality candidates per role. For permanent recruitment, it is expected that in-depth research based market mapping will be conducted to identify and approach potential candidates, introducing DE and S in a compelling way in order to attract them to the opportunity on offer. Framework Contractors will conduct a thorough assessment of all candidates before recommending the most suitable individuals to DE and S, and subsequently managing these individuals through the selection process of shortlist and interview stages before securing the preferred candidate.</P>
                  <P>Lot 3.</P>
                  <P>Technical leadership roles at DE and S within the disciplines of Engineering and Logistics. The emphasis is on striking the balance between leadership ability and a breadth and depth of technical expertise. Typical remits include Chief Engineer and Head of level positions within Supply Chain. Roles in this Lot require the specialist knowledge and understanding of an Executive Search Firm with expertise in recruiting senior technical leaders with backgrounds in engineering and science, safety and quality assurance, service delivery and optimisation.</P>
                  <P>Timescales.</P>
                  <P>The Contract duration for each Lot is expected to be 2 years from the framework establishment, with a further 2 option years anticipated. The Framework Contract will run for an initial period of 2 years from contract award, which the Authority may wish to extend for further period or periods dependent on forecasted recruitment demand and Contractor-success and performance in each Lot.</P>
                  <P>Pricing.</P>
                  <P>Firm prices are sought for all permanent recruitment work under the Contract. Interim recruitment will be subject to Firm daily rate price bandings.</P>
                  <P>The competition is being conducted under the PCR 2015 Open Procedure. This is a live Invitation to Tender and Bidders must respond directly to this ITT by obtaining the ITT documents published on the Government’s Contracts Finder website (www.gov.uk/contracts-finder) and completing the Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) on the Contract Notice for this requirement on Defence Contracts Online (DCO) (https://www.contracts.mod.uk/).</P>
                  <P>This Cyber Risk classification of this requirement is defined as Low. Tenderers wishing to tender for this requirement are required to complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire.</P>
                  <P>There will not be a separate pre-qualification stage, bidders conference or any further publication/issue of these ITT documents. The ITT document set is only available through the Contracts finder website.</P>
                  <P>Tenderers must:</P>
                  <P>— complete the online Suitability Assessment Questionnaire within this DCO Contract Notice by the due date/time. Access Code: Y966BX5GJU,</P>
                  <P>— complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire by registering on https://supplier-cyber-protection.service.gov.uk/ and entering the reference: RAR-Y9ZF5MPY,</P>
                  <P>— download the published ITT Documents for this requirement from Contracts finder and complete and submit postal tenders through the MOD Tender board by the due date/time.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">1005333</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">24</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>The Authority retains Options to proceed to each of the Contract Years 3 and 4 of each Contract Lot, subject to the Authority’s continued requirement for the Framework Contractors’ services under the Framework Agreement following completion of each Contract Year. The Framework Contractors hereby grant to the Authority irrevocable Options to proceed to future Contract Years at the firm prices stated in the Schedule of Requirements (Schedule 2). The Authority will not be obliged to take up the Option(s) and if the Authority elects not to take up the Option(s), the Framework Agreement will be deemed to have expired at the end of Contract Year 2 or Contract Year 3 if Contract Year 4 is not taken up.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>No business whatsoever is guaranteed under any resulting framework agreement indeed there is no guarantee that any framework agreement or contract will be put in place in relation to this notice. No compensation will be paid if a resulting framework agreement is withdrawn for any reason. Bidders should take part in this process only on the basis that they fully understand and accept this position.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="4">
               <TITLE>
                  <P>Project Management and Project Controls</P>
               </TITLE>
               <LOT_NO>4</LOT_NO>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79600000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK1"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Gloucestershire, Wiltshire and Bristol / Bath area.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>DE and S has a requirement to establish a multi-supplier framework of Executive Search Support for 6 distinct Lots, who can help us attract and hire the best talent in the market for the top levels of our management structure, in both permanent and interim roles. We need to get access to top talent, build our brand in the senior marketplace and use our freedoms around pay and reward to secure the very best individuals. We want to build relationships with external suppliers so they get to know DE and S and understand our business, our culture and senior leaders.</P>
                  <P>The role of the Executive Search Framework Contractor for each of the 6 framework Lots, will be to work face to face with HR, the business and key stakeholders, including our Chief Executives Committee and Senior Leadership Group to define and advise the correct person specification for each role, utilising market data to advise potential candidate sources that will provide access to the most relevant and high quality candidates per role. For permanent recruitment, it is expected that in-depth research based market mapping will be conducted to identify and approach potential candidates, introducing DE and S in a compelling way in order to attract them to the opportunity on offer. Framework Contractors will conduct a thorough assessment of all candidates before recommending the most suitable individuals to DE and S, and subsequently managing these individuals through the selection process of shortlist and interview stages before securing the preferred candidate.</P>
                  <P>Lot 4.</P>
                  <P>This Lot contains project, programme and portfolio leadership roles at DE and S across the Project Management and Project Controls disciplines. The emphasis is on effective portfolio leadership and strong delivery of equipment and support projects. Breadth of successful experience across project lifecycle is more important than depth of technical expertise. Typical remits include Head of level positions across Portfolio and Delivery.</P>
                  <P>Timescales.</P>
                  <P>The Contract duration for each Lot is expected to be 2 years from the framework establishment, with a further 2 option years anticipated. The Framework Contract will run for an initial period of 2 years from contract award, which the Authority may wish to extend for further period or periods dependent on forecasted recruitment demand and Contractor-success and performance in each Lot.</P>
                  <P>Pricing.</P>
                  <P>Firm prices are sought for all permanent recruitment work under the Contract. Interim recruitment will be subject to Firm daily rate price bandings.</P>
                  <P>The competition is being conducted under the PCR 2015 Open Procedure. This is a live Invitation to Tender and Bidders must respond directly to this ITT by obtaining the ITT documents published on the Government’s Contracts finder website (www.gov.uk/contracts-finder) and completing the Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) on the Contract Notice for this requirement on Defence Contracts Online (DCO) (https://www.contracts.mod.uk/).</P>
                  <P>This Cyber Risk classification of this requirement is defined as Low. Tenderers wishing to tender for this requirement are required to complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire.</P>
                  <P>There will not be a separate pre-qualification stage, bidders conference or any further publication/issue of these ITT documents. The full ITT document set is only available through the Contracts finder website.</P>
                  <P>Tenderers must:</P>
                  <P>— complete the online Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) within this DCO Contract Notice by the due date/time. Access Code: Y966BX5GJU,</P>
                  <P>— complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire by registering on https://supplier-cyber-protection.service.gov.uk/ and entering the reference: RAR-Y9ZF5MPY,</P>
                  <P>— download the published ITT Documents for this requirement from Contracts finder and complete and submit postal tenders through the MOD Abbey Wood Tender board by the due date/time. All required information is given in this documentation.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">1273333</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">24</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>The Authority retains Options to proceed to each of the Contract Years 3 and 4 of each Contract Lot, subject to the Authority’s continued requirement for the Framework Contractors’ services under the Framework Agreement following completion of each Contract Year. The Framework Contractors hereby grant to the Authority irrevocable Options to proceed to future Contract Years at the firm prices stated in the Schedule of Requirements (Schedule 2). The Authority will not be obliged to take up the Option(s) and if the Authority elects not to take up the Option(s), the Framework Agreement will be deemed to have expired at the end of Contract Year 2 or Contract Year 3 if Contract Year 4 is not taken up.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>No business whatsoever is guaranteed under any resulting framework agreement indeed there is no guarantee that any framework agreement or contract will be put in place in relation to this notice. No compensation will be paid if a resulting framework agreement is withdrawn for any reason. Bidders should take part in this process only on the basis that they fully understand and accept this position.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="5">
               <TITLE>
                  <P>Human Resources, Commercial and Finance</P>
               </TITLE>
               <LOT_NO>5</LOT_NO>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79600000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK1"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Gloucestershire, Wiltshire and Bristol / Bath area.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>DE and S has a requirement to establish a multi-supplier framework of Executive Search Support for 6 distinct Lots, who can help us attract and hire the best talent in the market for the top levels of our management structure, in both permanent and interim roles. We need to get access to top talent, build our brand in the senior marketplace and use our freedoms around pay and reward to secure the very best individuals. We want to build relationships with external suppliers so they get to know DE and S and understand our business, our culture and senior leaders.</P>
                  <P>The role of the Executive Search Framework Contractor for each of the 6 framework Lots, will be to work face to face with HR, the business and key stakeholders, including our Chief Executives Committee and Senior Leadership Group to define and advise the correct person specification for each role, utilising market data to advise potential candidate sources that will provide access to the most relevant and high quality candidates per role. For permanent recruitment, it is expected that in-depth research based market mapping will be conducted to identify and approach potential candidates, introducing DE  and S in a compelling way in order to attract them to the opportunity on offer. Framework Contractors will conduct a thorough assessment of all candidates before recommending the most suitable individuals to DE and S, and subsequently managing these individuals through the selection process of shortlist and interview stages before securing the preferred candidate.</P>
                  <P>Lot 5.</P>
                  <P>This Lot contains technical and people leadership roles at DE and S across Human Resources, Commercial and Finance. Depending on the role, the emphasis will vary between niche subject matter expertise and more generalist leadership. Typical remits include Divisional leader roles, Centre of Expertise and Business Partnering.</P>
                  <P>Timescales.</P>
                  <P>The Contract duration for each Lot is expected to be 2 years from the framework establishment, with a further 2 option years anticipated. The Framework Contract will run for an initial period of 2 years from contract award, which the Authority may wish to extend for further period or periods dependent on forecasted recruitment demand and Contractor-success and performance in each Lot.</P>
                  <P>Pricing.</P>
                  <P>Firm prices are sought for all permanent recruitment work under the Contract. Interim recruitment will be subject to Firm daily rate price bandings.</P>
                  <P>The competition is being conducted under the PCR 2015 Open Procedure. This is a live Invitation to Tender and Bidders must respond directly to this ITT by obtaining the ITT documents published on the Government’s Contracts finder website (www.gov.uk/contracts-finder) and completing the Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) on the Contract Notice for this requirement on Defence Contracts Online (DCO) (https://www.contracts.mod.uk/).</P>
                  <P>This Cyber Risk classification of this requirement is defined as Low. Tenderers wishing to tender for this requirement are required to complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire.</P>
                  <P>There will not be a separate pre-qualification stage, bidders conference or any further publication/issue of these ITT documents. The full ITT document set is only available through the Contracts finder website.</P>
                  <P>Tenderers must:</P>
                  <P>— complete the online Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) within this DCO Contract Notice by the due date/time. Access Code: Y966BX5GJU,</P>
                  <P>— complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire by registering on https://supplier-cyber-protection.service.gov.uk/ and entering the reference: RAR-Y9ZF5MPY,</P>
                  <P>— download the published ITT Documents for this requirement from Contracts finder and complete and submit postal tenders through the MOD Abbey Wood Tender board by the due date/time. All required information is given in this documentation.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">1025333</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">24</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>The Authority retains Options to proceed to each of the Contract Years 3 and 4 of each Contract Lot, subject to the Authority’s continued requirement for the Framework Contractors’ services under the Framework Agreement following completion of each Contract Year. The Framework Contractors hereby grant to the Authority irrevocable Options to proceed to future Contract Years at the firm prices stated in the Schedule of Requirements (Schedule 2). The Authority will not be obliged to take up the Option(s) and if the Authority elects not to take up the Option(s), the Framework Agreement will be deemed to have expired at the end of Contract Year 2 or Contract Year 3 if Contract Year 4 is not taken up.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>No business whatsoever is guaranteed under any resulting framework agreement indeed there is no guarantee that any framework agreement or contract will be put in place in relation to this notice. No compensation will be paid if a resulting framework agreement is withdrawn for any reason. Bidders should take part in this process only on the basis that they fully understand and accept this position.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="6">
               <TITLE>
                  <P>Support Services including IT</P>
               </TITLE>
               <LOT_NO>6</LOT_NO>
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="79600000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="UKK1"/>
               <MAIN_SITE>
                  <P>Gloucestershire, Wiltshire and Bristol / Bath area.</P>
               </MAIN_SITE>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>DE&amp;S has a requirement to establish a multi-supplier framework of Executive Search Support for 6 distinct Lots, who can help us attract and hire the best talent in the market for the top levels of our management structure, in both permanent and interim roles. We need to get access to top talent, build our brand in the senior marketplace and use our freedoms around pay and reward to secure the very best individuals. We want to build relationships with external suppliers so they get to know DE and S and understand our business, our culture and senior leaders.</P>
                  <P>The role of the Executive Search Framework Contractor for each of the 6 framework Lots, will be to work face to face with HR, the business and key stakeholders, including our Chief Executives Committee and Senior Leadership Group to define and advise the correct person specification for each role, utilising market data to advise potential candidate sources that will provide access to the most relevant and high quality candidates per role. For permanent recruitment, it is expected that in-depth research based market mapping will be conducted to identify and approach potential candidates, introducing DE&amp;S in a compelling way in order to attract them to the opportunity on offer. Framework Contractors will conduct a thorough assessment of all candidates before recommending the most suitable individuals to DE and S, and subsequently managing these individuals through the selection process of shortlist and interview stages before securing the preferred candidate.</P>
                  <P>Lot 6.</P>
                  <P>This Lot contains technical and people leadership roles that fulfil business wide services at a Corporate level at DE&amp;S, including within Information Technology, Business Process and Assurance and Occupational Health, Safety and Environment. The emphasis will vary between expertise and more generalist leadership. Typical remits will be specific in nature and include Marketing and Communications, Information Technology and Safety and Policy expertise. Roles in this Lot require a more generalist Executive Search Firm with experience recruiting niche skill sets.</P>
                  <P>Timescales.</P>
                  <P>The Contract duration for each Lot is expected to be 2 years from the framework establishment, with a further 2 option years anticipated. The Framework Contract will run for an initial period of 2 years from contract award, which the Authority may wish to extend for further period or periods dependent on forecasted recruitment demand and Contractor-success and performance in each Lot.</P>
                  <P>Pricing.</P>
                  <P>Firm prices are sought for all permanent recruitment work under the Contract. Interim recruitment will be subject to Firm daily rate price bandings.</P>
                  <P>The competition is being conducted under the PCR 2015 Open Procedure. This is a live Invitation to Tender and Bidders must respond directly to this ITT by obtaining the ITT documents published on the Government’s Contracts finder website (www.gov.uk/contracts-finder) and completing the Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) on the Contract Notice for this requirement on Defence Contracts Online (DCO) (https://www.contracts.mod.uk/).</P>
                  <P>This Cyber Risk classification of this requirement is defined as Low. Tenderers wishing to tender for this requirement are required to complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire.</P>
                  <P>There will not be a separate pre-qualification stage, bidders conference or any further publication/issue of these ITT documents. The full ITT document set is only available through the Contracts finder website.</P>
                  <P>Tenderers must:</P>
                  <P>— complete the online Suitability Assessment Questionnaire (SAQ) within this DCO Contract Notice by the due date/time. Access Code: Y966BX5GJU,</P>
                  <P>— complete a Cyber Security Supplier Assurance Questionnaire by registering on https://supplier-cyber-protection.service.gov.uk/ and entering the reference: RAR-Y9ZF5MPY,</P>
                  <P>— download the published ITT Documents for this requirement from CONTRACTS FINDER and complete and submit postal tenders through the Tender board.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="GBP">825333</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">24</DURATION>
               <NO_RENEWAL/>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <OPTIONS/>
               <OPTIONS_DESCR>
                  <P>The Authority retains Options to proceed to each of the Contract Years 3 and 4 of each Contract Lot, subject to the Authority’s continued requirement for the Framework Contractors’ services under the Framework Agreement following completion of each Contract Year. The Framework Contractors hereby grant to the Authority irrevocable Options to proceed to future Contract Years at the firm prices stated in the Schedule of Requirements (Schedule 2). The Authority will not be obliged to take up the Option(s) and if the Authority elects not to take up the Option(s), the Framework Agreement will be deemed to have expired at the end of Contract Year 2 or Contract Year 3 if Contract Year 4 is not taken up.</P>
               </OPTIONS_DESCR>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
               <INFO_ADD>
                  <P>No business whatsoever is guaranteed under any resulting framework agreement indeed there is no guarantee that any framework agreement or contract will be put in place in relation to this notice. No compensation will be paid if a resulting framework agreement is withdrawn for any reason. Bidders should take part in this process only on the basis that they fully understand and accept this position.</P>
               </INFO_ADD>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <TECHNICAL_CRITERIA_DOC/>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>Electronic Trading.</P>
               <P>Potential suppliers must note the mandatory requirement for electronic trading using the Contracting, Purchasing and Finance (CP and F) electronic procurement tool. All payments for Contractor Deliverables under the Contract shall only be made via CP and F. You can find details on CP&amp;F at https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/mod-contracting-purchasing-and-finance-e-procurement-system.</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
            <PERFORMANCE_STAFF_QUALIFICATION/>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_OPEN/>
            <FRAMEWORK>
               <SEVERAL_OPERATORS/>
            </FRAMEWORK>
            <NO_CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-04-24</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>10:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">3</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
            <OPENING_CONDITION>
               <DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>2018-04-24</DATE_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>10:01</TIME_OPENING_TENDERS>
               <PLACE>
                  <P>The Tender Board, Commercial Project Enabling Team, DE and S, The Central Gatehouse/VCP, MOD Abbey Wood South, Bristol BS34 8JH.</P>
               </PLACE>
            </OPENING_CONDITION>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <EORDERING/>
            <EINVOICING/>
            <EPAYMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The Authority reserves the right to amend any condition related to security of information to reflect any changes in national law or government policy. If any contract documents are accompanied by instructions on safeguarding classified information (e.g. a Security Aspects Letter), the Authority reserves the right to amend the terms of these instructions to reflect any changes in national law or government policy, whether in respect of the applicable protective marking scheme, specific protective markings given, the aspects to which any protective marking applies, or otherwise. The link below to the Gov.uk website provides information on the Government Security Classification.</P>
               <P>https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/government-security-classifications</P>
               <P>Advertising Regime OJEU:- This contract opportunity is published in the Official Journal of the European Union (OJEU),the MoD Defence Contracts Bulletin and www.contracts.mod.uk.</P>
               <P>Suppliers must read through this set of instructions and follow the process to respond to this opportunity.</P>
               <P>The information and/or documents for this opportunity are available on http://www.contracts.mod.uk.</P>
               <P>You must register on this site to respond, if you are already registered you will not need to register again, simply use your existing username and password. Please note there is a password reminder link on the homepage.</P>
               <P>Suppliers must log in, go to your Response Manager and add the following Access Code: Y966BX5GJU.</P>
               <P>Please ensure you follow any instruction provided to you here.</P>
               <P>The deadline for submitting your response(s) is detailed within this contract notice, you will also have visibility of the deadline date, once you have added the Access code via DCO as the opening and closing date is visible within the opportunity.</P>
               <P>Please ensure that you allow yourself plenty of time when responding to this opportunity prior to the closing date and time, especially if you have been asked to upload documents.</P>
               <P>If you experience any difficulties please refer to the online Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ&#x92;s) or the User Guides or contact the MOD DCO Helpdesk by emailing support@contracts.mod.uk or Telephone 0800 282 324.</P>
               <P>GO Reference: GO-2018319-DCB-12095740.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, Agencies/Misc, Other</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>MOD Abbey Wood, NH4 Elm 1c #4135</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bristol</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>BS34 8JH</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_MEDIATION_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Ministry of Defence, Agencies/Misc, Other</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>MOD Abbey Wood, NH4 Elm 1c #4135, Filton</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Bristol</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>BS34 8JH</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="UK"/>
            </ADDRESS_MEDIATION_BODY>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-03-19</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F02_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
