<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication" xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts" xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.8.S03/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd" DOC_ID="123016-2018" EDITION="2018055"><TECHNICAL_SECTION><RECEPTION_ID>18-124169-001</RECEPTION_ID><DELETION_DATE>20180502</DELETION_DATE><FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST><COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS></TECHNICAL_SECTION><LINKS_SECTION><XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu" xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/><OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple " xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/><ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/></LINKS_SECTION><CODED_DATA_SECTION><REF_OJS><COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ><NO_OJ>55</NO_OJ><DATE_PUB>20180320</DATE_PUB></REF_OJS><NOTICE_DATA><NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 055-123016</NO_DOC_OJS><URI_LIST><URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:123016-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC></URI_LIST><LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG><ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="MK"/><IA_URL_GENERAL>www.roads.org.mk</IA_URL_GENERAL><ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="45000000">Construction work</ORIGINAL_CPV><n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="MK">ПОРАНЕШНА ЈУГОСЛОВЕНСКА РЕПУБЛИКА МАКЕДОНИЈА (PORANEŠNA JUGOSLOVENSKA REPUBLIKA MAKEDONIJA)</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS><VALUES_LIST/></NOTICE_DATA><CODIF_DATA><DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180316</DS_DATE_DISPATCH><DD_DATE_REQUEST_DOCUMENT>20180502 11:00</DD_DATE_REQUEST_DOCUMENT><DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180502 11:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION><AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="8">Other</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE><TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE><NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="1">Works</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE><PR_PROC CODE="1">Open procedure</PR_PROC><RP_REGULATION CODE="8">Other</RP_REGULATION><TY_TYPE_BID CODE="Z">Not specified</TY_TYPE_BID><AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="1">Lowest price</AC_AWARD_CRIT><MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="S">General public services</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES><HEADING>02102</HEADING><DIRECTIVE VALUE="2004/18/EC"/></CODIF_DATA></CODED_DATA_SECTION><TRANSLATION_SECTION><ML_TITLES><ML_TI_DOC LG="BG"><TI_CY>Бивша югославска република Македония</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Скопие</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Строителни и монтажни работи</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="CS"><TI_CY>Bývalá jugoslávská republika Makedonie</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Stavební práce</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DA"><TI_CY>Tidligere Jugoslaviske Republik Makedonien, Den</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bygge- og anlægsarbejder</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="DE"><TI_CY>die ehemalige jugoslawische Republik Mazedonien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bauarbeiten</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EL"><TI_CY>πρώην Γιουγκοσλαβική Δημοκρατία της Μακεδονίας</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Σκόπια</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Κατασκευαστικές εργασίες</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="EN"><TI_CY>Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Construction work</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ES"><TI_CY>Antigua República Yugoslava de Macedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopie</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Trabajos de construcción</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="ET"><TI_CY>endine Jugoslaavia Makedoonia Vabariik</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Ehitustööd</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FI"><TI_CY>entinen Jugoslavian tasavalta Makedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Rakennustyöt</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="FR"><TI_CY>Ancienne République yougoslave de Macédoine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Travaux de construction</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="GA"><TI_CY>Poblacht iar-Iúgslavach na Macadóine</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Scóipé</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Construction work</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HR"><TI_CY>bivša jugoslavenska Republika Makedonija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Građevinski radovi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="HU"><TI_CY>Macedónia Volt Jugoszláv Köztársaság</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Szkopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Építési munkák</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="IT"><TI_CY>ex Repubblica iugoslava di Macedonia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lavori di costruzione</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LT"><TI_CY>buvusioji Jugoslavijos Respublika Makedonija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopjė</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Statybos darbai</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="LV"><TI_CY>bijusī Dienvidslāvijas Maķedonijas Republika</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Celtniecības darbi</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="MT"><TI_CY>Dik li kienet ir-Repubblika Jugoslava tal-Maċedonja</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Xogħol tal-kostruzzjoni</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="NL"><TI_CY>voormalige Joegoslavische Republiek Macedonië</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Bouwwerkzaamheden</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PL"><TI_CY>Była jugosłowiańska republika Macedonii</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Roboty budowlane</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="PT"><TI_CY>antiga República jugoslava da Macedónia</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Construção</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="RO"><TI_CY>fosta Republică iugoslavă a Macedoniei</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Lucrări de construcţii</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SK"><TI_CY>bývalá Juhoslovanská republika Macedónsko</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Stavebné práce</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SL"><TI_CY>Nekdanja jugoslovanska republika Makedonija</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Gradbena dela</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC><ML_TI_DOC LG="SV"><TI_CY>F. d. jugoslaviska republiken Makedonien</TI_CY><TI_TOWN>Skopje</TI_TOWN><TI_TEXT>Anläggningsarbete</TI_TEXT></ML_TI_DOC></ML_TITLES><ML_AA_NAMES><AA_NAME LG="EN">Public Entreprise for State Roads — Skopje</AA_NAME></ML_AA_NAMES></TRANSLATION_SECTION><FORM_SECTION><CONTRACT CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="2" LG="EN" VERSION="R2.0.8.S03.E01"><FD_CONTRACT CTYPE="WORKS"><CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION><NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><ORGANISATION><OFFICIALNAME>Public Entreprise for State Roads — Skopje</OFFICIALNAME></ORGANISATION><ADDRESS>Str."Dame Gruev", No. 14</ADDRESS><TOWN>Skopje</TOWN><POSTAL_CODE>1000</POSTAL_CODE><COUNTRY VALUE="MK"/><ATTENTION>Repairs and rehabilitation of state roads</ATTENTION><PHONE>+389 23118044</PHONE><E_MAILS><E_MAIL>zaklinab@roads.org.mk</E_MAIL></E_MAILS><FAX>+389 23220535</FAX></CA_CE_CONCESSIONAIRE_PROFILE><INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><URL_GENERAL>www.roads.org.mk</URL_GENERAL></INTERNET_ADDRESSES_CONTRACT><FURTHER_INFORMATION><IDEM/></FURTHER_INFORMATION><SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><IDEM/></SPECIFICATIONS_AND_ADDITIONAL_DOCUMENTS><TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO><IDEM/></TENDERS_REQUESTS_APPLICATIONS_MUST_BE_SENT_TO></NAME_ADDRESSES_CONTACT_CONTRACT><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_OTHER VALUE="OTHER">Public Enterprise</TYPE_OF_CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_OTHER><TYPE_OF_ACTIVITY VALUE="GENERAL_PUBLIC_SERVICES"/></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF><PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF_NO/></PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></TYPE_AND_ACTIVITIES_AND_PURCHASING_ON_BEHALF></CONTRACTING_AUTHORITY_INFORMATION><OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><TITLE_CONTRACT><P>Repairs and rehabilitation of state roads</P></TITLE_CONTRACT><TYPE_CONTRACT_LOCATION><TYPE_CONTRACT VALUE="WORKS"/></TYPE_CONTRACT_LOCATION><LOCATION_NUTS><n2016:NUTS CODE="MK"/></LOCATION_NUTS><NOTICE_INVOLVES><ESTABLISHMENT_FRAMEWORK_AGREEMENT/></NOTICE_INVOLVES><F02_FRAMEWORK><SEVERAL_OPERATORS><NUMBER_PARTICIPANTS>3</NUMBER_PARTICIPANTS></SEVERAL_OPERATORS><DURATION_FRAMEWORK_MONTH>12</DURATION_FRAMEWORK_MONTH></F02_FRAMEWORK><SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><P>Repairs and rehabilitation of state roads</P></SHORT_CONTRACT_DESCRIPTION><CPV><CPV_MAIN><CPV_CODE CODE="45000000"/></CPV_MAIN></CPV><CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA VALUE="NO"/><F02_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><DIV_INTO_LOT_NO/></F02_DIVISION_INTO_LOTS><ACCEPTED_VARIANTS VALUE="NO"/></DESCRIPTION_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><QUANTITY_SCOPE><NO_OPTIONS/><NO_RECURRENT_CONTRACT/></QUANTITY_SCOPE></OBJECT_CONTRACT_INFORMATION><LEFTI_CONTRACT><CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><P>Performance guarantee in amount of 15 %.</P></DEPOSITS_GUARANTEES_REQUIRED><NO_EXISTENCE_OTHER_PARTICULAR_CONDITIONS/></CONTRACT_RELATING_CONDITIONS><F02_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION><ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><P>For participation in criminal organization, corruption, fraud or money laundering:</P><P>— Certificate that it is not subject to bankruptcy procedure issued by competent authority,</P><P>— Certificate that it is not subject to liquidation procedure issued by competent authority,</P><P>— Certificate for paid taxes, contributions and other public duties by the competent authority in the country where that economic operator is established,</P><P>— Certificate from the Register of Penalties for Committed Criminal Acts of Legal Entities that a minor penalty ban on participation in procedures for public announcements, awarding of public procurement contracts and contracts for public-private partnership has not been imposed,</P><P>— Certificate from the Register of Penalties for Committed Criminal Acts of Legal Entities that a minor penalty temporary or permanent ban on performing certain activity has not been imposed,</P><P>— Certificate that it has not been announced any sanctions for misdemeanour with an effective Court decision, resulting in prohibition for pursuing professional activity or duty, i.e. in a temporary prohibition for performing professional activity,</P><P>— Document proving a registered business,</P><P>— Tenderer (Bidder) is required to possess Certificate (License) A for construction of first (I) category structures, issued by the competent institution in the country as per the Construction Law in force (Official Gazette of Republic of Macedonia nº 130/09, 124/10, 18/11, 36/11, 54/11, 13/12, 144/12, 25/13, 79/13, 137/13, 163/13, 27/14, 28/14, 42/14, 115/14, 149/14, 187/14, 44/15, 129/15, 217/15, 226/15, 30/16, 31/16, 39/16, 71/16, 103/16 and 132/16) or, for foreign economic operators, a Certificate issued by the authority responsible for operations in the area of spatial planning/management according to Article 42 of the Construction Law (Official Gazette of Republic of Macedonia no. 130/09, 124/10, 18/11, 36/11, 54/11, 13/12, 144/12, 25/13, 79/13, 137/13, 163/13, 27/14, 28/14, 42/14, 115/14, 149/14, 187/14, 44/15, 129/15, 217/15, 226/15, 30/16, 31/16, 39/16, 71/16, 103/16 and 132/16) (applies to each member of the group in case the tender is submitted by a group of economic operators – JV).</P></ECONOMIC_OPERATORS_PERSONAL_SITUATION><F02_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>— Minimum annual income of 1 000 000 EUR/year in the last 3 years.</P><P>The economic operator shall prove that he meets the requirements for economic and financial status by furnishing the following:</P><P>— Copy of balance sheet report and data on income statements for 2015, 2016, and 2017, certified by a competent authority, i.e. audited balance sheet or abstracts of the report on balance sheets, where balance sheet publication is required under the law of the country where the economic operator is registered,</P><P>— For foreign tenderers, in case balance sheet reports and data on income statements for 2015, 2016, and 2017 are not published, copies should be furnished of auditors’ reports of the Foreign Tenderer, which shall be positive and shall be issued by a reputable foreign institution registered to provide audit services. Auditor reports should contain data about the overall economic operation of the Foreign Tenderer (for the last 3 years).</P></EAF_CAPACITY_INFORMATION></F02_ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_CAPACITY><TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI><T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION><P>— Notification on contract items that the economic operator intends to subcontract to third parties, if any,</P><P>— Minimum one (1) successfully completed contract for construction, reconstruction or rehabilitation of state roads (motorway, expressway, national road/s, or regional road/s) in the last five (5) years in an amount of minimum 300 000 EUR.</P><P>Personnel: The key personnel for construction works must meet the following minimum requirements (with specified structures):</P><P>(i) Project Manager: Chief Engineer (1 Bachelor of Civil Engineering — BS CE) possessing a Certificate A for construction in civil engineering, with at least 7 (seven) years of work experience in construction activities, 5 years of work experience in similar projects (construction, reconstruction, or rehabilitation of state roads (motorway, expressway, national road/s and regional road/s));</P><P>(ii) Assistant for earthworks and concrete works: (1 Bachelor of Civil Engineering — BS CE) possessing a Certificate A for construction in civil engineering, with at least 5 (five) years of work experience in construction activities, 3 years of work experience in similar projects (construction, reconstruction, or rehabilitation of state roads (motorway, expressway, national road/s and regional road/s));</P><P>(iii) Assistant for asphalt works: (1 Bachelor of Civil Engineering — BS CE) possessing a Certificate A for construction in civil engineering, with at least 5 (five) years of work experience in construction activities, 3 years of work experience on similar projects (construction, reconstruction, or rehabilitation of state roads (motorway, expressway, national road/s and regional road/s));</P><P>(iv) Surveyor:</P><P>— Possessing minimum a high school diploma of a geodetic technician — surveyor,</P><P>— Minimum 5 years of work experience in road projects.</P><P>Equipment: The tenderer is required to either possess or secure an access (by renting, leasing, procurement contract, etc.) to the below specified key equipment that is fully operational, and is required to demonstrate that, based on the known commitments, it shall be available during the implementation of the proposed contract.</P><P>For the equipment that is not in his ownership, the tenderer will submit valid evidence as per the article 154 of the Public Procurement Law that this equipment and facilities are at his availability throughout the duration of the Contract.</P><P>The tenderer is required to either possess or have secured an access to the key equipment below (proof of ownership and completed tender form (9) Equipment and Machinery, which is an integral part of the tender documentation):</P><P>(i) Asphalt plant with total production capacity not less than 80 t/hour;</P><P>(ii) Excavation machines:</P><P>— Excavator with minimum capacity of 150 m<FT TYPE="SUP">3</FT>/day (1 unit),</P><P>— Bulldozer with minimum capacity of 100 m<FT TYPE="SUP">3</FT>/day (1 unit).</P><P>(iii) One paver for asphalt build-in that can perform asphalting, with minimum 6 m wide smoothing iron without a longitudinal seam (1 unit);</P><P>(iv) Asphalt scrapping machine (1 unit);</P><P>(v) One tank for emulsion spraying (1 unit);</P><P>(vi) Freight transport vehicles — trucks with minimum 20 tons loading capacity (6 units);</P><P>(vii) Road rollers (two rubber vibrating roller drums and four steel ones);</P><P>(viii) Grader and loader.</P><P>The economic operator shall prove that he meets the requirements of Technical and professional competence by submitting the following:</P><P>— Notification about contract items that the economic operator intends to subcontract to third parties,</P><P>— Copy of a contract and a written confirmation of satisfactory works completion for at least one (1) contract for construction, reconstruction, or rehabilitation of state roads (motorway, expressway, national road/s and regional road/s).</P><P>Personnel:</P><P>— For Project Manager: copies of the Diploma and of the Certificate (License) issued by competent national authorities, as per the Construction Law in force (Official Gazette of Republic of Macedonia no. 130/09, 124/10, 18/11, 36/11, 54/11, 13/12, 144/12, 25/13, 79/13, 137/13, 163/13, 27/14, 28/14, 42/14, 115/14, 149/14, 187/14, 44/15, 129/15, 217/15, 226/15, 30/16, 31/16, 39/16, 71/16, 103/16 and 132/16), copies of employment record or other proof of employment as per the Public Procurement Law, and a completed Bidding Form — Candidate’s Short Biography, provided as an integral part of the tender documents,</P><P>— For Assistant for earthworks and concrete works: copies of the diploma and of the Certificate (License) issued by competent national authorities, as per the Construction Law in force (Official Gazette of Republic of Macedonia nº 130/09, 124/10, 18/11, 36/11, 54/11, 13/12, 144/12, 25/13, 79/13, 137/13, 163/13, 27/14, 28/14, 42/14, 115/14, 149/14, 187/14, 44/15, 129/15, 217/15, 226/15, 30/16, 31/16, 39/16, 71/16, 103/16 and 132/16), copies of employment record or other proof of employment as per the Public Procurement Law, and a completed Bidding Form — Candidate’s Short Biography, provided as an integral part of the tender documents,</P><P>— For Assistant for asphalt works: copies of the diploma and of the Certificate (License) issued by competent national authorities, as per the Construction Law in force (Official Gazette of Republic of Macedonia nº 130/09, 124/10, 18/11, 36/11, 54/11, 13/12, 144/12, 25/13, 79/13, 137/13, 163/13, 27/14, 28/14, 42/14, 115/14, 149/14, 187/14, 44/15, 129/15, 217/15, 226/15, 30/16, 31/16, 39/16, 71/16, 103/16 and 132/16), copies of employment record or other proof of employment as per the Public Procurement Law, and a completed Bidding Form — Candidate’s Short Biography, provided as an integral part of the tender documents,</P><P>— For Surveyor: copies of the diploma for completed secondary education – Surveyor, copies of employment record or other proof of employment as per the Public Procurement Law, and a completed Bidding Form — Candidate’s Short Biography.</P><P>Equipment:</P><P>(i) For the asphalt plant — Proof of ownership or of secured access to one as per the article 154 of the Public Procurement Law, and statement that it is of the required capacity.</P><P>(ii) For excavation machines: proof of ownership or of secured access to ones as per the article 154 of the Public Procurement Law, and statement that they are in use and of the required capacity;</P><P>(iii) For the paver for asphalt build-in: proof of ownership or of secured access to one as per the article 154 of the Public Procurement Law, and statement that the machine is in use.</P><P>(iv) For the asphalt scrapping machine: proof of ownership or of secured access to one as per the article 154 of the Public Procurement Law, and statement that the machine is in use.</P><P>(v) For the emulsion spraying tank: proof of ownership or of secured access to one as per the article 154 of the Public Procurement Law, and statement that the tank is in use.</P><P>(vi) For the freight transport vehicles — trucks: proof of ownership or of secured access to ones as per the article 154 of the Public Procurement Law, copies of registration certificates proving they are registered and in use, and a Statement that they of the required loading capacity.</P><P>(vii) For the road rollers: proof of ownership or of secured access to one/s as per the article 154 of the Public Procurement Law, and statement that they are in use.</P><P>(viii) For the grader and loader: proof of ownership or of secured access to one/s as per the article 154 of the Public Procurement Law, and statement that they are in use.</P></T_CAPACITY_INFORMATION></TECHNICAL_CAPACITY_LEFTI></F02_CONDITIONS_FOR_PARTICIPATION></LEFTI_CONTRACT><PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE><TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE><PT_OPEN/></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE_DETAIL_FOR_CONTRACT_NOTICE></TYPE_OF_PROCEDURE><AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><LOWEST_PRICE/></AWARD_CRITERIA_DETAIL><IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE><USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION><P>Provided in the tender documentation.</P></USE_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION></IS_ELECTRONIC_AUCTION_USABLE></AWARD_CRITERIA_CONTRACT_NOTICE_INFORMATION><ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><P>9/2018</P></FILE_REFERENCE_NUMBER><PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F2><NO_PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_EXISTS_F2/></PREVIOUS_PUBLICATION_INFORMATION_NOTICE_F2><CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><TIME_LIMIT><DAY>02</DAY><MONTH>05</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>11:00</TIME></TIME_LIMIT><NO_PAYABLE_DOCUMENTS/></CONDITIONS_OBTAINING_SPECIFICATIONS><RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><DAY>02</DAY><MONTH>05</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>11:00</TIME></RECEIPT_LIMIT_DATE><LANGUAGE><LANGUAGE_OTHER><P>Macedonian</P></LANGUAGE_OTHER></LANGUAGE><MINIMUM_TIME_MAINTAINING_TENDER><PERIOD_DAY>365</PERIOD_DAY></MINIMUM_TIME_MAINTAINING_TENDER><CONDITIONS_FOR_OPENING_TENDERS><DATE_TIME><DAY>02</DAY><MONTH>05</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR><TIME>11:00</TIME></DATE_TIME><PLACE_OPENING><PLACE_NOT_STRUCTURED><P>Public Enterprise for State Roads — Skopje, str. Dame Gruev No 14, Skopje.</P></PLACE_NOT_STRUCTURED></PLACE_OPENING><EXISTENCE_AUTHORISED_PERSONS><P>Authorized persons possessing powerof attorney.</P></EXISTENCE_AUTHORISED_PERSONS></CONDITIONS_FOR_OPENING_TENDERS></ADMINISTRATIVE_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></PROCEDURE_DEFINITION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE><NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/><RELATES_TO_EU_PROJECT_NO/><ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><P>https://www.e-nabavki.gov.mk</P></ADDITIONAL_INFORMATION><NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE><DAY>16</DAY><MONTH>03</MONTH><YEAR>2018</YEAR></NOTICE_DISPATCH_DATE></COMPLEMENTARY_INFORMATION_CONTRACT_NOTICE></FD_CONTRACT></CONTRACT></FORM_SECTION></TED_EXPORT>