<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TED_EXPORT xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
            xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
            xmlns="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication"
            xmlns:n2016="ted/2016/nuts"
            xsi:schemaLocation="ted/R2.0.9.S02/publication TED_EXPORT.xsd"
            VERSION="R2.0.9.S02.E01"
            DOC_ID="049611-2018"
            EDITION="2018023">
   <TECHNICAL_SECTION>
      <RECEPTION_ID>18-049184-001</RECEPTION_ID>
      <DELETION_DATE>20180219</DELETION_DATE>
      <FORM_LG_LIST>EN </FORM_LG_LIST>
      <COMMENTS>From Convertor</COMMENTS>
   </TECHNICAL_SECTION>
   <LINKS_SECTION>
      <XML_SCHEMA_DEFINITION_LINK xlink:type="simple"
                                  xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"
                                  xlink:title="TED WEBSITE"/>
      <OFFICIAL_FORMS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <FORMS_LABELS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_CPV_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
      <ORIGINAL_NUTS_LINK xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="http://ted.europa.eu"/>
   </LINKS_SECTION>
   <CODED_DATA_SECTION>
      <REF_OJS>
         <COLL_OJ>S</COLL_OJ>
         <NO_OJ>23</NO_OJ>
         <DATE_PUB>20180202</DATE_PUB>
      </REF_OJS>
      <NOTICE_DATA>
         <NO_DOC_OJS>2018/S 023-049611</NO_DOC_OJS>
         <URI_LIST>
            <URI_DOC LG="EN">http://ted.europa.eu/udl?uri=TED:NOTICE:049611-2018:TEXT:EN:HTML</URI_DOC>
         </URI_LIST>
         <LG_ORIG>EN</LG_ORIG>
         <ISO_COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
         <IA_URL_GENERAL>https://eu.eu-supply.com/ctm/supplier/publictenders?B=ENERGINET</IA_URL_GENERAL>
         <IA_URL_ETENDERING>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=203070&amp;B=ENERGINET</IA_URL_ETENDERING>
         <ORIGINAL_CPV CODE="72000000">IT services: consulting, software development, Internet and support</ORIGINAL_CPV>
         <n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS CODE="DK">DANMARK</n2016:PERFORMANCE_NUTS>
         <n2016:CA_CE_NUTS CODE="DK032">Sydjylland</n2016:CA_CE_NUTS>
         <REF_NOTICE>
            <NO_DOC_OJS>2017/S 221-460145</NO_DOC_OJS>
         </REF_NOTICE>
      </NOTICE_DATA>
      <CODIF_DATA>
         <DS_DATE_DISPATCH>20180131</DS_DATE_DISPATCH>
         <DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>20180219 09:00</DT_DATE_FOR_SUBMISSION>
         <AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE CODE="4">Utilities entity</AA_AUTHORITY_TYPE>
         <TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE CODE="3">Contract notice</TD_DOCUMENT_TYPE>
         <NC_CONTRACT_NATURE CODE="4">Services</NC_CONTRACT_NATURE>
         <PR_PROC CODE="4">Negotiated procedure</PR_PROC>
         <RP_REGULATION CODE="5">European Union, with participation by GPA countries</RP_REGULATION>
         <TY_TYPE_BID CODE="1">Submission for all lots</TY_TYPE_BID>
         <AC_AWARD_CRIT CODE="2">The most economic tender</AC_AWARD_CRIT>
         <MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES CODE="N">Electricity</MA_MAIN_ACTIVITIES>
         <HEADING>01G05</HEADING>
         <INITIATOR>01</INITIATOR>
         <DIRECTIVE VALUE="2014/25/EU"/>
      </CODIF_DATA>
   </CODED_DATA_SECTION>
   <TRANSLATION_SECTION>
      <ML_TITLES>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="BG">
            <TI_CY>Дaния</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>ИТ услуги: консултации, разработване на софтуер, Интернет и поддръжка</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="CS">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Informační technologie: poradenství, vývoj programového vybavení, internet a podpora</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DA">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>It-tjenester: rådgivning, programmeludvikling, internet og support</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="DE">
            <TI_CY>Dänemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-Dienste: Beratung, Software-Entwicklung, Internet und Hilfestellung</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EL">
            <TI_CY>Δανία</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Υπηρεσίες τεχνολογίας των πληροφοριών: παροχή συμβουλών, ανάπτυξη λογισμικού, Διαδίκτυο και υποστήριξη</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="EN">
            <TI_CY>Denmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT services: consulting, software development, Internet and support</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ES">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicios TI: consultoría, desarrollo de software, Internet y apoyo</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="ET">
            <TI_CY>Taani</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-teenused: nõuande-, tarkvaraarendus-, Interneti- ja tugiteenused</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FI">
            <TI_CY>Tanska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Tietotekniset palvelut: neuvonta, ohjelmistojen kehittäminen, Internet ja tuki</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="FR">
            <TI_CY>Danemark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Services de technologies de l'information, conseil, développement de logiciels, internet et appui</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="GA">
            <TI_CY>Danmhairg, an</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT services: consulting, software development, Internet and support</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HR">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usluge informacijske tehnologije: savjetovanje, razvoj programske podrške, internet i podrška</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="HU">
            <TI_CY>Dánia</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-szolgáltatások: tanácsadás, szoftverfejlesztés, internet és támogatás</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="IT">
            <TI_CY>Danimarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizi informatici: consulenza, sviluppo di software, Internet e supporto</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LT">
            <TI_CY>Danija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT paslaugos: konsultavimas, programinės įrangos kūrimas, internetas ir aptarnavimo paslaugos</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="LV">
            <TI_CY>Dānija</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT pakalpojumi konsultēšana, programmatūras izstrāde, internets un atbalsts</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="MT">
            <TI_CY>id-Danimarka</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servizzi ta' IT: konsulenza, żvilupp ta' softwer, Internet u appoġġ</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="NL">
            <TI_CY>Denemarken</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-diensten: adviezen, softwareontwikkeling, internet en ondersteuning</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PL">
            <TI_CY>Dania</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Usługi informatyczne: konsultacyjne, opracowywania oprogramowania, internetowe i wsparcia</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="PT">
            <TI_CY>Dinamarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Serviços de TI: consultoria, desenvolvimento de software, Internet e apoio</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="RO">
            <TI_CY>Danemarca</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Servicii IT: consultanţă, dezvoltare de software, internet şi asistenţă</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SK">
            <TI_CY>Dánsko</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Služby informačných technológií: konzultácie, vývoj softvéru, internet a podpora</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SL">
            <TI_CY>Danska</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>Storitve informacijske tehnologije: svetovanje, razvoj programske opreme, internet in podpora</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
         <ML_TI_DOC LG="SV">
            <TI_CY>Danmark</TI_CY>
            <TI_TOWN>Fredercia</TI_TOWN>
            <TI_TEXT>
               <P>IT-tjänster: konsultverksamhet, programvaruutveckling, Internet och stöd</P>
            </TI_TEXT>
         </ML_TI_DOC>
      </ML_TITLES>
      <ML_AA_NAMES>
         <AA_NAME LG="EN">Energinet</AA_NAME>
      </ML_AA_NAMES>
   </TRANSLATION_SECTION>
   <FORM_SECTION>
      <NOTICE_UUID>edafb589-3775-47d6-b03b-957951098e99</NOTICE_UUID>
      <F05_2014 CATEGORY="ORIGINAL" FORM="F05" LG="EN">
         <CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Energinet</OFFICIALNAME>
               <NATIONALID>28980671</NATIONALID>
               <ADDRESS>Tonne Kjærsvej 65</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Fredericia</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>7000</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <CONTACT_POINT>Kirsten Ebstrup</CONTACT_POINT>
               <PHONE>+45 70102244</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>procurement@energinet.dk</E_MAIL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK032"/>
               <URL_GENERAL>https://eu.eu-supply.com/ctm/supplier/publictenders?B=ENERGINET</URL_GENERAL>
               <URL_BUYER>https://eu.eu-supply.com/ctm/Company/CompanyInformation/Index/228008</URL_BUYER>
            </ADDRESS_CONTRACTING_BODY>
            <CENTRAL_PURCHASING/>
            <DOCUMENT_FULL/>
            <URL_DOCUMENT>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=203070&amp;B=ENERGINET</URL_DOCUMENT>
            <ADDRESS_FURTHER_INFO_IDEM/>
            <URL_PARTICIPATION>http://eu.eu-supply.com/app/rfq/rwlentrance_s.asp?PID=203070&amp;B=ENERGINET</URL_PARTICIPATION>
            <ADDRESS_PARTICIPATION_IDEM/>
            <CE_ACTIVITY VALUE="ELECTRICITY"/>
         </CONTRACTING_BODY>
         <OBJECT_CONTRACT>
            <TITLE>
               <P>New Data Centre for DataHub</P>
            </TITLE>
            <REFERENCE_NUMBER>18/00303</REFERENCE_NUMBER>
            <CPV_MAIN>
               <CPV_CODE CODE="72000000"/>
            </CPV_MAIN>
            <TYPE_CONTRACT CTYPE="SERVICES"/>
            <SHORT_DESCR>
               <P>Energinet hereby initiates a tender concerning the contract for delivery of an infrastructure platform for the DataHub system and associated systems that together cover the Energinet's obligation to operate the DataHub in accordance with the Electricity Supply Act.</P>
               <P>As Energinet's current Hosting Agreement for DataHub expires Energinet would like to offer a new 4-year Hosting Contract with option for extension of up to two (2) years.</P>
            </SHORT_DESCR>
            <NO_LOT_DIVISION/>
            <OBJECT_DESCR ITEM="1">
               <CPV_ADDITIONAL>
                  <CPV_CODE CODE="72000000"/>
               </CPV_ADDITIONAL>
               <n2016:NUTS CODE="DK"/>
               <SHORT_DESCR>
                  <P>1) Through the establishment of the present Framework Agreement, the Contracting authority wants a delivery of a Platform as a Service Solution, including Virtualization, Server, Storage and Networking (PaaS) according, to schedule</P>
                  <P>2)  Delivery of Datacenter Services according to schedule 4.2, including Operation, Maintenance and Monitoring of Infrastructure including Runtime as well as error correction in collaboration with the Application Provider. Delivery of Cross tower Services according to schedule 4.1. Delivery of Transition and Transformation Services according to schedule;</P>
                  <P>3) For further details concerning the purchase, reference is made to the appendices to the tender documents. The total purchase is made for a period of 4 years from the signing of the Framework Agreement with the option of an extension for up to two (2) years.</P>
               </SHORT_DESCR>
               <AC_PROCUREMENT_DOC/>
               <VAL_OBJECT CURRENCY="DKK">90000000.00</VAL_OBJECT>
               <DURATION TYPE="MONTH">48</DURATION>
               <RENEWAL/>
               <RENEWAL_DESCR>
                  <P>A period up to two (2) years.</P>
               </RENEWAL_DESCR>
               <NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>5</NB_ENVISAGED_CANDIDATE>
               <CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
                  <P>The Contracting Authority will prequalify the 5 applicants who are evaluated as most qualified for the specific tender. Only these applicants will be invited to submit a tender. The selection of the applicants will be based on the submitted references. That is to which extend the references are similar to the tender assignment.</P>
                  <P>As a result, the number of references will not be the determining factor alone, but more importantly to which degree the specific forwarded references are comparable and relevant to the tender assignment regarding solution and scope.</P>
               </CRITERIA_CANDIDATE>
               <NO_ACCEPTED_VARIANTS/>
               <NO_OPTIONS/>
               <NO_EU_PROGR_RELATED/>
            </OBJECT_DESCR>
         </OBJECT_CONTRACT>
         <LEFTI>
            <ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
               <P>The Contracting Authority will only enter into a contract with economic solid companies. This to ensure that the company continues to exist through the whole contract period.</P>
               <P>The applicant must confirm the economic ability in the ESPD part IV.B:</P>
               <P>— ‘Economic and financial standing’ with information from the latest annual report regarding the following economic indicators:</P>
               <P>1) Turnover;</P>
               <P>2) Equity (total equity incl. share capital, reserves, revaluation, retained earning etc.);</P>
               <P>3) Equity ratio (equity / total assets).</P>
               <P>All three economic indicators should be stated in ESPD part IV.B (financial ratios).</P>
               <P>If the applicant is relying on the capacities of one or more other entities (e.g. a parent or sister company or a subcontractor) the information for the ESPD part IV.B must also be given in a separate ESPD from each of the entities, cf. section VI.3 ‘Additional information’.</P>
               <P>The applicant is obliged to document the requirement by request of the Contracting Authority.</P>
               <P>Minimum levels of standards possibly required:</P>
               <P>— turnover must be at least 96 000 000 DKK,</P>
               <P>— equity must be at least 33 pct. of the total expected amount of the contract,</P>
               <P>— equity ratio must be at least 20 pct. If the equity ratio is between 15 pct and 20 pct the supplier can qualify, ifEquity exceeds the total expected amount of the contract.</P>
            </ECONOMIC_FINANCIAL_INFO>
            <TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
               <P>The references of the most significant comparable contracts undertaken in the past five (5) years must be stated in the ESPD part IV.C:</P>
               <P>— ‘Technical and professional ability’.</P>
               <P>The references must include:</P>
               <P>— a detailed description of the work performed for each reference (please note the ‘description’ box can contain more text that is visible, that is, it is possible to copy-paste text into the box),</P>
               <P>— contract value (if possible),</P>
               <P>— date,</P>
               <P>— contact information for the entity in question (including contact person).</P>
               <P>If the applicant is relying on the capacities of one or more other entities (e.g. a parent or sister company or a subcontractor) the information for the ESPD part IV.C must also be given in a separate ESPD from each of the entities, cf. section VI.3 ‘Additional information’.</P>
               <P>The number of references should not surpass a maximum of the 5 most comparable and relevant references.If the reference list includes more than 5 references, the Contracting Authority will only consider the first 5listed. If the applicant is participating in the procurement procedure together with others in a group of economic operators (e.g. a consortium) or is relying on the capacity of one or more other entities for references the maximum number of references to be submitted must still be respected and cannot exceed 5 when combined.</P>
               <P>The Contracting Authority reserves the right to contact the stated references. The references of the most significant comparable contracts undertaken in the past five (5) years must be stated in the ESPD part IV.C:‘Technical and professional ability’.</P>
               <P>The references must include:</P>
               <P>— a detailed description of the work performed for each reference (please note the “description” box can contain more text that is visible - that is, it is possible to copy-paste the text into the box). In the assessment, see section II.2.9 of the contract notice, special emphasis will be placed on the applicant's experience and ability with:</P>
               <P>— — operation of systems with a high-security level in accordance with ISO standard 27001 or a similar standard (Please describe the process),</P>
               <P>— — operation of systems in a redundant Data Centre setup with more than 20 km in distance between the 2 data centres and please describe, how response time issue has been solved,</P>
               <P>—— operation of larger Oracle Database systems,</P>
               <P>— — contract value (if possible),</P>
               <P>— — date,</P>
               <P>— — contact information for the entity in question (including contact person).</P>
               <P>If the applicant is relying on the capacities of one or more other entities (e.g. a parent or sister company or a sub-contractor) the information for the ESPD part IV.C must also be given in a separate ESPD from each of the entities, see section VI.3 ‘Additional information’.</P>
               <P>The number of references should not surpass a maximum of the 5 most comparable and relevant references.If the reference list includes more than 5 references, the Contracting authority will only consider the first 5 listed. If the applicant is participating in the procurement procedure together with others in a group of economic operators (e.g. a consortium) or is relying on the capacity of one or more other entities for references the maximum number of references to be submitted must still be respected and cannot exceed 5 when combined.</P>
               <P>The contracting authority reserves the right to contact the stated references.</P>
               <P>Minimum levels of standards possibly required:</P>
               <P>— the applicant must document experience with Hosting, Oracle Database installations, transition and transformation phases,</P>
               <P>— confirmation that the applicant meets the demand must be stated in the ESPD - please see above for reference to the specific part in the ESPD. The applicant is obliged to document the requirement by request of the Contracting Authority.</P>
            </TECHNICAL_PROFESSIONAL_INFO>
            <RULES_CRITERIA>
               <P>The applicant must submit a completed version of the ESPD. Please see section VI.3 ‘Additional information’ for further information regarding the ESPD.</P>
               <P>The application must be submitted through EU-Supply, see link in section I.1 in this TED announcement. Applications not submitted via EU-Supply or received after the deadline will not be accepted.</P>
               <P>The Contracting Authority reserves the right to request the applicant to supplement, specify or complete the information submitted. Energinet has joined Global Compact and is using the 10 principles as a platform for working with CSR and our Code of Conduct.</P>
               <P>Contractors are expected to act in accordance with Energinet's Code of Conduct and CSR profile visible on our homepage:</P>
               <P>— www.energinet.dk.</P>
            </RULES_CRITERIA>
            <DEPOSIT_GUARANTEE_REQUIRED>
               <P>The information is stated in the tender material.</P>
            </DEPOSIT_GUARANTEE_REQUIRED>
            <MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITION>
               <P>The information is stated in the tender material.</P>
            </MAIN_FINANCING_CONDITION>
            <LEGAL_FORM>
               <P>The information is stated in the tender material.</P>
            </LEGAL_FORM>
            <PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
               <P>We draw attention to the fact that the contract will be subject to the rule of war in accordance with LOV nr. 429 31/05/2000 (Persondataloven), § 41 stk. 4 (In Danish “Krigsreglen”).</P>
            </PERFORMANCE_CONDITIONS>
         </LEFTI>
         <PROCEDURE>
            <PT_NEGOTIATED_WITH_PRIOR_CALL/>
            <FRAMEWORK>
               <SINGLE_OPERATOR/>
            </FRAMEWORK>
            <REDUCTION_RECOURSE/>
            <CONTRACT_COVERED_GPA/>
            <NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>2017/S 221-460145</NOTICE_NUMBER_OJ>
            <DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>2018-02-19</DATE_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>09:00</TIME_RECEIPT_TENDERS>
            <LANGUAGES>
               <LANGUAGE VALUE="EN"/>
            </LANGUAGES>
            <DURATION_TENDER_VALID TYPE="MONTH">6</DURATION_TENDER_VALID>
         </PROCEDURE>
         <COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
            <NO_RECURRENT_PROCUREMENT/>
            <EINVOICING/>
            <EPAYMENT/>
            <INFO_ADD>
               <P>The applicant must submit a completed European Single Procurement Document (ESPD) to apply for prequalification for this tender procedure. The ESPD for this tender can be found in the prequalification material via EU-supply.</P>
               <P>To complete the ESPD, please:</P>
               <P>— save the XML file onto your own computer (available from the Prequalification Material folder in EU-Supply),</P>
               <P>— open the link https://ec.europa.eu/growth/tools-databases/espd/welcome,</P>
               <P>— choose the preferred language,</P>
               <P>— choose ‘I am an economic operator’,</P>
               <P>— choose ‘Import ESPD’,</P>
               <P>— upload the XML file of the ESPD,</P>
               <P>— choose the country of your companies origin,</P>
               <P>— fill out and complete the ESPD with the information required in this contract notice,</P>
               <P>— when finished filling out the ESPD selected ‘Overview’ and check the information stated,</P>
               <P>— after checking the information select ‘Download as’ either pdf or/and XML file and it will be saved to the computer,</P>
               <P>— upload the pdf and/or XML file version to ‘My response’ in EU-Supply as your request for prequalification.</P>
               <P>Please note the following:</P>
               <P>— an applicant participating on its own, but relying on the capacities of one or more other entities (e.g. aparent or sister company or a subcontractor), must ensure that the application includes the applicants own ESPD together with a separate ESPD from each of the entities it relies on with a completed part II: ‘Information concerning the economic operator’ and part III: ‘Exclusion grounds’ of the ESPD as well as the relevant information regarding part IV: ‘Selection criteria’ and part V: ‘Reduction of the number of qualified candidates’.</P>
               <P>— the ESPD from each of the entities should be duly filled and signed by the entities concerned.</P>
               <P>— further, where an applicant wants to rely on the capacities of other entities, it shall prove to the contracting authority that it will have at its disposal the resources necessary, for example, by producing a commitment by those entities to that effect, which must be submitted as part of the final documentation.</P>
               <P>— where groups of economic operators, including temporary associations, participate together in the procurement procedure, a completely separate  ESPD for each the participating economic operators must be submitted.</P>
               <P>— further, the final documentation must include a signed declaration by all parties of the group of economic operators (joint venture, consortium or other) stating that all economic operators assume joint and several liabilities towards the Contracting Authority for the performance of the contract as a whole.</P>
            </INFO_ADD>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Klagenævntet for Udbud</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Nævnenes Hus, Toldboden 2</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Viborg</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>8800</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 72405708</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>klfu@naevneneshus.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>https://erhvervsstyrelsen.dk/klagenaevnet-for-udbud</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_BODY>
            <REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
               <P>Complaints regarding a candidate not being pre-qualified must be filed with The Complaints Board for Public Procurement within 20 calendar days starting the day after the contracting authority has sent the notification to the candidates involved, provided that the notification includes a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P>
               <P>Other complaints must be filed with The Complaints Board for Public Procurement within:</P>
               <P>1) 45 calendar days after the contracting authority has published a contract award notice in the Official Journal of the European Union (with effect from the day following the publication date);</P>
               <P>2) 30 calendar days starting the day after the contracting authority has informed the tenderers in question that the contracting authority has entered into a contract based on a framework agreement through reopening of competition or a dynamic purchasing system, provided that the notification includes a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision;</P>
               <P>3) 6 months starting the day after the contracting authority has sent the notification to the candidates/tenderers involved that the contracting authority has entered into the framework agreement, provided that the notification included a short account of the relevant reasons for the decision.</P>
            </REVIEW_PROCEDURE>
            <ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
               <OFFICIALNAME>Konkurrence- og Forbrugerstyrelsen</OFFICIALNAME>
               <ADDRESS>Carl Jacobsen Vej 35</ADDRESS>
               <TOWN>Valby</TOWN>
               <POSTAL_CODE>2500</POSTAL_CODE>
               <COUNTRY VALUE="DK"/>
               <PHONE>+45 41715000</PHONE>
               <E_MAIL>kfst@kfst.dk</E_MAIL>
               <URL>http://www.kfst.dk</URL>
            </ADDRESS_REVIEW_INFO>
            <DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>2018-01-31</DATE_DISPATCH_NOTICE>
         </COMPLEMENTARY_INFO>
      </F05_2014>
   </FORM_SECTION>
</TED_EXPORT>
